(Previously)
How's it going?
I asked you to look into Lion.
Kanit sent you, didn't he?
You don't understand.
You're an outsider.
One week.
Go break it off with that flight attendant.
Stop talking to Lion.
Why should I listen to you?
Your boyfriend is seeing a flight attendant
from another airline.
From now on, I won't make
you work for me anymore.
I'll consider it a donation to a stray dog.
I'M SORRY.
Please consider forgiving Toto.
You're playing hard to get, huh?
You're gonna get it.
Mom! Mom!
The clouds! The clouds!
Uncle! Uncle!
The clouds!
Go play with someone else.
I want to sleep.
Auntie! Auntie!
The clouds!
Woo! Woo!
Excuse me, Ma'am.
Is there anything I can help with?
Help with what?
It's normal for a kid to be playful.
But the other passengers are resting.
He's disturbing them.
For his safety,
could you please have him sit down
and fasten his seatbelt?
What?
He's playful by nature.
Can't you see?
He's so cute.
How could you ask him to sit still?
I'm afraid we have to. It's dangerous.
Woo! Woo! Woo! Woo!
Want a lollipop?
Want one?
But first, you have to
sit nicely for me, okay?
Come on, sit down.
Good job.
Come on, fist bump.
Pow!
Great.
Thank you so much, sir.
"A Dog and A Plane"
(Episode 4)
Hey!
What do you think you're doing?
This area is for cabin crew.
Passengers aren't allowed in here.
You wouldn't talk to me.
I even bought a ticket
to get on this flight.
I have nothing to say to a scammer.
Hey!
I swear I didn't mean to lie to you.
Hey.
Hurry up and say what you need to say.
I have to take care of the passengers.
I don't have any excuses.
I'm really sorry.
I want to apologize a hundred more times.
I misjudged Lion.
I didn't think
he'd go back on his word like that.
Besides, I know how much you love him.
So I wanted to give him another chance.
That was my decision to make.
You had no right.
Your job was only to spy on him
and report back to me,
not make decisions for me.
Knowing how much I love him was all the
more reason you should've told me the truth,
not lying and making
a fool of me like this.
Stop making excuses
and just admit it.
All you care about is money.
Hey.
I swear I didn't take his money.
I don't double-book myself.
You're my only boss.
Do you realize that your good intentions
hurt me even more?
Okay.
I really didn't think it through.
Alright.
I'll stay on my knees
apologizing to you until we land.
Hey.
I'm sorry.
Get up!
It's my fault.
I'm sorry.
Look, I'm sorry.
Hey.
I'm really sorry.
Get up. This is embarrassing.
I'm sorry.
Get up!
I'm not getting up
until you forgive me.
Let my guilt plunge to the ground with me.
I'm not going down with you.
Get up already!
Fine! I forgive you! Come on!
Do you mean it?
Yeah.
Don't ever do this again.
I don't like liars.
From now on, I promise that if anything
happens, I'll report it to you first, okay?
I won't take orders from anyone but you.
Mm.
Go now.
We can talk later.
Let's talk later.
Hey.
There's one more thing.
What now?
It's important.
Really important.
I feel kind of awkward telling you this,
but I think I should.
Can you buy me a ticket home?
I've run out of money.
I just paid for my house,
and I haven't gotten my salary yet.
Seriously?
Next time you want to be dramatic,
check your wallet first.
Please.
Fine, I'll take care of it.
Just go.
Go now.
Go.
I did some digging
and found out about
your boyfriend's side piece's family,
his parents' names,
the airline he works for,
and what his house is like.
His name is Veha.
The guy you met
at your friend's bachelorette party.
Remember him?
Ah.
No wonder
I got weird vibes from him when we met.
Yes.
He knew who I was.
I happen to be buying this bag too.
Whatever I think is mine,
I don't let anyone else take it easily.
Who knows?
Your taste and mine are similar anyway.
That's the exact same energy as when
Muta met Nopnapha in Raeng Ngao.
What a slap in the face.
You know where he lives, right?
Why?
Are you going to ambush and slap him?
No.
I want to know what kind of person he is
and what's so great about him
that makes Lion dare leave me for him.
I can definitely take you there,
but you have to follow my plan.
What do I have to do?
Since he's putting on an act for you,
you have to put on an act for him
and make it more convincing.
You have to pretend you're flying.
Hey.
It's your day off. You should be resting.
You didn't have to drop me off.
Well,
I don't often get a chance
to spoil my boyfriend.
What time do you get off today?
Don't let him pick you up.
Pretend you'll get off late.
Make him think you're
definitely not around.
Act like you're really sad
to be away from him.
Don't let him suspect you found out.
I've got four landings today.
I'll be back late for sure.
But it's okay. I can go home by myself.
You can go do your own thing, okay?
But I'd rather do it with you.
I don't think I'll go anywhere.
I'll just stay home waiting for you.
I want to rest too.
Alright, once I get off,
I'll hurry to hug you.
I can't wait to see you then!
After that, you walk to the gate,
and quickly get out.
Once he falls for it,
we'll catch him red-handed.
Alright, safe flights then.
Bye-bye.
Hey.
Huh?
Now that he thinks you'll be gone all day
and he can get away with it,
he'll definitely go
running off to see Veha.
Trust me.
Let's go.
Follow him.
SIDE PIECE'S CAR
What the hell?
Wow.
Nice paint job.
So red it looks like blood.
What the hell did you do?
What did you use to write on my car?
Calm down.
It's just pig's blood.
I just want you to know that
being a side piece is wrong.
Kāmesu micchācārā.
You broke the third precept.
Engaging in adultery with
someone else's partner,
brings suffering and separation.
It clouds the mind and blinds wisdom.
Your life will not prosper.
And you will face the consequences
of karma in the third realm of hell,
such as
being tortured by climbing the thorny tree.
Sadhu.
I'm calling the cops on you!
Trespassing and property damage charges.
I'll sue you until you're broke.
No money. No escape. No payment.
Unless you want to settle this another way.
If you don't have money, then go to jail.
Go ahead.
But before I go to jail,
I'm going to expose you.
Veha Wongsuksawat is a homewrecker.
I'll scream it so everyone
in your condo hears. How about that?
Veha is...
Stop!
So you still have some shame.
Why didn't you think before you did it?
Huh?
Side piece.
Shoo wee doo wab.
Shoo [as in side piece].
Side piece.
When was the last time
we watched a movie together?
Oh, I think it's been a really long time.
Oh.
It's been that long
since I last took you to the movies?
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
Wow.
What do you think?
Calm down!
Calm down.
Calm down, my ass!
Let me help you.
Shh!
Shh! Careful!
Wow.
Damn.
He brought him to such a fancy cinema.
They're even watching it in bed.
This is The Bed Cinema, right?
I guess they'll be watching,
making out,
and screaming at the same time.
Ahh!
Lion!
The ghost is here, Lion!
I'm scared!
Lion!
Hey.
Stop building it up.
I'll go see it with my own eyes.
Hey.
Where am I supposed to get the money
for such a fancy experience?
Think about it.
I dragged you here. I can pay for you.
Come here.
Hey, come on!
Hey.
The bed is so soft, isn't it?
It's so soft that I don't even want to
watch the movie anymore.
You don't want to watch the movie?
Then what do you want to do?
What do people usually do
on a bed this soft?
Bullshit!
Keep it down!
They might catch you!
He's probably too into the movie.
Are you cold?
Not really.
But if you hug me, I might warm up.
Someone's being lovey-dovey.
What are you doing?
Giving you more warmth.
It might get hot.
Shh!
Keep it down.
Let's focus on the movie.
Things are heating up.
They're shooting. Look.
Things are heating up over here too.
Scumbag!
Hey!
Are you crazy?
Oh, shit.
I've had enough. That's too many times.
Easy.
Babe, I'm sorry.
I won't hurt you again.
I won't be difficult anymore.
Please don't be mad at me.
Excuse me.
If you're going to fight,
could you take it outside?
I'm watching the movie with my partner.
I'm sorry.
I'll keep it down. Sorry.
That was close!
I had to think on my feet the whole time.
If it were you, would
you be able to stand it?
I'm watching my boyfriend cheating
right in front of my eyes!
2026 GREY-GOLD ALUMNI HOMECOMING
Come on!
Bottoms up!
Hey!
Hey! Come here!
It's been so long.
Where's my glass?
Here.
Take that.
I'll drink from any glass.
Hey, guys!
Hey. The school's star
football player is here.
Hey!
Hi, buddy.
Akki, I didn't think you'd come.
You didn't reply to our messages.
Of course, he came.
It's the class reunion.
Yeah.
This year's party is for
three batches together.
I haven't seen some
of the juniors in so long.
They've gotten really hot.
Look at that table.
Ouch!
That's all you're thinking about, huh?
Cut me some slack.
I'm old already.
By the way, what are you doing now?
I work at a local rescue foundation.
A rescuer?
That's just something
you do casually, right?
What's your full-time job?
Rescue work is my full-time job.
Oh.
You're so brave. I
can't even look at blood.
Whoa.
I thought you'd already made it
to the national team and gone far.
I don't want to play football anymore.
Oh?
I want to be a hundred-million CEO
like you guys.
Come on, you're just saying that.
I haven't hit a hundred million yet,
but I'm getting close.
Yeah, keep showing off.
Come on. Cheers.
Cheers?
Come on.
There are a lot of people tonight, huh?
Yeah, it's lively.
Nice. Lots of girls here.
Hey.
Huh?
Cheers!
How have you been?
What do you do now?
Electrical work.
Really?
Yeah.
Where?
Hey, guys.
Did he go to our school?
Who?
That guy.
Oh.
Of course, you don't remember him.
He's that Grade 10 kid
who used to cheer for you and bring
you stuff when you played football.
He's totally upgraded into
a whole different person now.
Don't you recognize me?
I do.
Then why didn't you say hi?
Why didn't you say hi first?
You've changed so much.
Who would recognize you?
But I've always remembered you.
You've really upgraded your look.
Why are you being someone's side piece?
That's my business, isn't it?
Why are you sticking your nose in?
You know full well he's in a relationship.
Why are you still messing with him?
You've upgraded your face.
Didn't your doctor also fix your heart
to make you a little more moral?
What are you, a teacher?
Why are you lecturing me?
What I do is my business.
Hey.
Think carefully.
Do you really think someone in a relationship
would leave their partner for you?
You've been fooled,
and you don't even realize it.
Look,
I'm warning you as your senior.
Hey.
Why are you mad at me now?
You never even noticed me before.
What changed?
I'm more handsome?
So you see me now?
I'm finally in your eyes, right?
PROJECT: CATCH THE CHEATER
FLIGHT ATTENDANT
Just tell me, boss.
How do you want to deal with this?
I don't want to just scold him
and be done with it.
I want him to hurt.
Hurt to the core.
In that case,
do you want to do it
the Thai music video way?
Pour dog food in front of him
and say,
“If you're hungry, eat it.”
Or…
Throw calamine lotion in his face
and say,
“Here. This should help with your itch.”
What do you think?
Isn't that fabulous?
Hey, I don't want to use violence.
Okay.
No old primetime soap opera–style violence.
Do it like a stage play then.
A stage play?
Someone like Lion
is more worried about losing his image
than losing love.
To deal with him,
you need a team and a production.
Meet the members of Mission Nopnapha.
A mission to reclaim your dignity
as the original, rightful partner.
This is Tong, the service unit.
Armed with sharp-tongued insults
that cut straight to the heart.
I undertake the precept
to refrain from sexual misconduct.
Those players?
I want to grab their balls
and pound them to pieces
like the som tam in front of me!
Fabulous!
This is Ja-O, the recreation unit.
He's in charge of music.
He'll add color
to our mission.
♪ Rage ♪
Woo!
Very good, Michelle.
Remember to do it exactly like that.
And this is Akki, the spiking unit.
He'll help distract our enemies.
Wingardium Leviosa!
And this is Beer.
Where the hell is he?
Beer couldn't make it.
He's on another mission.
But he asked me to say this:
“I hope all players
fall into every drain they pass
and end up in hell!”
Was that from Beer or you?
A mix of both.
Alright, it's fine.
We can get it on with just us.
But are you sure you dare to do it?
Of course.
The cheater needs to learn a hard lesson.
♪ Rage ♪
Hey, relax.
You really look like
you're ready to kill someone.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
What? You have a weapon?
Oh.
Why are you putting that on now?
I have to look handsome.
I'm going to see shameless people.
How do I look? Handsome now?
Mm. You're the most handsome.
Hey!
There they are!
What do you think?
Isn't this place nice?
Really nice.
Let's sit here.
Okay.
After you.
Thank you.
Go ahead and look at the menu.
I thought they only cheated in bed,
but they're cheating at the table too.
He brought him to such a fancy place.
I think they're going public soon.
Fancy place? Please.
More like flaunting a side piece.
Please give me your hand.
I have a little gift for you.
Hey!
Isn't this a limited edition?
Yes.
I really love it.
Oh!
Thank you so much.
I bought it for you
because you're my limited edition.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Same old trick.
Same spot. Same place.
This is where he asked me
to be his boyfriend.
(Oh?)
Is this a rerun?
4 YEARS AGO
Thank you for bringing me here.
You're very welcome.
You aced your exam.
I had to bring you to
a good place like this.
Kanit.
Yes?
Please give me your hand.
Why?
I have
a little gift for you.
Hey!
Are you really giving me this?
Yeah.
Thank you.
This is my favorite model.
I consider it my limited edition.
Will you be my limited
edition for a long time?
What do you mean?
Let's be boyfriends.
I've had enough!
What are you doing?
I'm going to yell at them.
Calm down.
They're shameless!
They're about to order food.
Stick to the plan.
Calm down.
Breathe in.
Breathe out.
Focus on your core.
Mission Nopnapha begins.
- Good evening.
Would you like to order a special dish?
We have a new course called
the Limited Love Set.
What do you think?
That sounds interesting.
Our Limited Love Set today consists of,
Cheating-Heart Minced Meat Salad,
Shameless Seafood Salad,
Two-Timing Beef Steak,
and Hot Adultery Tree Soup.
Interested?
It'll be served hot.
Weird names, huh?
They're fusion dishes. Italian style
with a touch of Northeastern Thai.
But don't worry. It won't be fishy.
We definitely serve fresh food here.
We don't tolerate anything fishy
or scandalous.
Interested?
Hmm…
Can I have some wine first?
Allow me to shift the vibe a bit.
Now things are heating up,
like you're rehearsing for hell.
Please excuse me.
Music unit, let's go.
Cheers.
♪ Don't be afraid even
if we are separated ♪
♪ Just stay there and wait for me,
I'll find you ♪
♪ No matter what tomorrow brings ♪
♪ Please remember this ♪
♪ I will live ♪
♪ Only for you ♪
This song is for
faithful couples like you two.
Thank you.
He came on his own.
Food unit, let's go!
The food's here.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Enjoy your meal.
Congratulations.
Oh? What's the occasion?
You two looked so sweet together.
I thought you were getting engaged.
Am I right?
We just started dating.
Really? Oh.
But it probably won't be long.
Congratulations.
Enjoy your meal.
Come on.
Let's eat.
How is it?
So good.
Mm.
Uh…
Excuse me. I need to go to the bathroom.
Are you okay, Veha?
I've got a weird stomachache.
Excuse me.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I MISS YOU SO MUCH, KANIT.
How dare he text me this?
MISS ME? WANT ME TO COME OVER?
Time to reclaim your dignity,
Nopnapha.
Kanit will no longer be your victim.
How are you feeling, Veha?
Are you okay?
You miss me, so here I am.
Am I a good boyfriend?
What brings you here?
Familiar vibes, huh?
You really care about the planet.
You keep recycling your tricks.
It's not what you think.
It's not what I think.
I saw it with my own eyes.
Why? Am I not enough for you?
It's not like that.
He and I are just talking casually.
Talking casually?
If you want to talk, you can talk to me.
I'm good at talking.
Stop making excuses
and just admit you're a jerk.
I know I'm a jerk,
but I…
just want some excitement.
Excitement? If that's what you want,
there are plenty of things you can do.
Go swim with sharks.
Base jump off a building.
Jump out of a helicopter.
Or jump anywhere you want.
But not cheating!
Allow me to change the photos
to match the mood.
Leave writing novels
to high school students on their break.
Stop making up stories already.
♪ Why would I regret losing a crappy guy ♪
♪ Like you? Just why? ♪
♪ Who knows where dating you
would take my life? ♪
♪ A playboy day and night ♪
♪ Cheating when the chance arises ♪
♪ I'm totally fine ♪
♪ Just losing a crappy guy ♪
♪ Like you ♪
That's a song for a nice vibe.
What's the meaning of this?
Veha,
hear me out.
Veha!
♪ Why would I regret losing a crappy guy
like you? Just why? ♪
♪ Who knows where dating you
would take my life? ♪
♪ A playboy day and night ♪
♪ Cheating when the chance arises ♪
♪ I'm totally fine ♪
♪ Just losing a crappy guy like you ♪
Veha.
Can I talk to you?
Can I talk to you, please?
You said you were breaking up with him.
What was that?
How am I going to show my face
after what he did?
I was really going to break up with him.
And I'm so angry
that he was completely disrespectful
to both of us.
I'm going to deal with the people
who humiliated you.
How are you going to take responsibility?
I'm going to talk it out with him.
Talk?
You've said that dozens of times already.
I feel like I've been
getting lied to every day.
Veha,
please calm down.
Calm down?
I've stayed calm for a year already.
I've been so stupid.
Veha…
I'm sorry.
Don't touch me!
I really didn't mean it.
This time, I'm really choosing you.
You're only choosing me
because no one else wants you anymore.
Veha,
can we not be like this?
Veha, please.
Don't leave me too.
Don't do this to anyone again.
Veha.
I don't want to say this,
but I warned you.
If you're here to gloat,
just say it.
If you're going to insult me, just do it.
I'm an asshole.
I'm terrible.
I deserve what's happening to me.
Go ahead and insult me.
I'm waiting to hear it.
Insult me.
Do it.
Go ahead and insult me!
Just do it!
I won't.
I just want you to know
you're not anyone's second choice.
I feel so worthless.
Just own up to your mistake.
You can start over.
If I weren't in the picture,
everyone would be happier, wouldn't they?
Did you see his face when you showed up?
I was so damn satisfied.
He looked so shocked.
I should've taken a photo
and posted it on social media.
It would've gone viral for sure.
Hey.
Aren't you satisfied?
Are you okay?
Hey.
Hey!
What are you doing?
Calm down.
Please listen to me.
It's just a bad guy.
Don't throw your life away for him.
You'll find someone good. Trust me.
You have so many people who love you.
Please don't jump. I'm begging you.
Hey!
Hey.
I wasn't going to jump.
I just came to throw up.
Oh.
Get it out.
Want some water?
Here.
Drink up.
Thank you.
The way you ran, I thought
you were going to jump off the building.
You startled me.
I wouldn't do anything like that.
It was just too much.
My heart was racing.
And my stomach was all upset.
I couldn't take it. I
had to get it all out.
I get it. I know it's not easy.
But you did great.
You got it over with.
Now you don't have to
obsess over it anymore.
I've wasted so many years
on a pipe dream.
It's just like when you warned me
about dropping dead.
I was just rambling.
I didn't mean it like that.
If Lion can't make your dream come true,
why don't you find someone else to do it?
I'm both relieved and sad.
I'm relieved it's over,
but I'm sad I used to love
a bad guy like him.
Take it as a life lesson.
You did your best.
Cut that shitty person out of your life.
None of it was your fault.
You were a good boyfriend.
If he doesn't see your worth,
you have to see it yourself.
Can you not touch me?
If someone were kind to me right now,
I'd definitely cry.
Then I won't let go of your hand.
Whatever's on your mind, let it all out.
I'll take it.
Cry it out.
Cry it all out.
(Next Episode)
Stop crying and open the door for me.
If you're here to rub it in,
then just leave.
Here are tools for letting out your rage.
Thank you
for making today not so bad.
Who would be into someone for that long?
Are you sure you're not into me anymore?
Can you sleep with me tonight?
You mean
sleeping next to each other?