It's always about Mikoy.
Is that really how it is?
Are you willing to die just for Mikoy?
He's important to the case we're building
against the Moravianos.
Hey! You devil.
I will finish him myself!
Hey!
I actually need your help.
Wait, was that a gunshot?
- Because I was followed.
- By who?
La Fornarina!
Mikoy!
Mikoy?
We received a report
about a road rage incident,
which apparently led to a shootout,
and we recovered several shell casings.
But the drivers of both vehicles
have already fled.
Agent Sianong, team.
We need to spread out quickly.
Our asset is being hunted.
Okay. Thank you.
Sir.
Men, back to work.
Mikoy!
Hey! Who are you?
You're a thief, aren't you?
No. Sir…
Please don't make noise.
I'm not a thief, I promise.
You have the nerve to lie!
Stay right there! Don't move.
- Please.
- You're even kneeling now?
This isn't a Quiapo Church!
Just relax?
That's what's on your mind?
In a situation like this?
Aren't you worried?
Doesn't that bother you?
Mikoy is a freaking spy!
I don't know.
Can't we do anything?
Is there nothing we can do, Viktor?
What are you talking about?
That's what you’re worrying about?!
Mikoy.
Well, you must be Kim Dominguez.
Or Kim Santo Domingo.
All I know is you look exactly
like the person I hate most!
You never really understood
your daughter, did you?
You don't understand her!
No!
Because if you truly
understood your daughter,
you'd know how painful this is.
You'd know how painful
what we're making her do is.
Viktor.
She's about to kill the person
she loves the most.
Chiara, please don't make me hurt you.
Chiara, please. Stop. Let's talk.
Here. A heart for a heart!
Be a father to your daughter! To Chiara.
Treat her like your daughter.
Not a weapon that you keep using
to take down your enemies.
I'm sorry, my love.
Viktor.
She's our daughter.
Mikoy!
Mikoy, don’t run. Let’s end this!
Mikoy?
Mikoy.
Agent Alex, are you okay?
You shouldn't be here.
I can handle this.
Sir, our agency teammates are here.
Maybe you can tell them
what happened again.
Well,
there was a man and a woman.
The woman was chasing
some guy who looked like an idiot.
Then, all of a sudden,
the woman started shooting at him.
Looks like Chiara really wanted
to finish Mikoy off.
Ma'am, no.
That's not how we see it.
What do you mean, not really?
Mikoy! Did you miss me, hon?
What's that?
A lovers' quarrel?
Pretty brutal, huh?
It really is.
If you ask me, ma'am,
they seemed like a married couple.
A toxic married couple.
The kind where
the husband did something wrong,
so the wife chased him down.
Just to scare him
because he screwed her over.
Mikoy, does it hurt?
You're just too violent.
I'm sorry!
- Sorry. Sorry.
- I'm gonna destroy you.
- Freaking liar!
- You were trying to shoot me!
- Liar!
- Can we talk first?
Please, let's talk first.
Screwed her over?
Screwed her over. Lied to her.
Gaslighted her. Cheated on her.
I don't know about you kids these days.
You're always on your phones.
That's why now, you're all clueless.
Airheads. Idiots.
You know?
You don't spend enough time
hanging out on street corners.
Sir.
- What happened next?
- Oh, right.
Anyway, the woman was furious.
She was yelling.
She said to the man,
"How dare you call me 'my love'?"
And the man replied,
"Chiara,
please stop. Let's talk about this."
So the woman didn't stop?
Bro, I told you, they're toxic.
For most couples,
they'd just throw plates.
These two were shooting at each other.
- Oh God.
- That's dangerous.
But wait.
I think
if she really wanted to kill the guy,
he would've been dead already.
- Right? Besides,
- Exactly.
it still looked like
they loved each other.
The only problem is,
they both seem crazy.
Right?
Let's talk first, okay?
Talk?
- You want to talk?!
- Wait.
You're really going to throw that?
You won't do it. You don't have it in you.
Was that part of your training?
Was that also part of lying to me?
Where's Mikoy?
Why? Didn't he tell you?
He never went to the office.
Yes, ma'am. Mr. Pinagpala
hasn't reported to the office yet.
If you didn't go to the office,
where did you go?
I left the house
to meet up with my friends.
Mikoy, listen to me carefully.
No! I'm only a police asset.
Alex just taught me some self-defense.
- Alex?
- Oops.
I mean, Sianong!
- Yes, Sianong.
- Alex?!
And Alex too.
Alex!
Bok.
They said there were more gunshots
near a grocery store.
I think it's still Chiara.
Hey. Bok.
Dara, Rafa.
Quick!
What happened?
The bandages are loose.
They need to rewrap them.
You talk to all the witnesses.
Police, SWAT, everyone.
Wait, what happened?
My God. Let me see.
- Boo.
- Ah! Good Lord.
Looks like you can't sleep either.
Viktor.
My goodness!
Or maybe she already did.
Do it.
Isn't this your mission?
Dara. Put more bandages on her.
She can't afford to lose
even a drop more blood.
Do it now.
I'm still coming.
- It's just a bandage replacement.
- No, Bok!
No, okay?
Dara, take her back to the hospital.
You can't order me around.
And I won't let myself lose
someone I love again.
Bok. Bok.
Bok, let me handle
tracking down Mikoy, okay?
I promise you, I'll bring him back alive.
Go on, Dara.
You're wrong about me.
I'm still me.
The Mikoy you came to know.
Maybe you never really knew me.
Goodbye, Mr. Michael "Mikoy"
D. Pinagpala!
So, what now?
Can we talk now?
Huh?
We found the place where Mikoy
and La Fornarina fought.
Looks like the two had an intense fight.
I already sent a sweeper team
to spread out
to also search for traces
that Chiara and Mikoy is there.
Whatever you said,
you can’t change the fact
that you fooled me and lied to me.
The reason I’m doing all this
is to protect you from your family
in this world of yours.
That’s Mikoy and Chiara! Let’s get them!
I do.
Let’s call Agent Sianong.