You still believe Chiara is innocent.
That she isn't part
of her family's criminal syndicate.
I will finish him myself!
The truth is right in front of you.
What are you waiting for?
I don't care who Chiara is.
Because I love her.
I love her very much.
Dad… Dad, we need to leave.
You need to go back to Cebu first.
Did something happen?
The Moravianos.
The Valtrovis, Dad.
They know now.
They already know
that I'm working for the police.
I'm sure you'll be their next target.
Yes.
That's why we need to leave immediately.
Dad… You need to take Mom
back to Cebu first.
What about you?
I'll take care of myself.
The protocol has already
been explained to me
for situations like this.
You know, it's a good thing the burger
and extra fries showed up when they did.
The timing was just perfect.
Cocoy won't be the only one
trying to kill you.
And there won't always be
a burger and fries around to save you.
I understand that.
That's why I'll be more careful, okay?
Promise.
Being careful isn't enough, Mikoy.
You have to prepare for the worst.
The worst?
- Like what?
- Like when your cover gets blown.
- You mean burned?
- Yes. Burned.
It means the Moravianos
have discovered your identity,
and they know you're an agency asset.
What do I do if that happens?
You need to upgrade your burger and fries.
You need a grande now.
Grande? What grande?
You can check into any hotel
in Metro Manila
under the name Grande.
Room for one.
Under Alexander Grande.
We have Grande here. Prepare the room.
Dad…
I'll be okay.
They'll provide me protection.
They should.
Dad.
You need to get away first.
Because I'm sure you'll be next.
Okay.
I'll take care of your mother and brother.
So make sure you stay safe.
Dad, I'm sorry.
I've dragged you into this.
I never thought it would come to this.
At first, I thought I was helping, but…
Mikoy.
I told you before.
We're a complicated family.
But we're still family.
We don't give up on each other.
No matter what happens,
we're on the same side, so there's
no reason for you to feel guilty.
How sweet, father and son
are hugging each other.
Even in this heat. What are you doing?
Let me join too, please.
Bok!
Bok, what are you doing?
Come on. Get back here.
- What are you doing?
- I need to leave. Let me go.
Bok, how are you going to leave? Huh?
You are in no shape to move. Bok.
Bok, so many-- You have so many wounds.
You're covered in bandages.
So how are you going to leave?
I can still move.
These wounds are nothing.
Okay, I understand.
But fine, let's make a deal.
Just recover first,
then I'll let you leave.
I'll even treat you.
Bok, come on.
I need to get to Mikoy.
His life is in danger.
Enough already.
It's always Mikoy.
You never talk about
anything else but Mikoy.
Now what? What happened to us? Huh?
Is that really how it is?
You're willing to die just for Mikoy?
He's important to the case
we're building against the Moravianos.
If that's the risk
I need to take, I'll take that.
Sianong, he's our asset.
And he is now our liability.
Can't you see that?
We need to get rid of him cleanly.
While we still have time.
While we still have a chance.
What do you mean?
Sianong, what did you do?
Well, we need to leave.
I've already bought tickets to Cebu.
You mean right now?
Why so suddenly?
You know what people say.
The view is beautiful.
Everything from…
from up there, there are moons and stars.
To make things a little romantic.
Stop fooling around with me.
What moon and stars are you talking about?
They're in outer space.
Besides, the pollution here
in the Philippines is so bad,
I can't even see those stars and moon.
Okay, so we won't have to wait
in a long line at the airport.
Tell me.
Is something bad happening?
Tell me. Is there something
I need to know?
Why would you think that?
How?
Honey, you're overthinking.
Let's just pack our things. Come on.
Where's Mikoy?
Tell me. Where's Mikoy?
He had something to take care of,
and he might be gone for a while. Okay?
We'll just call him once we land in Cebu.
Oh, Mario Pinagpala, you know,
you may be blessed,
but you're not very good at lying.
Do you think I don't notice those
knowing looks between you and Mikoy.
The way you look at each other.
When are you going to tell me the truth?
Okay, look.
I'll tell you everything.
But… not this time.
We need to leave.
Trust me.
Come on, let's go. Hurry up.
You're making me panic.
That's what you did?
You think Mikoy will betray us?
Bok.
I don't know if you're thinking
straight right now,. Sorry.
But isn't it obvious?
He fed us that fake intel.
What other reason could there be?
To throw us off
this investigation. That's it.
But haven't you realized
that it could have been
planted intelligence?
Exactly. Planted intelligence.
And for Viktor to do that,
it means he's been watching
for a long time.
He's suspected Mikoy for a long time.
Why can't you see that?
Looks like it's been a long time indeed.
Maybe it started when Viktor
assigned Carlota
as Mikoy's secretary,
and Mikoy never noticed
because he isn't trained to spot it.
Isn't that possible?
Fine.
Let's say you're right, okay?
That means we're also
responsible for this because
we failed to see it.
We are agents. We are trained for this.
Fine.
Bok, lie back down.
Exactly.
Even us agents make mistakes, Sianong.
What more Mikoy, who's just a civilian?
And now his life is in danger
because Viktor wants him dead.
No.
I don't think Viktor will kill him.
Because if he really wanted to kill Mikoy,
he would've done it a long time ago.
He should have done it already.
Knowing Viktor, he can kill anyone,
especially people who betray him.
But with Mikoy, somehow,
he made efforts to keep him alive.
And there's only one reason for that.
Chiara.
I think Chiara is trying to protect him.
Yes.
Either that
or maybe Chiara wants to kill him herself.
It's more than just good.
The cleanup has started.
And you'll be delighted to know
who initiated the attack.
I have now unleashed
our most dangerous weapon.
Hey! Idiot!
You should have your license revoked.
Hey! You devil.
Looks like you're hard to surprise.
I was trying to surprise you.
But it seems you have eyes
at the back of your head.
Your hobby?
Because I'm good at that too.
Oh. Stabbing?
No.
Backstabbing.
I know what you're doing.
I just want you to know
it's not working on me.
You want some? Here you go.
There!
Eat my smoke, idiot.
These reckless riders. They're everywhere.
What is it, harvest season?
Hey! Hey!
Hey!
What's this guy's problem?
I think he's messing with me.
Fight to stay alive,
even if you have to crawl.
Don't let go. Don't give up.
Because there's one thing
I can promise you.
Help will always come for you.
I won't stop you anymore.
I'll even back you up.
Sianong, you know me.
I don't back down from a fight.
- Sir.
- What's this?
Why is she dressed already?
We need to secure Mikoy.
His life is in danger.
Viktor already knows he's working for us.
And at this moment, he may have
already sent someone to kill Mikoy.
That was my plan, too.
That's why I'm here to tell you
not to worry about him.
What kind of help?
I've already talked to Mikoy.
I told him about our backup plan.
He's on his way to a nearby hotel.
To explore our Grande option.
That's good then.
We have information on his location.
So now, we can secure him better.
We can transfer him
to our nearest safe house.
Right?
That's a great suggestion.
But you have a lot of explaining to do.
A lot!
She is the Valtrovi's secret assassin.
She is La Fornarina.
Sweetheart!
Aren't you happy to see me?
It's Mikoy.
Mikoy? Where are you?
Hello? Agent Alex? How are you?
But wait, that can wait.
I actually need your help.
Sweetheart!
Wait, was that a gunshot?
Are you in a gunfire situation?
Looks like it.
And yes, those are real bullets.
Sorry, I wasn't able to make it
to our Grande plan.
- Because I was followed.
- By who?
La Fornarina!
Wait a second. Let me show you. Here.
- There she is!
- Mikoy!
Mikoy? Mikoy?
- I need to find Mikoy.
- Agent Dara, track Mikoy now.
I'm on it, Agent Sianong.
We're running out of time.
I said I'm on it.
Bok, this is exactly
what I've been telling you.
Can we please just stay
in the hospital. You?
I'll handle Mikoy. I'll take care of him.
I'll update you when it's over.
- Really?
- Yes.
Just a while ago, you looked like
you wanted to terminate him
like he was a disposable cup.
Okay, fine. Sorry.
Okay now, Bok?
Let me handle Mikoy.
I'll take care of him.
I'll keep you updated
from time to time. I promise.
How can you take care of him
when you were the first one
who didn't trust him?
Bok, I'm not blaming you,
but trust is the foundation
of our relationship
with all of our assets.
Including Mikoy.
And I hope this serves as a lesson.
You need to trust people
if you want them to trust you.
And Mikoy is putting all his trust in us.
So we should do the same for him.
Okay.
I'll make it up to him, okay?
I'll make it up to him, guys.
What's Mikoy's last known location?
We lost his phone signal.
But I intercepted a tip
about a shoot-out along Mapayapa Road.
Okay, good. Let's move.
Careful.
No, no, no.
Well… Start gathering
what crashed there.
We need to secure our own footage.
Global Agency for Government Operations.
We're only here to investigate.
The GAGO has no jurisdiction
over this matter--
Sir, there is an ongoing
national security operation,
and the syndicates we've been monitoring
appear to be connected to this.
Even so,
this is our crime scene--
This isn't just
a simple road rage case, sir.
And we'd like to reach them
while they're still alive.
Let's not turn this
into one of those shows
where the police arrive late and then
end up serving as nothing more
than the cleanup crew
and at the same time,
just take pictures at the crime scene.
No. Even so, sir,
- it's still our--
- And if something goes wrong
because we're arguing here
about whose jurisdiction this is,
we'll both be in trouble.
There are still gunshots
near the grocery store around here.
I think it's still Chiara.
Hey! Bok!
Is there nothing we can do?
Nothing at all, Viktor?
Maybe you never really knew me.