Trouble is normal in missions.
That's why what you need
is a reliable partner, like me.
Are you still hiding
something from me, Dad?
Just keep your eyes open.
We are looking for Quebec Romero 1020.
That's the plate number
of the container van.
And if Mikoy is right,
that would bring us to the secret hideout.
Agent Kian, go after them.
She has shrapnel wounds
and some minor burns.
And the doctor said they still
need to operate on Alex.
Unfortunately,
we've lost two lives already.
Sir, I think Mikoy's just playing us.
How much more evidence do we need
before you realize that
what I'm saying is true,
that Mikoy is compromised?
We don't need any more reports
or any debriefing,
because what's the point of all that
if the Moravianos keep
outsmarting us anyway?
I think
the problem is our office.
The problem is the entire agency, sir.
I don't like it when someone's
wasting my time.
I'm here for you. To help you.
To talk to you.
I think we started on the wrong foot.
I'm here to help you.
These setbacks really are discouraging.
It lowers morale.
But we must soldier on.
- That's our job.
- No, sir.
I already warned you
about Mikoy several times.
That I think Mikoy is compromised
and anytime soon,
he will just turn against us.
And what about Alex?
I already told you
how many times I've noticed
something's off with Alex.
She's not thinking straight anymore,
that Mikoy is manipulating her,
that I don't know what else
would make her believe.
And what did you do last time?
Did you listen to me?
You didn't listen to me, sir!
You thought I was just overreacting.
And all of this happened
because of your negligence.
At first, of course,
I had my doubts.
Maybe
they were just jealous of Mikoy.
Like they say,
"The more fruitful
a tree is,
the more bashers it gets."
Sir Viktor, I'm just worried
about Mikoy's questions.
He doesn't miss any detail.
It's like he's investigating.
You know,
Easy there, son.
Are you okay?
Come on.
That choking fit was so dramatic, son.
Why?
I don't know.
Maybe that's why you're
trending everywhere right now?
What exactly did you do
to become everyone's
favorite gossip topic?
Wait, but…
Is that saying still true until now?
That when you choke,
someone's talking about you.
What about politicians
who are in the headlines every day?
Do they still choke too?
You're really something.
Isn't that what the elders say?
When you choke,
it means someone remembered you.
Or maybe
someone misses you, dear.
Hey!
Chiara already misses him.
Son, why don't you call Chiara?
You know,
kids these days are so lucky, right?
As long as there's internet,
you can talk to your sweetheart,
no matter where they are in the world.
No, Mom, it's okay.
Chiara's busy too.
Why not?
We're just checking up on her.
We're not strangers to her, right?
You know, Mom. She has a lot
to take care of in Prague.
Maybe it's better
if we don't bother her for now.
Is that so?
You know, seeing Chiara
really lifts my mood.
She has such a gentle face.
Such a kind child.
Right?
That's why La Morte Bianca sent me.
I will be the one to kill him.
I needed to warn Mikoy
because Viktor was suspecting him.
No.
What you did was tell him that Chiara
is La Fornarina.
I will order the director
to remove you from this case,
because clearly,
you're not listening anymore.
You are blind and deaf to the truth.
If you remove me from this case,
then you're also protecting
the Moravianos.
You're the one who should stand down.
Why don't you try?
Try to disarm me,
and let's see what happens.
Are you and Chiara having problems?
Or is Chiara the one who has a problem?
It's obvious.
Ever since you met
your handler that night,
you haven't been yourself.
Which could only mean
one of two things.
Either your handler said
the world is ending tomorrow,
or they have information
about Chiara.
That could mean
she isn't innocent in all of this.
Dad, no offense, but…
I'm not comfortable
talking about this right now.
I'm not ready yet.
When will you ever be ready?
Son, if you keep bottling it up,
you'll only suffer more.
Look at you.
It's showing all over your face.
You can't sit still.
Your mind is always somewhere else.
Son,
it's simple. Just face the truth.
That's unless…
you still believe
that Chiara is innocent.
That she's not part
of her family's syndicate.
Mikoy,
the truth is right in front of you.
What are you waiting for?
You want the truth, Dad?
I don't care what Chiara is.
Because I love her.
I love her so much.
We're doomed.
Looks like I'm not the only one
with nine lives here.
Agent Alex too.
The doctors said she's incredibly lucky
because all of her injuries
are only superficial.
That's why we need to be twice
or even three times more careful now.
Especially with Mikoy.
Mikoy, our asset?
Exactly!
Haven't you noticed?
He's turning all of us against each other.
No. All the intel he's giving us is dirty.
He's not the kind of person
who would knowingly
feed us dirty intelligence.
How sure are you about that?
I'm a profiler, remember?
But have you also considered
that maybe Viktor and the Moravianos
are just manipulating Mikoy?
So, what's your plan?
I really don't know, Dad.
So you're choosing Chiara.
She's the one my heart chose.
I hope you realize
that your love has consequences.
If you keep turning a blind eye
to everything that family is doing,
you will become an accessory
to her crimes and her family's crimes.
In the eyes of the G.A.G.O,
that's a form of connivance,
conspiracy,
and they will see you as a traitor
because you were supposed to be an asset
who defected.
Son, I understand your situation.
I know how to love.
But
are you ready
for the huge and messy complications
that come with loving Chiara?
I hate to be the bearer of bad news,
but as your father,
I have to tell you the truth.
Maybe they know he's an asset.
That's what the Moravianos do best.
So we won't trust each other.
You know, you have a point.
As far as he's concerned,
we can't trust Mikoy.
We can't do that.
So
we can tell him what's really happening.
Sir, you have a visitor.
All right, let them in.
Sir.
As they say, when one door closes,
you enter through the sliding door.
Special Agent Sianong.
Of course, I know you.
You're hardworking, dependable,
and most of all,
the most handsome one in this story.
Oh, well,
you know,
as they say,
everything happens for a reason.
That's public service for you.
Some get hospitalized.
Some get promoted.
We've been avoiding each other
for so long.
Looks like we'll only reunite now.
What do you need?
I'm not asking for help, Norberto.
I'm collecting a debt.
What do you need?
Looks like he has a deep
and serious problem.
Why aren't we at the office?
Why here? What's this about?
Listen to me carefully.
You're the only one I trust in the agency,
and I need your help.
This is making me nervous.
If something happens to me,
promise me you'll make sure
that Mikoy stays safe.
Why? What's going on with Mikoy?
This isn't the first time
the Moravianos attacked me.
Is Mikoy really that important?
Why me?
Why not Agent Sianong?
Just trust me.
Do what I'm asking you to do.
Hello? Who is this?
I don't have much time,
but I need to tell you this.
Agent Alex is in the hospital.
What?
Why? What happened?
Remember the intel you gave us?
The one about Vertex's warehouse?
Well, turns out
it was a trap set by the Moravianos.
They set Agent Alex up,
and when they got there,
a bomb was waiting for them.
Huh? What?
Wait. What happened to Alex?
Is she okay?
Looks like the Moravianos
deliberately gave you bad intel.
Where's Alex? I'm going to see her.
No! You can't.
Why not?
Because there's a bigger problem.
Looks like the Moravianos know
you're an asset for the agency.
Because I'm sure you're their next target.
Before it's too late.
Bok!
Wait. What are you doing? Bok.
I'm going to Mikoy. His life is in danger.
Mikoy again?!
Because if he wanted to kill Mikoy,
he would've done it already long ago.
Or maybe Chiara
is the one who wants him dead.
Room for one
under Alexander Grande.
We have Grande here. Prepare the room.