What seems to be the problem?
- Sir.
- What’s happening with the two of you?
We have to remove Alex from this case.
If we’re going to count contributions,
every breakthrough
in this case came from me.
I know it’s bothering you,
those consecutive attacks
of the Moravianos.
And if you think we’re just going
to stand here and accept their attacks?
It’s time to strike back.
GLOBAL AGENCY FOR GOVERNMENT OPERATIONS
I prepared a file for the operation.
All the details are in there,
so study it carefully.
And if you have any questions,
do not hesitate to talk to me.
Is that understood?
- Copy.
- Yes, ma'am.
How long are you going
to give me the silent treatment?
You're like my classmate
back in grade 1, Barry Gonsales.
He got mad at me
because I spelled Gonsales wrong.
I used "Z" instead of "S".
Okay.
I know I haven't been myself lately,
and I'll admit
I've gotten attached to Mikoy.
But it's not because of what you think.
Because, you know,
I'm the one who got him involved in this.
I really want to bring
the Moravianos down,
but not at the expense
of someone else's life.
Bok, I won't be able to handle it
if another innocent life
is lost because of me.
Maybe this kind of thinking
clouds my judgment, like you said.
Sianong, I need you.
So, Bok, whatever this is,
please stop already.
Please?
Why?
Is this about Chiara?
What did Brusko say?
He didn't say anything.
But I know it's about Mikoy.
Chiara is hurt.
Because of him.
Mikoy? I don't get it.
What did Mikoy do? Cheat on her?
Cheat with a guy? I don't know.
Why did he hurt Chiara?
I don't get it.
I know it might sound impossible,
but it seems like Mikoy
has bigger and darker secrets than that.
La Morte Bianca is not happy.
She has sent the Painter.
Painter?
The mansion still looks fine though.
Yes.
Our color scheme still looks beautiful.
- Though the bathroom--
- Not that kind of painter.
The one who can paint our walls
bloody red.
Dad.
Mikoy.
I let you meet your handler last night.
Even by yourself.
I also didn't ask you what happened
or for an explanation.
But I'm not naive.
I notice a lot of things.
Especially when
you couldn't answer your mother's question
about how Chiara was doing.
Is something going on?
It's nothing, Dad.
There was just an emergency
at the agency last night,
but it had nothing to do with my mission.
Liar.
I can tell you're lying.
Come on, Dad.
I already told you last night,
and I'll say it again.
I don't want you getting involved
in the mess I got into.
Dad, just leave me be.
Trouble is normal in missions.
That's why what you need
is a reliable partner
like me.
Boys!
I'm heading to the market.
Do you boys have any requests?
Anything you want me to buy?
Like ideas for a dish?
So I can buy the ingredients.
Just fresh coconut juice, Mom.
Okay. How about you, dear?
Later.
Later, Tess.
We're discussing something important.
Is that so?
Okay, request granted. Dear,
I'll see you later!
Trust me, son, I'm the only one
you can rely on right now.
Oh my!
That’s what I’m talking about.
I forgot my wallet again.
You're getting forgetful again, Tess.
What do you mean by that?
And why do you seem
so confident about this mission?
Are you still hiding
something from me, Dad?
And were you really
just an intelligence asset
for law enforcement before,
like what you told me the other night?
Is this my final hour?
Dad?
And you still haven't explained
why you have so many hidden guns, Dad!
I'll only tell you this.
This is top secret, okay?
Okay, Dad.
I was part of a…
kill squad.
A clandestine operative
in a top military unit.
Like…
Naruto's ANBU?
Like that?
Mikoy, I have some very special skills.
I was the best ANBU you're talking about.
And my name isn't Mario.
- I am known as…
- Dad.
Isidro Catacutan.
The Butuan Executioner of Butuan.
Butuan Executioner of Butuan?
Yes.
I never back down.
No one can make me tremble,
no matter who they are.
Honey!
What are you doing there?
You've been chatting too much.
- Aren't you coming to the market with me?
- All right.
I'll carry the bags.
Okay, okay.
Remember.
The Executioner of Butuan.
- Mario! You’re still chatting!
- Okay, okay, I'm coming.
The Executioner.
- I’m telling you, time is running out!
- All right, I’m going to carry the bag!
You know, I watched Lord of the Rings,
the director’s cut.
That’s when I realized
Sam is the real protagonist of the story.
All this time, I thought it was Frodo.
How about you? What do you think?
Are you in Aragorn's camp?
Bro, keep the change.
Are you still upset?
Okay, fine, be that way.
Just keep your eyes open.
We are looking for Quebec Romero 1020.
That’s the plate number
of the container van.
And if Mikoy is right,
that will take us to the secret hideout.
And may I just remind you
that you’re violating habit number five
of Seven Habits
of Highly Effective People.
Get it?
Seek to understand, then to be understood.
The habit that forces you
to understand the fears, needs,
and the perspective of the other person.
I just wanted to protect the people
who’s important to me, Sianong.
And if you were in Mikoy’s situation,
I’d do the same for you.
I wish you would see my intentions
and understand why I'm doing this.
That’s our truck.
Eagle Two, target location confirmed.
Copy that, Mother Eagle.
Dara.
Ouch. Mario, wait.
I can't take it anymore.
I really need to pee.
Mikoy, I'm telling the truth.
I can still help you.
Dad!
Are you joking again?
I'm not joking.
I can still fight.
Look at my moves.
Up. Cross.
See?
Wait.
- Why?
- It hurts.
- See, Dad, that's what I was saying.
- Ouch.
- Ouch. What is this?
- Mom!
What happened, Mario?
- I don't know.
- What happened?
I forgot to tell you earlier,
I went to the gym.
I worked out. I lifted around 350 kilos.
I did 50 reps.
- Wow.
- I think something gave out.
- Fifty…
- Rotator cuff…
Fifty reps? Fifty reps
carrying vegetables maybe.
Okay, help…
Help your father. I'll just get some oil.
Yes, Mom.
Are you really okay, Dad?
- Of course.
- All right, Dad, I believe you now.
You don't need to do that anymore.
But that doesn't mean
I'll agree with what you want,
that I'll still let you do it.
Why are you so stubborn?
Why don't you want to ask for help?
Because I've already
made my decision, Dad.
I'm going to tell Chiara everything.
Instead of stressing myself out,
I should be true to her, right?
It's time for her to know
about everything I've been doing.
The site is 12 clicks from our position.
The hideout has three entry points.
There's entry 1.
Entry 2.
And entry 3.
Security is lighter than expected.
But let's assume it's a trap.
- Copy, ma'am.
- Now move.
Move.
Well, now
I know.
Hold.
What do you want
We are the Global Agency
for Government Operations,
and we have a search warrant.
May I see it?
Cover!
Clear! Move!
You're being careless, Viktor.
Extremely careless.
And your security team? Stupid.
They don't know what they're doing.
That's why I can take them all down.
No wonder La Morte is unhappy with you.
Is it because you're that old
that you've forgotten all your failures,
Viktor?
You're no longer
the Valtrovi I remember.
Ridiculous.
Get down, Bok!
Let's go, Bok.
Cover, Bok! Cover!
Mother Eagle, area 2 clear.
Copy that.
Clear!
Move.
Bok.
Be careful.
Go, go, go!
Open it.
But you know?
Don't!
Alex!
I cannot believe
you fell into that honey trap.
Sir, I think it's Mikoy.
How much more evidence do we need
before you realize
that what I'm saying is true,
that Mikoy is compromised?
The Moravianos know
that you're an asset to the agency.
I’ll be the one to kill him!