=Angels and Guards=
=Episode 7=
(Guan Yunfeng,
Eighth-Rank Black-Robed Head Constable)
Enforcement Division,
Ministry of Justice.
We've been waiting for you.
You Ministry scum.
(Diaotu, the Flower-Picking Bee, No. 5)
You think you can arrest me?
You're Diaotu,
the Flower-Picking Bee,
No. 5 on the List.
Get him.
(Enforcement, Ministry of Justice)
Useless fools. Useless!
All these men,
and you let a lecherous bandit escape?
Guan Yunfeng.
What's wrong with you?
I failed in my duty.
Please punish me, Chief Constable.
At least you know
you should be punished!
Guan Yunfeng failed to catch the thief.
By rule, he must be punished.
Take him away.
Give him 20 heavy strokes!
Chief, Diaotu is a lecherous fiend
and highly skilled.
Constable Guan did his best.
Yes, Chief Constable.
Anyone who pleads for him again
will share his punishment.
Guys,
don't plead for me.
I failed in my duty.
I accept my punishment.
Do it!
Diaotu,
I won't rest
until I catch you.
(Northern Bureau)
Miss, is your surname Shen?
Yes. How did you know?
There's a letter for you.
Thank you.
(Feng Fuliu)
I came as promised.
Show yourself.
Congratulations, Miss Shen.
You passed the assessment.
Thank you.
Is that all?
Nothing else to say to me?
Feng Fuliu.
I have joined the Northern Bureau.
From now on, we are sworn enemies.
What are you laughing at?
Officer Shen,
in your eyes,
am I truly so unforgivable?
I don't care what kind of man you are.
What matters is
that you are No. 2 on the Bounty List,
a wanted fugitive of the court.
I am an officer. You are a thief.
Catching you is only right.
You're still too naive.
Once you spend more time in the Bureau,
you'll understand
that this world
is not only black and white.
There is gray too.
In my eyes,
there is only black and white. No gray.
Then you'll never catch Leng Xin
and avenge your father.
How do you know that?
Who exactly are you?
Me?
I am Feng Fuliu,
the phantom thief
ranked No. 2 on the List.
But
I'm also your friend.
Since you walk the criminal path,
we can never be friends.
You don't want to be my friend?
Then what do you want to be?
Enemies. That's all.
You're still so impatient.
If you can't change that,
you may never uncover the truth.
Who are you?
(Feng Fuliu.)
(Chang Beiming.)
(Sun Manor)
You may go back.
Yes.
Who are you?
Help!
(Enforcement Division,
Ministry of Justice)
My poor daughter!
You died so horribly!
Here in the capital,
under the Emperor's very nose,
that monster is getting bolder
by the day.
He attacked the Vice Minister
of Rites' manor.
(Duan Li, Southern Bureau's Commander)
What's the Ministry of Justice doing?
Commander Duan, Vice Minister Sun,
we're doing everything to catch him.
But he is highly skilled.
So we haven't...
Brother,
you must
seek justice for your niece!
Chief Constable Lin,
if you fail
to give me an answer for this,
I'll report you
before His Majesty myself.
Useless fool.
Apologize to Commander Duan
and Vice Minister Sun. Now!
I have failed you.
You certainly have.
From now on,
your Enforcement Division
is off this case.
I'll petition the court
to put the Jinyiwei in charge.
(Northern Bureau)
A depraved criminal runs rampant,
terrorizing the imperial capital.
(Imperial Edict)
The Ministry of Justice has failed.
Lin Feng is dismissed pending review.
The Jinyiwei Northern Bureau
is hereby ordered
to take full charge of the Diaotu case.
(Imperial Edict)
Within ten days,
the Northern Bureau needs
to capture the criminal
and uphold the law.
These criminals are out of control.
They even dared target
an official from the Ministry of Rites.
His Majesty and the Cabinet
have set a deadline.
Guokai,
I think this case
should go to the female Jinyiwei.
My lord,
we're dealing with
a predator who preys on women.
Well...
Having the female guards handle it
doesn't seem appropriate.
I think they're
exactly right for it.
But
they just started.
They have no experience.
If you never use them,
how will they get any?
Fine, fine. Use them.
Someone.
Yes!
Summon Shen Bingfan, Hua Mange,
and Cheng Xintian.
Greetings, Commander.
Greetings, Commissioner.
Soldiers are trained for years
for one moment of need.
Now this predator is running wild.
He even dares to harm
the family of a court official.
He has no fear of the law
and deserves no mercy.
The first case I assign to you
is to capture Diaotu,
the Flower-Picking Bee.
I give you
ten days.
If you catch him within the deadline,
you will be richly rewarded.
If you fail,
go back where you came from.
Ten days?
Where are we supposed to find him
in ten days?
Within ten days,
I will capture Diaotu.
Good.
If you don't catch Diaotu in ten days,
the three of you can resign.
(Northern Bureau)
Why did you agree
to solve it in ten days
without asking us?
Because I'm confident.
I'll capture Diaotu within ten days.
Who do you think Diaotu is?
He's No. 5 on the Bounty List.
Liu Sankong nearly got you killed.
You're no match for Diaotu.
Do you know Diaotu well?
Me?
I don't.
But I know this.
No. 5 on the Bounty List
is no easy target.
Bingfan,
let's think this through.
(Northern Bureau)
Yes, Bingfan.
At least ask the Commander
to assign us some male Jinyiwei.
This is the first mission
the Commander gave us.
How can we ask the men for help?
You're not planning
to do this alone again, are you?
Bingfan, we're a team.
We do this together.
What do we do, Hua?
This won't work.
We need to borrow some men.
Everyone in the Northern Bureau
answers to Mr. Lu.
What if he refuses?
Not necessarily.
We don't have to borrow Jinyiwei.
Hua, Xintian, I found something out.
Constable Guan Yunfeng
of the Enforcement Division
failed to catch Diaotu.
Not only was he caned,
but he was also scolded in public
by the Chief Constable.
Now,
after hearing the Jinyiwei
took over the Diaotu case,
he's too angry to eat or drink.
I was thinking we could join forces
with him
and borrow a few skilled men
from the Enforcement Division.
Then we might stand a chance
against Diaotu.
But why would he help us?
Because I'll make him.
Diaotu, I'll make sure
you die horribly.
Hey, handsome.
Drinking your sorrows away alone?
Get lost.
Go hustle somewhere else.
What?
What do you take me for?
Duoyu.
Guan.
Xu.
You misunderstand.
This is Hua.
She's a Squad Leader
from Jinyiwei Northern Bureau.
A female Jinyiwei?
The Northern Bureau
really recruited women?
Not only that,
but
the mission to catch Diaotu
has been given to Hua and her team.
Take a look around.
That's absurd.
Diaotu is vicious.
How can they send women after him?
Exactly.
That's why we came to you for help,
Constable Guan.
When it comes to catching that scum,
I will do my duty.
Diaotu, the Flower-Picking Bee.
Diaotu?
Tell me everything you know.
Zhu Zijun, daughter of Mr. Zhu
from the east-side gold shop.
Beauty, here I come.
Who are you?
Diaotu, the Flower-Picking Bee.
Assaulting women,
abduction, and plunder.
73 lives on your hands.
The reward is 5,000 taels.
Dead or alive.
You are a bounty hunter.
But you got one thing wrong.
After tonight,
it'll be 74 lives.
Are you all right?
A skilled fighter.
Constable Guan, are you all right?
I'm fine.
I'll go after him.
Hua, be careful!
Bingfan...
You know martial arts?
I never said I didn't.
I just don't like fighting.
There's a distinctive scent.
What a strange smell.
Hold this.
I can walk myself.
Don't move.
Put me down.
(Yin Manor)
You love acting alone, don't you?
Always playing the hero?
Listen, Shen Bingfan.
You only have one life.
If you don't value it,
no one else can value it for you.
I'm warning you, Shen Bingfan.
If you keep this up,
hurting yourself
and dragging down the team,
I'll tell Zhang Weimin
to strike you from the Jinyiwei roster.
What did I do wrong?
Be quiet.
Think about it yourself.
Cheng Xintian, where's the medicine?
Coming.
I saw you two arguing,
so I didn't dare come in.
- We weren't.
Leave us.
Bear with it. I'll apply the medicine.
I'll do it myself.
Be quiet.
Stay still.
♪In a fleeting moment♪
♪Whose face crosses my mind♪
♪Whose name is it♪
♪I whisper in my heart♪
♪Yet in the crowd, we brush past♪
♪Afraid memories will fade like dreams♪
♪Was hidden in the day we met♪
♪A fate that cannot be severed♪
♪Round and round♪
♪Threads of love bind us together♪
♪Afraid love will fade like smoke♪
♪Afraid memories
will vanish like dreams♪
♪This longing I cannot say♪
♪I wish you could hear♪
Bingfan.
Maybe...
I should go.
I'm applying medicine.
Xintian, what is it?
Hua is back.
(Yin Manor)
Officer, you...
(Jinyiwei Squad Leader
of the Left Qianhu Office)
I'm Shen Bingfan, a Squad Leader
from Jinyiwei Northern Bureau.
I am under orders to arrest Diaotu,
the Flower-Picking Bee.
I need to search the manor.
A Jinyiwei officer is here!
Officer! Officer!
Hua, bad news.
Fan went to Marquis Taiping's manor
alone.
(Yin Xian, Marquis Taiping)
What?
Did I hear that right?
You want to search my manor?
My lord,
I suspect
Diaotu, the Flower-Picking Bee,
is hiding here.
Please allow me to search.
How dare you!
A low-ranking Squad Leader
wants to search my manor?
Do you have an imperial edict
or the Cabinet's gold token?
I am acting under orders
from the Northern Bureau...
To hell with your Northern Bureau!
To hell with it!
Northern Bureau?
No edict. No gold token.
A Squad Leader
dares barge in
and search a marquis's manor?
This is contempt for the court.
Guards!
Get her!
Yes, my lord!
Don't you dare.
In this situation,
we need the Commander to step in.
Only he can stand up to Marquis Taiping.
There's one more person who can help.
The Jinyiwei act first
and report later.
It's by imperial authority.
Let me tell you.
I'm a first-rank marquis
from a house of merit.
My father won glory
for the empire in battles.
Drawing your blade in my manor
is as good as treason.
Lock her up.
Who dares touch
my Northern Bureau officer?
Well, well.
If it isn't the Commander.
My lord.
A man of your status
needn't lower himself
to quarrel with a young woman.
You don't understand.
This young woman
came here in broad daylight
to search my manor.
She even used the Northern Bureau
to threaten me.
She accused me
of harboring a wanted outlaw.
This young woman
is no simple girl.
She is new here
and doesn't know the rules.
When we return,
I will punish her severely.
My lord,
would you
do me this favor?
♪Because you once entered my dreams♪
♪Truth and illusion blur in wine♪
♪My heart drifted lost♪
♪Yet found you in the crowd♪
♪My blood still burns
as the world surges♪
♪The land is fair, and you are free♪
♪Sword drawn, lost in obsession♪
♪I've softly let it go♪
♪The vow you made was true♪
♪Yet like clouds, it stops for no one♪
♪Put away those dreamlike words♪
♪And forget at world's end♪
♪Embracing memory♪
♪Through blossoms and dreams♪
♪You hide in the crowd, silent♪
♪I wish to let it pass♪
♪And run toward this vast life♪