=Angels and Guards=
=Episode 6=
Why have you been so nice to me?
Because I like you.
What did you say?
Don't joke about that, or I'll hit you.
Beat me to death and I'll still say it.
I like you.
And I mean it.
No. You can't like me.
Why not?
Because I swore an oath.
I won't marry until I catch Leng Xin.
Then I'll help you catch him.
(Northern Bureau)
My lord, you personally promised me
that if I defeated Commissioner Lu,
you would let me enter the Bureau's
chamber to read Leng Xin's file.
I said after
you pass the month-end assessment
and defeat him.
But I already defeated him.
The assessment is only a formality.
Then finish the formality first.
Leng Xin's file is sitting right there.
It won't grow legs and run away.
Don't rush.
A couple of days won't hurt.
Just a couple of days.
Here.
Have a drink with me.
I heard
you want to get into that chamber.
You have a way in?
To be honest,
I've been
quite interested in that chamber.
And I've already asked Xu Duoyu
to get us a fake pass.
Xu Duoyu can forge passes?
So?
Are you coming?
Wait.
If you have a pass, why not go alone?
Why drag me into it?
Because going alone
is scary.
Commander.
The matter you arranged is done.
(Prince Luo's Treason Case)
(Why is there nothing in the chamber)
(about why Leng Xin killed my father?)
(Who does he work for?)
(Zhang Weimin)
(What?)
(When my father carried out
that mission,)
(his direct superior at the time)
(was Zhang Weimin?)
Greetings, Commissioner.
Here. Authorization.
What are you two doing here?
Studying.
Yes. It's quiet here.
Good.
Very good.
That's the spirit.
(If Zhang Weimin knows something,)
(how do I get it out of him?)
(That old man may look muddled,)
(but he's actually very sharp.)
(If he finds out)
(I'm investigating a sealed case,)
(will that cause trouble?)
Three days from now
is the month-end assessment.
All of you,
don't think getting into the Bureau
means you can rest easy.
Mr. Lu said that if even one
of you three fails,
all of you are out.
Is that clear?
Yes.
What?
Even you dare laugh at me?
Nice shot.
Young Master Chang.
It's for you.
For me?
Thank you, Young Master Chang.
To be Jinyiwei,
you need more than martial arts.
You have real talent with a slingshot.
I got good
at shooting sparrows back in my village.
Then make that your strength.
If you make a good archer,
how could Zhang Weimin reject you?
Really?
But you only have three days.
You need to train hard.
You don't have to be perfect,
but you can't miss.
Otherwise, why would they keep you?
(The month-end assessment is tomorrow.)
(I have to pass.)
Commander, Commissioner,
Shen Bingfan and Hua Mange
passed the month-end assessment.
Good.
Wait, wait.
Isn't there still one left?
Yes, you. Come out.
Commander,
I have something to report.
What?
Well...
I know
I'm not good with short weapons.
But I do have a special skill.
So I humbly ask
if I may use this skill
to make up for my short-weapons score.
Nonsense!
The assessment is not a game.
Let her speak.
What special skill does she have?
Everyone,
this is just a village boy's toy.
How is that a special skill?
What a joke.
Good.
Who here can't shoot down a bird?
Anyone can do that.
Exactly.
Am I right?
Anyone can.
My lord.
If the Southern Bureau hears about this,
they'll laugh their heads off.
Cheng Xintian.
Can that thing
only shoot birds?
I can hit pressure points from afar.
Stop bragging.
I'm not.
Strike a pressure point to prove it.
All right.
Then let's do as Guokai said.
We'll let her slingshot skills
count for the short-weapons test.
My lord.
That isn't what I meant.
I was saying this slingshot...
Then what did you mean?
As the saying goes,
a man's word is his bond.
In front of all these people,
surely you won't go back on your word.
Zuo Da. Jiang Biao.
And you there.
The second one.
Yes, you. Step forward.
Good shot!
Didn't you say
you could
hit pressure points?
Do it.
Zuo Da, why are you laughing?
Sir, she hit my laughing point.
Jiang Biao, why are you crying?
She hit my crying point.
She hit my numbing point.
I can't move.
You two useless fools. Get out.
You idiot.
Stand down.
Stop laughing.
All of you, stop!
Are you scolding me too?
I wouldn't dare.
In that case,
Cheng Xintian,
although you failed the weapon test,
your slingshot skill makes up for it.
I hereby decide
that all three female Jinyiwei
have passed.
You may now take on missions.
Wow!
Guokai,
one must learn
to open up.
Open up!
Bingfan,
I passed!
On such a wonderful day,
let's drink again. Come on.
Cheers.
- Cheers.
Congratulations on passing, ladies.
My young master sends gifts.
How thoughtful of Young Master Chang.
What are these?
Three Shu brocade cloaks.
My young master said
that when you travel for cases,
you may be exposed to the elements.
These will shield you from the elements.
And three pairs of cloud-brocade boots.
Warm in winter and cool in summer.
Also for you three female officers.
How does he know all our shoe sizes?
You'll have to ask my young master.
He sent us gifts.
Let's not be difficult.
Honestly, Young Master Chang
deserves much credit for this.
Now he's sent such fine gifts.
Shouldn't we go thank him?
(Emerald Pavilion)
Young Master, I came to thank you.
Without you,
I wouldn't have passed the assessment.
It was nothing. Don't mention it.
And you sent us gifts too.
Thank you.
Only you came to thank me?
They didn't?
I...
I'll thank you for them.
Wait.
This red sandalwood slingshot
and these 24 steel pellets
were mine as a child.
There's a pressure-point chart inside.
I taught you three pressure-point shots.
The rest is up to you.
Such a precious gift.
Thank you.
I'll study it carefully
and won't let everyone down.
Do your best.
What a strange dream.
For once, it wasn't a nightmare.
Good thing it was only a dream.
(Leisurely and Free)
Clear sky.
What lovely weather.
Fresh and bright. Looking good.
♪In a fleeting moment♪
♪Whose face crosses my mind♪
♪Whose name is it♪
No nightmare last night?
How do you know I have nightmares?
Day one, you refused to share a room.
That made me suspicious.
Most nights, you scream in your sleep.
Even through these thick walls,
I can hear you.
So... you heard everything?
Do you have nightmares every night?
Since I was thirteen,
I've had nightmares almost every night.
Have you sought treatment?
I've seen famous doctors.
They said it was an emotional scar,
with no cure.
Sit.
I have a folk remedy.
Wait here.
♪This longing cannot say♪
Open it before bed,
and you'll never have nightmares again.
If it can cure this old illness,
I'll be forever grateful.
(A Night of Sweet Dreams)
What?
(Place this portrait by your pillow.)
(Pay your respects
before bed each night.)
(You'll sleep straight through
till morning,)
(and all nightmares will vanish.)
Did you sleep well last night?
I've never met anyone
so full of himself.
Did it work?
Did it?
♪Because you once entered my dreams♪
♪Truth and illusion blur in wine♪
♪My heart drifted lost♪
♪Yet found you in the crowd♪
♪My blood still burns
as the world surges♪
♪The land is fair, and you are free♪
♪Sword drawn, lost in obsession♪
♪I've softly let it go♪
♪The vow you made was true♪
♪Yet like clouds, it stops for no one♪
♪Put away those dreamlike words♪
♪And forget at world's end♪
♪Embracing memory♪
♪Through blossoms and dreams♪
♪You hide in the crowd, silent♪
♪I wish to let it pass♪
♪And run toward this vast life♪