=Angels and Guards=
=Episode 5=
She outshines all others in training,
making all the male guards lose face.
Now she wants to take my place?
How could I allow that?
Mr. Lu has arrived.
Greetings, Mr. Lu.
Shen Bingfan, aren't you impressive?
I heard
not one of the male guards here
can beat you.
Do you have the nerve
to spar with me?
Mr. Lu,
Bingfan is recovering from her injury.
Is she truly injured,
or is she afraid?
Don't tell me
you've all been going easy on her.
No.
I accept your challenge, Mr. Lu.
- Bingfan!
So she really is injured.
I'm fine.
Again.
Bingfan.
Stop.
Don't push yourself.
I heard Lu Guokai abused his power
and hurt you on purpose.
He just has it out for us.
I'll drag him here right now
and make him apologize to you.
Wait.
Don't go after Lu Guokai.
I lost because I wasn't good enough.
He took advantage of you!
Come on.
Lu Guokai's Wind Blade
is sharp and perfectly controlled.
Even if I weren't injured,
I still wouldn't be his match.
If I let you stand up for me
because of this,
I'd be using power to bully him.
Then what do you want?
I want to learn to break his Wind Blade.
And I'll defeat him
in the training yard.
Lu Guokai has practiced Wind Blade
for at least 20 years.
Can a few days' training beat it?
My master once said
even the finest martial arts
will reveal a weakness.
Officialdom isn't the martial world.
If you defy your superior like this,
nothing good will come of it.
But he humiliated me in public.
He's your superior and your elder.
What's wrong with yielding a little?
If I yield now,
he'll go even further next time.
Then ask Beiming to speak for you.
If he puts in a word,
Lu Guokai will back down.
Why should I ask him to step in?
I'll win it back myself.
Why are you so stubborn?
So you plan
to fight your superior to the end?
I just believe
you get back up where you fell.
If you refuse to bend,
one day,
you'll pay dearly for it.
Hua told me
you've gone mad to master Wind Blade.
At the end-of-month assessment,
Lu will use Wind Blade against me.
If I lose again,
even if I'm not expelled
from the Bureau,
I won't get promoted anytime soon.
You want a promotion that badly?
My business
is not something you'd understand.
I want to know. Will you tell me?
Why do you want to hear it?
Because I want to help you.
Fine.
If you truly want to help,
then help me figure out
how to break Lu Guokai's Wind Blade.
Lu's Wind Blade leaves no openings.
It's very hard to break.
Not quite.
Bingfan,
you and Hua,
show me how you fought Lu that day.
I've got it.
Lu Guokai's Wind Blade is powerful,
but he neglects his lower body.
Hua,
can you show her
the Thirty-Six Forms of Ground Boxing?
Got it?
Try it.
I understand now.
I'll practice some more.
Young... Young Master.
How did you get here?
I'm really sorry.
I was too focused on training.
This is
the second time you've hurt me.
Then... what do you want?
If you want my forgiveness,
then
give me a massage
and apply medicine.
You arrived.
Why are you taking your clothes off?
Do you apply medicine through clothes?
I...
What are you waiting for?
Where... where are you hurt?
Here.
So this is a man's body.
It doesn't look
that different from a woman's.
Why are you making comments on my body?
That tickles.
Then do it yourself.
No, you do it.
Young Master Chang.
I...
Just say what you want to say.
This isn't like you.
My master once told me
there's something in a man that's bad.
It can make women pregnant.
What is it?
Can I see it?
Are you insane?
Is that something you just ask to see?
You can make all kinds of medicine,
and you can cook too.
I've been alone since I was little.
Over time, I learned to do everything.
What about your family?
My parents
died when I was very young.
By the way, Hua,
do you know the Ever-Changing Wildcat?
Why bring her up?
I was just asking.
Are you
curious about her?
The only woman in the list's top ten.
Aren't you curious?
Then do you know
why, among the ten most wanted,
she's the only one they want alive?
Because men want to capture her alive,
humiliate her,
and soothe their bruised egos.
And she
has to keep getting stronger,
so they never get what they want.
You understand her well.
I understand women.
So,
if I ever meet her,
I'll let her go.
By the way, Hua,
this is the sick-day pill you wanted.
Take one,
and your forehead will heat up.
It'll look just like heatstroke.
Duoyu, your sick-day pill really works.
Help me to your room to rest.
(Firecrackers)
Duoyu.
You really are something.
Hua, keep your voice down.
I've never brought anyone here before.
What are you shy about?
(Jinyiwei Handbook)
I just like studying strange things.
The way I see it,
you're no ordinary errand boy.
The assessment is coming up.
The Commander is here
to watch your training today.
What would you like to see, my lord?
Short weapons.
Line up!
You three will train today.
Hua Mange.
My lord.
I am
feeling unwell.
My lord, she fainted a few days ago.
It seemed to be heatstroke.
Then next.
Cheng Xintian.
My lord.
I'm on my period.
What are you laughing at?
Why are you making a fuss?
You've never had one?
Well...
Shen Bingfan, can you fight?
Yes.
But I would like to challenge Mr. Lu.
What?
Shen Bingfan, who do you think you are?
Do you know what this is called?
Insubordination. Defying your superior.
Do you know the rules or not?
You can't beat him.
I'm willing to try.
Mr. Zhang, she challenged me first.
Don't blame me for bullying my junior.
Prepare extra wound medicine for her.
(Lu Guokai's Wind Blade is powerful,)
(but he overlooks one thing.)
(His lower body.)
(Wind Blade
focuses on upper-body attacks.)
(Lu Guokai's footwork is terrible.)
(Once you spot an opening,)
(attack his legs.)
(That should give you a chance to win.)
My lord!
Are you all right?
Shen Bingfan!
If I don't kick you out of the Bureau,
I'll eat my hat!
My lord, please compose yourself.
Guokai.
You've broadened your mind.
You truly have.
I'm deeply moved.
Guokai,
you've opened up.
All the way.
You've truly moved me.
Such consideration for your subordinate.
Did everyone see that?
That is Mr. Lu's magnanimity.
Here.
Thank you.
Have a drink.
What is this taste?
This is a happy occasion.
We should all be happy.
Smile.
Everyone, smile!
Be happy!
Guokai, take a rest.
Did you see that?
That is true magnanimity.
Mr. Lu held back,
and you clearly learned a great deal.
All right, today
we'll
stop here.
Everyone, dismissed.
Dismissed. Go on.
Are you feeling better?
Guokai, how generous of spirit.
Help Mr. Lu get back to rest.
Get some rest.
Yes.
Add a couple of extra dishes for Mr. Lu.
Move.
Bingfan.
Let's go.
You knew when to stop.
Good. Very good.
Impressive.
Duoyu,
how has Shen Bingfan
been lately?
She's been...
Enough.
Don't say it.
I know.
(Chong'er Pavilion)
Come on.
Coming.
Come on. A toast to Beiming.
Yes, a toast.
Congratulations.
Beiming,
you did Miss Shen
a huge favor this time.
That must've earned you major points.
My points were already high.
Of course.
Beiming.
Miss Shen will come see you today.
I think so too.
Why?
To confess her love to you.
Chang Beiming.
Go, go.
Go out.
Chang Beiming.
I came to thank you.
Without your help,
I couldn't have beaten Lu's Wind Blade.
So you don't hate me anymore?
You are the only man
who can come within three feet of me
without making me uncomfortable.
And you're also
one of the male friends
I'd most like to make.
Bingfan,
I like...
What happened?
I couldn't help it.
What are you doing?
Miss Shen, hi.
We...
We weren't doing anything.
Right.
Nothing at all.
They're drunk.
We're not drunk.
We were betting on
when Beiming would win you over.
What nonsense.
Chang Beiming.
No.
You...
Let me explain.
Please, let me explain.
What's there to explain?
So you were nice to me
because of a bet.
What...
That's not true.
I knew nothing about their bet.
I really didn't.
Then why have you been so nice to me?
Because I like you.
♪Because you once entered my dreams♪
♪Truth and illusion blur in wine♪
♪My heart drifted lost♪
♪Yet found you in the crowd♪
♪My blood still burns
as the world surges♪
♪The land is fair, and you are free♪
♪Sword drawn, lost in obsession♪
♪I've softly let it go♪
♪The vow you made was true♪
♪Yet like clouds, it stops for no one♪
♪Put away those dreamlike words♪
♪And forget at world's end♪
♪Embracing memory♪
♪Through blossoms and dreams♪
♪You hide in the crowd, silent♪
♪I wish to let it pass♪
♪And run toward this vast life♪