=Angels and Guards=
=Episode 9=
The Northern Bureau matter is settled.
You asked Mr. Ye for help?
He loves the wine at Chong'er Pavilion.
Getting his help was easy.
Chang Beiming.
Who exactly are you?
I am
a friend you can trust.
If we are friends,
why not tell me the truth?
When have I not told you the truth?
Everyone knows Young Master Chang
of Chong'er Pavilion.
Fine.
Since you will not tell the truth,
I will stop asking.
I would hate to be annoying.
Then
let me ask you something.
What?
What is it
that you wear inside your clothes?
This...
See?
You are not honest with me either.
So why push me so hard?
Fine.
I will tell you.
Go on.
Five years ago,
on my master's orders,
I was hunting
the Iron-Blooded Three Eagles,
ranked No. 21 on the Bounty List.
It was my first mission.
To complete it well,
I chased the Iron-Blooded
Three Eagles nonstop
for three days and nights.
At last, those three outlaws
were forced into a corner.
(Take her down!)
Their poisoned darts were not deadly,
but they left the victim weak
and paralyzed,
unable to fight.
I had lost all hope.
Then someone suddenly appeared.
With one move,
they killed all three men
and saved me.
They carried me into a hollow tree.
I was burning with fever,
and they cared for me all night.
They saved me.
But I was poisoned and unconscious,
so I never saw their face.
(A Humble Gift)
(May I know which master saved me?)
(May we meet?)
(I wish to thank you in person.)
That is how I got this amulet.
That story
is rather touching.
What was that laugh?
Do you think I am lying?
No.
I just think the story
is a little dramatic.
What makes you say that?
Think about it.
This master must have been a god.
One strike, three men down.
Bang, bang.
Besides,
all great masters these days
help people without asking for thanks.
They come and go as they please.
So very dashing.
Didn't you say
you don't like men?
Was your savior a man or a woman?
How would I know?
I was too grateful to think about that.
I never wondered if it was a man
or a woman.
And,
my savior
was probably about my father's age.
When they cared for me,
it felt like when I was sick as a child,
and my father looked after me.
I'm seriously starting to doubt
whether this story is true at all.
Maybe the poison took effect,
and you hallucinated.
Then who killed the Three Eagles?
How would I know?
Even if this master really existed,
they
may not be a good person.
Do not speak that way of my savior.
I told you my secret.
Now you must tell me one of yours.
Fine.
I will tell you.
My secret is...
I am allergic to pineapple.
Chang Beiming!
You are awful.
It is a secret.
I never promised
to tell you who I really am.
Men really are all liars.
I will never believe you again.
Bingfan.
Don't bring me pineapple next time.
(Now that I know the truth,)
(why do I still feel uneasy?)
Go, go.
Bingfan.
Constable Guan is here.
Guan Yunfeng, Eighth-Rank Head Constable
of the Enforcement Division,
at your service.
Constable Guan, please sit.
Why is the Jinyiwei here?
Miss, may I
ask your name?
Constable Guan,
do you have news of Diaotu?
Constable Guan?
Since that day,
he has not appeared again.
Did your men search
near Marquis Taiping's manor?
My men searched every street
near Marquis Taiping's manor.
There was no sign of him.
That predator
seems to have vanished into thin air.
The deadline to catch him
is almost up.
How will we answer our superiors?
Bingfan,
why don't we discuss this with Hua?
Excuse me.
Miss.
What is it?
I still don't know your name.
Shen Bingfan, Squad Leader
of the Jinyiwei Northern Bureau.
Shen Bingfan.
What a lovely name.
(Northern Bureau)
My lord.
Today is the last day
of the ten-day deadline.
If you must explain this to the Cabinet,
please take us with you.
For what?
So we can all get scolded together?
Enough.
I will handle this matter.
You trusted us,
but we failed at the start.
How is that a failure?
At least you scared that scum enough
to keep him from showing himself.
That still counts as
protecting security around the capital.
Doesn't it?
All right.
Don't feel pressured.
Don't carry this burden.
I will bear it alone.
My lord.
Diaotu is very likely hiding
in the Marquis's manor.
With your permission,
I will investigate again.
No, no. Don't go.
I value caution above all.
The case is still unsolved.
Do not cause an even bigger mess.
My lord, Young Master Chang said
that because of us,
you were reprimanded by the Cabinet
and mocked by Mr. Duan
of the Southern Bureau.
It is nothing.
I'm old and thick-skinned.
So they chewed me out a little.
No big deal.
I don't care.
My lord.
I don't recall
having much connection with you.
Why do you protect me like this?
You are the daughter of my old friend.
Of course I would protect you.
You know who I am?
Your father was Jinyiwei
Qianhu Shen Lian, wasn't he?
The first time you came here,
I already knew who you were.
Get up.
How did you get so bold?
How dare you sneak into my Bureau
as a female Jinyiwei?
Such obsession.
So deep.
You came for revenge, didn't you?
Commander, please help me
uncover the truth
and clear my father's name.
If I knew the truth,
I would have cleared your father's name
long ago.
You wouldn't have had
to come here yourself.
You don't know the truth either?
I only know part of what happened.
Please tell me, my lord.
I know
that the men sent to receive your father
were Lu Guokai, then a Jinyiwei Qianhu,
and Wang Yan, then Commissioner
of the Southern Bureau, now Commander
of the Five Armies Command.
Wang Yan
is also a direct subordinate
of the current Southern Bureau
Commander.
Lu Guokai?
Lu Guokai was sent to receive my father?
According to Lu Guokai's report,
when he and Wang Yan arrived,
the witness and your father
had already been killed.
Prince Luo's case
involved too many people.
The court didn't want
a greater scandal exposed,
so it handled the case quietly.
That means
it was Lu Guokai or Wang Yan
who framed my father.
Bingfan!
Remember this.
Without solid proof,
never suspect your colleagues.
Yes, my lord.
Lu Guokai is greedy and self-serving,
but he doesn't have the nerve.
Wang Yan is reckless and bold,
but he is nothing more than a brute
with courage but no brains.
He
doesn't have the mind for it.
My lord,
please help me uncover the truth
of what happened.
This case
has been buried for too long.
I can't help you rashly.
However,
if it is about investigating Leng Xin,
I can offer you a few leads.
If we can capture Leng Xin,
the truth will naturally come to light.
Please tell me, my lord.
Bingfan,
let me tell you a secret.
Since Leng Xin first appeared,
he has had no equal
in the martial world.
The only one
he truly fears is the phantom thief
Feng Fuliu.
If you can find Feng Fuliu,
you will find a way to counter Leng Xin.
What is it?
(On the night of the full moon.)
(To the venerable Duke Wei.)
(I shall take the imperial-bestowed
Azure Dragon Jade.)
(Feng Fuliu.)
Bad news!
The phantom thief Feng Fuliu
has sent a calling card.
Hua. Miss Shen. Miss Cheng.
I heard that last night,
the phantom thief Feng Fuliu
appeared in the capital.
They say he sent a challenge letter
to Duke Wei's manor.
He said that on the night
of the full moon,
he will steal Duke Wei's
imperial-bestowed Azure Dragon Jade.
Today,
Duke Wei reported it to the court.
Now the Three Judicial Offices,
the Southern and Northern Bureaus,
and the Five Armies Command
are all in an uproar.
Feng Fuliu has appeared.
The imperial-bestowed
Azure Dragon Jade...
It must be worth a fortune.
The Commander
has been summoned
to the Cabinet to discuss it.
It seems Feng Fuliu
is really going to throw the capital
into chaos.
Good chance.
What did you say?
Say that again?
I request permission
to arrest Feng Fuliu.
Shen Bingfan.
Who do you think you are?
I...
Even if we send Jinyiwei officers,
it won't be you female Jinyiwei.
You failed to capture Diaotu last time.
Do you know how much shame
that brought on the Jinyiwei?
Go, go.
Out.
Get out.
We failed to catch Diaotu last time.
That was embarrassing.
But if we catch Feng Fuliu this time,
wouldn't that be worth
far more than catching Diaotu?
By then,
we female Jinyiwei will win back
all our dignity.
Hua is right.
But the Cabinet has assigned
Feng Fuliu's case
to the Ministry of Justice.
The Commander and Commissioner Lu
both warned us repeatedly
not to act rashly.
Are you silly?
If we go as private citizens
and manage to catch Feng Fuliu,
the credit will naturally go
to the Northern Bureau.
And if we do not catch him,
we can say we were just passing by.
They cannot really blame us for that.
Bingfan.
You two are both trying
to convince me today.
That is strange.
To be honest,
we are very curious about Feng Fuliu.
Aren't you curious?
Of course I want to catch him too.
Then it is settled.
Then we
will lie in wait outside
Duke Wei's manor
on the night of the full moon.
If we can catch Feng Fuliu,
let us see who still dares to say
female Jinyiwei are useless.
Fine.
(Treasure Pavilion)
Anything unusual?
No.
(Treasure Pavilion)
Watch out!
Much obliged, Constable Guan.
This Azure Dragon Jade
shall be mine to admire for a few days.
Ladies, enjoying the evening?
Feng Fuliu.
Ladies,
until we meet again.
You are not getting away!
You used the Three Wildcat Leaps.
Who are you?
Your figure is familiar too.
The spring wind dares
to brush the willows.
The night rain comes unseen
to nourish the flowers.
Hua.
Duoyu.
My eyes hurt so much.
Hua.
Let me check your injury.
No need.
Hua.
How are you? Are you all right?
I'm sorry. Feng Fuliu got away.
Did you see his face clearly?
I...
I don't think I saw it clearly.
But his silhouette
felt like someone we all know very well.
Chang Beiming.
♪Because you once entered my dreams♪
♪Truth and illusion blur in wine♪
♪My heart drifted lost♪
♪Yet found you in the crowd♪
♪My blood still burns
as the world surges♪
♪The land is fair, and you are free♪
♪Sword drawn, lost in obsession♪
♪I've softly let it go♪
♪The vow you made was true♪
♪Yet like clouds, it stops for no one♪
♪Put away those dreamlike words♪
♪And forget at world's end♪
♪Embracing memory♪
♪Through blossoms and dreams♪
♪You hide in the crowd, silent♪
♪I wish to let it pass♪
♪And run toward this vast life♪