=Angels and Guards=
=Episode 1=
(Shen Bingfan, the greatest female
bounty hunter in the martial world)
(This is the legendary Northern Bureau.)
(Northern Bureau)
(My father's betrayer works there.)
(I will definitely join the Jinyiwei)
(and avenge my father.)
Is this where women sign up?
(Xu Duoyu, a servant at Northern Bureau)
Are you here to apply?
The Sixi Troupe's leading star is here!
Where?
The top star performer!
She's stunning!
Like a goddess!
(Hua Mange,
leading star of the Sixi Opera Troupe)
Impressive!
Hey there.
(Female Jinyiwei Recruitment)
Do I sign up here?
Are you here for recruitment too?
Anyone else too?
(Zhang Weimin,
Commander of Northern Bureau)
Good. Good.
My lords.
I am Hua Mange,
former leading star of the Sixi Troupe.
A few days ago,
a new girl joined our troupe
(Lu Guokai, Commissioner)
and took my top spot.
I had nowhere left to go...
Poor girl...
My lord.
Your manners, please.
And you?
I am Shen Bingfan.
I've practiced martial arts since I was young
and want to serve the court
as a Jinyiwei.
I heard
you're recruiting women.
So I came.
My lord,
she's actually decent.
Shen Bingfan?
Are you the female bounty hunter
feared across the martial world?
Hey, handsome.
What's your name?
I'm Xu Duoyu, a Northern Bureau servant.
So you're not a Jinyiwei?
I've been here for ages,
but never passed the physical test.
So I'm just a servant.
I'm grateful my lord took me in,
so I could stay here, even as a servant.
Xu Duoyu?
Then you'd better stay away from me.
Why?
Because...
My animal sign is "cat".
You look like a fish.
(Cat?)
Duoyu.
Where is this place?
Here?
This is the North Bureau's archive room.
It holds
(Archives)
the most complete criminal case files.
It's a top-class classified division.
(This is where I can dig into)
(my father's wrongful case.)
(Northern Bureau)
Commander has already
arranged your lodging and meals.
(Northern Bureau)
Please go across to Chong'er Pavilion.
Chong'er Pavilion?
It is
(Chong'er Pavilion)
among the capital's top establishments.
So what?
You'll see when you get there.
Remember to report for duty tomorrow.
I won't see you out.
(Chang Le, Chong'er Pavilion attendant)
Meal or lodging?
Sir.
We're from the North Bureau...
Help!
- Stop!
Get her!
Go away!
Don't come closer!
Come here!
Stop!
What are you all doing?
A group of men bullying a woman?
How did you get mixed up with them?
My name is Cheng Xintian.
(Cheng Xintian)
My mother died when I was little.
Then my father remarried.
My stepmother treated me like dirt.
She beat me all the time.
She said she'd marry me
into a rich family.
But then...
She meant their master,
an old eunuch.
Please.
I'm only seventeen.
I can't marry an old eunuch.
They...
They came to drag me back
for the wedding.
Is she telling the truth?
Her family took our master's money.
So she goes back and marries him.
Your master is a eunuch.
And he still wants a wife?
Half a man, twice the nerve.
How dare you!
She belongs to me.
I paid 500 taels for her.
You people
must have lost your minds.
(Mr. Lü, Eastern Depot Director's aide)
How dare you cross me?
Try saying that again.
Our young master is here.
(Chang Beiming,
owner of Chong'er Pavilion)
(Shizhen, son of the Minister of War)
(Feng Zhihe,
nephew of the Eastern Depot Director)
(Ye Ping, son of the Grand Secretary)
Didn't I make it clear?
No ugly faces in my Chong'er Pavilion.
What...
This is our business.
No need to drag you into it.
In Chong'er Pavilion,
you don't get to talk.
Someone's helping. Take the win.
Listen carefully.
She is my wife.
I bought her for 500 taels.
Take this to the Dali Temple for review
and the law is still on my side.
I'm not afraid of you.
What do we do?
He does have proof.
We don't have a case.
Then I'll buy her out.
Fine.
Principal and interest.
1,000 taels.
You only paid 500 for me.
Your food, your clothes,
everything came from me.
I...
1,000 it is.
Good. Pay up.
Could you
lend me one thousand taels?
I'll repay every coin.
You don't have the money?
Then why agree to pay?
When will you pay me back?
Within three days.
And if you can't?
I'll work off the debt.
Anything?
If it doesn't betray my conscience
and my honor.
I like that.
Chang Le.
Pay them off.
Here.
Let's go.
Go. Go.
Thank you, both of you.
Mr. Chang.
We were ordered to stay here.
That's right.
We're the new female Jinyiwei.
The Jinyiwei has women now?
(Zhang Weimin)
Zhang Weiming.
Chang Le.
Yes, sir.
Get these ladies settled.
Check them in.
Thank you.
Chang.
Quite a scene today.
Shall we settle the bill?
(Leisurely and Free)
Here at Chong'er Pavilion,
every single piece
is either an antique
or imperial kilnware.
You know exactly
how much you broke.
And for Miss... what was it?
Miss Cheng.
Buying her freedom cost me...
1,000 taels.
Yes, 1,000 taels.
All together,
that comes to...
Let's call it 3,000 taels.
3,000 taels?
(Cheng Xintian)
(Hua Mange)
(Shen Bingfan)
All settled. Everyone out.
Miss.
You know, you look nice when you smile.
You can talk all you want,
but I'm not letting you three stay here.
Seriously,
why did you have to hit him?
He was harassing me.
How was that harassment?
He... he got so close to me.
And he said things like that.
I just said you look nice smiling.
I don't like that.
Well, you never told me.
Miss Shen,
allow me to be fair here.
Beiming may have
overstepped with his words,
but you struck him.
Wasn't that a bit much?
Exactly.
Young Master Chang,
she's a girl.
She's naturally sensitive.
Teasing her the first time you meet
can easily come off as improper.
But still,
she was wrong to hit you.
How about this?
Both sides take a step back.
Shen,
apologize to Young Master Chang.
Sir, be the bigger man
and let this go.
Beiming cares about face the most.
No one has ever dared hit him.
Especially not in front of a crowd.
Today,
you really made history.
Guys.
He
really can defy the Northern Bureau?
Zhang Weimin can't afford to cross him.
Why not?
Northern Bureau's in debt to him.
Those people
come here all the time
and eat on credit.
It adds up to quite a debt in a year.
Just apologize.
Don't make this worse.
Or we'll have nowhere to sleep tonight.
If you're still angry,
you can hit me back.
You really are stubborn.
So tell me. What do you want?
You want to stay here
and keep working at Northern Bureau?
Then sell yourselves to me.
For six months,
you'll wait tables for free
and do whatever I say.
♪Because you once entered my dreams♪
♪Truth and illusion blur in wine♪
♪My heart drifted lost♪
♪Yet found you in the crowd♪
♪My blood still burns
as the world surges♪
♪The land is fair, and you are free♪
♪Sword drawn, lost in obsession♪
♪I've softly let it go♪
♪The vow you made was true♪
♪Yet like clouds, it stops for no one♪
♪Put away those dreamlike words♪
♪And forget at world's end♪
♪Embracing memory♪
♪Through blossoms and dreams♪
♪You hide in the crowd, silent♪
♪I wish to let it pass♪
♪And run toward this vast life♪