= Angels and Guards=
=Episode 2=
You really are stubborn.
So tell me. What do you want?
You want to stay here
and keep working at Northern Bureau?
Then sell yourselves to me.
For six months,
you'll wait tables for free
and do whatever I say.
Then I may consider
wiping out all your debts.
And I'll forget about
you blasting me into my signboard.
Fine.
Then it's settled.
But I now serve Northern Bureau,
so I'm only yours in my spare time.
Deal.
(Chong'er Pavilion)
All sliced.
Take them out.
Okay.
Set that here for now.
Hua has it easy.
She serves guests in private rooms,
with all the good food and wine.
And we're stuck doing grunt work.
But at least
we got into Chong'er Pavilion.
Chang Beiming is crazy.
We'd better watch our backs.
Really? I think he's quite handsome.
He made us sign our lives away,
and you're defending him?
Bingfan,
we're already here.
We might as well
look on the bright side.
Mr. Chang is handsome and rich.
I don't think working for him
is such a bad deal.
What do you mean by handsome?
Handsome means...
He's good-looking.
His features are all in the right place.
And every time I see him,
I feel a little
shy.
I don't think he's handsome at all.
Whenever I see him,
my chest gets tight,
and I want to hit someone.
Bingfan,
you're actually pretty handsome too.
Even more than him.
Miss Shen.
(Chang Huan, attendant)
Mr. Chang wants you to clean his study.
What?
(Guide to Joining the Jinyiwei)
This is the Northern Bureau
onboarding guide.
You can't buy this anywhere.
Then how do you have it?
Because I took
the Northern Bureau exam too.
Why?
Because...
Jinyiwei's Robe and Blade
look amazing.
Did you pass?
No.
I ranked first in the written exam
but failed the physical test.
A grown man,
and you couldn't pass the physical?
And you admit that out loud?
What gets you by these days?
Brains.
Come on.
Start cleaning.
From now on,
we're landlord and tenant.
We should look out for each other.
Now, clean.
Bingfan,
Hua told me everything.
You're the famous
female bounty hunter.
I've always been a huge fan.
You're my biggest hero.
Well, and one other person.
The phantom thief, Feng Fuliu.
Feng Fuliu ranks second
on the bounty list,
a Class-A fugitive.
You can't idolize a wanted criminal.
But he's so handsome.
Let me do it, Xintian.
Take a break.
You shouldn't do this.
Sit down.
Sit.
I brought these oranges from home.
Try one.
The oranges back home
are really sweet.
Thank you.
Bingfan.
I've always wanted to thank you.
From now on, I'll do all the hard work.
You don't have to worry about it.
I can handle it all.
I've always felt useless.
My parents disliked me
since I was little.
They thought I was stupid.
So I always thought
I shouldn't have been born.
But you're different.
You mean something to me.
When I first met you,
we didn't even know each other.
But for my sake,
you stood up to those men.
Because of you,
I get to live in a place this nice.
Otherwise,
I'd have to marry that old eunuch.
If I hadn't met you,
I honestly don't know
how I would have gone on.
So,
Bingfan,
let me follow you
for the rest of my life
and be your little fangirl, okay?
Okay.
Then I'll take you as my little sister.
Join me to register
at the Bureau tomorrow.
You mean, the Northern Bureau?
Bingfan.
I get to work for the court with you?
Thank you so much, Bingfan.
Northern Bureau,
here I come.
(Northern Bureau)
It's beautiful.
The real test
will be set by the Commander himself.
For young women like you,
to have such loyal hearts,
devoted to the throne and the realm,
I am deeply pleased.
Deeply pleased indeed.
Therefore,
I have decided
to waive the written exam.
Go straight to the combat test.
My lord!
My mind is made up.
No written exam?
Unbelievable.
Hua Mange will go first.
Begin.
Time's up.
How did the incense burn so fast?
We barely started.
Right. How did it burn that quickly?
It's already over?
I can't do this. Maybe...
Maybe I should just go home.
I'm leaving.
How about this?
When it's your turn,
you...
Next.
You. Xintian. Step forward.
Wait.
Sir, I'm just a weak young woman.
I really can't beat you.
Can we keep this friendly?
Very well. I'll allow you three strikes.
Sorry about this, sir.
Time's up.
What?
She won!
Bingfan. Mange.
My lord.
This...
This is cheating.
My lord.
Cheng Xintian
stalled him on purpose.
Then had someone land a cheap shot.
Am I wrong?
My lord,
that is against the rules.
Guokai,
rules are made by people.
No need to be so rigid.
You said it, my lord.
Cool.
What do you mean?
You.
Last one.
Shen Bingfan, step forward.
Zuo Da. Jiang Biao.
(Zuo Da, Qianhu,
Northern Bureau's Captain)
Yes.
(Jiang Biao, Qianhu)
Two men?
Us?
That's right.
Two?.
Against one woman,
do you really need two of your best men?
This lady warrior is known as
the realm's greatest bounty hunter.
I had to find two top Jinyiwei men
to test her properly.
Move.
Begin.
Come on!
Fight!
Get up!
Up! Get up!
Stop!
You two useless fools.
Stand down!
Come back.
Bingfan, you're amazing!
Useless.
Duoyu,
where are you taking us?
The Records Office.
You need an identity check,
and then you'll be entered in the registry.
Didn't we register yesterday?
That was different.
That was just the application.
There's still the background check.
Only after you pass
can you become official Jinyiwei.
May I ask
which officer handles the check?
Name.
Hua Mange.
(Hua Mange)
Age.
Seventeen.
Where are you from?
Huguang.
That's it?
Yes.
What?
Then,
what are your parents' names?
Who trained you?
I cannot reveal my parents' names.
And my school
must remain secret.
What?
My lord.
What shall we do with the three women?
What do you think?
Hua Mange's origins are suspicious,
but she can be admitted.
Hua Mange.
Background check passed.
Enter her name.
Cheng Xintian
has a clean background.
She can be admitted.
Cheng Xintian.
Background check passed. Enter her name.
Only
Shen Bingfan
refuses to name her parents or school.
This is really suspicious.
Indeed.
It is suspicious.
Shen Bingfan's origins are unclear.
She is rejected.
Commissioner!
Why the panic?
Young Master Chang
of Chong'er Pavilion is here.
Are you accepting me or not?
Shen Bingfan's origins are unclear.
She is rejected.
Accepted. Accepted!
Shen Bingfan. Background check passed.
Enter her name.
My lord.
Shut up!
Enter her name. Now.
Yes, my lord.
♪Because you once entered my dreams♪
♪Truth and illusion blur in wine♪
♪My heart drifted lost♪
♪Yet found you in the crowd♪
♪My blood still burns
as the world surges♪
♪The land is fair, and you are free♪
♪Sword drawn, lost in obsession♪
♪I've softly let it go♪
♪The vow you made was true♪
♪Yet like clouds, it stops for no one♪
♪Put away those dreamlike words♪
♪And forget at world's end♪
♪Embracing memory♪
♪Through blossoms and dreams♪
♪You hide in the crowd, silent♪
♪I wish to let it pass♪
♪And run toward this vast life♪