=Angels and Guards=
=Episode 8=
Since the Commander has spoken,
I won't lower myself
to argue with a nobody.
But she trespassed into my manor
and disturbed a noble house.
If I let her go just like that,
word will spread,
and people will think
I'm easy to push around.
Am I wrong?
What do you want, then?
What should I do?
Buddy,
help me out.
What should I do?
I've got it.
Hey.
Bring that dog food here.
You tried to use the Jinyiwei
to intimidate me.
But no matter how powerful
the Jinyiwei are,
they're still the Emperor's dogs.
Dogs.
Finish this bowl of dog food,
and I'll spare you
the charge of treason.
You've gone too far.
Yin Xian!
You show no respect
for the Northern Bureau.
Your Northern Bureau
barged into my manor.
Did you show any respect for me?
Zhang Weimin,
if I report what happened today
to His Majesty,
you won't just lose your post.
Your new female Jinyiwei
will be disbanded.
And
this insolent Shen Bingfan
could be beheaded as a warning.
Marquis Taiping,
I alone will answer for what I did.
This has nothing to do
with the Commander or the Bureau.
But if you think you can humiliate me,
dream on.
What are you doing?
I would rather die than yield.
Don't!
I can't drag you all down.
Go ahead and kill yourself,
and I may spare the Northern Bureau.
Don't you dare touch her!
- Young Master Chang!
- Bingfan!
Are you all right?
Young Master Chang,
what brings you here?
Who do you think you're bullying?
I...
Who were you trying to feed dog food?
No, it was her problem.
She trespassed into my manor.
I was disciplining her
for the Commander.
What gives you the right?
A useless man who owes his title
to connections
has no right to discipline
a Jinyiwei of the Northern Bureau.
For a man with nothing
but borrowed status,
you sure have a lot of nerve.
Young Master Chang.
It's not like that.
She really did barge in first.
She barged in?
That's because a criminal
entered your manor at night.
She came to investigate for your safety.
How is that barging in?
She hadn't even reached
the front courtyard
before you stopped her.
You've had your fun
throwing your weight around.
Why push it further?
You want to report this to His Majesty?
Fine. I'll tell your cousin's husband
and His Majesty what you've been up to.
Let them see it for themselves.
No, no.
Look, Young Master Chang,
I didn't know
what your relationship
with Officer Shen was.
But
now I understand.
This was all a misunderstanding.
A misunderstanding.
Really.
Can I take her with me, then?
Of course.
Young Master Chang,
please do as you wish.
Take care.
♪The past, like a song,
still echoes in my ears♪
♪A scene of birds and dusk♪
Why did you bring me here?
Do you understand
that the Jinyiwei
is a tightly run court agency?
That Flying Fish Robe
and Embroidered Spring Blade
were not given lightly.
Once you wear them,
you no longer act for yourself.
You represent the Northern Bureau.
Before you act,
can you think of the bigger picture?
I'm used to working alone.
Then turn in your badge
and go back to the martial world.
You have no sense of teamwork,
and you're arrogant.
You're not fit to serve
in the Northern Bureau.
But I suspected Marquis Taiping's manor
was hiding a fugitive.
Was it wrong to investigate?
Do you think everything in this world
can be done your way?
Even His Majesty
has things he cannot do,
no matter how much he wishes to.
The court
has its rules.
If you want to keep serving
in the Northern Bureau,
learn how it works.
If you want to stay a wandering hero,
fine. Do whatever you want.
But resign from the Northern Bureau.
Does entering official service
really mean losing all freedom?
Yes.
The martial world has its rules.
You settle debts and grudges freely,
without restraint.
That is why I opened Chong'er Pavilion.
To live freely.
But once you serve the court,
you must know where you stand.
Your every word
and every action
are no longer yours alone.
You are a Jinyiwei.
If you keep acting on your own,
how many people will you drag down?
If Marquis Taiping
had pressed the matter,
the female Jinyiwei
could have been disbanded.
What would happen to Hua Mange?
What would happen to Cheng Xintian?
Did you ever think of that?
(Northern Bureau)
I overstepped.
I acted rashly as the Jinyiwei
and forced my way
into Marquis Taiping's manor.
I put the Northern Bureau at risk.
I deserve punishment.
Please punish me, my lord.
Shen Bingfan,
that was reckless.
You dared provoke Marquis Taiping,
Yin Xian.
Do you know
what a dangerous schemer he is?
I only wanted to catch the criminal.
I forgot who I was dealing with.
Naive!
Extremely naive!
Even if you saw
Diaotu
enter Marquis Taiping's manor,
even if you found out
that Yin Xian was sheltering him,
what could you do to him?
Without solid proof,
you can't touch him.
To bring down
a first-rank marquis
appointed by the court
is no simple matter.
I understand my mistake.
Enough.
Since you know you were wrong,
I won't punish you.
Remember.
Do not let it happen again.
Thank you, my lord.
But Diaotu has disappeared.
What do we do now?
Since we've already spooked him,
for now,
we do nothing.
But
if the ten-day deadline comes,
how do we answer the court?
That is my problem.
I've caused you trouble.
Since we've alarmed Diaotu,
he likely won't strike again
anytime soon.
But you female Jinyiwei
must remember this.
Do everything you can
to capture Diaotu,
the Flower-Picking Bee.
Only then will your place
as female Jinyiwei be secure.
And I may save some face.
If I fail to bring Diaotu in,
I will leave the Jinyiwei.
You caused quite a mess this time.
I was too reckless this time.
It won't happen again.
Good.
From now on,
discuss things with us first.
More heads mean more ideas.
But
this does make me wonder.
About what?
Who exactly is Chang Beiming?
Why did someone as arrogant
as Marquis Taiping
turn frightened before him?
You have a point.
But
I have a question too.
That day, when you used your footwork,
why did I hear a cat meow in midair?
(I'll go after him.)
(Are you all right?)
(I'm fine.)
(Hua, be careful!)
What? I don't think so.
Funny.
You must have heard wrong.
Maybe I'm overthinking it.
Bingfan,
I think
our top priority now
is catching Diaotu.
You're right.
Yeah.
Wait.
If I lose this round,
your monthly pay is gone.
Squad Leader Shen.
Why is Marquis Taiping afraid of you?
Have you forgotten yesterday?
I haven't forgiven you yet.
And now you're interrogating me?
Yin Xian isn't even
afraid of the Commander.
Why would he fear you?
That
is a good question.
As they say, evil never beats good,
and right is on my side.
I want the truth.
The truth
is...
Guess.
Does he owe you money too?
As if he's worthy.
What?
I mean,
yes, exactly.
Smart girl.
If you won't tell me, fine.
I'll find out myself.
(I only meant to sneak into the Bureau,
destroy the records, and leave.)
(Why have I started enjoying this life?)
(Could it be)
(that those two girls
have gotten to me?)
The Northern Bureau
abused its power
and insulted imperial kin.
(Submitted by Yin Xian, Marquis Taiping)
Without an edict or gold token,
(Northern Bureau)
they forced their way into my manor
and accused me of harboring a fugitive.
I beg Your Majesty for justice.
An imperial edict arrives.
By the Mandate of Heaven,
the Emperor decrees:
Marquis Taiping, Yin Xian,
has accused the Northern Bureau
of overstepping its rank
and insulting imperial kin,
gravely damaging imperial authority
and the court's dignity.
They violated the law,
abused their power, and disrupted order.
Upon receipt of this edict,
Jinyiwei Commander Zhang Weimin
shall enter court at once
and explain the matter to the Cabinet.
By imperial order.
Absurd. Absolutely absurd.
I deserve death for my mistake.
Your usual arrogance
and disrespect for your peers
is one thing.
But this time,
you provoked the wrong man.
If the court blames us,
I will bear it alone.
Zuo Da. Jiang Biao.
Yes.
Take Shen Bingfan's saber and badge.
When the Commander returns,
we will decide her punishment.
Everyone's here!
The Northern Bureau
has caused quite a stir
and disgraced the Jinyiwei.
Mr. Duan,
you came to laugh at the Bureau,
didn't you?
Zhang Weimin,
Marquis Taiping has accused you
of indulging your subordinates,
disturbing his manor,
and insulting imperial kin.
My lord,
that is an exaggeration.
Then give me the modest version.
Isn't this your fault?
What?
Now you're twisting the facts?
You were the ones
who forced me into this.
You gave me ten days
to catch that predator Diaotu.
After Diaotu slipped
into Marquis Taiping's manor,
whether Yin Xian knew it or not,
I had to send someone to check.
For his safety, of course.
Who knew Marquis Taiping
would reject my goodwill,
then go to His Majesty
and the Cabinet to file a complaint
against me?
What do we call that?
That is...
That is biting the hand that helps you!
Am I wrong?
From what I heard,
that is not how it happened.
It was Shen Bingfan,
your newly recruited female Jinyiwei.
She stormed into the Marquis's manor
and demanded to search it by force.
Let me tell you.
That is only one side of the story.
Grand Secretary, please have some tea.
What happened was
a few careless words.
She only talked back
to Marquis Taiping a little.
That's all.
A man of Marquis Taiping's status
should be magnanimous.
Surely he would not stoop to arguing
with a young woman.
If he really did,
it would hardly befit a first-rank lord.
Am I right, Grand Secretary?
I have heard
the Commander of the Northern Bureau
always protects his own people.
Now I see the rumors were true.
My lord,
even if this was a misunderstanding,
it remains true
that Shen Bingfan disturbed
the marquis's manor.
Marquis Taiping has complained
to His Majesty.
His Majesty has asked about it.
The Cabinet is in a difficult position.
How about this?
Go back and punish Shen Bingfan.
Give Marquis Taiping an answer.
Then
I
will mediate
and smooth this over.
How does that sound?
My lord,
please
have some water.
But do not cover for your own people.
Rest assured.
I will punish her severely.
She won't... There will be no next time.
That's more like it.
Bring in Shen Bingfan,
the offending officer.
(Northern Bureau)
Greetings, Commander.
Shen Bingfan, you overstepped your rank
and disturbed a marquis's manor.
I
must punish you severely.
Do you accept this?
I know my fault.
I accept any punishment.
Good. In that case,
I will punish you
by docking three months' pay.
Let this be a warning.
My lord, only three months' pay?
That's too light.
What do you mean?
Try losing three months' pay yourself.
I did nothing wrong. Why punish me?
My lord, if you keep
favoring them like this,
if the Cabinet
or the Southern Bureau finds out...
What scumbag would dare
gossip about this?
I'm punishing her according to the law.
Guokai,
you must open your mind. Open it.
Open it!
If you show no care
for your subordinates,
who will risk their lives for you later?
Thank you for your mercy, Commander.
My lord.
Bingfan, what brings you here?
I came to thank you again
for protecting me.
You shouldn't thank me.
It was
Chang Beiming who spoke up for you.
Otherwise,
I would have punished you harshly.
Who exactly is Chang Beiming?
Why would even the Grand Secretary
show him respect?
You two live right next door.
You should ask him.
(Went home?)
(Isn't this his home?)
(Of course not.)
(This is the young master's business.)
(He has another residence.)
(My young master is mainly worried
about you, Miss Shen.)
(He went home to settle this for you.)
♪Because you once entered my dreams♪
♪Truth and illusion blur in wine♪
♪My heart drifted lost♪
♪Yet found you in the crowd♪
♪My blood still burns
as the world surges♪
♪The land is fair, and you are free♪
♪Sword drawn, lost in obsession♪
♪I've softly let it go♪
♪The vow you made was true♪
♪Yet like clouds, it stops for no one♪
♪Put away those dreamlike words♪
♪And forget at world's end♪
♪Embracing memory♪
♪Through blossoms and dreams♪
♪You hide in the crowd, silent♪
♪I wish to let it pass♪
♪And run toward this vast life♪