=Angels and Guards=
=Episode 30=
A prince of the blood,
scrambling for profit with commoners.
How impressive.
Your Majesty, the Crown Prince
has just been named.
The realm has only just settled.
I fear someone may use this
to stir up trouble
and force our son to leave for his fief.
Shouldn't he go?
Your Majesty, if someone at court
uses this to cause more unrest
and attack our son,
what are we to do?
Yes. Father.
Son.
Tell me the truth.
Behind my back,
have you been building factions
and reaching for court power?
I would never dare.
Not even if my life depended on it.
If you haven't,
there is nothing to fear.
Go to the Cabinet.
When you see the Grand Secretary,
deliver my order.
The Meizhen House case
must be handled with care.
No one is to use it as a pretext
to implicate half the court.
Grand Secretary.
What is that supposed to mean?
We only charge Gao Tianxi
with detaining a female Jinyiwei
and drop everything else?
More than half the court
is standing behind Meizhen House.
We have witnesses and evidence.
Your evidence is just
a few account books.
Besides the two female Jinyiwei
under you,
do you have any other witnesses?
(Hua.)
(There is blood here.)
(Follow the trail.)
(Empty.)
(Hua. Hua.)
(Hua.)
(I already told the Commander.)
(You have left the past behind.)
(You are a true Jinyiwei now.)
The medicine is here.
Here.
How is Hua?
You all can leave.
I will stay with her
and make sure nothing happens to her.
Open the door.
Gao Tianxi.
I will kill you!
What are you doing?
Stop!
Put the blade down.
Shen Bingfan.
You think you can kill me?
What a joke!
Shen Bingfan.
I knew you would do this.
If you kill him,
you become no better than him.
Give it to me.
Bingfan, listen to Mr. Lu for now.
Bingfan.
Leave this to me.
Come on, Bingfan.
They are gone.
Now get out.
Get out!
Gao Tianxi.
What is this?
You deserve to die.
What?
What is this thing?
You deserve to die!
What is this?
Why does it taste sweet?
Rats!
Help!
We searched all of Meizhen House,
every last inch,
but found no trace of Leng Xin.
Tell me.
Could Gao Tianxi
be Leng Xin himself?
We have all fought Leng Xin before.
He is short,
thin,
and Gao Tianxi is big and tall.
It's not him.
Gao Tianxi is skilled,
but he is no match
for Young Master Chang.
Leng Xin's skill
is beyond all of us.
Could it be
that before we sealed off Meizhen House,
Leng Xin had already slipped away?
It seems
we must uncover every secret
in Meizhen House
before we can find Leng Xin.
Hua, you are awake.
You...
How do you feel?
Any discomfort?
I'm fine.
I will live.
I have nine lives, remember?
Then...
Are you
thirsty?
Hungry? Or...
Do you want anything?
Waking up
and seeing you beside me
is enough.
This is my fault.
I failed to protect you.
You fool.
When it really matters,
you are quite useful.
I swear,
from now on,
I will never let you get hurt again.
I went through the account books.
There is nothing concrete.
The court officials listed inside
all used false names.
They will never admit to it.
If physical evidence is not enough,
we still have witnesses.
You mean
the girls they kidnapped here?
Yes.
Young Master Chang, do you want
some of them to testify as witnesses?
That is our only way
to break through Meizhen House.
Baihu Shen.
I would like to speak with the girls.
Don't be afraid.
You are safe here.
Yes.
Tell us whatever you need.
We want to go home.
Don't worry.
When the case is over,
we will send you home.
But the case is not over yet.
Is any one of you
willing to testify against Meizhen House?
Don't worry.
Whoever is willing to come forward,
I will keep her safe.
Taozi, you tell them.
I don't know anything.
I don't know anything either.
We know nothing.
Nothing.
It's all right.
Go back and think it over.
There is no rush.
Let's go.
Xintian.
We don't want to stay here.
Move the witnesses?
Yes.
The girls are terrified
at staying at the Northern Bureau.
I want to move them somewhere else
and have the female Jinyiwei
look after them.
It may help.
Once they feel safe, we can talk to them
and maybe get something out of them.
Do you have a safe place in mind?
Duke Zheng's household
has a secret estate
outside the capital.
Outside the capital?
Where exactly?
Just outside the capital.
Bingfan.
So now,
you don't even trust me?
For the witnesses' safety,
the fewer who know, the better.
You will stay here for now.
Chief Squad Leader Cheng
and I will protect you.
From now on,
Constable Guan will bring supplies
every day.
You don't need to go out.
If you need anything,
tell me or Chief Squad Leader Cheng.
That was amazing!
Xintian is amazing!
Xintian, you never miss.
I will teach you later.
Then no one will be able
to bully you again.
If I learn it,
can I join the Jinyiwei too?
The Jinyiwei?
You want to join the Jinyiwei?
Can girls join too?
If I join the Jinyiwei,
no one will dare hurt me again.
We want to join too.
I want to join.
So do we.
As long as you don't look down
on yourselves,
no one can break you so easily.
I know you have suffered.
But if you are willing to testify,
I swear
I will bring down every filthy official
who hurt you
and everyone behind them.
But...
Well...
Taozi, what do you think?
Your people went to Meizhen House
to investigate
and nearly got killed.
Gao Tianxi only got eight years.
He was not even an official,
and you still couldn't touch him.
What about those high officials
and nobles?
Exactly.
You couldn't even bring down
that beast, Gao Tianxi.
How can you fight those powerful men?
You can't beat them.
Please just let us go home.
Yes, let us go home.
Let us go home.
I want to go home.
Please let us go.
Let us leave.
I don't want to stay here anymore.
Let's go.
We should leave.
Let's not get into trouble.
Yes.
Being safe is enough.
We should protect ourselves.
Xintian.
I'm sorry
I couldn't help you.
It is all right, Taozi.
I don't blame you.
Don't worry. None of us will.
I don't want to keep swallowing this.
But I'm scared.
I'm scared that
if I tell the truth,
you still won't be able to beat them.
Taozi.
Trust me.
As long as you tell me the truth,
no matter how high his rank is
or how powerful he is,
we will bring him down.
Then, do you dare touch Marquis Taiping?
Mr. Zhang.
Why have you brought so many men
into my manor?
Marquis Taiping.
Do you know
this young lady?
No.
Don't be afraid, Taozi.
Today, we settle every debt
and every wrong.
Say it all.
It was him.
When I first came to Meizhen House,
they sent me to serve him.
He raped me.
You liar!
Insolent wretch!
Framing a marquis?
Do you know the crime?
Don't be afraid, Taozi.
Say what you need to say.
I have nothing left to lose.
It was him!
What proof do you have?
He...
He has a red birthmark
on his lower back.
Marquis Taiping.
Must I strip you in front of everyone
to verify her claim?
Commander Zhang.
As an imperial official,
you visited brothels
without the slightest shame.
Now you raped an innocent woman
and still dare deny it.
Guards.
Yes!
Take Marquis Taiping, Yin Xian,
to the Imperial Prison
to await judgment!
Who dares?
Get them! Get them!
Take him away.
Mercy! Have mercy!
Mercy!
Have mercy!
(Imperial Edict)
(Fanyang County Office)
Look at the mess you have made for me!
And you still dare complain
about hunger?
Answer me.
The day Meizhen House was sealed,
why did you bring out my golden token?
Were you afraid people wouldn't know
you were connected to me?
I only wanted to use
Your Highness's name
to scare Chang Beiming.
Do you know what has happened
now that everything is exposed?
Our people across the network
are being arrested.
The secret ledgers have all
been destroyed.
But you left witnesses alive.
Those trafficked girls
are coming forward to testify.
Chang Beiming and Zhang Weimin
took this straight to His Majesty.
He was furious.
Half the network
we spent years building collapsed
overnight.
How could this happen?
Those spineless cowards
will tear each other apart in prison
just to survive.
Our secrets won't stay buried
much longer.
Your Highness.
If we kill those witnesses,
the arrested officials can change
their stories together.
Then, Your Highness
can turn the chaos to your advantage.
At least you are not completely useless.
This address came from my spy
inside the Jinyiwei.
(Qingyin Villa, outside the capital)
Come. Sit.
Hard day?
I went through four or five offices
today,
arrested seven or eight officials
involved,
and nearly worked myself dizzy.
My mouth is dry too.
You look rather pleased.
Of course I am.
This time, we took down Meizhen House
in one move
and arrested so many parasites at court.
It felt great.
Then, right now,
you should be out catching criminals.
Why come to Chong'er Pavilion?
To see Hua, of course.
Only Hua?
And also,
to see what someone else is doing.
Who is this someone else?
You missed me, didn't you?
Who missed you?
I really came to see Hua.
Young Master! Young Master!
Do you have to
show up at the perfect time every time?
Young Master.
An invitation from Prince Fu's manor.
What?
(Invitation)
(To the Heir of Duke Zheng)
Prince Fu has invited me
to his place
for a banquet at noon tomorrow.
Don't go. This is a trap.
He is up to no good.
A trap?
Even as a prince,
he wouldn't dare openly murder
an imperial official.
This is my chance to meet the man
behind it all.
(Prince Fu's Manor)
Young Duke.
You are going to Prince Fu's banquet?
Yes.
After Meizhen House,
Prince Fu will not let this go.
And I owe those girls
an answer.
But on the way here,
I kept feeling uneasy.
Guan.
No one should know
where Qingyin Villa is, right?
Not many. I'm one of them.
Then, could you take some men
and check on the villa?
Bingfan said that too many people
would draw danger.
So watch from a distance.
If all is safe, leave quietly.
If there is danger,
notify me at once.
You think Bingfan and the others
may be in danger?
(Prince Fu's Manor)
Prince Fu invited me for no reason.
I fear he has a scheme.
Right now, it is safer
to overthink than overlook something.
♪Because you once entered my dreams♪
♪Truth and illusion blur in wine♪
♪My heart drifted lost♪
♪Yet found you in the crowd♪
♪My blood still burns
as the world surges♪
♪The land is fair, and you are free♪
♪Sword drawn, lost in obsession♪
♪I've softly let it go♪
♪The vow you made was true♪
♪Yet like clouds, it stops for no one♪
♪Put away those dreamlike words♪
♪And forget at world's end♪
♪Embracing memory♪
♪Through blossoms and dreams♪
♪You hide in the crowd, silent♪
♪I wish to let it pass♪
♪And run toward this vast life♪