=Angels and Guards=
=Episode 29=
What treasure is this?
Such a large chest.
Good eye.
Is it for us?
Don't ask.
Pour the wine.
You want the post
of Henan Provincial Commissioner?
Henan is Prince Fu's fief.
I wish to serve in Henan
and devote myself to His Highness.
This is all?
This is a gift for you, Mr. Gao.
As for Prince Fu, His Highness
names his own price.
Go prepare the money.
Wait for my word.
Hua, are you all right?
I'm fine, Xintian.
This place really is where power
and money trade hands.
Prince Fu is selling offices
and building his own faction here.
Hua, I found something too.
Most of the people here were trafficked.
They treat lives like dirt
and force women into prostitution.
Right, Xintian.
Did you find anything about Leng Xin?
Hua,
I asked many kitchen helpers,
but none of them knew him.
Ouch, it hurts!
Xintian. It's me.
Sorry, Taozi.
Xintian.
Didn't you tell me to eat drumsticks
tonight?
Right.
Come. Sit.
I will get one for you.
Okay.
Xintian, you know martial arts?
I...
No, I don't. Don't say that.
Don't worry.
You are the kindest person to me
in all of Meizhen House.
I will treat you like my real sister.
Then from now on,
you are my real little sister.
Ms. Jiang, spare me!
You think I can't handle you?
I will never do it again!
I will beat you to death. Believe me?
Do you know who Mr. Liu is?
Do you know what happens
when you offend him?
Do you?
Ms. Jiang.
These are fresh honey peaches
picked today.
I washed them with well water.
Have a taste.
You know how to please people.
You two should have one too.
Thanks.
Let's go.
Act up again,
and a beating will be the least of it.
Taozi.
Come here.
If you get hungry tonight,
sneak into the kitchen.
I will save you a drumstick.
Taozi,
how did you end up at Meizhen House?
I...
I was abducted by traffickers.
I missed home and tried to run,
but every man in Meizhen House
knows martial arts.
I couldn't escape.
Before,
one girl in my room ran away.
They caught her and brought her back.
After that, no one ever saw her again.
So I became even more afraid to run.
So that's what happened.
Beiming, look.
Such a luxurious carriage...
What is it doing in the middle
of nowhere?
Zheng Lun.
Who did this to you?
Gao Tianxi.
I served him for so many years,
yet he
killed my whole family.
Stop talking.
I will take you to a doctor.
No.
Meizhen House
is where Prince Fu plants his faction
and eliminates his enemies.
Prince Fu
uses money and women
to control court officials.
His goal is to bring down
the Crown Prince,
then
seize the throne.
There you are.
I have been looking everywhere.
Ms. Jiang.
Were you looking for me?
Good. You are both here.
Listen up.
There is a curfew tonight.
What is a curfew?
A curfew means exactly
what it sounds like.
No business tonight.
After dark,
everyone in this house,
no matter who they are,
stays in their room.
If anything happens,
don't say I didn't warn you.
Be careful.
Hua. Xintian.
Taozi.
Does this happen every time
an important guest comes?
Yes.
It happens once a month,
at the end of the month.
We are locked in our rooms
and forbidden to wander around.
Then, Manager Gao picks one of the girls
to serve the important guest.
And the girl he picks
is gone by the next morning.
No one ever sees her again.
(Account Book)
Master, the last month's account book.
How is the matter arranged?
For an assassination,
we need someone absolutely reliable.
Leng Xin must be handled in secret.
It's done.
Who's there?
Assassin!
Xintian, we are exposed. Run!
Stop!
Don't run!
Run!
Stop!
Who sent you?
Hua.
Xintian, go!
Darn it!
All right.
Tell me.
Who sent you here?
Jinyiwei
Northern Bureau.
Shut up!
Tell me the truth.
The Crown Prince sent you, didn't he?
What Crown Prince?
I told you.
Can't you understand my words?
Still refusing to talk?
Then let's make this hurt.
Chili oil.
Wake her with cold water.
Yes.
Gao Tianxi.
One day,
I will make sure you die screaming.
Then I will burn out your eyes first,
then ruin that face of yours.
Boss!
Boss, bad news!
A large force is outside.
They have surrounded Meizhen House.
Hide her!
Yes!
Chang Beiming.
What is the meaning of this?
Hand over Hua.
Gao Tianxi.
Hand over Hua Mange, Chief Squad Leader
of the Northern Bureau.
Or
I will level Meizhen House.
With just you?
Add the three of us.
Is that enough?
Do you think
this whole capital
belongs to the Chang family?
Don't forget,
even the Jinyiwei are split
between North and South.
Young masters,
you bring armed men here
without cause or warrant.
Don't you fear Prince Fu's wrath?
So, you are saying
the power behind Meizhen House
is Prince Fu himself?
If we find her here,
the law stands above all.
Prince Fu doesn't matter.
You can't search
just because you say so.
What do you take Meizhen House for?
Meizhen House is not
a government office.
If we want to search it, we search it.
Do we need Cabinet approval too?
Besides, the Eastern Depot
may act first and report later.
(Prince Fu)
Prince Fu's imperial gold token is here.
Who dares defy it?
Bring forth the Founding Emperor's
Iron Certificate!
We pay our respects
to the Founding Emperor.
Chang Beiming.
Since you have brought
the Iron Certificate,
I have nothing more to say.
If you find nothing,
you
will answer to Prince Fu.
What answer do you want?
You want an answer?
How about I give you one?
Gao Tianxi.
Have you grown that bold?
You dare lay hands
on my Northern Bureau officer?
Every Jinyiwei here
answers only to the Emperor.
Let's see who dares make a move.
Mr. Zhang.
I mean no disrespect.
But if they find nothing,
will she
dare answer to Prince Fu
with her life?
Bingfan.
Search this place!
Beiming and I will search below for Hua.
You search up here.
Xintian. Xintian.
Xintian.
Taozi.
Do you know where Hua is being held?
Anyone who breaks the rules here
is taken to the dungeon and tortured.
They locked me there once.
I can take you.
Hua! Hua!
Hua!
Please save us!
Please!
Hurry. Get them out!
Yes!
Who are these girls?
They were all abducted.
Thank you.
This could
go all the way to the throne.
Are you sure this will work?
Not at all.
But neither of us has a way out.
Bold.
This is the torture room.
They punish rule-breakers here.
Hua was tortured here?
Hua!
Bingfan, you found nothing?
Chang Beiming, where is the woman
you came for?
You can't find her, can you?
This is clearly a trumped-up charge.
Seize Shen Bingfan.
Guards!
Take her!
Yes!
Gao Tianxi, you scum!
Gao Tianxi, I will kill you!
Duoyu.
Xintian.
Find a doctor for Hua. Now!
Go!
You monster!
I will kill you!
Bingfan.
Calm down.
Take him alive!
Gao Tianxi deceived me.
I had no idea
he had taken someone
from the Northern Bureau.
A man should choose a side,
not bend with the wind.
You saw what happened to him.
All Jinyiwei, hear my order!
Yes!
Seal off Meizhen House.
Baihu Shen, all the enforcers
have been captured.
Yes.
Go!
Bingfan, this is Taozi.
Without her, we couldn't
have saved Hua today.
Thank you.
It's nothing.
Don't be afraid, Taozi.
Bingfan is like a sister to me.
She is very kind.
Bingfan.
Xintian.
Settle these girls
at the Northern Bureau for now.
We may need their testimony later.
Baihu Shen.
(Account Book)
Baihu Shen, we found many account books.
These are key pieces of evidence.
Seal and store them.
Yes.
(Prince Fu)
You have made quite a mess, huh?
(Noble Consort Zheng)
Your Majesty, our son is young.
He was misled by outsiders.
He knew nothing about this.
He was completely deceived.
Please see the truth, Your Majesty.
Yes. Father.
A prince of the blood,
scrambling for profit with commoners.
How impressive.
♪Because you once entered my dreams♪
♪Truth and illusion blur in wine♪
♪My heart drifted lost♪
♪Yet found you in the crowd♪
♪My blood still burns
as the world surges♪
♪The land is fair, and you are free♪
♪Sword drawn, lost in obsession♪
♪I've softly let it go♪
♪The vow you made was true♪
♪Yet like clouds, it stops for no one♪
♪Put away those dreamlike words♪
♪And forget at world's end♪
♪Embracing memory♪
♪Through blossoms and dreams♪
♪You hide in the crowd, silent♪
♪I wish to let it pass♪
♪And run toward this vast life♪