=Angels and Guards=
=Episode 10=
Come on. Are you taking it or not?
Hurry up.
Are you playing or not?
Wait. Bomb.
What...
What luck.
Double it.
Why are you here?
You never left Chong'er Pavilion
all night?
Does a bathroom break count?
Miss Shen.
What happened?
We can testify.
That's right.
Chang was playing cards
with us all night.
I even won a thousand taels.
(Great Ming Treasure Note)
Nothing.
Carry on.
Miss Shen.
Go on. Come on.
Pay up first.
It doubled.
(Maybe I'm overthinking it.)
(Chang Beiming is not short on money.)
(Why would he risk becoming a thief?)
(But)
(I still feel he and Feng Fuliu)
(have something in common.)
(And)
(Mr. Lu)
(and Marquis Taiping.)
(Why do they both fear him?)
(Northern Bureau)
How many times have I told you?
Don't act rashly.
Are you ignoring your superiors?
No respect for authority.
What punishment do you deserve?
We...
Mr. Lu,
the three of us went shopping last night
and ran into the chivalrous thief
Feng Fuliu.
What?
Phan...
Phantom thief Feng Fuliu.
How could we ignore a thief
right in front of us?
Shopping and passing by?
Are you
treating Mr. Zhang
like a three-year-old?
Who goes shopping that late?
Passing by what?
Who has time during the day?
Excuses.
Nothing but excuses.
My lord, she is clearly making excuses.
Guokai,
didn't they just say it?
Whether they happened to meet him
on the street
or happened to meet him elsewhere,
in short, all in all,
they didn't interfere, did they?
My lord, if you keep covering for them,
they will only get more out of line.
That's not true.
With you here keeping them in line,
that won't happen.
My eyes are injured,
so I will skip the formal salute.
It's fine.
Duoyu,
how is her injury?
My lord,
it is only a scrape on the eyelid.
Nothing serious.
Then may I
skip training for the next few days?
Of course.
You may skip training
for the next few days.
My lord.
If you keep this up,
I will never keep them in line.
Guokai.
You need to open your mind.
Go rest.
(Ministry of Justice)
Guan Yunfeng.
Duke Wei
is a descendant of General Xu Da,
Prince Zhongshan.
The Azure Dragon Jade
is a family heirloom bestowed
by the Hongwu Emperor.
You will be the death of me!
(Ministry of Justice)
Come on.
Feng. Feng.
Are you all right, Feng?
I'm fine.
Feng, we all know you did your best.
We are just unlucky.
The criminals we run into
are always at the top
of the Bounty List.
Drop it. Drop it.
Feng, let's buy you a drink.
A drink?
Yes, a drink.
At Chong'er Pavilion.
(Chong'er Pavilion)
We drink until we drop.
That's right.
Let's go.
The wine at Chong'er Pavilion
is excellent.
I have heard so much about it.
Exactly.
What are you doing here?
Untidy clothes.
Not handsome.
Vulgar rich men.
We don't serve your kind.
How am I not handsome?
Exactly.
What do you mean, not handsome?
Forget it.
Let's go.
Feng.
Constable Guan.
Our female Jinyiwei's quarters
are in the back courtyard.
Tell me whatever you
and your men want to eat.
Good.
So good.
What is good?
I mean,
today's wine and meat
are on me.
Thank you, Feng!
That's our brother, Feng.
Always so generous.
Fill them up.
Constable Guan.
You seem troubled.
Did something happen?
Wait.
Hold on.
Young Master Chang.
Isn't that Miss Shen?
Come here.
It is all that phantom thief
Feng Fuliu's fault.
Feng Fuliu
has ruined our Enforcement Division.
I, Guan, swear today
that if I fail to catch Feng Fuliu,
I will never take a wife.
Well said, Feng!
Then you are destined to die a bachelor.
Who are you?
Why are you defending Feng Fuliu?
Who am I?
The owner of Chong'er Pavilion.
Young Master Chang himself.
You say I'm defending Feng Fuliu?
Do you know what kind of man
Feng Fuliu is?
A peerless phantom thief
ranked second on the Bounty List.
You rookies
think you can catch Feng Fuliu?
Isn't that laughable?
Very laughable.
At least
Constable Guan has a heart for justice.
Unlike some people,
who cannot tell right from wrong
and only know how to run their mouths.
You...
You are taking his side against me?
Fine.
If he can catch Feng Fuliu,
I will carry a cauldron from Chong'er
to the imperial city.
If he can't,
you will serve me like a slave
for the rest of your life.
Fine. Bet accepted.
Bingfan,
this bet is far too unfair to you.
It is fine.
Constable Guan, I believe in you.
You can surely capture Feng Fuliu alive.
I will catch him,
even if it costs me my life.
Go, go.
That owner...
Duoyu.
That night,
why did you suddenly appear
beneath the city wall?
I was worried about you,
so I followed you.
You...
You are no ordinary servant.
(Chong'er Pavilion)
Let's go there.
- Sure.
- My treat today.
Why is that constable standing there?
No idea.
Is he all right?
Leave him. Let's go.
What is that constable doing there?
Go, go.
Bingfan.
I'm coming.
Excellent blade work.
Constable Guan.
Are you here on a case?
No.
My mother said
that before seeing a lady,
a man should show his best side.
This uniform is the best thing I own.
Did you need something?
What does this mean?
These handcuffs are forged
from fine steel.
My father passed them down to me
when he was a constable.
No blade or famous sword
can cut through them.
For arrests, cases,
and catching thieves, they are essential.
You can't buy these anywhere.
Are you trying to sell them to me?
No.
I want to give them to you.
From now on, when you catch thieves,
clap these on them,
and they will never escape.
Give them to me?
Why give me something so precious?
I...
Well...
Just take them.
If I take them, what will you use?
It's fine.
They are yours. Keep them.
What are you laughing at?
Why were you eavesdropping?
I didn't mean to.
I only came out to cool off.
But
I really couldn't help it.
Cool off?
You came out of your room.
You were clearly eavesdropping.
This is
the first time in my life
I have seen a man court a girl
by giving her handcuffs.
Don't talk nonsense.
We have
a professional friendship.
Chang Beiming,
nothing decent ever comes out
of your mouth.
Constable Guan and I are not like that.
Look at him.
The way he dressed today,
everything he just said,
and these ridiculous handcuffs.
Who would believe
he doesn't mean it that way?
You have the dirtiest mind
in all of Chong'er Pavilion.
Constable Guan,
I will accept these handcuffs.
I will use them
to catch more notorious thieves.
I won't let your fine gift
go to waste.
Yeah! Yeah!
Excellent!
Bingfan accepted them!
He gave me a gift.
Why is he
happier than I am that I accepted it?
How should I know?
What...
What is he angry about?
You men are all so strange.
Hua.
I heard Feng Fuliu hurt you yesterday.
Are you all right?
Thank you for your concern,
Young Master Chang.
What does Feng Fuliu look like?
Is he handsome? Tell me.
I really didn't see clearly.
I'm going back.
The spring wind dares
to brush the willows.
What?
Nothing.
Good night, Young Master Chang.
Why are you here?
Bingfan.
I wanted to see you.
The food at Chong'er Pavilion
is too expensive.
So I begged the attendants.
They said
if I wash dishes here
for free every day,
I can come to the back courtyard
to see you.
That is bullying.
I will go talk to Chang Beiming.
It's fine.
I actually enjoy it.
Besides, last time I treated everyone
at Chong'er Pavilion,
I spent all my money
and still owed a debt.
Young Master Chang didn't make a fuss.
I will wash dishes for free
to pay off the debts.
Then I will help you.
Take these back.
Why?
They are your family heirloom.
I can't accept them.
A gift once given
should never be taken back.
If you don't like them,
throw them away.
(Chong'er Pavilion)
From now on, anyone in official uniform
is banned from Chong'er Pavilion.
Then I will take it off.
Untidy clothing is forbidden.
That has always been the rule.
You are clearly targeting me.
I am. What about it?
Chang Shuai, Chang Jun. See him out.
You...
Guan Yunfeng.
Why wash dishes of all things?
Why are you washing dishes here?
Lost a bet?
We are short-handed today.
Come help.
All right.
So shiny.
Hey.
This is how you wash dishes?
Rinse them twice in salt water first,
then twice in clean water.
That is the only way to get them clean.
Otherwise, the guests
will get upset stomachs.
Like this. Watch.
See? Nice and shiny.
Don't get mad.
I will stop teaching.
(Scar Balm)
Scar Balm.
It treats scars on the body.
Take it.
(Scar Balm)
Thank you.
Now wash the dishes.
(Imperial Edict)
Duke Wei
lost an imperial treasure.
He filed a petition before His Majesty,
requesting the Jinyiwei
to capture the phantom thief.
(Northern Bureau)
This time,
we are acting by imperial order
to capture Feng Fuliu.
We must
catch him with ease
and show the Cabinet,
the Six Ministries, and the Commander
that the Jinyiwei are no pushovers.
Yes, my lord.
Advisor Dong,
go draw up a flawless plan
to trap Feng Fuliu.
This time,
I will personally oversee the arrest.
Yes, my lord.
Commissioner.
This time, we use only male Jinyiwei,
not the female ones, right?
Of course.
Those three
will only drag us down.
This time, I want the male Jinyiwei
to take all the credit.
Yes, my lord.
Capture Feng Fuliu?
Lu Guokai won't let us join?
Correct.
This time, he has gathered
all six Qianhu,
twelve Baihu,
and every skilled fighter he can find.
Only
you female Jinyiwei were left out.
Outrageous.
Feng Fuliu is highly skilled
at disguising.
When the time comes,
we will have the advisor set a password.
Greetings, Commissioner.
Who let you in?
No one was guarding the door.
So I came in.
What is it?
I request permission
to capture Feng Fuliu.
This matter
is already under my command.
You were not summoned.
Don't make trouble here.
I have fought Feng Fuliu before.
I know a little about him.
Please...
Shen Bingfan.
Deploying officers is my job
as Commissioner.
You are a mere low-ranking Squad Leader,
yet you want a say in our strategy?
Why do you keep refusing
to let the female guards join?
Is this because of a personal grudge?
Shen Bingfan, you defied
and insulted your superior.
Advisor.
Put it on record.
Suspend her for ten days.
Mr. Lu.
What? Is that not enough?
Dismissed!
Suspended? So be it.
At least we can go shopping together.
Let's check this place.
Exactly. A rare bit of free time.
If a fool like Lu Guokai
can catch Feng Fuliu,
I'll eat my hat.
True.
With Lu Guokai,
there is no way he can catch Feng Fuliu.
When the male Jinyiwei fail,
it won't be too late for us to shine.
Hua,
is this one of those
Nanyang imports?
Yes.
This is nice.
Smell it.
Sir.
What fragrance powder is this?
This is a special fragrance powder
called Soul-Stealing Fragrance.
(Constable Guan, are you all right?)
(I'm fine.)
Bingfan.
Smell this. Does it seem familiar?
Isn't this the same scent
from the fragrance powder
scattered on the ground
when we fought Diaotu?
♪Because you once entered my dreams♪
♪Truth and illusion blur in wine♪
♪My heart drifted lost♪
♪Yet found you in the crowd♪
♪My blood still burns
as the world surges♪
♪The land is fair, and you are free♪
♪Sword drawn, lost in obsession♪
♪I've softly let it go♪
♪The vow you made was true♪
♪Yet like clouds, it stops for no one♪
♪Put away those dreamlike words♪
♪And forget at world's end♪
♪Embracing memory♪
♪Through blossoms and dreams♪
♪You hide in the crowd, silent♪
♪I wish to let it pass♪
♪And run toward this vast life♪