=Angels and Guards=
=Episode 3=
From now on, you are
female Jinyiwei officers
of the Northern Bureau.
But remember this.
You have no official posts,
no formal status,
and many won't even know you exist.
You are nothing more
than shadows of the Jinyiwei.
Yes.
I have high hopes for you.
(Jinyiwei Squad Leader
of the Left Qianhu Office)
Thank you, my lord.
Don't tease my bird too much.
Yes, Young Master.
Chang Beiming.
What is your connection to Lu Guokai?
I know Lu Guokai didn't want me in.
You must have said something
to make him change his mind.
Who exactly are you?
How can a few casual words from you
sway a Commissioner's decision?
Lu Guokai
owes me money.
I threatened him.
If he didn't let you in,
he had to pay me back at once.
Do all you men
handle things this carelessly?
I was helping you.
Either way,
you helped me again.
In the martial world,
we repay every favor and grudge.
Name your price.
Really?
Yes.
Go on one date with me,
and we'll call it even.
A date?
What are you laughing at?
You don't even know what a date is?
I grew up in a Taoist temple.
I rarely dealt with people.
That's why I'm asking.
(If she finds out what a date means,)
(with that temper of hers,)
(she will beat Chang Beiming up.)
(Why not help things along?)
A date?
It's just
a perfectly ordinary social call.
Two people dress up
and meet at an agreed place.
Then they eat, drink,
and enjoy the sights.
(Go with the Flow)
Xintian, Bingfan, from now on,
we're sisters
eating from the same bowl.
Come on. Drink up.
From now on, we share fortune
and face hardship together.
Cheers.
Well said.
I'm so happy today.
Not just because I joined the Bureau,
but because I met two sisters
who help me and care for me.
A toast to you both.
What about a toast to me?
Young Master Chang?
Young Master Chang,
that seat is mine.
this is a girls' gathering.
What is a grown man like you
doing here?
You only passed an entry test,
and you're this happy?
Still better than someone
who couldn't even pass it.
Fan, don't hit below the belt.
Don't call me that.
There's something
I want to
ask of you.
Ask me?
Can you move me to another room?
One with better soundproofing.
Why?
Secret.
Fine.
But
after work at the Bureau every day,
you'll serve me
as my personal maid for two hours.
You...
You're asking me for a favor,
and you're still glaring?
Give me a smile.
This one.
Well?
Quiet and elegant.
Who lives next door?
You?
What?
In all of Chong'er Pavilion,
my room is obviously the best.
Thick walls. Great soundproofing.
(Late Lord Shen Lian)
Father,
I have entered the Northern Bureau.
May your spirit watch over me.
I will uncover the truth
as soon as possible,
expose the traitor,
kill Leng Xin myself,
(Late Lord Shen Lian)
and avenge you.
(Phantom Thief Feng Fuliu,
No. 2 on the Bounty List)
Feng Fuliu.
Feng Fuliu, stop right there!
Congratulations, Miss Shen,
on joining the Jinyiwei Northern Bureau.
A cup of wine
to show my respect.
What?
Are you afraid
it's poisoned?
Who exactly are you?
Me?
Just a wanderer passing through.
Then do you know
the first thing I'll do as Jinyiwei
is bring you in?
To be on a beauty's mind
is one of the great honors
of my life.
I drank your wine.
Now I'm taking you in.
Bold and direct.
Just as expected.
(Miss.)
(You look pretty when you smile.)
(You know,
you look nice when you smile.)
(I ranked first in the written exam)
(but failed the physical test.)
(Feng Fuliu.)
(Chang Beiming.)
(It can't be.)
(His fighting skills)
(are terrible.)
(Leisurely and Free)
(How does he look this good every time?)
(Why is my heart beating so fast?)
Young Master Chang,
where are you off to?
Well...
Isn't it obvious?
I hope Bingfan
will understand your devotion.
She's not made of stone.
I offered my heart
to...
Let's go.
You brought your blade?
The Jinyiwei are here!
Jinyiwei!
Go, go!
The Jinyiwei are here!
Jinyiwei!
Cover me!
I need this too!
Give it back.
You wore your uniform on a date?
Doesn't it look more proper?
Don't you know? When Jinyiwei appear,
everyone runs for cover.
Are you trying
to clear the whole street?
Let go!
No!
Give it to me!
Then I'll go back and change.
No need.
I'll take you somewhere.
Give it back!
Let's go.
That dress is nice.
If you like it, I'll buy it.
Look. A female Jinyiwei officer!
Officer,
my shop obeys the law.
We are honest citizens.
We have never done anything illegal.
What are you doing? Don't bow to me.
We're here to buy clothes.
Pick out something suitable for her.
Choose anything you like.
Anything at all.
You choose. Anything that suits her.
And dress her up properly.
Officer,
right this way.
Why are the Jinyiwei here?
No idea.
Is this all right?
A beauty like you belongs in heaven.
Why would you
come down to earth for me?
♪Because you once entered my dreams♪
♪Truth and illusion blur in wine♪
♪My heart drifted lost♪
♪Yet found you in the crowd♪
♪My blood still burns
as the world surges♪
♪The land is fair, and you are free♪
♪Sword drawn, lost in obsession♪
♪I've softly let it go♪
♪The vow you made was true♪
♪Yet like clouds, it stops for no one♪
♪Put away those dreamlike words♪
♪And forget at world's end♪
♪Embracing memory♪
♪Through blossoms and dreams♪
♪You hide in the crowd, silent♪
♪I wish to let it pass♪
♪And run toward this vast life♪