=Angels and Guards=
=Episode 4=
Candied hawthorns!
Do I look strange dressed like this?
You look beautiful.
When people go on dates,
do they all dress like this?
That's the rule.
Is tapping my nose a rule too?
More or less.
The capital truly lives up to its name.
So lively,
so magnificent.
This place is my private hideaway.
Even Shizhen and Zhihe
don't know about it.
So, are you pleased with today?
I'm here to repay a favor.
As long as you're pleased.
Just now,
did you feel the ground shake?
No.
Then why
did my heart just tremble?
Tremble? What do you mean?
Because you're beautiful.
So?
So...
They stole my money!
Thieves!
Catch them!
Move!
Catch the thieves!
He stole my money!
Someone help! Catch the thieves!
It's them!
You're dead.
Go.
- Unbelievable.
- Yeah.
♪In a fleeting moment♪
♪Whose face crosses my mind♪
♪Whose name is it♪
♪I whisper in my heart♪
♪Yet in the crowd, we brush past♪
♪Afraid memories will fade like dreams♪
♪This longing I cannot say♪
♪I wish you could hear♪
Oh my god.
What are you looking at?
Let's go.
You just dated, and now you're training?
The end-of-month assessment is coming.
You bought a few dresses,
had a few bites,
then ran off to catch thieves,
and came right back?
That was your first date?
But he paid for the clothes and meal.
Well,
did he say anything
sweet and flirty?
Words can be sweet and flirty?
Forget it.
Anyway,
I repaid him for getting me
into the Bureau.
Now we're even.
Bingfan,
are you putting on an act,
or do you really not get it?
Get what, Hua?
This has nothing to do with you.
Go play somewhere, kid.
I'm not a kid anymore.
Instead of bickering,
you should think about
what we'll do about the assessment.
I'm doomed.
In the 28th year of the current reign,
Captain Shen Lian of Northern Bureau
was ordered to protect
(Unclosed Cases)
Xu Wenchang, a key witness
in Prince Luo's treason case,
into Huguang.
However, during the escort,
due to Shen Lian's negligence,
Xu Wenchang
and his family were attacked.
That's nonsense.
Silence. This is the Archives.
Archivist Li.
(Case File: Prince Luo's Treason)
May I borrow this case file?
Are you all right?
(Prince Luo's Treason Case)
Prince Luo's treason case?
This case shook
both the court and the country.
It was one of Northern Bureau's
greatest failures of the past ten years.
Why?
Shen Lian couldn't guard
the key witness,
which led to the witness's death.
He lost his own life far from home,
and Prince Luo's case came to nothing.
The Northern Bureau
became a laughingstock.
And the Southern Bureau
mocked it for ages.
At the time, Shen Lian
was escorting the witness
to the capital.
But in Huguang,
they were ambushed by assassins.
Even Leng Xin, the top assassin,
was there.
With no allies and no reinforcements,
Shen had to fight to the death.
In the end, he died
under Leng Xin's blade.
He was a hero of Northern Bureau.
How can you call that a failure?
You're awfully upset.
What was Shen Lian to you?
No one.
I just find it unjust.
Why?
Because this file is full of holes.
Tell me.
Shen was escorting the witness
to the capital.
Why would he reveal his own route?
And,
if Xu Wenchang was such
an important witness,
why was no one sent to receive him?
Jinyiwei relay stations
are highly confidential.
How could outsiders know?
And who hired Leng Xin,
the greatest assassin in the land?
Are we ignoring all these questions?
Now that a hero is dead,
people still smear his name.
How is that justice?
Yes.
You do have a point.
But
Northern Bureau isn't stupid.
If this case was buried,
it means
there's more to it.
What more?
How would I know?
I don't work for Northern Bureau.
But I'll tell you this.
The files won't have the truth.
If you want the truth,
you need to get posted
and access the classified archives.
(I can't waste my time here
washing dishes.)
(I need to pay Chang Beiming back,)
(kill Leng Xin,)
(find the traitor,)
(and avenge my father.)
Hey, friend.
I want to buy some information.
What information?
Information on the bounty list.
That kind of information isn't cheap.
Ranked ninth on the bounty list,
Qiankun Rat,
also known as Liu Sankong,
will appear near the capital.
Liu Sankong, the Qiankun Rat.
(Liu Sankong, No. 9 on the Bounty List)
Robbery, burglary, assault,
and 38 lives on your hands.
Ranked ninth on the bounty list.
Reward is two thousand taels.
Dead or alive.
You're the legendary
number one
female bounty hunter?
Take the goods.
Let me go.
I can bring you in
and still collect the bounty.
In your dreams.
If I'm dead either way,
you're not cashing in on my head.
(Chong'er Pavilion)
That was reckless.
Going after Liu Sankong alone?
What were you thinking?
Do you know why he's ranked
in the top ten?
Because he's ruthless.
I wanted to pay you back sooner.
Who asked you to pay me back?
Who said I was in a hurry?
If you ever do something dangerous again
because of this debt,
or because you want to pay me back,
I'm telling you,
I'll charge you triple interest.
All right, Young Master Chang.
I'm coming in.
Come in.
Bingfan, I'll go bring the medicine.
Here's the medicine.
I'll do it.
Here.
Come on. Take your medicine.
I thought I had him.
I didn't think he'd fight desperately.
From today on,
your debt is cleared.
I won't pick fights with you anymore.
And you two.
You don't have to work for me anymore.
Just stop risking your lives, all right?
Debts must be paid.
That's the rule of the martial world.
I'll go capture
Hua Yunfeng, the Ever-Changing Wildcat,
and pay you back.
Hey!
What does Hua Yunfeng have to do
with this?
Hua, who is this Wildcat?
The only woman
in the bounty list's top ten.
Ranked fourth,
the Ever-Changing Wildcat.
That's way too dangerous, Bingfan.
Can you please not go?
It's too dangerous.
Bingfan.
From now on,
if you have the money,
pay me back whenever you want.
And if you don't,
I won't bring it up.
Just stop taking risks, okay?
Fine.
I'll find another way once I'm healed.
This woman is impossible.
You feed her.
Okay.
Young Master.
We recovered Liu Sankong's body.
He drowned
after sustaining severe injuries.
His face was destroyed,
so he can't be identified.
Even if we take him to the authorities,
we probably won't get the bounty.
He got off easy.
Take him away and bury him.
Yes.
Bingfan.
What do you think of Chang?
What do you mean?
I mean...
Since it's just us girls here,
let me ask you.
What kind of husband do you want?
I...
I've really never thought about it.
What about Young Master Chang?
(Just now,)
(did you feel the ground shake?)
(No.)
(Then why)
(did my heart just tremble?)
♪In a fleeting moment♪
♪Whose face crosses my mind♪
♪Whose name is it♪
I...
I don't dislike him.
I just don't feel that way about men.
♪Yet in the crowd, we brush past♪
♪Only then did I understand fate♪
♪Was hidden in the day we met♪
♪A fate that cannot be severed♪
♪Round and round♪
♪Threads of love bind us together♪
♪Afraid love will fade like smoke♪
♪Afraid memories will vanish like dreams♪
♪This longing I cannot say♪
♪I wish you could hear♪
(Case File: Prince Luo's Treason)
(Awe in Authority, Grace in Virtue)
Last night,
Scholar Huang Yi of the Hanlin Academy
was assassinated at home.
One strike through the heart.
It was Leng Xin.
Mr. Huang was the top scholar
of the last imperial exam,
a leader among the upright officials.
He was to tutor the Crown Prince,
but was killed at home.
And now Leng Xin is involved.
This is serious.
Could it be connected to that case?
Prince Luo's...
The Cabinet wants this
handled quietly.
Archivist Li,
why are there no files on Leng Xin?
Leng Xin is a top Class-A fugitive.
All his records
are locked in the classified archives.
Not just me.
Even the Commissioner
has no free access.
Even the Commissioner can't?
How long will it take
before I can see Leng Xin's file?
Pump Zhang Weimin for information.
Pump him?
That old man loves wine.
Once he's drunk,
he becomes a big blabbermouth.
Young Master Chang knows you enjoy wine.
He prepared this rare vintage
and sent me to bring it for you
to taste.
Good. Full-bodied and strong.
Bingfan,
how has training been lately?
How are your lessons?
Thank you for asking.
I'm doing all right in every subject.
It's just...
Just what?
Before joining Northern Bureau,
I wanted nothing more
than to capture Leng Xin,
the top killer on the bounty list.
But why are there so few records
on Leng Xin here?
Actually, here at Northern Bureau,
we have plenty on Leng Xin.
It's all locked
in the classified chamber.
If you want to catch Leng Xin,
I'll make you a promise.
If you pass
the end-of-month assessment,
I
will grant you special access
to the classified chamber for two hours.
And if you truly capture Leng Xin,
I'll recommend you to His Majesty
for Lu Guokai's post.
♪Because you once entered my dreams♪
♪Truth and illusion blur in wine♪
♪My heart drifted lost♪
♪Yet found you in the crowd♪
♪My blood still burns
as the world surges♪
♪The land is fair, and you are free♪
♪Sword drawn, lost in obsession♪
♪I've softly let it go♪
♪The vow you made was true♪
♪Yet like clouds, it stops for no one♪
♪Put away those dreamlike words♪
♪And forget at world's end♪
♪Embracing memory♪
♪Through blossoms and dreams♪
♪You hide in the crowd, silent♪
♪I wish to let it pass♪
♪And run toward this vast life♪