Adjutant Zhang,
about what happened earlier,
I hope you don't take it to heart.
You are too noisy.
[Archives: The Nanyang Mystery]
[Episode 26]
[Jiutou Yandai, Caravan Tactician]
This woman is so heavy-handed.
She doesn't look like someone
who's dying at all.
Su Ya, you old jerk!
Let me go!
Yell again, and I'll cut out
your brothers' tongues!
Let's fight one-on-one!
I'll give you a two-move handicap!
As long as they haven't entered Bailejing,
I have a way to approach them.
They are a caravan
that has been traveling
in this area year-round.
Their tactician is called Jiutou Yandai.
As his name indicates,
he has 9 pipes.
His tobacco is made of
various strange secret medicines.
Smoking it makes you
completely disoriented.
Some
even have all sorts of unexpected effects.
It's him.
Jiu or Shan something,
let me ask you a few questions.
Let me go!
Let's fight one-on-one!
I'll give you a two-move handicap!
-Chief Shan! Chief Shan!
-Murder! Murder!
-Murder!
-Murder! Murder! Murder!
Stop! Stop!
Stop!
Are you going to talk?
Who are you?
What do you want?
I am the top detective in Nanqiang.
Patrolling here with my colleagues today,
I feel an overwhelming evil aura.
I must set up a clever layout,
risk my own life,
and go deep into the tiger's den
to investigate thoroughly.
Top detective?
Do you even believe yourself?
What do you know?
Everything is under my control now.
Who do you think you are?
Okay, okay, okay.
Okay.
Go on.
Do you know Zhang Qiling?
No.
Answer properly.
I really don't know him,
Top Detective.
Then why are you cursing Priest Su Ya?
Everyone here seems to love him.
Su Ya seems very humble on the surface,
but secretly,
he does all kinds of dirty deeds.
Extorting money, murdering.
Do you know why my brothers and I
were arrested?
Why?
He wanted me to help him
kill people along the way
and transport corpses.
Transporting corpses again.
Old jerk.
Who does he think Jiutou Yandai is?
I'm a real man.
I would rather die than do such a thing.
Su Ya, you jerk!
Untie me right now!
Let's fight one-on-one.
I'll kill you.
Do you want to get out?
Of course, I do.
Then help me take off my shoes.
[Su Ya, High Priest of Bailejing]
High Priest,
this is a token
of our family's appreciation.
You saved my grandson.
You are a benefactor to our whole family.
Is that all?
This is my dowry.
It is top-grade Hetian jade.
Please accept it, High Priest.
Do you not like these?
How about we bring you
something else tomorrow?
Your eye is not bad.
Please sit, Miss.
The High Priest is busy
with something at the moment.
He will be here shortly.
Let's go. Let's head out. Come on.
Let's go.
Gu-Bite Casket?
Something not even the Archives could find
is actually here.
About what happened just now,
thank you.
What's your name?
My surname is Zhang.
You have already met.
That is my family.
It doesn't like me
entertaining beautiful women.
It will be watching from above.
You should mind your boundaries.
Don't make it unhappy.
Miss Zhang, you don't look like a local.
What brings you to Bailejing?
Looking for someone.
Who?
Feikun Balu.
All our people
want to see Feikun Balu.
If you want to see a god,
you must worship devoutly.
Have you ever made
offerings to the true god?
As a priest of Bailejing,
have you seen Feikun Balu
with your own eyes?
I am the messenger
of the true god Feikun Balu.
What do you think?
Where did you see him?
No one dares to speak to me like that.
Do you know who I am?
Guards!
Send her straight to Jin for a snack.
Yes.
Where are you kicking?
Are you blind?
Down, down.
Here?
No, no.
Here, yes.
Okay.
-Here?
-Right.
To the right.
Yes, yes.
Right here, right here.
Right here.
Forward, forward.
Fire.
Fire, fire.
I got it.
Hold on. Turn forward.
Come on.
-Murder!
I killed someone!
Catch me!
Come catch me!
-Murder! Murder!
Jerk,
untie us. Hurry!
This tobacco is something.
It's called Obedience Tobacco.
As long as you start with "Jerk,"
they'll do whatever you want.
Jerk,
tell me
how to get to High Priest Su Ya's room.
Behave!
Or I'll feed you all to the snakes later!
Dad.
Are we
really going to die here?
So the rumors are true.
Rumors?
What rumors?
A few years ago,
I heard the priest went into the mountains
to worship the gods
and died of illness on the way.
He was about to be buried,
but he actually came back to life.
I heard he met Feikun Balu,
was saved by him,
and became his messenger.
Everyone thought it was a miracle.
In the first few years
after coming back to life,
the priest was just like before
a kind-hearted person.
But a year ago,
people started saying
his temperament changed drastically,
becoming very greedy and cruel.
But no one had seen it,
so no one believed it.
Turns out...
turns out it's actually true.
Dad.
Go back.
I need to go back.
Who's there?
Let's go!
Guards!
This tobacco of yours is really nice.
Give it to me for some fun.
No.
Then I can at least take this, right?
Give it to me.
You...
Don't come closer!
If you come closer, I'll throw it.
This old man's treasures
are even more than Jiutou Yandai's.
This damn bow.
My King Bow.
Kill them.
Kill them all!
Mentor.
Let's go.
Dude!
They all call me Big Pot.
I still don't know what to call you.
My surname is Zhang.
Zhang.
I hope we can meet again.
I hope we can meet again, Big Pot.
Go.
Where did these two come from?
To be so stupid
as to offend the High Priest.
Shh.
The High Priest has been erratic lately.
Many people in the mansion have died.
We should catch these two as scapegoats.
Otherwise, we will be next.
Then let's catch them quickly
and kill them.
Let's go.
[Wanted]
Did I owe them in my past life?
Sir,
do you have firearms and gunpowder?
I'll buy them all.
No firearms.
Gunpowder was just...
All bought out.
Out again?
They were just bought out.
Leave.
You're too late.
Who's the blind fool
working against me?
He just left.
I'm the clerk from the hardware store.
The boss asked me to help deliver.
Where are you going?
How come I didn't see you in the store?
I just started.
Does delivery cost extra?
No.
Then I'll trouble you.
Deliver it behind that mountain.
Okay.
Oh right.
The boss said
he forgot to give you your change.
Really?
Then wait for me a moment.
Wait.
Give them back to me!
You liar!
Give them back!
Move aside!
Sister!
Give them back!
Liar!
Here's another accomplice!
Wait for me!
Move aside!
Stop!
Get out of the way!
Stop running!
Stop!
Don't mess around!
Stop running!
Stop!
Why are they only chasing me?
A flare shot.
[Priest Su Ya's Mansion]
Shrimpie,
what happened to you?
Someone, go check over there!
Shrimpie, where are you?
They just ran this way. Search.
See where they all are.
Open all these coffins.
Nothing.
Shh.
We are safe for now.
You...
Are you crazy? What's wrong with you?
I... you...
I think there's something wrong with you.
Robber!
Hooligan!
Stop arguing.
You two gave me a headache.
Why did you take someone's thigh bone?
Send it back.
I know how to find Zhang Qiling.
Who is Zhang Qiling?
None of your business.
She is my sister.
Who do you think you are?
She is my mentor's wife.
Stop claiming false relationships.
The marks on this bone
were left by the Zhang family's
unique bone-scraping tool.
If I'm not mistaken,
the chief must have handled these bones.
So as long as we figure out
where these bones came from,
we can find him.
Little Taoist,
do you know any place in Bailejing
that specializes in handling bones?
I actually do.
Xigudong, one of the Six Great Fortresses
of Nanqiang.
The people in Bailejing believe
that a person's skin, flesh, and bones
are 3 different things.
Flesh has the shortest lifespan,
so people can only live
as long as their flesh lives.
But bones are different.
Bones have the longest lifespan.
Forty-nine days after death,
the skin dies.
And 30 years after death,
the bones finally die.
So they believe
that physical death is not true death.
As for the bones
stripped of skin and flesh,
they are sent to Xigudong to be washed
and then returned to their relatives.
Xigudong?
Where is the entrance?
Do you know the way?
I don't know.
I thought you knew everything.
But I know,
among the Six Great Fortresses
of Nanqiang,
only the outermost Bailejing
allows outsiders to enter.
The rest do not.
Moreover,
among these fortresses,
there is an unwritten rule.
That is, in each fortress,
only a very few people
know how to enter the next fortress.
The mountain roads and valleys
are complicated,
just like a maze.
I don't think we can get in.
Are you going to Xigudong to find someone?
I heard that Bailejing
holds a Bone-Washing Ceremony every year,
and it's happening in these two days.
You can participate
as long as you prepare a set of bones.
But...
for the Bone-Washing Ceremony,
the bones need to be at least
10 years old.
How many years has your mentor been dead?
[Mentor Zhang Qianzhang's Tomb]
Mentor, I'm sorry.
Mentor,
I am so sorry.
I am sorry.
I didn't want this either.
That's enough.
Don't you...
have anything to say to him?
Then stay one more night.
We must go to Xigudong tomorrow.
Also,
call Zhang Hailou back.
A flare shot.