[Bailejing, Deep in Mount Shiwan]
[Feikun Palu Temple]
Keep your feet on the clods
and don't move.
Keep the small shovel away
from the old brick joints.
Whoever moves will be fined
half a basket of firewood.
Keep your feet on the clods
and don't move.
Keep the small shovel away
from the old brick joints.
Whoever moves will be fined
half a basket of firewood!
Wake up.
[Archives: The Nanyang Mystery]
[Episode 23]
Bailejing?
It's located deep
in Mount Baiwan of Nanqiang.
Legend has it that it is an extremely
prosperous paradise.
Although Bailejing is famous,
the mountain is vast,
[Bailejing Research Files]
snakes, insects and poisonous ants
are very common,
bandits are everywhere,
and the folks there are fierce.
Very few people
can actually get inside.
Mentor, you've been to Bailejing,
haven't you?
The last time I went there
was many years ago.
I went to Bailejing
to investigate an incident,
and I personally wrote the file.
We have members of the Zhang family
there in Nanqiang,
responsible for some...
intelligence work.
It's written here that
none of the cases there have been closed.
Is the situation in Bailejing
really that complicated?
Even you couldn't deal with it?
The key is whether you can handle it.
[Bailejing Research Report]
Give it to me.
Don't get me wrong.
I'm going there to enjoy myself.
Having been the Director
for so many years,
it's time for me to take a rest.
By the way,
you will be the Director
of the Archives from now on.
Is it that simple?
Wait.
I have no subordinates now.
What's the point of me being the Director?
Mentor,
how about you help me recruit some people
before you retire?
Figure it out yourself.
Believe me. You can't go wrong.
Okay.
Don't worry.
Bro.
It looks like you have an unusual talent.
Do you want to be a great detective?
Really?
Of course.
Okay.
We now have our first member.
Mentor, what does this chief look like?
How can we find him?
Our chief,
Zhang Qiling—
very few people truly knew him.
But wherever he went,
he left legends about him there.
Wherever he went...
he left legends...
So this chief
was quite the ladies' man
wherever he went?
I only met this chief
a long time ago.
The chiefs are all very formidable.
When they act,
they all wear special Macabre Masks.
What is a Macabre Mask?
Macabre Masks—
it's a tradition of the Zhang family.
The older generation of the Zhang family,
when they needed to eliminate evil,
assassinate, or launch surprise attacks,
would wear masks designed by themselves.
These masks,
unlike human-skin masks,
cannot be used for disguise.
They can only be used to cover the face
and intimidate the opponents.
The Zhang family
really has a lot of rules.
Is it necessary
to intimidate the opponents?
The enemies we face are all very powerful.
So the masks are usually made into
the most terrifying images
in people's hearts.
What do you fear the most?
♪ The wind cannot disperse
the overlapping mist ♪
♪ Deep in the rainforest,
we whisper of the past ♪
♪ Holding up a lonely lamp
toward the abyss ♪
♪ Crossing wilderness,
through war fields ♪
♪ Behind us
are burning unfulfilled wishes ♪
♪ What is called
a fate-destined calamity ♪
♪ Is merely human's obsession ♪
I want two of these.
Give it to me.
♪ Let the waves rise in layers,
to be crossed ♪
♪ Crashing through day and night ♪
♪ Yet they cannot wash away
that year's moon ♪
♪ If you ask what destiny truly means ♪
♪ It is heroism, it is regret ♪
♪ It is separation, never to meet again ♪
♪ In the end, it is simply the fortune
of having a confidant at your side ♪
♪ Passing through endless years,
no words needed ♪
♪ As long as we once had it,
even if it vanishes in an instant ♪
Miss, please buy one.
♪ It is still worth it ♪
Take it.
Thank you.
This is not bad.
Keep it well.
See?
-Thank you, miss.
♪ What is called
a fate-destined calamity ♪
♪ Is merely human's obsession ♪
♪ Let the waves rise in layers,
to be crossed ♪
♪ Crashing through day and night ♪
Why did everyone leave?
I booked the whole place.
We haven't even entered Bailejing yet,
and we have spent almost
all the money we brought.
Go make money then.
I'm almost dead.
Can't you let me die happily?
I raised you for nothing.
Here comes the rice noodles.
Here. Enjoy.
Sir.
What is it?
I want to ask you about something.
Ask something?
Sure.
One piece of information,
one copper coin.
Copper coin.
Is it enough?
Just ask whatever you want.
How far is it to Bailejing?
Well...
You shouldn't go there.
Shouldn't go there?
I'll give you two. Is it enough?
Well...
Take it.
Thank you.
You guys
need to cross a mountain.
But after that,
no one has ever made it farther.
Why?
Because these years,
a gang of bandits
has been entrenched
at the entrance to Bailejing.
Whoever wants to enter Bailejing
must pass through them.
And they are very scary.
They specialize in robbing outsiders.
They never leave anyone alive.
Since they never leave anyone alive,
how did you know it?
Just guessing.
Enjoy your meal.
What are you planning?
We are out of money anyway.
Let's go make some money from the bandits
and enter Bailejing.
Since we are entering the bandit's lair,
it's better to disguise ourselves.
Mentor.
You just added hair extensions.
What kind of disguise is this?
None of your business.
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
I just washed my hands.
Phoenix Inn?
Come on! Drink up!
Bring it over!
-Great!
-Delicious!
Where did this lady come from?
The best tables here
have already been booked by us.
However!
You can sit on my lap!
Come on!
Come drink with me!
Sir, let me sit on your lap, will you?
Go away! Go away!
Sit on my lap!
Drink with me.
Don't cause trouble.
Good wine!
Drink up!
Come on!
-Let's drink.
Come, drink up.
Take a look. Who are the bandits here?
This is good wine.
Come on.
Bottoms up!
Drink more!
Really?
That's amazing!
These are all outsiders
eager to make money.
Please have some tea.
Enjoy.
This is a bandit inn.
The waiters are bandits.
They will probably strike soon.
Excuse me!
-Cheers!
Yes?
Don't we need a token to enter Bailejing?
When are you selling us the token?
Yeah!
When will you give us the token?
Our Phoenix Inn
will auction
the token of Bailejing shortly.
Please be patient, everyone.
Alright, alright.
We need a token to enter Bailejing?
Bailejing is the stronghold
of Mount Shiwan.
There are many treasures inside
that have never been seen outside.
If you have the ability to bring them out,
any of them can make you rich overnight.
Everyone here
wants to go to Bailejing for the treasure.
Then what is this token?
Bailejing
is just like a palace
where the emperors used to live.
No matter how capable you are
or how high your rank is,
without this pass token,
you will be stopped at the palace gate.
Then why is this token
not being kept by Bailejing itself,
but here in your Phoenix Inn?
Our boss got this token.
We had the advantage
of a favorable position.
You two are also going to Bailejing,
right?
Yes.
Do you want to join the auction?
You just need to pay a registration fee.
We need to pay for it?
Miss.
Your man is useless.
He doesn't even have this much money.
Why don't you be with me?
I'll pay the registration fee
for you.
Boss!
These guys
are really useless.
Exactly.
Didn't you just
tell me not to cause trouble?
I said that to you.
But I only have 2 months to live.
It's for the auction.
Two people.
Everyone, everyone.
Calm down, please.
Our manager
is treating you
to good wine and dishes.
We wish everyone here
good luck and great fortune in Bailejing.
We wish you great wealth.
Come on.
Hurry up.
Zhu! Check with the kitchen.
Bring over the wine! Hurry!
Come on!
Cheers!
Come on. Drink up.
Come on, cheers.
Let's drink on our own.
Here!
These are all signature dishes of our inn.
Come! Cheers!
As long as they are dead.
If you chop them into pieces,
how can I send them to Bailejing?
Let's do it as usual.
Keep the good-looking ones
and present them to the Chief,
and the ugly ones—
kill them.
Got it.
This one is good-looking.
Let's keep him and take him away.
That woman—
Kill her.
Who are you?
Robbers.
Give me your money.
So we are in the same business.
Please show mercy.
I have no money.
All my money
is with the Chief.
We...
We have no money.
Where is the Chief?
[Zhongshan Fortress]
According to the rules of the fortress,
when I blow the horn,
they come out to receive the goods.
This man looks pretty good.
Carry him away and change his clothes.
[Zhongshan Fortress]
The rest, the old place.
You are the Chief?
Disgusting!
[Feng Huang, Head of Phoenix Fortress]
This man is in good shape.
I like him very much.
Chief, this guy is a good fighter
of unknown origin.
We don't know what he's up to.
It's safer to kill him
to avoid any trouble.
Do you think I can't handle this brat?
No.
I just think he doesn't deserve you.
He's so handsome.
I think we're a good match.
I don't think you deserve me.
I'll kill you!
Get out!
How arrogant.
I like it.
I like conquering.
This is our first time meeting. Isn't...
Isn't this moving a bit too fast?
I actually prefer being reserved.
Wait, wait!
Chief.
We can't.
What do you mean?
I mean,
I'm like a corpse right now.
I can't move.
It's no fun.
Fulfill one wish for me,
and you can have me.
I promise to blow your mind.
What wish?
I actually already have a wife.
She is seriously ill and dying.
But she heard Bailejing is very beautiful.
So she wants to see it before she dies.
Chief, your token—
could you lend it to me?
I'll let her go there and see it,
so I can fulfill her wish.
Once I bury her properly,
I'll come back
and have babies with you, okay?
You're quite an affectionate man.
I can give you the token
so your wife can go to Bailejing herself.
But you have to stay.
Actually, it's my first time.
Who are you kidding?
This drug can knock out 3 tigers
for 12 hours.
Yet you broke free
in just 10 minutes.
You're amazing.
I like you so much!
Who are you?
That is my wife.
Didn't you say she was dying of illness?
She has a mental illness.
The token!
Move!
This woman.
The token...
Thank you for saving me.
Come on.
You saved my life.
So you are the savior of me
and the entire Phoenix Fortress.
Since I've decided to be your friend,
from now on,
I'll make sure the whole fortress
turns over
a new leaf.
We won't disgrace you.
As for our past misunderstandings,
they are all in this wine.
Let's bury the hatchet.
Alright.
Miss, what's your name?
You're like a completely different person
from during the day.
You speak Chinese very well.
I'm also Han Chinese.
I came here from Bailejing
with my dad when I was 13,
became the Chief at 17,
and I'm 22 this year.
What's your name?
How old are you?
Who's older between us?
Zhang Haiqi. I'm from the south.
As for my age...
I'm much older than you.
Then I'll call you Sister from now on.
Alright.
Everyone, stop eating!
Hold on a second.
From today,
she is my sister.
You will treat her
just as you treat me.
A toast to my sister first.
Come on.
To the Chief!
Chief!
His name is Zhang Hailou.
He is my apprentice.
Sorry for offending you today.
A toast to you.
Alright.
We got to know
each other through fighting.
May this wine
wash away
our grudges.
I never said I wanted to wash them away.
I want us...
to be tangled up forever.
Try this.
Let's go.
Hero.
This is my son.
He is 18.
Hero,
thank you for letting us go.
Your martial skills are really amazing.
Can I be your apprentice?
This young man looks like
he's made for martial arts.
Are you interested
in joining our Archives?
Kneel.
Mentor, you are right!
Get up. Get up.
Come on.
Let's have a drink.
I will take him as my apprentice.
We're so happy.
Mentor, enjoy your drink.
Eat first.
Come.
My son has a mentor now.
Come on, let's have a drink together.
Zhang Hailou.
Our engagement is always valid.
If you want to fulfill it,
you are welcome anytime.
Engagement?
Just forget it.
Chief,
you actually deserve someone better.
I'll help you woo her.
You'll help me...
Sister, try this.
It's delicious.
Come on.
For this kind of thing,
I have a lot of experience.
It takes skill.
I'll tell you in detail later.
You are still too young.
Did you come to Nanqiang
for sightseeing or business?
We are going to Bailejing.
You really are going to Bailejing?
No, it's too dangerous there.
You can't go.
What's so dangerous about Bailejing?
I'll take you to see something
that came from Bailejing.
We're here.
This talisman is used for suppression.
What's inside?
Have you noticed
how quiet it is around here?
It really is.
This forest is dense,
and the air here is damp.
In theory, there should be a lot of
snakes, bugs, rats, and ants.
But it's gotten much quieter
since we came in.
Ever since this coffin was placed here,
all the animals nearby have disappeared.
They seem to be very afraid of
what's inside the coffin.
Animals have a much faster ability
to sense danger
than humans do.
After all this build-up,
let's open it and take a look.
Are the people here a bit superstitious?
Dying in red clothes
won't turn you into a vengeful ghost.
Give me a hand.
Who is this person?
What happened to her?
Her name is Wanduo.
She is from Bailejing.
I used to do business with her.
A month ago,
she suddenly said she was getting married,
but on the day of the wedding,
she escaped from Bailejing.
She wasn't dead yet
when I was trying to save her.
The last thing she said to me was,
"Never go to Bailejing."
We have a custom
of keeping the coffin here.
Those who die unexpectedly
must be kept above ground
for 49 days before burial.
That's why I put her here.
What happened to Bailejing?
I don't know.
I only do business
with people coming out of Bailejing.
I rarely go in.
You trade corpses with Bailejing
for tokens?
Why does Bailejing need so many corpses?
I have no idea.
The rule of trading corpses for tokens
only started in recent months.
Moreover,
at first, picked-up corpses
were acceptable.
But in recent months,
their demand for corpses has been growing.
Killing living people
is also acceptable now.
Are there any tokens left?
All the people I sent to Bailejing
never returned.
Why do you still want to go there?
My mentor is sick.
I have to cure her.
Sister,
you're late.
The last 10 tokens of this year
have all been sold to a caravan,
to a man named Jiutou Yandai.
This afternoon, the caravan
has already set off for Bailejing.
If you want to go there,
you can only ask the caravan for them.
Otherwise,
you'll have to wait until next year.
Then prepare a horse for me.
As long as they haven't entered Bailejing,
I'll have a way to get close to them.
Hurry, hurry.
Yes.
Tie it tighter.
Alright.
You really have to rely on friends
when you're away from home.
Feng Huang,
you are much more reliable than
our relative in Changxiang.
Just put it in that pocket.
It's because I became friends
with you today, Sister.
That's enough.
Tell them to stop packing.
These things are too cumbersome.
Just pick one or two of them.
A dying person like me
can't use all of them.
Sister, what are you talking about?
You must live on
and get well.
Bailejing is a magical place.
Your illness
will definitely be cured there.
And your apprentice
seems to be quite worried about you.
He is still young
and hasn't experienced
the loss of loved ones yet.
He'll be fine after experiencing more.
But if I die,
he will be left all alone.
Mentor,
are you leaving so soon?
I'll be waiting for you here.
When you come back,
take me to that Archives.
Here, take this.
When I come back,
I'll teach you.
I'll go have your grandmaster cured first.
Take care.
Thank you, Mentor.
Well.
This doesn't look bad.
Come on.
It must be worth a lot of money.
Of course.
Bro,
if you're not good with words,
you can say less.
Charm her with things you're good at.
Look, you always wear too little.
How do I charm her?
How?
If you're good at singing,
sing some songs.
Some love songs.
Just wait patiently
for your mentor to return.
The clear mountain
breeze brushes over you.
I miss you again and again in my heart.
If I'm in your heart,
I'll follow you to the ends of the earth.
Adjutant Zhang.
Can you feel the strange spiritual energy
in this southern forest?
I am dull
and haven't perceived it.
Commander.
We found an inn ahead.
It's the only way to Bailejing.
We should be able
to find some news about Bailejing.
Adjutant Zhang,
go ahead and check it out.
Yes.