Sir,
have you seen
an outsider with a beast-pattern tattoo?
The tattoo is around here.
What's wrong with him?
That man is a bandit.
He abducted the Mountain God's bride
and committed a grave crime.
Sit down.
Tell me about it.
What exactly was going on?
Let me think whether I've seen him.
He's just some pretty boy,
actually quite good-looking.
I don't buy that he's a bandit at all.
He must be having an affair
with the bride.
That's why she didn't want
to marry the Mountain God.
They must've slept together—
two filthy bastards.
Guys like him
bring bad luck to their parents—
born lowly and worthless.
If we catch him, we'll castrate him
and parade him through the streets.
Is the bride beautiful?
She is.
If she's untouched,
taking her home as a concubine
wouldn't be bad at all.
Hey man,
where did you come from outside?
Where I come from—
what's it to you?
Just asking.
Casual chat.
What about you?
Local?
Got a daughter?
I have a daughter.
How old is she?
Has she reached marriageable age?
About the right age to get married.
When your daughter gets married,
will she also take this route?
Will she run into a bride kidnapping too?
What do you mean?
Have mercy! Please, spare me!
Am I being too harsh?
No, no, not at all.
Not at all.
Will you kill me then?
I wouldn't dare.
Seems like I still haven't
been harsh enough.
I wouldn't dare do that again.
Sir, please spare me!
Sir, please spare me! Don't kill me!
Don't kill me!
Sir, please have mercy!
Please have mercy!
Where is the Mountain God's
wedding taking place?
Spare me!
After you pass the mountain pass
and reach Xitou Beach,
just follow the stream forward—
that's the Mountain God Temple.
Please, spare me!
Spare me.
No, no—
please, spare me!
Sir, please spare me!
Spare me, sir.
Don't kill me!
Spare me, sir. Spare me, sir.
Spare me, sir.
[Archives: The Nanyang Mystery]
[Episode 28]
This is the only way
into the Mountain God Temple.
The bridal procession
should be coming through here, right?
They're here.
Why is there no bride in this procession?
Don't tell me
that after what happened
between me and the bride earlier,
they've hidden her away.
Right now, the top priority
is finding the bride.
Let's go down and blend into the crowd
and ask someone around.
Help me!
[Wulang Huazha, Local of Nanqiang]
Quick, say you've caught the man
who abducted the mountain bride!
I-I caught the man
Do they not understand what you're saying?
I said I've caught the man
who abducted the mountain bride—
it's him!
Ask who their leader is.
Ask for a reward from them.
I want to see your leader.
Is there a reward for this?
This is the man who abducted the bride.
Yes, he is.
He's a beggar from the mountains.
Who are you calling a beggar?
I'm a Daoist priest,
a legitimate cultivator.
Tell them
you were the bodyguard
I hired before,
-To fulfill your duty...
-I... I...
And then later you realized...
I'm the bodyguard.
-You got angry and caught me...
-He didn't pay me.
So I arrested him.
Do you think I'm deaf?
Cut their hamstrings.
Take them back
and leave them to the bride's families.
Invoke the Patriarch!
Five-fire orthodox law—
thunder spirit, ignite the flames!
That's incredible!
This guy can use sorcery!
Zhang Qianjun,
let's get out of here!
We'll meet again!
Boss, he got away!
Sorcerer,
are you just going to
abandon your companion like that?
Actually, that little Taoist just now
was just handling logistics.
I'm the real professional here.
Nobody move!
Sir,
we're just
hired to do a job
and earn a living.
See? All thanks to me.
Damn it!
What?
Yueshu is gone.
You really don't know
where the bride is hidden?
To be honest,
I grew up with this bride
since we were kids.
Bailejing hasn't been peaceful lately—
there've been rumors
that something in the forest
has been eating people.
I came along this time
to protect Yueshu.
And you managed to lose her?
The procession is so long
that those in front thought
she was behind,
and those behind
thought she was in front.
If it weren't for you,
we might not have
even noticed
Yueshu was missing
until we reached the Feikun Balu Temple.
Did you see two men—
one a Taoist,
and the other a pretty boy?
What?
I'm asking you—
have you seen two men?
What's going on, sir?
And where are the other group of men?
The ones who were chasing me just now.
I didn't see them in the procession.
Follow me.
The best way to hide someone
isn't to conceal them in a crowd—
but beneath lanterns
and the roar of drums.
Found them.
Then why is there
still another procession?
Wait here for me.
Don't be afraid.
I'm here to save you.
Mentor.
Why is it you?
Where's the bride?
She was switched. Can't you tell?
Do I really have to wait for you
to do everything?
I'm the bride now.
Get down, now.
You're such a liability—
how am I supposed to get married
with you in tow?
Should I go too?
Stay hidden.
I'll handle things here.
Wait for my signal.
Alright.
I'm going.
What's going on?
What do you mean what's going on?
That's my mentor.
Some things are as inevitable as rain
or a mentor wanting to marry—
just let it be.
But that escort procession
is definitely suspicious.
Those boxes are covered in talismans.
They don't look like they're
meant for the living at all.
Who would send off a living bride
with talismans all over?
What about Yueshu?
Could she be in danger?
You care about her that much?
You've still got feelings for her?
No, no.
We just grew up together.
Well, this bride sure is quite the flirt—
she's got the chief, and she's still
fooling around with other people.
Don't talk nonsense.
Yueshu is a good girl.
If it weren't for her sick father
and younger brother,
she wouldn't still be unmarried by now.
Well, if you're that close with her,
do you know our chief?
Your chief?
He has a tattoo on his chest,
something like this.
I've been blind to the truth—
with skills like yours,
I should've known
you're one of Feikun Balu's people.
So if he really is some kind of deity,
do you have a place here
where Feikun Balu is worshipped?
Yes, there are temples. Many temples.
Feikun Balu Temple?
Yes, yes.
So would the bridal procession
be heading to the Feikun Balu Temple?
Yes.
The bride will be sent
to the Feikun Balu Temple in Xigudong,
where the priest
will preside over the wedding.
The bridal procession won't stay—
they'll continue on to Xigudong
for the Bone-Washing Ceremony.
And the bride?
The priest says
the bride will remain
in the Feikun Balu Temple
and serve the Mountain God.
That is the honor of Bailejing.
I thought the Zhang family was finished.
I didn't expect
the Zhang family
to still have a temple here.
This chief is something.
I hope he can save Mentor and Shrimpie.
I've got an idea—follow me.
Zhang Hailou,
don't say I'm not a loyal brother—
I'm here to help you.
Don't worry.
It's just part of the ritual.
[Su Li, High Priest of Bailejing]
Feikun Balu will protect you.
High Priest,
what are
these corpses
being dug up for?
To offer them to Feikun Balu.
So you're saying I'm supposed
to be married off to Feikun Balu?
What exactly
is Feikun Balu?
You'll see soon enough.
Remember—
when serving him,
don't look him in the eye,
unless you want to anger him.
Now,
is everything here
being done as a bridal ritual?
Yes, High Priest.
All we have to do is deliver
the bride and these corpses
to the Feikun Balu Temple
as offerings to the great Feikun Balu.
Sir,
what is this...
No way like this.
This shadow procession is too sinister.
I need to get in there
to be with my mentor.
With your build,
you can just go in as a porter.
I literally just
came through here, didn't I?
Oh, Zhang Qianjun...
You can even get lost like this?
How useless can you be?
Feng Huang?
What are you doing lying there?
Don't come over!
Huh?
Why do my legs feel so weak
all of a sudden?
You idiot—
what are you even good for?
That's Nanqiang Horse-Stinger Grass.
It's poisonous.
How was I supposed to know?
Is anyone there?
Give me your hand.
Are you stupid?
If this grass is highly poisonous,
you'd still come save me?
Then why didn't you tell me earlier?
Have you been staying
in the Taoist temple for too long?
If I weren't kind-hearted,
you'd already be dead.
I attempted to save you—
what did I do wrong?
You're so capable,
then tell me—
what are we supposed to do now?
Well, since you came to my rescue,
let's head over and meet up
with my sister first.
Let's go.
You're okay now?
I'm fine.
People from the Zhang family
are all in good health.
Just like that?
Let me help you.
Are you sure about this—
going for revenge?
I've made up my mind.
I'm going to get revenge.
Don't try to talk me out of it.
I'm not going to try.
And I can't really understand
what you're going through,
so I don't have the right
to stop you either.
Little Taoist,
what happened—no more preaching?
Did that toxic weed
cure your yapping?
I've spent my whole life
in the mountains,
guarding a Taoist temple
and a firework.
I never had the chance to go out,
to see what the outside world
is really like.
But honestly...
I've always wanted to see it.
I want to come down the mountain,
see the world,
and find a firework
that belongs to me.
Sounds good.
You go find your firework,
I'll go take my revenge.
If I die,
just set off a firework for me—
count it
as visiting my grave.
What's with the "mm-hmm"?
Have you forgotten how to talk again?
Why don't you go roll around
in that grass a couple more times?
How are you feeling now? Let me help you.
[Feikun Palu Temple]
The auspicious hour is approaching.
Prepare the wedding ceremony.
Don't keep Feikun Balu waiting too long.
Soon, you will
be married to the great Feikun Balu
and fulfill your destiny.
Don't worry—your father
and younger brother,
I will take care of them for you.
I will take good care of them.
If she's to marry Feikun Balu,
then you're not allowed to touch her.
This is my younger sister
who comes with me as part of the dowry.
She will stand with me, no matter what.
The stench of corpses...
There are drag marks...
What are you doing wandering around
instead of taking care of the bride?
Sir,
I came out to find something to eat.
We can't let the bride go hungry, can we?
Sir,
my sister is supposed
to be marrying a deity, right?
Why is this place so eerie?
It clearly looks like she's marrying
some kind of monster.
Shh!
Come here.
A deity is a deity—
don't talk nonsense.
Miss,
you
don't need to be afraid.
When the wedding ceremony starts,
only your sister will be allowed in.
Even if you want to,
you won't be allowed to enter.
Just stay quietly
in the room and wait.
I'll make sure you...
How did this thing end up here?
Could everything be connected to this?
Sir, come on, let me help you up.
Sir,
I see you're close with the High Priest.
Tell me a bit more please.
Let me learn a bit.
What exactly is going on with
the mountain bride ritual
in Bailejing?
So you're saying
Bailejing's so-called
"marrying the mountain bride"
is actually a sacrificial ritual?
And it's not the first time either.
I found this in a crack
in the main hall doorway—
Wanduo's fingernail.
I looked into it.
A few months ago,
a major disaster broke out
deep in Nanqiang.
Strange mist spread everywhere,
and many people died.
The roads between
the six mountain settlements
were completely cut off.
Priest Su Ya
then publicly claimed
that someone had violated tribal taboos,
triggering the catastrophe—
and that things were still getting worse.
Priest Su Ya,
to prevent panic
from spreading through Bailejing,
came up with this idea
of marrying the mountain bride.
On the surface,
it's meant to calm the people.
In reality, it's used to cover up
disappearances and deaths,
and stop anyone
from investigating further.
But one thing I can't figure out—
why do they need so many corpses?
Also, this thing
and Mo Yungao
have both suddenly appeared
in Nanqiang recently.
Do you think this change
has something to do
with Mo Yungao's arrival?
My head hurts.
I'm not the Director—
why should I care?
That's for you to think about.
Right—so I'm the Director now, huh?
Then of course
we'll turn their plan against them.
Wait—what are you so worked up about?
The last bride died such a horrible death.
What, not pretty?
You look drop-dead gorgeous.
What happened to the original bride?
She was already released.
Nobody's going to stop my wedding—
come on, help me get dressed.
Yueshu, wait for me here for a moment.
Move!
Haiqi!
I'm serious about you—
come out and see me!
Haiqi!
I'm serious about you!
Why are you looking for my mom?
My dad isn't home today.
Why don't you stay for a meal?
Don't joke around.
Miss Zhang isn't that kind of woman.
You know what kind of woman
she is better than anyone, huh?
Flowers and gifts—
we'll accept those.
No.
But as for seeing her in person,
that won't be necessary.
I haven't even seen her yet.
Go back.
Go on, leave.
How can you treat me like this?
We won't see you out.
Young Master, what do we do?
What do you mean what do we do?
Let's go.
Goodbye.
Mentor,
this is already the third one today.
Aren't you tired of it?
I'm getting sick of it.
Why don't you just marry someone?
Are you stupid?
If she gets married,
what happens to us?
You're the stupid one.
We'd just follow her
after she gets married.
I'd rather live freely on my own.
What do I need a man for?
Besides,
don't I already have you two
to take care of me in my old age?
What are you looking at?
I'm looking at how beautiful my mentor is.
No,
I don't like this one.
I think the previous outfit looked better.
This one looks great.
I'm going to change.
You go out first.
But if I go out dressed like this,
won't I blow my cover?
Then find an empty latrine and hide in it.
Fine.
Just hurry up—
don't keep everyone waiting.
High Priest,
after every ritual is completed,
before Feikun Balu descends,
Priest Su Ya  always leaves from here.
What is this place inside?
It seems to be a structure built
by people from a long time ago.
Each time, Priest Su Ya goes deep inside
and takes something before leaving.
Could it be...
the secret of Feikun Balu
is hidden in here?
High Priest,
the auspicious hour has arrived.
Let's go.
Mentor.
Hurry up—
are you done yet? I'm coming in.
You're running away at a time like this?
Seriously?
Bride,
hurry up.
Are you ready yet?
Come on—are you done?
Why are you rushing me
so much?
Are you in a hurry
to be reborn or something?
Let's go. Time to get married.
It's the Zhang family.
So the source of the resurrection drug
really is Nanqiang—
and it comes
from the Zhang family themselves.
They were trying to use this medicine
to bring the dead back to life.
But how could the Zhang family
develop something like this
in a place like this?
What exactly is hidden deep in Nanqiang?
They actually came back to life...
But these resurrected people
don't seem normal.
These deranged people
took another dose of the medicine,
and they seem to have returned to normal.
If that's the case,
there must be something here
that can restore people to normal.
Where is that medicine?
These...
are the medicinal materials
used to refine that drug.
A cliff...
So that's it...
they use Zhang family blood
to make the medicine.
So this is what's hidden deep inside.
Then Zhang Haixia might also...