The person in the painting
is the woman my mentor loved the most.
So it's you.
What do you mean?
What does that mean?
What exactly is the relationship
between your mentor and mine?
Explain it clearly.
Actually, I'm not sure myself.
I only know that my mentor
waited for someone his whole life.
Since I entered the mountain,
my mentor told me
[Memorial Tablet
of Mentor Zhang Qianzhang]
that his only mission in life
was to wait for a flare shot.
Whoever fires the flare,
my mentor must obey
all of their commands.
But why did it take you so long?
He waited for you his whole life.
I forgot.
What did you say?
Y-Y-You forgot?
It's normal for you to be emotional now.
You're still young.
But you'll understand later
that being too attached
only moves yourself.
If your mentor was willing to wait,
that was his business.
Everyone has their own path.
Let's talk business.
How many things have you promised
others recklessly?
Can you stop making reckless promises?
Ordinary people have hard lives.
They are not meant to play with you.
But I never promised him I'd come back.
And I didn't know he'd wait so long.
Little Taoist,
since you're the contact for the Archives,
I have a question.
Which one of you fire the flare?
I only listen to that person.
-Me.
Why are you talking nonsense?
Why are you spouting nonsense?
You are my mentor.
Can't you be more tolerant?
-Are you fighting me for it now?
-He shot it. He did it.
Don't we need tokens to go to Bailejing?
I heard they're hard to get.
-Do you—
-Come with me.
These...
These
are what my mentor collected for you.
He thought they'd be useful one day.
I didn't expect you
to be so untrustworthy.
If we go, I'll only take you.
Not her.
If I don't go,
he won't either.
How about this?
Give me 2 tokens,
and I'll go with my mentor.
The path to Bailejing is complex.
Without a guide,
you can't get in at all.
If she goes, I won't.
Then no one will.
Then I won't go.
You two go.
Little Taoist.
My mentor is sick.
I brought her to Bailejing
to seek treatment
from the chief of the Zhang family.
Why did you...
Look at you.
My mentor is really dying.
If my mentor dies,
and you don't save her,
you'd be leaving her to die.
Would your conscience be clear?
Then...
then I'll go with you two.
For no other reason,
I just want to see
what the woman my mentor loved
is really like.
Have you been to Bailejing?
Of course, I have.
Wait.
Why are you both so arrogant?
[Archives: The Nanyang Mystery]
[Episode 25]
[Nanqiang to Changxiang]
Come out.
Let's talk.
About what?
Zhang Haixia.
Zhang Haixia is in Mo Yungao's team.
Stop joking, will you?
Am I joking?
Isn't that perfect?
Saves you the trouble of looking for him.
You two didn't hide anything else
from me before?
Like what?
Didn't he say anything else
to you before?
No.
I actually want to ask you
if you know something.
I've told you everything I know.
Shrimpie must have his reasons.
It's quite unusual for Mo Yungao
to suddenly appear in Nanqiang.
Do you think Shrimpie
did those abnormal things
just to get close to Mo Yungao?
If you want to find him,
go now.
Leave me in peace for a while.
Forget it.
He might have his reasons,
but you are really going to die.
I'm not the same as before.
I know what's more important.
Let's find the chief to cure you first.
We'll solve his problem later.
Mo Yungao has such a large team.
He'll be easy to find.
Then let me ask you,
if he really did something
unforgivable,
what would you do?
Pretend it never happened.
Then clean up his mess
and take him home.
Just like he did for me before.
It's late. Stop drinking.
We have to hit the road tomorrow.
[Routine inspection of flare shots]
[Zhang Qianzhang, the Zhang family's
contact in Nanqiang]
♪ The past fades into traces on the page ♪
♪ A silent breeze
brushes past that lingering warmth ♪
♪ In this fleeting world,
I long for a moment of vivid life ♪
♪ I may have a chance to open a door ♪
♪ Where love and wish
meet in a fleeting moment ♪
♪ There's no need to ask questions
in the maze ♪
♪ The world's bustle ♪
♪ Can briefly warm
those under a shared roof ♪
♪ And the story has come to an end ♪
[Four months later]
Will you come back?
If I do,
I'll let you know with a flare shot.
♪ Clouds drift and fade just a few years ♪
♪ Mortal world grass
regrows after parting ♪
♪ Truth or lie, seasons pass
in fleeting years ♪
Come on, get up quickly.
From now on,
♪ A silent breeze
brushes past that lingering warmth ♪
[Young Zhang Qianjunwanma]
you are my beloved disciple.
Your only mission in this life
is to wait for a flare shot.
♪ In this fleeting world,
I long for a moment of vivid life ♪
Whoever fires the flare,
you must fulfill
whatever request they make.
♪ I may have a chance to open a door ♪
♪ Where love and wish
meet in a fleeting moment ♪
♪ There's no need to ask questions
in the maze ♪
♪ The world's bustle ♪
♪ Can briefly warm
those under a shared roof ♪
♪ And the story has come to an end ♪
Mentor,
this year marks your 60th year of waiting
♪ Gifted to us the luck to walk
side by side a stretch of way ♪
in this mountain forest.
I've always wanted to ask you,
how can you wait your whole life
♪ After partings and meetings,
spring breeze comes round tomorrow ♪
for something that seems
so illusory?
♪ The world's bustle ♪
♪ Can keep whose dream under the roof? ♪
I'm here.
What can make me wait for a lifetime
♪ No farewell wishes needed in this life ♪
is never an arrow.
Then what is it?
I'm thirsty.
I'll go get you some water.
So,
she really isn't coming back.
I no longer want to wait for
other people's signal.
I want to become the signal myself.
[Memorial Tablet
of Mentor Zhang Qianzhang]
I'll come back to see you.
[Nanqiang to Changxiang]
Deep inside Nanqiang,
there are Six Great Fortresses.
The outermost one is called Jinyadong,
also known as Bailejing.
Jinyadong is the only place
where Nanqiang people
and outsiders live together.
During festivals,
they coat their teeth with gold powder
and then gather on the streets.
They're that rich?
How did they make their fortune?
There is a river inside Bailejing.
One side leads to Jinzhou,
and the other side
leads to the Hongfen River.
It's a freight path
along the ancient Tea-Mule Trail,
leading to the Central Plains.
That's why it's so rich there.
At night, it's brightly lit
and bustling with people.
From a distance,
it looks like a galaxy in the mountains.
It's beautiful.
Halt. Show your token.
[Bailejing]
It's fake?
Let's go in.
Finally, something reliable.
[Bailejing]
Zhang Qianjun,
are you sure
you're leading us the right way?
This is different from what you said.
Yeah, this is Bailejing.
Isn't it written on the sign?
I was dragged around for half a month
just to see this?
You know I don't have
many days left to live, right?
When exactly did you come?
In your past life?
When I was young,
my mentor brought me here a few times.
But it's been a while.
[Happiness after Death]
Right, right.
That's the place
where my mentor
brought me to eat last time.
[Ancient Qiang Texts]
[Happiness after Death]
Is there any food?
Sir?
I'll do it.
We got customers.
Order.
Okay, okay.
What would the three of you like to eat?
Give us some specials.
Okay, okay.
Hurry up.
All dishes are served.
You really haven't eaten
anything good, have you?
Sir, is this really Bailejing?
Bailejing, Jinglebai,
call it whatever you like.
Enjoy your meal.
I think everyone here's not all there.
The chief is definitely not here.
Don't eat these either.
Let's discuss
how to find the chief.
I don't know what the chief looks like.
But I can take you to find him.
Follow me.
Mentor.
The wind and waves are strong here.
Is he out of his mind too?
Where are they?
What's wrong with you two?
Well...
Why is there a little chick here?
This chick is quite cute.
This chick is so cute.
Hurry up,
we're almost there!
-Hurry up!
-The food is useful.
Open your mouth.
Follow me!
Mentor.
Do you feel much better?
What's wrong?
Outsiders can't eat
the food of Bailejing.
One bite,
and you're dead.
What do you mean?
It means once you eat it,
there is no turning back.
Only after death can you
become a true Bailejing person.
True Bailejing people!
You won't die.
Everyone has to die!
I'll take you to a doctor.
Let's go.
I won't let you die.
All must die!
Let's go.
Let's go, Zhang Qianjun.
Hang in there.
We'll find a doctor.
Zhang Qianjun.
Mentor.
Hang in there.
Somebody, help!
Please!
Mentor.
So this is Bailejing.
That's right.
This is the familiar feeling.
This is what Bailejing should be like.
Shouldn't Bailejing
be like what we saw just now?
Why did it suddenly change into this?
I have a bold guess.
Is it possible
that it's always been like this?
It's just that the miasma here is toxic.
After outsiders come in,
they will be mind-controlled
by the miasma,
and their behavior will become strange.
Only by eating the local food
can they return to normal
and see the true appearance of Bailejing.
No wonder.
Every time my mentor
brought me to Bailejing,
he made me eat terrible food.
So that was the food of Bailejing.
Little Taoist,
you just remembered
such an important message.
Aren't you a bit too...
Mentor, this outfit looks good on you.
Mainly to avoid unnecessary trouble.
It's better to do as the Romans do.
He'll pay.
Alright.
Sir, you haven't paid yet.
How much is it, Ma'am?
Twenty.
Alright, take a look at something else?
No need, thank you, Ma'am.
Take care.
Why did you make me pay
for the clothes you bought?
What's going on?
Why are you so happy?
You weren't like this at all
when we were outside.
Am I?
It's because of the food here.
The food here makes people happy.
Otherwise, why would it
be called Bailejing?
Fellow folks,
last time we talked about
the patron saint of our Bailejing,
Feikun Balu.
This time, I'll tell you in detail.
This Feikun Balu
is a god of the mountains.
He was born with divine power,
controlling wind, rain,
thunder, and lightning.
He is incredibly brave.
Twenty years ago,
there was once
a notorious Black Bone Demon
running amok in the villages.
The common people suffered unspeakably.
At this time,
Feikun Balu rode the wind
with his divine weapon.
Amidst the sky-shaking roar,
he fought with the demon.
When the divine weapon was brought out,
the Black Bone Demon was no match for him.
It instantly turned into blue smoke
and dissipated.
From then on, Feikun Balu
has protected our Bailejing day and night.
No more demons
dare to set foot in our land.
-Great!
Feikun Balu is just the chief.
It seems that people here
treat him as a god.
What's so good about being a god?
It's better to be a mortal.
Only when a person is dead
will they know how precious
it is to be alive.
This divine weapon of Feikun Balu
fell right here in our Bailejing.
But since it's a divine weapon,
ordinary people definitely can't use it.
Only when it meets its destined owner
can it
unleash its divine power.
The priest is here!
The priest is here.
-The priest is here.
Let's go.
-Let's go.
-Come on.
Great.
Let's go.
Who is that sitting in the sedan?
It's the High Priest of Bailejing.
His name is Su Ya.
Is that a person up there?
No.
It's a corpse.
I heard that the people here
who want to rest in peace
after death or prosper in life
all need his blessing.
Some people want to be high officials.
Some want to be wealthy businessmen.
All of this
relies on him pointing the way.
The life and death of the people here
are all arranged by him.
He can be saved.
High Priest,
is it true?
Can my child really come back to life?
Can he really save him?
-Is he lying?
-Is it true?
He's really brought him back to life!
That's amazing!
The priest is simply our true god!
Thanks to him!
-Hail the priest!
-Brilliant!
-He knows the magic
and never claims credit.
No wonder the people here
love him so much.
Why don't we also go
channel spirits
and ask if there's any news
about the chief?
-Hail the priest!
Who are you?
Shh.
Don't be afraid.
I just want to ask one question.
Do you know Zhang Qiling?
Guards,
arrest him!
Bofu (Thank you).
It's my honor to protect you.
I have a matter to ask you.
I wonder if we could
speak in private.
Honored guest, thank you.
Please follow me inside.
Commander,
there is no road ahead.
Adjutant,
in this situation,
what do you think we should do?
There is only one road to Bailejing.
We have to turn back.
But I'm curious.
Why did you choose a dead-end road?
Go to the front
and set a fire.
-Yes.
Do you know
what I came to Bailejing for?
I'm not interested in what you want.
But I won't help you find
the Zhang family's chief.
You are very smart.
You will find Zhang Qiling for me,
because I will give you
what you need.
Even I don't know
what I want.
You do?
Our eyes
sit on the front of our faces,
so they can look at others.
That's why I can see you clearly,
Zhang Haixia.
However,
eyes are also the most foolish.
They often forget to look at themselves.
Can you see
how I'll eventually kill you?
With all my elites around me,
are you so sure you can kill me?
How will you do it?
Commander,
you don't really think
I came here
just because of your phone call, do you?
Have you ever considered
I might have planned all this
just to be within half a meter of you now,
so I could kill you with my own hands?
Or maybe I don't even need
to do it myself,
and they can kill you for me.
I like you very much.
It's just a pity
that you are not Zhang Qiling.
You won't kill me.
Because right now,
you are still in trouble and confusion.
Are you in pain?
You thought you had made your choice,
but when your mentor
and Zhang Hailou appeared,
you suddenly found yourself in pain again.
Do you know why?
It's your past self haunting you.
If you want me to kill
Zhang Haiqi and Zhang Hailou,
I'll kill you right now.
There is no room for discussion on this.
In that case,
your ending will be terrible.
There is only death waiting for you.
Do you know what it means?
It will be your past self
who kills you.
Actually, you've always been running away
from your past self.
This is ridiculous.
How can one hide from oneself?
It's a pure waste of time.
Remember, if you want to live,
you must defeat your past self.
Look.
There was no path,
so make one yourself.
To live in this world,
there is no retreat—
only forward progress.
Commander.
I'm really glad
I answered your call back then.
Are you going to help me
find Zhang Qiling?
In my own way.
Excellent!
You three,
follow the adjutant
and execute his every order.
Violators will be killed.
Yes.
Commander,
do you trust him that much?
He's very dangerous.
You are not dangerous,
so you are useless.
It's only fun if it's dangerous.
This man
won't stay.
But eventually, he'll come back.
He will clear all obstacles for me,
because
he is my third adjutant.
So once he finishes
doing all the dirty work for me,
his time will be up.
The moment he dies
will mark the success of my grand plan.