Commander, we found an inn ahead.
It's located on the only route
to Bailejing.
We should be able to get information
about Bailejing there.
Adjutant Zhang, go and scout ahead.
Understood.
Coming.
It's so late, and there are still people
coming here to die?
You guys go hide first, quickly.
Coming!
In the dead of night...
Sirs, are you here for a stay?
Sirs.
Officers,
do you want some rooms?
How many people can this place hold?
My little inn
can hold over 30 people.
We'll book the whole place.
The whole place?
There are only 4 of you.
I'm afraid you won't be able to fill it.
Okay, okay.
I'm going to discuss it
with the guests now.
Please sit and wait for a while.
We'll serve you
nice food and wine immediately.
Please take your seats.
Just 4 soldiers.
Let's kill them.
They don't look like Nanqiang warlords.
I think they should be scouts.
If we wipe them out,
no one should find out.
Let's kill them
after they collapse.
Okay.
The Chief just told us
to turn over a new leaf.
How does the saying go?
"Only kill bad people,
not good ones."
Besides,
these soldiers are no pushovers.
But there are knockout drops in the water.
Knockout drops?
Adjutant Zhang,
I heard you used to be
a member of the Southern Archives.
It seems that the two of us
do have quite a bit of fate between us.
I have a very excellent memory.
Captain Chen,
I think we haven't met before, right?
How should I put it?
When I was in Nanyang,
I killed all the people in your Archives.
And you killed all my men
in our Xiaojiang camp.
I'm wondering
if this is also a kind
of special destiny.
The people of the Southern Archives
acted very covertly.
They were just like mice,
hard to find
and kill.
Therefore,
killing them
gave me a greater sense of achievement.
Why don't you tell me more about
how you killed them?
If you really want to hear about it,
I'll tell you.
I
have
a little hobby.
I like
to collect pretty human skin.
I especially like the exquisite, tattooed
human skin of the staff
from your Archives.
Every time I caught them,
I used a knife
to cut a cross
on the top of their heads.
And then,
I slowly poured
mercury in,
so their blood
would help the mercury
spread all over their bodies.
At this step,
I could listen to their screams
while watching their skin and muscles
separate naturally.
When the time was about right,
I peeled off their skin
little by little,
starting from the top of their heads.
There was a requirement
in this.
After the skin was peeled off,
the person
must still be alive.
So here comes the question.
Adjutant Zhang,
I wonder if you also have
any beautiful tattoos on your body.
Kill him.
I wonder if you felt guilty
when you peeled off the skin.
Did you feel that killing a person was
the same as killing a pig?
Some people have physiological reactions
when they kill humans.
Do you have any?
Come out.
I've been immune
to poisons and drugs since I was little.
Your drugs
can't work on me.
What...
[Archives: The Nanyang Mystery]
[Episode 24]
Sister! Sister!
Sister!
Sister...
Chief,
something went wrong at the inn.
Choose how you want to die,
and I will make that happen.
Hurry!
Everyone, pull back into the fortress!
The Phoenix Fortress is on fire?
Everyone, find a way
to shake off the soldiers immediately
and retreat into the secret passage.
Commander,
we can't find the bandits.
There's a secret passage here.
I've figured out its approximate location.
I'll draw the map for you.
Come out!
You guys!
Get down.
Get down!
Don't move!
Hurry up!
Everyone in the secret passage, come out!
Otherwise,
I won't leave any of them alive!
Let them go!
Little girl,
are you the Chief?
I am the Chief!
Look at her.
You all should learn from her.
She's a mere chief of a fortress
and a little girl,
yet she's so insightful.
She knew that if she shot me dead,
everyone in her fortress would get killed.
Then you must understand this logic.
Killing is very simple.
But there are many issues that
matter much more than killing.
I don't want it to end up like this.
Your men killed my men first.
This is not like Nanqiang's way
of treating guests.
I will ask you a question.
If you answer me,
you can save the lives
of everyone in your fortress.
So you'd better answer me carefully.
Don't listen to his crap, Chief!
Son...
Bro!
What should we do?
Son...
My son...
What is your question?
Good.
Here's my question. There is a man
in a mask
who is super good at fighting,
like seriously
not even human-level good.
Do you know his whereabouts?
I haven't seen anyone like this.
My intuition is very accurate.
She
didn't lie.
So it's fine now.
It's fine.
You may leave.
I mean, take the people
of your fortress and leave.
I just need
to borrow this fortress, okay?
Go!
I'll kill you!
Commander.
You didn't keep your word.
What's the difference
between you and those bandits?
There's no difference.
Well, there is one thing.
It's that I am smarter than them.
You see, if I were her just now,
I would have definitely grabbed the gun
and shot me.
With the leaderless enemy,
at least there would be a glimmer of hope.
Look, now they've fallen into my hands,
and they're done for.
Look at our soldiers
and their men.
There's absolutely no difference.
Aren't they just a bunch of lunatics?
Dangle a bit of temptation
in front of anyone,
and they will risk their lives for you.
That's why
we must
maintain their brutal animal nature
like this
and offer temptation at the right time
to satisfy them.
I am good at this sort of thing,
so
I can become a dominant figure
in these troubled times.
I think today is
the perfect time
to let their animal nature
run free.
This is my reason for killing.
What's your reason for killing?
So brutal.
Mo Yungao.
Why did he also come to Nanqiang?
Take the secret passage.
Behave yourself!
Don't move!
They are the ones at fault,
not you.
You must live.
You bastard!
Brother...
Brother!
Hurry up.
It's in the room ahead.
Keep up, quickly!
-Go!
Hurry up!
Quickly!
Shrimpie...
Fate brings people together
no matter the distance.
It should be this way.
I want to go back.
Going back now is a suicide act.
Where there's life,
there's hope.
If we don't have a chance now,
will we have one in the future?
Xiao'er is dead.
Great Golden Blade is dead.
Everyone is dead.
You run first. We'll cover the rear.
Run now.
You guys go.
Take care, sister.
See you in Bailejing.
Go quickly.
This way.
Let's go.
It's the sign of the Archives.
"When you think there's no way out,
a mighty army will come to help."
This is what you mentioned,
the Zhang family in Nanqiang?
It seems
that there are quite a lot of them.
Let's get out of here first.
Okay.
There's nowhere to go.
Smoke.
You're craving a smoke at the moment?
Wait a minute!
You didn't even say a word,
yet you chased us this far.
You all have good stamina, huh?
There's no way out anyway.
There's no need to rush it.
Take your breath.
I will perform
a show for you guys!
You people from the Zhang family
are quite interesting.
But sometimes you are way too confident
in your capabilities.
In this situation,
you are still struggling?
As the old saying goes,
nothing ventured,
nothing gained!
A flare shot into the sky
summons a mighty army to come.
Who summoned me?
The Zhang family's Southern Archives!
Then who are you guys?
Why is it just you?
Where is the "mighty army"
of the Zhang family?
It's me.
I am
Zhang Qianjunwanma (means mighty army).
Is the Zhang family
so unreliable in Bailejing?
You'll get us all killed!
I'm the one
who's going to be killed because of you.
If I had known
it'd summon such a useless guy to come,
we wouldn't have bothered
wasting so much time there.
Are you done talking?
Will you ever stop?
It's your first time in Bailejing.
As a local member of the Zhang family,
I must fulfill my duty as a host.
Take it easy, please.
Take this!
Go after them!
Go that way!
You're not good at fighting,
but you sure can run.
Come with me.
They won't catch us for sure.
What is this place?
This is where my mentor and I live.
It's also where the Zhang family is
stationed in Nanqiang.
Your mentor?
Little Taoist,
what was that amazing sorcery
you just used?
It's divine magic.
I've been in this temple
with my mentor since I was a child,
practicing the Five Ghosts Delivery.
I've already mastered it thoroughly.
Divine magic?
Does our Zhang family
have this secret technique?
It's just a trick.
This Little Taoist conjured a fire dragon
just in order to distract the enemy.
But he was so fast
that even you didn't notice.
What do you know?
The Five Ghosts Delivery
can move everything in this world.
As long as I want to,
I can even move
this temple away overnight.
Zhang Qianzhang
taught you all this, right?
You know my mentor?
Who on earth are you?
This is
the former Director
of our Southern Archives,
Zhang Haiqi.
My mentor's wife...