[NOA] Every Filipino kid
knows it.
- You don't talk back.
- [SOBS]
Nobody told me
that's how you trip
for the rest of your life.
[WOMAN] Oh, dear.
You still don't know
how to tie your own shoes?
Are you expecting me
to do it for you?
Answer me, Noa.
Parents didn't teach
you any manners, huh?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC SWELLS]
What did you say to her?!
- I-I told-- [STAMMERS]
- Just what?!
She'll be a nurse one day!
And you, still bullying children
with Dunkaroos frosting
on your fingers.
[SIGHS]
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOBS QUIETLY, SNIFFLES]
Speak up for yourself.
I can't.
I know...
I taught you
to listen to the elderly.
But she's not old!
She's still a child
with diabetes.
[GENTLE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SQUEAKS]
What are you? Seven?
Tess didn't teach you
how to tie your shoe?
Tess?
I'm just kidding.
Uh, don't haunt me.
[CHUCKLES WRYLY]
I'm just kidding.
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
"Tongue Tied"
[NOA] Good morning!
I brought donuts.
Please, take two.
It's that kind of day.
[CHUCKLES]
Oh, that's really
sweet of you. Thanks.
Yes! Donuts!
As if my arteries
aren't inflamed enough.
[GROANS]
Morning pass downs are the most
important part of leadership.
It's how you set
the tone for the day.
So yeah, positive vibes only.
Even when everything's on fire.
Good morning, Ward Five!
Millie?
- Coffee.
- Here, boss.
Still at your required temp.
Oh, thank you.
He's annoying. So controlling.
He wants everything
to be his way.
Fix your posture.
You look exhausted.
Nia, it's come to the
hospital's attention that
too many people are
speaking in another language.
Look, he doesn't even
know your name. Geez!
Shh!
[CHUCKLES]
You're new.
I'm your boss.
Try not making me regret that.
Oh, okay. Is Jane--
Oh, no, no. Not available.
You get to deal
with me directly, Nisa.
Noa.
That's what I said.
Oh, this is Millie.
She's the head of HR.
So nice to meet you both.
Announcement, everyone.
Announcement!
[CHUCKLES]
Starting today, you are
only allowed to speak English
while on the premises.
We're in America.
Our patients need
to feel comfortable
with the lingo around here.
(In Spanish) This guy wants me
to stop speaking Spanish?!
He can go to hell!
Anyone caught
breaking the rules
will be subject
to disciplinary action.
Anyone breaking the rules.
Oh, right.
[SNAPS FINGERS]
[SHOE SQUEAKS]
[NOA GRUNTS]
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
So much for positive vibes.
[HUFFS]
Atzin!
Where are you?
[GROANS]
You're not fair!
And your ghost rules
don't make any sense!
Sometimes I can move things.
Sometimes I can't.
What's the deal with that?!
I haven't taken human form
in 30 centuries.
Are you listening to me?
You know what?
Just go to heaven
where you're supposed to go.
And I won't bother her again.
I promise.
Maybe you were white
in your past life, huh?
That's why this is okay for you.
[SNICKERS]
Well, I'm neither. And I'm all.
I'm not attached to any form.
I'm not attached to any race.
But I'm Filipino now.
Fake Filipino!
Irrelevant. Rules are rules.
Watch me.
I'll fix this and
I'll stop this madness.
Oh my god!
Uhm...
Dude, maybe you want to
save some for the rest of us?
Oh my god!
He's one of those idiots
who can eat whatever
they want and not get fat!
[HIGH-PITCHED TONE]
My bad.
I just came to fix the intercom.
[EXHALES]
You people let him die!
He was fine last week!
Ma'am, I understand
your frustration.
- What you have to understand--
- Uhm, Jane! Excuse me!
- Give me one second.
- No! No! No!
We're not done here.
No, I'm not leaving.
- Please, come back here.
- I'm not really leaving.
- I'll be right back.
- Oh my god!
What kind of hospital is this?
You are not here to argue
that stupid language rule.
- No?
- Mh-mm.
I'm not dealing with that today.
...Kind of hospital.
For how long are you
going to keep us waiting here?
- One more second.
- Please come back.
[DOOR CLOSES]
Just go down to Ward One.
They seem to be doing
everything right.
- Okay. Good talk.
- Okay, uhm...
He had a condition for a while.
He just didn't tell his family.
I'm sure he feels
really bad about it.
- How did you know--
- [DOOR OPENS]
Excuse me? For how long
are you going to keep us?
- Please stop blowing us off.
- I have something to tell you.
[DOOR CLOSES]
Infective endocarditis
is a rare but serious infection
of the heart lining and valves.
Usually caused by
Staph aureus or fungi.
And it can kill you?
The bacteria stick
to the endocardium,
form vegetations which lead
to multi-organ failure.
And it can kill you?
Okay, you know what? I'm just
going to read super fast
because you look, like,
really bored right now.
Our management is surgical
incision of the infected valve
with prosthetic replacement.
Which could also kill you.
Yeah.
Do you have any questions?
I just really want to
get the verbiage right
so I don't get written up
or whatever.
Which would also, like, kill me.
Hey lady, do you understand?
What are you trying to say?!
I don't understand
a single word!
Go get a translator!
I don't understand your English,
and you don't understand me.
You just keep talking
and I don't understand
what you're trying to say!
Does your brain work?!
Oh boy.
Don't do it.
The Ward One girls
are evil incarnate.
[SIGHS]
Do you hear that?
I don't hear anything.
Exactly. Zero noise.
No dust.
It even smells like
sampaguitas in here.
["IT'S TOOTSIE"
BY TOOTSIE GUEVARA PLAYING]
["IT'S TOOTSIE" CONTINUES]
Oh, hello!
Oh, my bad.
Ew. I think she's one of them.
Totally.
Oh, Ward Five. So cute.
Can I help you with something?
Um...
Nope. I think I'm good.
Okay, bye!
[TESS]
See? You don't listen.
(In Tagalog)
That stubborn attitude of yours,
you didn't inherit it from me.
(In English) I know, I know.
We're not happy
about the new rule.
[PAPER CRUMPLING]
But I have a surprise
for everyone
that I think will
cheer everyone up.
Here we have a language jar!
Oh, pretty.
What is it?
Let me guess.
If we slip, we have to pay.
Tacky.
It's so I don't have to
write anyone up.
Yay, we can finally go on a
trip to Nickelodeon Studios.
Oh, Ros, that place closed
like 15 years ago.
So did your straight phase?
I told you, those photos
are for fitness inspiration.
[JAR CLINKS]
Atzin, what are you doing?
(In Spanish)
Stupid motherf#$%!
Now I can only speak English,
in a hospital
with these damn patients
from all different countries!
(In English) Wait! Wait, Atzin!
It's only 10 cents a word.
Come back here.
[DOOR SLAMS]
Oh, I get it.
It's like a swear jar.
[CHUCKLES]
[SNICKERS]
Yes!
It'll triple our profits.
Write that down.
Yes, profits.
What are you doing?
(In Tagalog) He'll know
what a real haunting is.
You want to
bully my daughter?
[WIND GUSHING]
- [SCREAMING]
- [ELECTRIC CRACKLE]
[SCREAMING]
(In English)
How do we feel...
[SCREAMING]
...about cutting overtime pay?
Hmm...
Hold on one second.
Ugh, old wiring.
- Call maintenance.
- Anyway...
I'm sorry, I have to
cut my break now.
HIPAA ruins everything.
Gotta go.
Oh, hi, sir.
My name is Camille.
I know I may look
familiar to you.
She used to be
a Pinay celebrity.
And this is Atzin.
I asked them to help because
I really need you to sign off
on the surgery because, like,
the infection could kill you.
(In Dari) Hey girl,
you came last week.
I told you I don’t want
to have the operation.
In the name of God,
please leave me alone.
(In Spanish)
Why are these people idiots?
He’s not even speaking Spanish!
You're wasting my time.
(In English)
Please speak to my wife.
So, it's not Spanish.
- Okay, yeah, I did talk to her.
- Please.
And she said she, like,
didn't want to talk to you
because you're, like,
a bad, corrupt, evil person.
Okay, okay, okay, fine, fine.
I heard it.
Why are you making me
work on my break?
My followers are waiting for me.
Didn't you spend
some time in Dubai?
Yeah, for a movie for
three months in 1991.
I don't understand.
Please, no surgery. Please.
No surgery.
So sorry, sir.
Excuse her.
Her IQ tends to match
the temperature up there.
It's freezing.
But he needs the surgery!
He could die.
Come here.
- [LAUGHTER]
- [COINS CLINK]
(In Bisaya)
She doesn't know how to manage!
[LAUGHING, CHATTERING]
Okay, my turn!
[LAUGHS]
I said my turn!
Sorry.
[CHUCKLES, CLEARS THROAT]
(In Pig Latin)
Noa is actually pretty cool.
(In English)
That's Pig Latin.
[ROS] Yeah, but you have
to say something bad.
Oh, you are a fellow
Pig Latin speaker.
Well, I just, you know,
said that because, um...
You know what, Ros?
I'll give you 10 dollars
if you say a swear word
in Tagalog right now.
[ROSS SCOFFS, LAUGHS]
(In Tagalog)
What the--
[LIGHT SWITCH CLICKING]
[ROS STUTTERING]
(In English) P-Put this away.
It's not even funny.
Come on, everyone.
Back to work.
And that is how
you shut them up.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Nora, it's come to our attention
that the nurses on this floor
aren't following the rules.
Boss, I really need your help.
(In Tagalog)
Tell him, "Kiss my ass."
(In English) Guys,
I think we have enough money
to buy Red Ribbon
for the year.
Sir, I assure you,
we're doing every--
(In Tagalog)
It's so dirty!
Tess, don't haunt me, okay?
(In English)
Oh, those are from surgery.
- If he refuses...
- Don't worry.
I brought reinforcements.
Ward One here, everyone.
I heard we're playing
games here today.
I'll gut them like a fish.
[GIGGLES]
- Seriously.
- No, that won't be necessary.
I just need Narnia here to
write up that EVS loudmouth.
Don't worry, everyone.
This isn't some
violent takeover.
[WHISPERS]
Unless you want it to be.
Noa, what are those
delulu-holes doing here?
So, I really need your help.
- I really need your help.
- (In Tagalog) Speak up!
Show him who's boss!
Fight back!
(In English)
Everyone!
Rules are rules!
Ros.
Come with me.
You will be getting a write-up.
Excuse me?
- Never in my 20 years of...
- As Mr. Alderman says,
you will be getting a write-up.
[BUZZING]
[SIGHS SHARPLY]
Tess, Tess, I hope you're proud
of your daughter.
(In Tagalog)
So obedient!
(In English) I'm not.
[KNOCKING]
DonDon, we're busy.
I know, I know, but you
said, like, patients first.
And, oh, no, not another
preventable death.
[GRUNTS]
Why are you going?
Curious.
You know, I think your
daughter is about to quit.
(In Tagalog) You know,
you're becoming human.
You're such a gossip!
(In English) Mr. Hamid, this
procedure will save your life.
(In Dari) I think
I need to rest a little
and not talk
to anyone for a while.
(In Tagalog)
Get rid of him. He's a gossip.
(In English)
Please, I can't focus!
But I didn't say anything.
Or at least, I think I didn't.
I'm, like, literally, totally
holding my breath right now.
Sorry, what is it, Grim?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I just wanted to see if
you needed some help.
Thanks, but I don't think
you speak his language.
Actually, I...
Wait, I totally misjudged you.
I thought you were Filipino.
You know,
maybe we can make a deal.
I'm sorry?
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
Nothing. I just...
don't understand why
everyone's so afraid of death.
Wait, did you just like,
tell him to die?
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
Uh, I'll see myself out.
[WHOOSH SFX]
Such a shame.
Someone felt the need
to report Ward Five.
You! Of course, it was you!
- [GRIM GROANING]
- [GASPS]
Finally, I figured it out.
My mood swings are useful
for something.
- [CHUCKLES]
- That hurt!
I know, you're right.
You can make her life
a living hell.
Are you proud of yourself?
Why? Do you think she can
do this forever?
She's in a ward, full of ghosts,
full of sick people.
Her plate's already full, right?
[GRIM SCOFFS]
I feel sorry for her.
I wanted to help her patient,
but I don't feel
like it anymore.
Fine!
[TESS] Help her.
And I promise,
I will cross over.
[GRIM EXHALES SHARPLY]
It's been a couple of centuries
since I spoke his language.
Why do we have to
be funny all the time?
Sorry, I meant couple of years
since I spoke Dari.
I can help explain.
(In Arabic) Peace be upon you.
(In Arabic) And upon you
be peace.
(In Dari) Look into
my eyes, Mr. Hamid.
Hell is no joke.
If you die now,
do you know where you’ll go?
Okay, okay, I'll do the surgery!
[HAMID] I'll do the surgery.
You ate that!
That was like so hot.
Wow, thank you.
That was...
Excuse me.
What are you thinking, dear?
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[NOA] I got it, Mom.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
Mr. Alderman, this stops now.
Excuse me?
I used to think speaking
perfect English
meant that you were smart.
But today, a man chose death
because he couldn't
understand us!
Rules are rules.
That rule, Mr. Alderman,
is not ethical.
People don't come
in one language.
And we speak these languages
because our patients do.
Because their families do.
Because our moms do.
And we can't erase that.
Not now. Not ever!
I'm with Noa on this.
It doesn't matter what you speak
as long as you're a good person.
Wait, you speak English?
Since when?
Ugh.
Millie!
Coming!
[SLOW CLAP]
[APPLAUSE]
[CHEERING]
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
[NOA SIGHS]
[PAPER RIPPING]
You certainly put on
a show today.
[NOA] Oh, no.
Took me a minute.
But I had legal go through
all those damn rules.
Turns out, they can't tell us
they can't tell us what language
we can speak inside these walls.
So, I'm not fired?
Nope. Not yet.
But that doesn't mean you didn't
put a target on your back.
It's a good thing you
have me protecting it.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
You people keep clutching
at air like it'll hold you back.
Oh, come on, please. Admit it.
You can see the goodness
in her heart.
That's why you can't stop
yourself from helping her.
She got it from her mom.
[GRIM CHUCKLES]
Are you ready?
Ready for what?
Huh?
Didn't you say that if
I helped her, you'd move on?
I didn't say when.
So, technically, I didn't lie.
Okay, so you really want
to level up this game?
Okay, fine-- Hey!
Thought so.
You do realize that
I have a scythe right?
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
[MELLOW MUSIC CONTINUES]