(Respect copyright)
♪Memories hold you back
from fulfilling your dreams♪
♪Only by moving forward
can you find reunion♪
♪Endings only mark new routes♪
♪It's all part of the scenery♪
♪To the horizon's call♪
♪Your journey hasn't started♪
♪Towards mountains,
chase the stars bright♪
♪Let time embrace you
and wash away the past♪
♪Put every twist behind you♪
♪Drift leisurely through time♪
♪Make headway against the wind♪
♪Let mountains bow to your pace♪
♪Rush towards a life without regret♪
♪Let your nature burst free♪
=The First Jasmine=
=Episode 25=
(The Office)
Get the carriage. We'll go back.
Yes.
♪Fortunately, the wounds
the world gave me♪
♪Will be romantic in your eyes♪
♪I came alone♪
♪But with you, all is worthwhile♪
♪We've found a place to belong♪
♪Who hasn't come coated in frost♪
♪But that won't stop us
from filling our home with sunlight♪
♪Through heat and cold♪
♪No one disturbs our peace♪
♪Our shadows have overlapped♪
♪In the vast world,
longing only for some moonlight♪
♪Seeking an ordinary life♪
♪To be together side by side♪
♪You tugged at my heartstrings♪
♪Our wonderful times are filled♪
♪With poetic chapters♪
♪From all the world,
we share a cup of tea♪
♪Small as the fragrance of a flower♪
♪To share it with you♪
♪The candlelight is flickered
by the wind♪
♪In spite of the storm♪
You're back.
You're awake?
You slept so soundly.
You must be tired today.
I had a long dream.
It felt like I couldn't wake up.
What is it about?
Can't recall clearly.
It's late now. Have you eaten?
I'm not hungry.
But I could eat some.
I'll let them prepare food.
No need. I have prepared some.
♪Things change, but you're with me♪
I've been craving
roasted meat for so long.
There were no cows or sheep
on the mountain. I could rarely eat meat.
So I made up my mind that
if I could come down the mountain,
I would treat myself to a great feast
and satisfy my cravings.
I recall this today,
so I had Qingyu buy some fresh lamb.
It's perfect for roasting.
Li, I must leave the capital tomorrow.
Why?
Qin Cang was rescued.
He provided some valuable clues.
For how many days?
Including travel time,
probably four or five days.
Is it dangerous?
Not really. With a large retinue,
I think nothing would go wrong.
Rest assured.
Then I'll prepare five days of poultice.
Remember, apply the poultice
to your legs every day. Don't skip it.
What's the point of telling you?
I should go to Jin.
Don't rush.
It's so late. Let's do it tomorrow.
Let's eat first.
When you're away, you must be careful.
Don't stand for too long, run or jump.
Don't engage in fights.
And don't act recklessly again.
Done, try it.
The lamb was marinated
in honey and rice wine.
It tastes tender and flavorful.
Why do you keep staring at me
instead of eating?
You're beautiful.
Smooth talker.
Am I more beautiful than Lady Su?
You can't compare like that.
Perhaps some see
Lady Su as quite beautiful,
but to me,
you are the woman
who no one can match in this world.
Li, thank you for coming into my life.
You're quite a smooth talker.
Want to rank top in some exams?
Then have I ranked top in your exams?
Yes. You won the highest honors.
Eat it.
A celestial phenomenon as a warning?
These pedantic scholars
got scared out of their wits
by a mere solar eclipse.
I asked you to read memorials.
What made you so cross?
Mother, look what they wrote.
A celestial anomaly occurred yesterday.
Yet today, these ministers acted
like lunatics, nothing's off-limits.
They even dared submit
such memorials to me.
Calm down. Finish reading them first.
Where's the Empress Dowager?
Your Highness,
Her Majesty went to the Imperial Study.
Please wait here for a moment.
Got it.
(Xiankun Miscellany)
Master Xiankun once said
you are my fortune goddess.
We share the same fate and fortune.
Your well-being ensures mine.
After all these years,
you still believe him that firmly?
Of course, I do.
You also told me that Master Xiankun
possesses true talents.
I believe both of you.
Oh, this is the Xiankun Miscellany
I have newly compiled.
The first volume has been completed.
So I brought it to you for review first.
Mother, aren't you angry?
Ancestors interpreted heaven's will
with tortoise shells.
Then, they communicated
with spirits through sorcery.
Later, they predicted
fortune or doom using omens.
Throughout every dynasty, people have used
celestial phenomena for their purposes.
Even our founding emperor once used
the saying of Mars staying at Antares
to execute Chancellor Guo.
Celestial phenomena
are like a chessboard.
The pieces become formidable weapons
for whoever controls them.
Do you understand now?
I see now.
Veteran ministers like Chen Jingzhi
want to use mourning rites to warn you off,
so they can safeguard
their entrenched interests.
Wang Ke manipulates celestial phenomena
to undermine your authority,
hoping to gain a reputation
as an outspoken advisor.
Zheng Yuan and Feng Zhao'an
cite judicial unfairness as a pretext
to exonerate their relatives
and friends who are imprisoned.
Everyone has their own agenda,
so public power becomes their tool
for private gain.
I see now. I shouldn't be mad at them.
Instead, I should learn
how to wield this weapon myself.
Has the Dowager Consort visited?
Yes, Your Majesty.
Her Highness came earlier.
I told her you're at the Imperial Study
and asked her to wait.
But she sat in the hall for a moment
and then left in silence.
(Xiankun Miscellany)
(Qingfeng Mingyue Tower)
When we reach the peak tomorrow,
we'll pitch tents
in a wind-sheltered spot.
Then we'll set a campfire and grill.
I have to impress her.
Right.
I must bring this thick wool blanket.
The nights at the mountain peak
are chilly. If we catch a cold,
it would ruin our sunrise viewing plan
the next day.
Imagine this.
Viewing sunrise from the peak,
how spectacular!
Don't forget this, azure-glazed tea set.
Brewing fresh tea
with mountain spring water
while overlooking the capital of Chu.
What a pleasure!
It's indeed a pleasure.
Pack them all up.
Yes, my lord.
Perfect!
Your Highness.
You're finally back?
Yes.
Since you're back,
lie low and avoid further trouble.
Yes, Your Highness.
(Prison)
How's the wound?
The stab wound is extremely deep.
The physician said it's so close
to his vital pulse, extremely perilous.
He's lucky to be alive.
Even tigers don't harm their cubs.
Marquis Muyang is really ruthless.
Qin Cang is vital. You must save him.
Yes.
Chen Longxiang
is Marquis Muyang's confidante.
Five years ago, out of drunken rage,
he killed seven, including
his wife, child, and mother-in-law.
Then he was sentenced
to be beheaded in public.
Yet he was switched with a double
by Marquis Muyang.
And he's been hiding in Huaixi ever since,
managing weaponry smuggling.
Your Highness, do you think it's true?
We'll know once we catch him.
Then, when will you set off?
Prefect, everything's ready.
We can set off at any time.
Let's set off now.
Guard him vigilantly.
Yes.
This volume was finally returned.
From Year 3 of Jinghe to Year 9 of Jinghe,
Master Xiankun secluded himself
at Qingyang Mountain for cultivation.
He never stepped
beyond the gate during that period.
Records are crystal clear on it.
What's the doubtful point?
Nonsense!
I witnessed it myself.
In the autumn of Year 8 of Jinghe,
in the west of Jinling City,
at Yanyu Pavilion,
a Chongyang Poetry Gathering was held.
And poets crammed the pavilion.
Master Xiankun was one of them.
He challenged poets
to compose on the hibiscus theme.
When the wine was at its peak,
he was inspired to compose poems,
chanting repeatedly
and praising hibiscuses.
Under the bright moon,
ask not where I belong.
I only gather beneath the hibiscuses.
If only the hibiscuses caught my sight,
I would gladly stay by the water
appreciating them.
The world praises
the early bloom of the plum.
Yet I say, the hibiscuses
seep deep into my bones.
This poem earned
thunderous applause back then.
Master Xiankun...
(Furong... Her Majesty...)
[*"Furong" means "Hibiscus" in Chinese]
Get back to work.
Your Highness.
Greetings, Your Highness.
What brings you here, Princess Ding?
My niece likes to visit me
whenever she's available.
Upon hearing you're
compiling star scriptures,
she got so excited
and insisted on coming.
You make it sound like
I'm a three-year-old.
(Stellar record)
Is this the Meteor Shower
in Summer Night?
The meteor shower
from Year 4 of the Xide Era?
Fixed stars vanished, and meteors
rained down across the night sky.
I saw it too while on Lishan Mountain.
You also have some knowledge
of celestial phenomena?
Celestial phenomena are profound
and unfathomable.
Yet all things have patterns to follow.
By following their patterns,
things far beyond reach
can become within reach.
Compiling texts here, you must be quite
knowledgeable about celestial phenomena.
I merely inherited
the legacy of a friend.
Master Xiankun is a true polymath.
It's said that he couldn't bear to see
the great drought in Nanyi years ago,
and then he painted a dragon.
Once he finished,
a dragon soared to the skies,
and the rain poured down,
breaking the great drought in Nanyi
and saving countless lives.
You were present that day.
You must have witnessed it, right?
Master Xiankun's talent
was utterly compelling.
To be honest, regarding
the technique Master Xiankun
used to summon rainfall
through painting a dragon
with his marvelous brushwork,
I know a little about it.
I wonder if you want
to see me demonstrate it.
Sure.
I would like to see if that technique
can be reproduced today.
Today's celestial phenomenon
is perfect for that technique.
The brush and ink are ready.
The paper and brush are fine,
but I have to use my own ink.
Done now?
One step left.
It's gone! The dragon vanished!
The dragon...
It's raining.
(How could there be
so many coincidences?)
There are even bigger coincidences.
Lishan Academy compiled
historical records spanning millennia.
If you read them, you'd know
that given a long enough time span,
the strangest coincidences
become possible.
Celestial phenomena are profound
and unfathomable.
Yet all things have patterns to follow.
By following their patterns,
(things far beyond reach
can become within reach.)
Uncle Wenshen, I'm sorry.
Proving Master Xiankun was just a charlatan
who exploited celestial phenomena,
what good is it for you?
Dowager Consort Qin has been loyal
to the Empress Dowager
since entering the palace.
It was largely because of Xiankun.
Who does Xiankun work for?
What does that have to do
with the edict you want?
Even if Dowager Consort knows,
she'd only go to Empress Dowager.
She won't.
Did those two book restorers
talk about Furong as you said?
How did you figure it out?
Did you forget? The Empress Dowager
also hails from Lishan Mountain.
The only person who can help her
settle this score now is me.
She may not trust you.
But she's become suspicious.
For a clever person, that's sufficient.
Ye Li.
Do you know why your father
could never truly love your mom?
Because your mom
was too clever, just like you.
That's because my father
didn't deserve her.
Why do you think like that?
No wonder you are still not married.
What about Prince Ding?
If he learns the truth about the edict,
how will he think of you?
My mom wanted to help General Xiuwen.
At that time, Grandfather
had come down the mountain.
They planned to present
the edict in the court
to testify for General Xiuwen
and the Heiyun Cavalry.
You didn't witness what happened
to Prince Ding's Mansion.
Some things can't be justified just
by bringing out the facts and reasons.
Li, I am indeed unmarried.
But in this world,
not many lovers can truly get together.
Shouldn't you cherish what you have?
Listen to me.
Let the bygones be bygones.
Stop chasing after the truth.
I promised General Xiuwen
and my mom
to clear the name
of Prince Ding's Mansion.
I observed
the celestial phenomenon yesterday
and predicted that the sun
would shine today.
But I didn't expect sunshine and rain
to occur simultaneously.
I had a meticulous plan.
What was your plan?
My plan was that
we'd reach the peak before dusk.
You like Golden-Scaled Bloom, right?
A flower grower down the mountain
grows it very well.
And I bought his field.
How glorious and beautiful
it would be under the setting sun!
But it got ruined
by this wretched weather!
But this scene also has a unique charm.
Yun, don't try to cheer me up.
Here. Try my Feng family's
secret barbecue.
Delicious! Better than what I had
at the Northern Frontier.
See?
I might be rotten at weather prediction,
but I am good at barbecue.
When it comes to cooking, no one
in the capital of Chu can beat me.
What's your secret recipe?
I can't tell you.
I plan to pass this secret recipe
down to my children.
You've worked so hard
on your culinary skills.
Is it because we suffered from hunger
in the Northern Frontier?
To be honest, it really
has something to do with you.
You said that having a small shop
capable of sustaining a life,
a happy marriage,
and a harmonious family,
makes the best life.
I thought what you said
made perfect sense.
Your Feng family owns
a huge family business.
Yet you're content just running
Qingfeng Mingyue Tower?
Of course.
With food and drink,
I could live a carefree life.
Why can't I just live like that?
If any lady could marry you,
it would be her blessing.
To be honest,
over the years,
I've been helping an old friend
manage various mundane affairs.
Now, his old illness is cured,
and he's found a good wife.
It's time for me
to consider my own marriage.
If you know of any suitable ladies,
you can introduce me.
Perfect. I have a younger sister.
Her temperament is similar to mine,
and so are her looks.
Great! Glad to hear that!
However...
What?
She's been married once.
Back then, for profit,
our elders forced her to marry
an abusive old guy.
She nearly lost her life.
Later, unable to bear the humiliation,
she managed to escape.
And then?
Then, an unexpected event occurred,
and that old man died.
I mean your sister.
She had escaped,
but did her heart truly escape?
Does she still believe
someone will treat her sincerely?
Well, may I have the honor
of meeting her?
You wouldn't mind?
Mind what?
Her past.
Remember.
No wind or snow can cloud the sincerity.
Alright. I'll let you two meet
in seven days, at the Shen hour.
Under the old elm tree
outside the Confucius Temple,
I'll wait for you there with
the blooming Golden-Scaled Bloom.
Me?
Makes no difference.
It's settled.
See you there.
Come!
Come on!
Come and dance!
(Auspicious)
(Yuncha Posthouse)
(The Grocery Shop)
Rouge and powders!
Three wen.
What a bargain!
Family recipe liniment!
What would you like to buy?
Three qian of Falling Star of Dubhe.
Not enough Falling Star,
will Waning Moon suffice?
The deep pool mirrors all,
star and moon share their light.
This way, please.
Here.
(Han Mingyue)
You're here.
You've lost weight.
How is His Highness?
Everything goes well.
We only await the moment.
And you?
When have I ever delayed
His Highness's plan?
I'm asking how you've been recently.
I'm fine.
But I'm not.
You've been staying in
Prince Ding's Mansion lately,
seeing your old sweetheart every day.
It's rare for me to see you once.
He is my enemy.
I came here
not to listen to your nonsense.
What do we do next?
Next, we must stir up conflict
between Dachu and Cangbei.
I've already arranged everything.
From Imperial West Street
to Taiping Ward...
Why did you come to see me today?
You look so pale.
Why do you keep silent? What happened?
Nothing. I just haven't been
sleeping well these past few days.
Why?
That day on the street,
I witnessed a solar eclipse
with my own eyes.
I heard commoners gossiping.
They were saying
the solar eclipse brings great disaster.
This is a very bad omen
and an inauspicious sign.
I feel so worried
and couldn't stay composed.
Just nonsense.
That's just a solar eclipse,
a common celestial phenomenon.
Don't take those superstitious tales
from ignorant folks to heart.
In his Records of Mystical Signs and Omens,
Master Xiankun wrote clearly:
"A solar eclipse
foretells war and disaster,
shaking the very foundation
of the empire."
How could I not worry about you?
Even if disaster strikes,
I won't let you bear it.
Even if the earth collapses,
I'd always protect you.
You will definitely enjoy
a prosperous and peaceful life.
I have been truly blessed in this life.
In my early years,
my father shielded me.
Then I had the fortune to enter the palace
and enjoy the late Emperor's favor.
The only time I nearly lost my life
was that year during the plague.
The late Empress abandoned me
in the Western Courtyard,
with no doctors or medicine,
wanting me to rot away in silence.
When I was in such a situation,
Master Xiankun came to help me.
Then I met you.
And I feared no danger anymore.
You always offer me advice
and protect me.
Do you know?
Actually, after I first introduced
Master Xiankun to you,
he cast a divination for me.
He said that as long as I stayed
by your side, never leaving you,
then I could enjoy a lifetime
of peace and prosperity.
We're so close like sisters.
Why mention this?
Back then, the late Empress caused us
trouble and oppressed us every day.
We really had a tough time.
But looking back now,
I quite miss those days
amidst danger and oppression.
Let the past stay in the past.
Now, the nation is at peace.
This is the present,
and also the future.
It has been so long since anyone
called me by my childhood name.
What about you?
Me too. No one has called me that
in a very long time.
What's your childhood name?
I'll call you that if you want.
My childhood name is Furong.
It sounds lovely.
(Vast as the Earth)
(Look at these two flowers.
Do they look like us?)
They really do.
Rest assured.
I'll stay by your side
for this lifetime.
In this deep palace,
there are very few people I can trust.
We should support each other,
never doubting one another.
(Vast as the Earth)
(Xu Wanzhou refuses
to hand over that edict.)
The Empress Dowager has sent
Marquis Muyang to coerce the Ye Mansion.
You have to think of a way
to obtain that edict.
If you manage to obtain that edict,
hide it well and never tell
the Empress Dowager.
But that edict is very important to her.
That edict implicates Marquis Muyang,
Prince Ding's Mansion,
and several factions.
At a critical moment,
you can use it to ensure your safety.
Remember.
Never let yourself
get into the situation I'm in now.
I don't quite understand. I...
You don't need to dwell on it.
Just remember what I told you today.
Stay calm.
(Vast as the Earth)
Give me another one.
Your Majesty.
(Poetry of Hibiscus)
Poetry of Hibiscus.
Moonlight washes the hibiscus
in hues of green,
while the Southern Star
glows upon the jade pavilion.
Your Majesty, is this the poetry book
Master Xiankun made for you back then?
Every verse mentions hibiscuses
and praises them.
Shut it.
(Poetry of Hibiscus)
(Preview)
My mom's life became a sacrifice
to your struggle for power.
Even after death,
she bore the stain of disloyalty.
Right now, you must want to kill me.
Since you've already known
the answer, why bother asking?
Princess Lingyun died in the Dachu.
The Cangbei soldiers
are all filled with grief and anger.
They believe Prince Ding's Mansion
deliberately set up this lethal trap.
Princess Ding assassinated
Princess Lingyun herself.
Now, they have given us
a three-day deadline
to execute the culprit.
♪Memories hold you back
from fulfilling your dreams♪
♪Only by moving forward
can you find reunion♪
♪Endings only mark new routes♪
♪It's all part of the scenery♪
♪To the horizon's call♪
♪Your journey hasn't started♪
♪Towards mountains,
chase the stars bright♪
♪Both joy and grief
make the trip worthwhile♪
♪Trying to catch up
to your own lost shadow♪
♪Within the wilds, echoes thrive♪
♪Clear mind leads to a clear path♪
♪Be grateful to your losses♪
♪Make your steps weightless♪
♪Towards mountains,
chase the stars bright♪
♪Let time embrace you
and wash away the past♪
♪Put every twist behind you,
drift leisurely through time♪
♪Make headway against the wind,
let mountains bow to your pace♪
♪Rush towards a life without regret♪
♪Let your nature burst free♪
♪Unbound by form♪