(Respect copyright)
♪Memories hold you back
from fulfilling your dreams♪
♪Only by moving forward
can you find reunion♪
♪Endings only mark new routes♪
♪It's all part of the scenery♪
♪To the horizon's call♪
♪Your journey hasn't started♪
♪Towards mountains,
chase the stars bright♪
♪Let time embrace you
and wash away the past♪
♪Put every twist behind you♪
♪Drift leisurely through time♪
♪Make headway against the wind♪
♪Let mountains bow to your pace♪
♪Rush towards a life without regret♪
♪Let your nature burst free♪
=The First Jasmine=
=Episode 26=
Moonlight washes the hibiscus
in hues of green,
while the Southern Star
glows upon the jade pavilion.
Your Majesty, it's the poetry collection
Master Xiankun compiled for you, right?
It frequently deals with hibiscus
and praises hibiscus.
You talk too much.
(Poetry of Hibiscus)
Go burn it.
Yes.
(Linjiao Courtyard)
You should leave.
If the Empress's people find out,
you'll be implicated.
I know what to do.
You focus on recovering your health.
Consort Guo is doing her utmost
to negotiate and get you out.
We can't let her efforts go to waste.
Guo Jin?
With her help, you can rest easy.
I'm lucky to have you both.
You really are a fool.
Remember,
never let yourself
get into the situation I'm in now.
(Under the bright moon,
ask not where I belong.)
(I only gather beneath the hibiscuses.)
(If only the hibiscuses
caught my sight,)
(I would gladly stay by the water
appreciating them.)
The world praises
the early bloom of the plum.
Yet I say, the hibiscuses
seep deep into my bones.
This poem earned
thunderous applause back then.
(Master Xiankun really adores hibiscus.)
Why are you here?
I'm in a bad mood.
What about you?
Who made you angry?
My father...
He killed Qin Cang.
Right?
You knew?
Of course.
After years of efforts,
there's no way for him to give up.
But Qin Cang was his son.
Does that matter?
When my father traded my marriage
for his interests,
did he ever think
that I was his daughter?
When I was trapped in the palace walls,
did he ever think about
how I would survive here?
It was Zhou Xiankun.
He helped me survive.
And Guo Jin.
Ten years.
Eight years.
The only thing that kept me going here
turns out to be fake.
Guess what? All of it was fake.
You're such a fool too.
Leave right away. Don't stay here.
So,
you're abandoning me too, aren't you?
You flattered me back then
to help your father.
Now, I can't help you anymore.
I'm telling you,
it was not like that.
Whether it was or not
doesn't matter anymore.
I don't care about anything now.
If you want to drink,
get drunk with me one more time.
If not, just leave.
Your Highness,
Dowager Consort Qin is here.
What exactly are you trying to do?
From the day of the solar eclipse
to drawing a dragon to pray for rain,
what exactly are you trying to prove?
Since you already know the answer,
why bother asking, Your Highness?
How did you find out?
I don't know the truth,
but I'm looking into something.
The Empress Dowager
has two capable people.
One is Marquis Muyang,
who eliminates dissenters for her.
He is her sharpest blade
in the imperial court.
The other is you,
the eldest daughter of the Nanyi's lord,
with the backing of the power there.
But why are you willing to work for her?
Is it just because of the friendship
with her?
After much deliberation,
all clues point to one person.
That person is Zhou Xiankun.
He drew a dragon to pray for rain.
His sorcery shook Lingnan.
If he sought fame,
why did he not do it in the capital?
The only reason is you.
What do you want to achieve
by investigating all this?
You and my mom were close friends.
You should know she didn't die in peace.
And you should also understand
why she felt scared and guilty
before her death.
Ye Wenhua told you, didn't he?
Since when could he ever keep a secret?
In that case,
you must want to kill me right now.
After my mom passed away,
Ye Wenhua used Marquis Muyang's power
to rise rapidly.
I thought the one who asked my family
for the edict was Marquis Muyang.
But why did it end up in your hands?
The day you and your mother left home,
I was outside the Ye Mansion.
So you took the edict from Ye Wenhua?
Yes.
- And then?
- I presented it to the Empress Dowager.
It was Marquis Muyang
who coerced the Ye family.
But for the Empress Dowager, you are
far more trusted than Marquis Muyang.
Why would you need
to claim credit for that?
Did you take the edict
truly just for the Empress Dowager?
That edict is of huge importance.
Once I saw it, how could I not take it?
Indeed.
It sounds perfectly reasonable.
But something doesn't add up.
Zhou Xiankun was imprisoned
due to his association
with the Eastern Palace.
You went to the prison
to see him one last time.
After you sent my Uncle Wenshen away,
what did he tell you?
Given the Empress Dowager's power,
was she truly unable to protect him?
He served the Empress Dowager
and was also close to you.
How could he conspire
with the Eastern Palace?
Dowager Consort Qin, did Zhou Xiankun
ask you to keep the edict?
That was his final advice to you
as a discarded pawn.
When I was little,
my mom often brought me to the palace.
She always had me call you Sister Qin.
She said you were bold and spirited,
and quite interesting.
She believed I'd like you.
I did like the old you
with all my heart.
My mom's life
became a sacrifice
in your power struggle.
She became a discarded pawn
in your schemes.
Even after death,
she bears the stigma of betrayal.
Eight years. Dozens of loyal souls
from Prince Ding's Mansion
and the blood debts of tens of thousands
of Heiyun cavalrymen
will be buried forever
in all your schemes
without justice for them?
To clear their names
was my mom's dying wish.
Sister Qin, if the edict still exists,
please give it to me.
Madam, be careful!
Mom! Mom, are you alright? Mom!
Madam.
Mom, are you alright?
Careful.
Be careful.
(Ye Mansion)
Greetings, Consort Qin.
What brings you here?
What's wrong with Wanzhou?
Consort Qin,
she is just weak, nothing serious.
I've informed Lishan, and there will be
people to care for her on her way back.
Is this what Marquis Muyang
asked you to get?
Yes.
Give it to me.
Consort Qin, Marquis Muyang
specifically instructed me
to hand this to him personally.
This item is of huge importance.
Your household has many eyes and ears.
If anything goes wrong again,
even the lives of your entire family
won't be enough to atone.
Tell Marquis Muyang
that I've taken the item.
He won't give you trouble over this.
Yes.
The edict? How did you get this?
I just took it from Ye Wenhua.
Just burn it.
Since it's a curse,
it naturally can't be kept.
Someone?
Why did you tie me up?
Where's my father?
Stop the carriage! Stop!
Where is my father? Stop!
Didn't you hear me?
Where is my father?
I'm asking you, where's my father?
Say something! Are you mute?
I...
Even if I kill myself, won't you care?
Your father told me to ignore you.
You won't die, anyway.
Master Zhou.
Eunuch Shunxi.
The Empress Dowager wants
to see you in the palace.
The Empress Dowager?
He has other things to do.
Could that wait till he returns?
The Empress Dowager
meets him for urgent matters.
Anyway, you all may follow me
into the palace.
After meeting the Empress Dowager,
you can do your thing then.
Your Highness.
Come in.
Prince Ding's Mansion
sent an invitation.
Princess Ding invites me to a banquet
at Qingfeng Mingyue Tower tomorrow?
You have no personal relationship
with her.
Why did she invite you?
Women here are truly narrow-minded.
You've come all the way
for the peace between our two nations.
How presumptuous of her to ask you
to help her deal with family matters.
Your Highness.
Princess Ding is not a simple lady.
She is from Lishan Academy.
Moreover, she is the only one
leaving Lishan Mountain in eight years.
It's worth meeting her.
I see.
Since you wish to go,
I'll arrange the carriage for tomorrow.
Do you want to go with me tomorrow?
I am your maidservant.
Since you are going,
I must naturally follow.
Alright. Go make preparations.
Yes.
Take him away.
This is a folk remedy
my father developed.
It stops bleeding and promotes healing.
It works well.
Thank you.
Your family members are all dead?
Back then, I came to the capital
on official business.
But right after I left,
Suixue Pass was breached.
Then Lingzhou was lost,
and my family was all gone.
Prefect.
Working with you recently,
I know that you're a good person.
The incident back then
really wasn't your fault.
But my heart aches.
It's like...
It's like a fire is pent up in my heart,
scorching me from inside.
I find no peace day or night.
But who should I hate?
Should I hate Cangbei?
Or should I hate heaven?
Sometimes,
there isn't even a person to hate.
In the end,
I could only take it out on you.
To be honest,
before, when I got drunk,
I even wrote letters cursing you
and threw them into your mansion.
I know.
How did you know?
I knew on my first day
at Jingzhao Prefecture.
That's the worst handwriting
I've ever seen.
I'm a rough man. Since childhood,
I've never liked to write or read.
My grandfather beat me often for this.
My handwriting looks terrible,
even after my family forced me
to learn with a lame scholar.
I can now read official documents,
which is a blessing from my ancestors.
Ever since I came to the capital
eight years ago,
I've been thinking
that I'll avenge my entire family
on the battlefield one day.
But after all these years,
the two nations have finally stabilized.
If war breaks out, many people will die.
Letting the majority live on
is better than anything else.
Staying alive to guard your homeland
is the best way to console their souls.
Prefect, you've saved my life twice.
I am not an ungrateful man.
Before, I was obstinate.
I am sorry for what I did.
Thank you.
Get up.
You've worked hard.
Your Highness.
- Let go of me!
- Move!
Let go of me!
Chen Longxiang, Marquis Muyang's lapdog,
a notoriously brutal official.
Five years ago,
you committed murder while drunk.
You killed your wife and relatives.
You even killed your mother-in-law
and your seven-year-old brother-in-law.
You should have been executed long ago.
But Marquis Muyang secretly
pulled strings to help you escape
and live under a false name. Am I right?
How do you know all this?
Someone told me, of course.
Who is it?
- Someone
- Behave!
betrayed Marquis Muyang!
Take him away.
Get up.
Tell me!
- Move!
- Tell me!
Qingyu got her period.
It's finally my turn
to accompany Your Highness out.
You're so happy.
I'll take you out more often.
Great.
Where are you from?
Xiaohe Village, in the south of Yunzhou.
Have you heard of it?
I know Yunzhou.
You left home at such a young age.
Are your parents not worried?
My parents are in poor health,
and medicine is very expensive.
And I have a little sister.
I'm the smartest one in the family.
I left home to earn money.
Please reward me generously,
so I'll go back to them someday.
You're just
cleverly angling for a reward.
You're indeed smart.
I don't usually see you talk so much.
Stop running, Ding! Stop!
I'm definitely going to hit you!
What's wrong? Don't want to be a worker
at Shende Shop anymore?
Want to be a gatekeeper here instead?
I haven't seen you at the shop lately.
I'm afraid...
You're afraid I'm dead
and that you can't repay me?
Don't say horrible things.
Come touch this red pillar.
Come on.
Satisfied?
Don't worry. I'll live well.
Hurry back to the shop.
Otherwise, I'll count it as absenteeism.
But you never said you'd pay me wages.
Where are you going?
Going to meet Princess Lingyun
at Qingfeng Mingyue Tower.
Then we're going the same way.
(Qingfeng Mingyue Tower)
Your Highness,
we'll go up first to prepare.
Go.
Everyone, please follow me.
(It's the Golden-Scaled Bloom
you mentioned liking in your letter.)
(It's time for its bloom.)
(I expect it to blossom in a few days.)
(When you go back to Cangbei,
I'll prepare some for you to take back.)
Your Highness,
this is my boss's treasure.
If it gets damaged, we'll be doomed.
Alright, I won't touch it.
Your Highness, please come inside.
Your Highness, we've arrived.
Princess Ding, I'm a maidservant
of Dowager Consort Qin.
Does she have something to give me?
She has compiled the first four volumes
of Xiankun Miscellany.
Hearing that Your Highness
is interested in astrology,
she specially gifts them to you.
Hope it's helpful.
Thank you.
(Edict)
(Year 14 of Jinghe Era)
Your Highness.
(Guests Filling the Shop)
Why don't I see Master Feng?
I haven't seen him these past few days.
What are you still doing here?
She brought a guard,
so shouldn't you bring one too?
Alright then.
Your Highness, please go upstairs.
Your Highness, this way, please.
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
It's okay.
When I was hunting in Cangbei,
I saw she was pitiful and took her in.
I brought her along this time
simply because she's from Dachu
and knows your customs.
Beyond that, there's no other intention.
I heard she took leave a few days ago
and stayed at your home.
I never asked her to do that.
I understand.
Everyone has a past.
Lady Su has her own difficulties.
I understand.
I overthought.
Let me toast you with tea.
You should be returning
to Cangbei soon, right?
I have plans with a friend,
so I'll stay a few more days.
Sounds like your friend is a local.
That's right.
You've been here before?
I met him on the Northern Frontier,
during my most desperate time.
But you're the princess of Cangbei.
How could you have been desperate?
That is a long story.
I'm listening.
Your Highness, it's all ready.
Please.
Help! Someone come quickly!
It was her! She killed the princess!
Su Zuidie!
Seize him!
(Danque Gate)
- Sir.
Where is Prince Ding?
Your Majesty,
Prince Ding has been away
on official business for a few days.
Duke Hua has arrived.
Greetings, Your Majesties.
No need for formalities.
How is the situation outside?
I've sent orders.
All northern border towns will now
light beacon fires, round the clock.
The military supplies
have been requisitioned urgently
and are being transported
to the northern front.
Also, emergency dispatches
have been sent to all border towns.
Once any unusual movements of Cangbei
are detected,
big or small,
a preemptive strike is authorized.
Duke Hua, are you worried overmuch?
Although Cangbei is strong,
the princess's death is not clear yet.
They may not send troops immediately.
Your Majesties.
Princess Lingyun is the elder sister
of Cangbei's ruler.
The ruler loves
and respects her very much.
Now, Princess Lingyun has died here.
Cangbei's guards are filled
with grief and indignation.
They firmly believe it was a trap set
by Prince Ding's Mansion.
Princess Lingyun's maidservant
also witnessed firsthand
that Princess Ding
personally killed Princess Lingyun.
They asked us to execute the murderer
within three days.
Otherwise, the war will break out
between our two nations.
Marquis Muyang, do you truly believe
executing Princess Ding will be fine?
Prince Ding's household
once defended our cities.
For Cangbei,
they represent the gateway to Dachu.
Prince Ding and Dachu
share the same stance.
If Princess Ding
truly killed Princess Lingyun,
why would Cangbei's ruler
not send troops?
Then what do you suggest?
Your Majesty, Princess Ding
has not confessed to the crime so far.
I believe
we cannot hastily close this case.
Moreover, what is most critical now is
that Cangbei may have received the news
and could send their army at any time.
Your Majesty, I've sent men
to intercept the messengers.
If the real culprit behind this intends
to start a war between the two nations,
I'm afraid the secret scouts
were notified long ago
and have traveled quickly to Cangbei.
Those you've intercepted
are merely the overt couriers.
And the secret message to be delivered
is the blade hanging over our heads.
So, is it still in time
to send light cavalry to intercept it?
If it's too late,
prepare for war, Your Majesty.
Starting today, the city gates will
be open for four hours each day.
Post notices at the city gates
to inform the people.
Do not disrupt their normal lives.
All citizens leaving the city
must be strictly checked.
Non-permanent residents
are not allowed to leave the city.
- Yes!
Thank you.
May I ask how Princess Ding is doing?
She is currently detained in prison.
Chief Imperial Secretary Murong Shen
is personally watching over her.
For now, her life is not in danger.
But if it drags on a few more days,
I am not so sure.
Princess Lingyun died in Dachu.
This is a catastrophe.
If the killer isn't found in three days,
Princess Ding will be targeted.
The founding principle of Lishan Academy
is to uphold justice
and defend the state.
No matter what happens,
the entire Academy will give our all
to move forward.
Ye Li is the granddaughter of Qingyun,
our Academy's Headmaster.
For the sake of our Headmaster,
I implore you to speak out for justice
and clear Princess Ding's name.
If you can ensure her safety,
the entire Lishan Academy and I
will be grateful for your kindness.
The situation is currently unclear.
Because of the old grudge
with the Heiyun Cavalry,
Cangbei suspects Princess Ding
of deliberate murder.
Both His Majesty and the Empress Dowager
need a resolution.
A resolution
that can quell the rage of Cangbei
and give an account
to the entire court and the public.
I believe there must be something fishy
behind this case.
Since a catastrophe is imminent,
the outcome is no longer important.
I'll do my best to protect Princess Ding
before Cangbei violates our borders
so that she won't be executed quickly.
However, whether Princess Ding
can ultimately get through this
depends on her own fate.
And more importantly,
we must find evidence to turn the tide.
Your Highness, you...
Tao!
Princess.
Help! Someone come quickly!
Ye Li!
Wake up.
Are you alright?
What happened to you?
What exactly happened?
Someone must have drugged the tea.
What?
It was that evil woman
who poisoned you both.
And she killed Princess Lingyun
and framed you.
Evil woman?
You know Su Zuidie?
I don't know why she did this.
Anyway, she is not a good person.
She previously bewitched my brother
into doing many bad things.
Who exactly are you?
Tianyi Pavilion.
You're working for Mo Jingli?
Prince Li?
(Preview)
That guy seems off. Jin, go after him.
Wang Suwu, you stay
and keep an eye on Chen Longxiang.
Yes.
Jingzhao Prefecture!
Halt for inspection!
Help! Someone come,
Princess Ding is vomiting blood!
If I don't take the antidote
within four hours,
I will die.
Go find Gu Zheng. He has the antidote.
Prince Ding is plotting rebellion.
Ye Li is the murderer.
I'll make this
(Prison)
an irrefutable case at any cost.
♪Memories hold you back
from fulfilling your dreams♪
♪Only by moving forward
can you find reunion♪
♪Endings only mark new routes♪
♪It's all part of the scenery♪
♪To the horizon's call♪
♪Your journey hasn't started♪
♪Towards mountains,
chase the stars bright♪
♪Both joy and grief
make the trip worthwhile♪
♪Trying to catch up
to your own lost shadow♪
♪Within the wilds, echoes thrive♪
♪Clear mind leads to a clear path♪
♪Be grateful to your losses♪
♪Make your steps weightless♪
♪Towards mountains,
chase the stars bright♪
♪Let time embrace you
and wash away the past♪
♪Put every twist behind you,
drift leisurely through time♪
♪Make headway against the wind,
let mountains bow to your pace♪
♪Rush towards a life without regret♪
♪Let your nature burst free♪
♪Unbound by form♪