[alarm beeps]
[theme music playing]
THIS IS A WORK OF FICTION
CHILD ACTORS WERE FILMED SAFELY
WITH SUPERVISION
Releasing my first album after 30.
That's way beyond late,
isn't it?
THE 1ST ALBUM
BAND GA-EUL
I only had one thing in mind.
I just wanted to make it first
and then propose to you.
Pretty soon, I'll be signing with a label.
And after that,
we can move into a house like you wanted.
-Come on, let's give it another sho--
-Ga-eul.
Do you really want us to get married?
I don't want to break up with you.
If we do…
then what?
Forcing yourself
to fit into the future that I want,
will you really want to live like that?
If you want,
I'll release albums more often,
and I won't go anywhere.
[Ji-yoon] You idiot.
That's not the person
that I fell in love with.
The thing is…
I don't want you to change because of me.
What a selfish thing to say.
You built up all these expectations,
and now you're walking back on them.
I am…
too late, aren't I?
You know me.
I'm the kind of person who thinks
that releasing your first album
after 30 is beyond late.
But the thing is that
you're not just any 30-year-old.
You actually spent all that time…
learning music and writing lyrics.
And pretending to travel
while working a lot of part-time jobs.
Oh…
You actually knew?
You were right, Ga-eul.
This album wasn't ready then.
[sighs] It had to come out now.
You really…
want it to end like this?
Mm-hmm.
[sighs]
Ji-yoon.
You were amazing up there.
You were exactly the way you were
when I first fell for you.
Ga-eul,
just be yourself.
Just as you are now.
Don't change yourself to fit into my mold.
I'll do the same thing.
[sniffles]
[wistful music playing]
Thanks so much…
for letting me see you shine on stage…
one last time, Ga-eul.
[sniffles, sobbing]
[sobbing]
And in the end, I couldn't open the album.
It felt too much like prying open a heart
that had barely found closure.
EPISODE 4
BROKE UP YESTERDAY, STILL CLOCKING IN!
Just how much did you cry?
Enough to… [sighs]
…not leave a single drop of regret.
You should've gotten back together.
You said he's finally starting
to do well for himself.
We'd end up breaking up again.
And I'd end up looking like this again.
Puffy toad face.
[both chuckle]
Playing the damsel in distress
in your own movie every night
is just what
a real relationship is all about.
Good morning, Ms. Cha Ji-yoon!
My name is Shin Na-ri from Marketing.
Hi, Na-ri!
-We were hired together.
-Okay.
Why are you here to see me?
Oh, I heard you're able to help
with work this weekend.
Sorry?
So I assume that you're free this weekend.
She's been working overtime,
and you want her to work on the weekend?
[chuckles] It's fine.
I actually said I could do it.
Great.
We're collaborating with a highball brand
to promote our ice sphere fridge.
Oh! Baseball?
Yeah, it's SAEUM's home game this weekend.
All 20,000 seats are sold out.
Don't you think it's the perfect chance
to make an impression?
Hmm. That sounds amazing.
Na-ri's pretty good.
Thank you, but this project
was actually proposed by Mr. Kang himself.
Mmm. True to form.
He's incredibly thorough.
On that note then,
is that why you have that look
on your face? Because of Mr. Kang?
-I've been hearing wild rumors about him.
-[laughing] Oh, no…
They're not rumors. It's a fact.
Don't get me started on his attitude.
Really?
He's just not very talkative, you know?
But he's not always like that.
He's actually very kind though.
Ms. Cha…
Seriously?
Are you taking Mr. Kang's side right now?
It's not that I'm taking his side…
[gasps] Are you two perhaps… [gasps]
Is there something between you two?
Oh, come on. Stop that!
Everyone knows Mr. Kang has an
insufferable way of speaking, doesn't he?
And once he gets something on you,
he won't let it go.
-Brutal honesty, huh?
-[coughs]
-Sharp tongue, right? Huh?
-[clears throat]
[Na-ri coughs]
-We should get back to work. [chuckles]
-Mm-hmm.
I'll contact you again later
about the project. [chuckles]
M-Mr. Kang.
Did you happen to hear what I said?
Hear what exactly?
Just now, I said…
That I'm insufferable when I speak?
I'm sorry, sir.
If you say that I am,
it must be true.
[chuckles]
[Si-woo] If you say that I am,
it must be true.
If you say that I am, it must be true.
[echoing] …it must be true.
[sighs]
What are we going to do
about the launch presentation?
Since you're just riding
on someone else's coattails,
you can't possibly be thinking
of doing it yourself, right?
No, I have no intention to.
Well, at least there's that.
In that case,
Ms. Cha, write up a draft for it.
I'll need to revise it a few times.
So you better hurry.
The launch…
will be presented by Ms. Cha.
M-Me?
Yes.
After all, you're the one
who has been on the project
from the beginning
until its successful development.
[Young-sam scoffs] Oh, please. Come on.
Give me a break. Are you serious?
A senior associate can't handle
a product launch presentation!
Hey, Ms. Cha, tell him now.
Honestly, does this make sense to you?
If my manager is saying so,
I suppose it does.
What?
[Si-Woo] You are totally capable.
You just need to do what you did
when you convinced me and Development.
Do you think getting up on that massive
stage and giving a presentation is a joke?
Let's not be so reckless
and ruin the whole thing!
I will do it.
I will.
Hey, Ms. Cha. [clicks tongue]
Very well.
Don't worry, I'll help you.
Thank you, sir.
[grunts]
[sighs] Seriously?
[sighs]
A product launch presentation?
[groans] A new product presentation?
[groans] Come on.
Why do I keep digging my own grave
like this? Why? [sighs]
Maybe it's better this way.
At least that way
I can lose myself in the work.
Hey, work.
Thank you
for helping me
forget my sadness with pain.
THANKS A LOT FOR LETTING ME
DROWN OUT MY SADNESS WITH PAIN!
[No-ah sighs]
[zipper unzips]
-[chuckles]
-[zipper zips]
[No-ah] No-ah being proactive
and passing DELF A2!
Please write down your name on this.
[chuckles] I have a boyfriend.
Good for you.
Sorry?
I'm getting everyone's contact info.
I'm the TA for this class.
Ah. Oh, I'm sorry.
I misunderstood. Just a second.
Here.
YOON NO-AH
010-0705-8005
"Yoon No-ah."
-I'll contact you at this number.
-Sure.
Next time, please bring my hat.
Sorry?
Oh.
That hat is actually really special to me.
[crying]
[in French] You should hide your tears.
[sighs]
[chuckles]
[in English] There's no way.
Why not? You're actually super tall, sir.
Not taller than the tree.
Well, you can use this then.
No, there's no way.
[groans]
What are we gonna do about that?
I can't leave it up there and lose it.
Get a firm grip.
[child 1] Oh. Oh.
-Oh! Wow!
-[child 2] Wow!
Thank you very much, sir.
I didn't do anything. You did it yourself.
Okay.
Wait. Here you go.
Is that a gift?
Let's go!
[Ji-yoon] Do you not like chocolate?
No. I do like it.
Why that face then?
And also, if you were gonna help them,
why did you say you couldn't at first?
I knew that I couldn't have done it alone.
[scoffs] This is why people…
You know, you're the type
who's easily misunderstood.
Know that?
You know, the Clock-in Fairy
has been running late.
I stayed up late last night
because of the presentation.
I mean, I'm already short on time
preparing for the launch.
And now you want me to help
with the Marketing Team's work.
Two of me is a bit too--
We're not here just to help out Marketing.
Then what?
You can think of this as a rehearsal
for the product launch.
Either way, it's about
pitching the product to customers.
Doing this today will help you figure out
an angle for your presentation.
So, you did this for me?
For my own sake.
A coach gets all the blame
for choosing the wrong player.
Let's go.
Are you sure you like it?
You look like you don't.
[Na-ri] I'll be taking care of the event
and of course promoting the brand too.
All you need to do, Ms. Cha,
is stand next to this refrigerator
and explain all the features
and benefits of an ice sphere.
Okay. Got it.
As for you, Mr. Kang…
I didn't expect you to be here too.
[chuckles]
I'll just be handing out the brochures.
Sure.
In that case, here.
I managed to secure one for Mr. Kang too.
[gentle music playing]
[Na-ri] Wow.
I almost mistook him for a real player.
He can't look like that
and work at an electronics company.
Yeah, he has no business
working out as much as he does.
Who cares if he's a little snarky
when he's such eye candy? [chuckles]
Thankfully, he doesn't talk that much.
[Na-ri gasps] That's so nice.
[both chuckle]
-What do you think you're doing?
-[both] Sorry?
Can't you see all the people
waiting behind you?
Oh! [stammers]
Uh, I'm so sorry! [chuckles]
-[Si-woo] We are from SAEUM.
-Hello! How are you?
Would you like this one? This one's good.
The fridge you see here
is SAEUM's soon-to-be-released
Ice Sphere Refrigerator.
Now, as to what an ice sphere is…
Hello, we're from SAEUM.
Uh, could I get your autograph?
I am not a player.
Since the game started,
you can leave things here with us,
and go enjoy the game for a bit.
-Is that okay?
-Yes, of course.
Mr. Kang, let's go.
All right, let's go.
Yes!
[crowd cheering]
[crowd chanting, singing]
♪ Victory! ♪
[crowd continues singing]
♪ SAEUM ♪
[cheerleaders chanting]
-Should we watch from here?
-Sure.
-Oh, excuse me.
-Yes?
Would you like one too?
They're on me this time.
I drove here though.
-Just one glass, please.
-Just one?
-Thanks.
-Sure.
-Here. Thank you.
-Thank you very much.
[sighs] That hits the spot.
When you're at a game,
you just can't do without a beer.
I question your loyalty.
You were just running a highball event,
and now you're drinking beer?
[scoffs] Beer and my loyalty
are different things.
Come on.
No outs with runners on first and second.
Why keep swinging for the fence?
What's wrong with the fences?
Well, right now
we're actually down by one.
In times like these,
he should just be thinking
of getting one more run with a sac bunt.
A single hit could turn the game.
If I were the coach,
I'd tell them to be aggressive
even if he ends up striking out.
[crowd chanting]
[chanting continues]
[groaning]
[stammers] Oh!
[calm music playing]
[commentator 1] Wow, a spectator
caught it. And with his bare hands too.
-[crowd cheering]
-[commentator 2] Wow.
I think he moved his hand out of reflex
just so his girlfriend wouldn't get hit.
[commentator 1] Is this the power of love?
Thank you so much, sir.
Shouldn't you know
how to avoid getting hit?
Well, oddly enough,
I freeze up when I panic.
That's because you don't work out.
You should work out three times a week.
[sighs] Thank you. [gasps]
Mr. Kang! Wait, is your hand okay?
Oh, no.
It's all red and swollen.
I mean, you can't just tell me to duck
and then just go for it like it's nothing!
-What are you, a baseball player?
-It does hurt.
Yeah, I bet. Oh, my goodness.
Oh, what should we do?
That's making it hurt more.
[crowd exclaiming, cheering]
[romantic music playing]
[chuckling]
[spectator exclaims]
[commentator 1] Oh, that's the couple
who caught the ball barehanded earlier.
Are you two not a couple?
You're not? Oh.
Then, how about you
start dating today!
-Give her a kiss! Give her a kiss!
-[crowd chanting] Give her a kiss!
[commentator 1, crowd chanting]
Give her a kiss! Give her a kiss!
[friend] Is this your sister?
[crowd cheering on phone]
-[commentator 1 chattering]
-Hey, Mom. Mom!
-Yes?
-Come over here.
-Look at this.
-What?
[commentator 1, crowd]
Give her a kiss! Give her a kiss!
-Is that your sister?
-It does look like your daughter.
Who's the man she's with?
Don't know.
-[chanting continues]
-[mother] Hmm?
[chanting continues]
What… What do we do?
Excuse me a moment.
[chanting fades]
[crowd cheering]
[crowd groaning, exclaiming]
[comical music playing]
The event was a great success,
thanks to you both.
Thank you so much.
Don't mention it. I had fun too.
Oh. I'll get the survey results
and get them to you by Monday.
Would that be okay with you, Mr. Kang?
All right. Great work today.
Mr. Kang,
now that I've worked closely with you,
I get why Ms. Cha said
what she said about you.
No, back then, I just…
Anything else,
besides how insufferable I am?
Yes. [chuckles]
She said you don't talk much,
but that you're actually very kind.
When exactly did I say "very," huh?
I actually said "kind of."
-Did you? Either way.
-Mmm.
Well, see you at work then.
Okay! Have a good afternoon.
It's true though.
I didn't say "very."
Okay.
I wasn't the one who started
talking about you first, either.
It's just that everyone seems to have
the wrong idea about you.
Yes, I know.
[calm music playing]
Thank you for that.
For what?
For actually believing me.
Let's just take my car.
I've made you work on the weekend,
so dinner is on me today.
Oh.
I'm so sorry,
I already have plans tonight.
Right.
Well, I guess I'll see you Monday.
Sir.
[sighs]
Come to think of it, we've never
even had a proper meal together.
[sighs]
CHO GA-EUL
[sighs] Didn't they break up already?
LIKE A CAT
[in Korean] ♪ I don't know when it began ♪
[sighs, chuckling]
♪ Your gaze
Made every part of me breathe ♪
[in English] What am I doing?
TIER 1 BEEF
Wow, this is so good.
You should've just gotten
the best one while you were at it.
[Ji-yoon] This is Prime grade.
I thought Prime was the very top,
because that's what you've always been.
But just like with beef,
it turns out there were higher tiers
above you all along too.
You're not making any sense.
Mom had a matchmaking agency
actually run your numbers.
And why would you do such a thing?
Okay, so?
What tier am I then?
Out of fifteen tiers,
you're a nine.
-Not exactly flattering. [chuckles]
-[scoffs]
Why am I a Tier 9? Huh?
Well, above you, there are professionals
like doctors and lawyers
or very good-looking celebrities.
Apparently, to be rated at the top,
you need to have rich parents.
[scoffs]
What, so they can leech off their parents
even after marriage or what?
That's just so ridiculous.
They even asked if you'd be okay with
being with someone divorced.
Mom, why? What's gotten into you?
What happened to telling me
I should never get married,
and I should just focus on my career?
I said that because
I was worried you'd marry that punk.
But now, your Mom has a new goal in mind.
What kind of goal?
I'm gonna get you married off,
-and then I'm separating.
-What?
-And me?
-And then I'm getting a divorce.
Mom!
It's bad enough that you've
kicked Dad out of his room. Really?
He comes in when we're all asleep
and leaves after breakfast.
[sighs]
Who was that man?
Who are you talking about?
-The man you were with at the game.
-[sighs]
You got caught on the kiss cam.
He's my boss at work.
He's the manager of the team I'm on.
Is he married?
If he's a manager at Ji-yoon's company,
he probably is.
And his salary must be like his face.
-He's pretty good-looking.
-[sighs]
[sighs] I really liked Ga-eul, though.
Yeah, but Ga-eul had no money whatsoever.
Other than that, he was very nice.
Ga-eul's doing pretty well nowadays.
He's got an album and tons of concerts.
He probably earns a ton of money.
-Really?
-Uh-huh.
Then maybe you should get back together.
This… This is exactly the reason
why I hate coming home.
I don't care if you and Dad
get a divorce or just separate.
Just stay out of my love life.
There she goes with that temper of hers.
She's exactly like her damn father.
I don't share your thoughts.
I mean, what kind of mother
wants to marry her daughter off
so she can finally separate?
[Hye-ji] Why not? I understand her.
It's every parent's wish
to marry their kids off
with a perfectly clean marriage record.
But who even thinks divorce is a flaw…
[sighs] I mean…
I used to cheer when I heard
about couples splitting later in life,
but the second it's my own parents,
my heart shatters into pieces.
That's why divorce is completely different
from just breaking up after dating.
It's a decision made
with the entire family in mind.
Meaning it carries the tears
of so many more lives.
It must've been really hard.
For who? Your mom?
Oh, not her. Someone else who's divorced.
[jazz music playing on speakers]
Why are you here alone?
You should've come with Ms. Ji-yoon.
Since when is she "Ms. Ji-yoon"?
What do I call her then?
Shall I call her "Ms. Cha" too?
She had plans.
[sighs] Figures.
Who would want to be
with their boss on the weekend?
You should've treated her better
in the first place.
I bet you've been hounding her
for being bad at her job.
Ms. Cha's good at her job.
She's the best employee
I've ever worked with.
You have a soft spot for competent women.
And for competent men as well.
I've just never seen one.
That's not what I meant.
I mean… [clicks tongue]
Do you have… hmm…
feelings for Ms. Ji-yoon?
Huh? What was that?
Stop meddling. It's rude.
[scoffs] That punk.
[calm music playing]
[panting]
[song continues through earphones]
[song distorts, stops]
YEONG-MOOK REPAIR SERVICES
Hello, sir.
Do you repair cassette players here
by any chance?
The one I have suddenly
just stopped working.
[sighs]
Ma'am,
this was discontinued in '98.
There won't be spare parts.
[groans] That's right. What kind
of father gifts their kid this thing
when everyone else was listening to CDs?
And a secondhand piece of junk
he fixed up, no less.
You liked it back then.
Yes, I did.
Plugged my headphones in
and I was the coolest kid in school.
Geez.
And you've been using this all this time?
You know, they're back in style now.
Retro, right?
[laughs] Retro, my foot.
[tender music playing]
Let's see here…
Hey, Dad, why did you marry Mom?
Because I wanted to be with her.
Then why do you
make her feel lonely like that?
Did she say something again?
She didn't.
But I mean, let's be honest, Dad.
You're a total zero as husband material.
You're always obsessing
over broken stereos,
and you barely even come home.
If I were her, I'd want to leave you too.
I know. I know.
But when… [sighs]
I mean, whenever someone
walks through that door, I just soften up.
Because to some,
it doesn't matter the cost
or the time it takes,
it's memories they want to repair.
I know. [sighs]
But maybe you could work
on keeping Mom's memories alive too. Huh?
At this rate,
she'll just end up hating you.
Well, this place is bound
to close down soon anyway.
Besides, hardly anyone comes by anymore.
Hmm. What's this?
Does mom know you splurged?
That was actually a gift.
Hey, hey, hey.
Careful.
Hold on.
Who would gift this kind of thing to you?
Some guy.
A punk who's been coming here
since he was a kid.
What?
[Yeong-mook] He once took apart
his home stereo, broke it,
and then he brought it here.
I told him, "Sure, well,
if you're that curious,
you can come here
and tinker all you want."
[chuckles] And he's been
coming here ever since.
What does this guy actually do?
Isn't that sketchy?
Why would it be sketchy?
He just comes to fix broken stuff
and then leaves.
Just?
Well, it's nice to have him around.
It keeps me from getting bored.
[exclaims, scoffs]
It sounds like you enjoy his company
more than your daughter's.
My goodness. How could I ever do that?
-[chuckles]
He should be here soon.
[knocks on door]
Oh, you're here.
What's that?
[Yeong-mook] Oh, my daughter
left me something she needed me to repair.
Oh, is that the daughter
who asks a lot of questions?
[Yeong-mook chuckles]
She's a real handful, that one.
Ever since she was a kid,
she was always curious.
Why is this like this?
Why is that like that? [chuckles]
And still, just looking at her
makes me smile. [chuckles]
Right, some are like that.
Mind if I give that a go?
Really?
Go ahead.
[whimsical music playing]
[sighs]
Whoa, I saw him over the weekend,
and now he's in my dreams too.
[scoffs]
[groans]
[automated voice] Doors opening.
Doors closing.
SUNNY
[employee] Breaking news!
Office romance! Kiss me!
Three-No-Man and Clock-out Fairy
caught on the kiss cam!
[laughs] What the…
[employee 2 gasps]
Why were they at the game?
-[employee 3] Did they kiss?
-[employee 4 laughs] On a date?
[employee 5] Nah, no way.
-[chuckles] Wait… What's this?
-What?
What is this?
Seriously, what is wrong with everyone?
Why make such a big deal
when a man and a woman are seen together?
So hurry up and clear things up
-before it gets more awkward for Ms. Cha.
-Right.
"Hello, everyone.
This is Shin Na-ri from Marketing.
Last weekend,
Manager Kang Si-woo
and Sr. Associate Cha Ji-yoon
were assisting the Marketing Team
with an event at the baseball stadium.
I hope there are
no further misunderstandings."
Mmm.
SHIN NA-RI
REPLY FROM ELECTROCUTED MAN
[employee] He made her work
on the weekend? Mr. Kang is ruthless.
[employee 2] Insane.
Good thing I didn't join the task force.
[employee 3] She'll end up being
thrown out like yesterday's trash.
[employee 4] Run away, Ms. "C"!
[employee 5] "Three-No-Man"?
No. "Three-No-Hope."
Are you sure that didn't make it worse?
[sighs] It's better than having
strange rumors going around.
Do you think they saw this too?
Mm-mmm. Ms. Cha doesn't read this.
[sighs] Thank goodness.
SHIN NA-RI
REPLY FROM ELECTROCUTED MAN
[scoffs]
But isn't it obvious
that we were just working?
Plus, shouldn't people just drop it?
Why make Mr. Kang be the Grim Reaper?
-[footsteps approaching]
-[scoffs]
-[employee giggling] So funny.
-[employee 2 laughs]
-Hey, did you see the kiss cam?
-Yes! I got so excited.
But I heard they were just working.
[scoffs] What a bummer.
[employee] I mean, the camera
wouldn't just film them for no reason.
They must've appeared
lovey-dovey or something.
That's right.
You could tell by their vibe
that they had something going on.
We'll wait and see
whether Ms. Cha becomes another victim
of Three-No-Man or not.
[both giggling]
-[employee 2] Seriously. Let's go.
-We shall see.
-[both chuckle]
-[door opens]
I'm not being anyone's victim.
[Ji-yoon] Mr. Kang,
I really need to do a good job
with this launch.
So please, would you help me?
I like for things to be perfect.
Yes, I am aware.
Therefore, I'm going to hold you
to a very high standard.
I am prepared for that.
Sure you won't regret this?
Yes.
Wow.
He's even giving her presentation lessons.
Isn't assigning the presentation
to Ms. Cha a punishment?
I get he dislikes Mr. Ko, but still.
As long as she does well,
it's an opportunity for her too.
It's all true, but…
But?
You know that employee
who took a leave of absence for therapy
while working under Mr. Kang?
I looked into it.
And apparently, he ended up like that
during a product launch presentation.
Are you serious?
[Kee-tae] Yeah.
He must've buckled under the pressure
of the presentation.
He did all the prep work, but in the end,
it was Mr. Kang who presented.
[employee] Is Mr. Kang a pro
at riding others' coattails or what?
It's all or nothing.
It's either a jackpot or a total bust.
[sighs, groans] This must be
so nerve-racking for Ms. Cha.
…transforms an ordinary drink
into an experience…
-[groans] Awkward, right?
-What do you think the problem is?
The way I'm saying things,
and my tone's off.
Well, none of that matters.
Then what?
The self-confidence in knowing
that you have created a gem.
That's what's missing
from your speech right now.
Focus on your delivery.
There will be subtitles anyway,
so it doesn't matter if they can't hear.
But be a little more
arrogant and confident.
Try it again.
Okay.
[sighs]
With less surface and area in contact…
Smile.
-…with your drink…
-Your gestures need to be
bolder and bigger.
-…the ice melts slowly…
-Drop your shoulders,
and tuck your chin.
…preserving flavor longer…
Eyes steady.
…and above all…
it's beautiful.
Let's try again.
Remember everything I just said.
Sir.
Thank you, sir.
How many cups of coffee
have you had today?
Uh, around two, three, or four?
I'm sure I told you
that caffeine aggravates anxiety.
I also drank a lot of chamomile tea.
Do you think chamomile
is some kind of antidote?
Well, I mean, I'm sure it's better
than not drinking anything at all.
[chuckles]
[clears throat]
-[chuckles]
-[elevator bell dings]
Ms. Choi.
[chuckles] Please.
Ms. Choi, I see you're back already.
Mm-hmm.
Did you enjoy your honeymoon?
Mmm, it was amazing.
I saw you switched teams though.
Yes.
I was worried about it,
but you seem well.
[elevator bell dings]
Hello there, Mr. Ko.
You know, I tend to get lucky whenever
I meet you in an elevator, Ms. Choi.
I guess something good's about to happen.
[chuckles] Is that so?
Mmm, that's such a nice thing to hear.
Oh.
By the way, do you happen to know
an employee by the name of Lee Young-hun?
Hmm… I don't. Why?
[sighs]
I heard that he was forced into doing
a product launch presentation by his boss…
[clicks tongue] …and had a panic attack.
Goodness.
So I thought that
if you knew his contact number,
maybe I could send him
a friendly message of support.
[chuckles] Well, Mr. Ko,
that's very considerate of you.
Well, a company doesn't just run itself.
Us managers
must always look after everyone.
Wouldn't you agree,
my dear Mr. Kang?
[Young-sam sighs]
[phone ringing]
Hmm?
Lee Young-hun speaking.
I see.
[phone buzzing]
Who's this?
Hello?
[TA] This is my number.
Make sure you save it.
And who are you?
I need to wear that hat tomorrow.
Can you bring it to me after class?
[scoffs]
[electronic music playing]
[No-ah] Thanks for the hat.
But giving it to me
and then asking for it back
is a bit uncalled for.
You wouldn't have come
if I'd just asked you to.
What are you trying to pull here?
I'm saying we should hang out.
How old are you?
Twenty-three, and you, No-ah?
Excuse me?
Wow, seriously?
I'm 29 years old.
I see.
All right, No-ah. Uh, want a drink?
[No-ah sighs]
Oh? That looks like No-ah's boyfriend.
[sighs, groans] You scared me.
[groans]
He sure does.
Wait a minute.
But how would you even know that, huh?
Did… D-Did you see?
Just how much of it?
Well…
How much did I see?
[No-ah] Did you cheat on me?
[Goo-won] It's not like that.
She doesn't even know I like her.
And I'm not telling her.
But how could I keep seeing you
when I'm feeling like this?
If we were to get married,
I'd just be lying to you.
Wow. He's getting clocked
if he keeps that up.
[patron] What's wrong with him?
That's it. Grab the cup and throw it.
[Goo-won] What do you think you're doing?
[No-ah] I'm begging you right now.
I'll forgive you, but take it back.
No-ah, just get up.
Then just tell me
you didn't mean what you said!
[Goo-won] I'm sorry.
I'll carry this guilt forever.
[No-ah sobbing]
[groans]
You saw the whole thing.
I did, yeah.
[groans] I can't believe this.
Want revenge?
What?
They say you should enjoy life
after you get revenge.
Let's do it. Get revenge on that bastard.
Let's do it?
Mm-hmm. No-ah and me.
Let's do it.
You're not exactly
in your right mind either, are you?
[clicks tongue, sighs] Fine.
[screams]
[phone buzzes]
[friend 1] Hey, Yoon No-ah!
Did you break up with Goo-won?
[No-ah] Where did you hear that?
Goo-won couldn't keep quiet
in his group chat.
-[scoffs] Whoa.
-Said he broke up with you,
but you stalked him
and even got on your knees.
[friend 2] Is it true? Why would you?
[No-ah] I guess he left
that part out, huh,
that he dumped me
because he cheated on me?
[friend 3] Seriously?
Pathetic excuse for a human.
[friend 1] Hey,
I'm telling the guys about this, okay?
[No-ah] Okay.
[electronic music continues]
[groans]
Let's do it. Revenge.
Where do we start then?
I knew you'd be fun.
Yes, then I'll proceed accordingly.
I'll see you at the venue tomorrow.
The presentation's tomorrow.
You shouldn't still be working.
Go home now.
-Right.
-[typing]
I'll just send this email. Okay.
Come on, stand up.
I'll take you home now.
[groaning] Just a moment.
I need the bathroom.
[groans]
Ms. Cha!
[sighs] I feel like throwing up.
I warned you about junk food.
The coffee and sugary drinks!
Sorry?
Please forgive me.
[groans]
Let's go to the hospital.
[sighs] Mr. Kang.
Just let me hit "send" on that email.
SEND
EMAIL SENT SUCCESSFULLY
[sighing]
Mr. Kang.
I'd like to go home, not the hospital.
That won't do. I'll get you to the ER.
Oh, no.
No, this is just period cramps.
I forgot to bring painkillers from home,
so that's all.
All right, I understand.
Are you sure painkillers
will be enough though?
Mm-hmm.
I can still take you to the hospital.
I'll be fine in no time, don't worry.
I didn't know…
you could pass out from period cramps.
It's just mine are particularly bad.
Thank you so much,
Mr. Kang.
[sighs]
[Ji-yoon] Ga-eul?
Hey, why are you here?
You awake?
Stay in bed longer.
Guess he wants to be all polite
now that we broke up.
I couldn't use your kitchen,
so I bought this.
When you wake up,
make sure you eat the porridge
and then the medication.
Don't take it on an empty stomach.
And even if you feel better after,
go to the hospital.
And make sure you get checked out.
Ga-eul.
Looks like your fever came down.
I'm sorry.
[chuckles]
Well, that's a bit upsetting.
[Ji-yoon] Mr. Kang?
Don't be sick.
[Ji-yoon] Is this a dream?
Mr. Kang and his kind voice.
And his warm touch…
[groans]
[sighs] It was especially bad this time.
I should see a doctor or something.
[groans] The presentation prep is really…
[gasps]
Oh, no.
It has become
the most personal space we have.
A reflection of who we are
and how we choose to live.
-Is Cha Ji-yoon not here?
-[sighs]
Another person driven over the edge.
Don't you think this is too far?
How could he work someone
to the point of collapse?
One missing screw won't affect
this giant corporation at all,
because there are always spare parts.
And on top of that,
they're stronger and tighter.
I'll look into it right away.
Thanks.
[upbeat music playing]
SAEUM'S SPHERE ICE REFRIGERATOR
NEW PRODUCT
How are you?
Good.
Home is no longer just where we live.
[Ji-yoon] Mr. Kang!
Are you okay?
I know it's out of line,
but may I do the presentation?
Please go ahead.
I didn't want to make a mistake.
No one else here knows more about
the ice sphere fridge than you, Ms. Cha.
And now…
go out there and show off your skills.
Sir.
Cha Ji-yoon…
Home is no longer just where we live.
It has become
the most personal space we have.
A reflection of who we are
and how we choose to live.
After a long day, we unwind at home
with a glass of whiskey.
In the evening, friends gather.
Good food, easy conversation,
and ice-cold cocktails.
At Saeum Electronics,
we asked ourselves a simple question.
"What makes this moment
truly complete?"
The answer was
ice.
But not just any ice.
A crystal-clear sphere of ice.
Once found only
in the world's finest lounges.
We've made it possible
to create this ice at home,
using our proprietary
reverse icicle freezing technology,
freezing water drop by drop.
With less surface area
in contact with your drink,
the ice melts slowly,
preserving flavor longer.
And above all,
it's beautiful.
That moment,
when a perfectly formed sphere of ice
drops into your glass…
[microphone feedback]
[sighs, breathing shakily]
[Young-sam]
Give me a break. Are you serious?
A senior associate can't handle
a product launch presentation!
[employee] We'll wait and see
whether Ms. Cha becomes another victim
of Three-No-Man or not.
[breathes shakily]
[sharply exhales]
[Si-woo] What's wrong with the fences?
A single hit could turn the game.
I'd tell them to be aggressive
even if he ends up striking out.
Forget the sacrifice bunts,
just be a hero.
When you get nervous, remember…
[breathes deeply]
…and you'll know the answer.
Is that your sign, Coach?
Yes.
[sharply exhales]
…transforms an ordinary drink
into an experience.
Today, we are proud
to bring that experience
into your home.
We present to you
the all-new SAEUM Ice Sphere Refrigerator.
[pop music playing]
[sighs] What can I say,
Ms. Cha is killing it up there.
Yeah, I'm jealous as hell. [chuckles]
Wasn't that woman
a senior associate on your team?
Why'd you send her to the task force?
She's efficient,
so she's great to delegate to.
But there's a ceiling
to how far you could take her.
And she leaves work at 6:00 on the dot.
Who cares about her leaving right on time
if she's good at what she does?
You're such a bad judge of character.
[sighs] No wonder you're stuck
in management.
Wow, it was received
so much better than I expected.
Oh. Just a moment.
Excuse me.
Great work.
Thanks to both of you, the new product
has become highly anticipated.
[chuckles]
Please join us. Let's get dinner together.
We have prior plans.
Oh… Oh, oh. Sure, sure, sure.
All right.
Well, then I look forward
to your next project.
Goodbye. [chuckles]
Looks like it's just us. [chuckles]
-You sure?
-Yes.
-All right.
-[clicks tongue] Oh, it's fine.
What do you mean, plans?
What kind of plans would make you
refuse dinner with the President?
We have a team dinner.
What?
Is there anything you're craving?
I would always just choose chicken?
Sounds good.
Really? [chuckles]
Everyone knows chicken is better fried.
Fried food on an empty stomach's
not good for you.
-Did you eat the porridge?
-No.
But it's okay, I'm feeling fine right now.
Well, it was particularly bad
this time… [chuckles]
…but it's a very familiar kind of pain.
Corporate slaves can't get sick.
Reduce your coffee intake,
start working out, eat better,
and make sure you see a doctor.
Oh, do you take any vitamins at all?
I don't.
In that case,
next time we'll be buying vitamins.
[Ji-yoon] Has there ever been
a man in my life
who was this concerned about my health?
Well then?
Eat up.
What is it? Does it taste bad?
No.
It's delicious.
Would you like a popsicle?
Tell you what, you can be the wind.
And I'll be the sun.
I got it.
Brows of truth.
You actually frown
when you like something, don't you?
Now I get it.
I had no idea, and it was making me
anxious because you kept frowning at me.
Did I frown that often at you though?
Yes.
Mmm…
I guess you won me over then.
[gentle pop music playing]
It's yummy.
[Si-woo] Don't forget the porridge
and the meds.
Don't be sick.
[Ji-yoon] It wasn't a dream.
WE'RE A TEAM
[typing]
[person] Did you make it
to work okay today?
Aren't the trees
in front of the office so beautiful?
[passengers exclaiming]
[phone buzzes]
[Kee-tae] Hey!
Have you checked the company forum?
[person] Hello, everyone.
My name is Lee Young-hun.
I'm in my ninth year at SAEUM
and currently on a leave of absence.
Between sick leave and parental leave,
I have spent almost
three whole years away from work.
One day, three years ago,
I encountered an unwelcome guest
in the form of panic disorder.
But I couldn't really
tell anyone at the time.
I didn't want to be seen as weak.
Because having a newborn at home
meant I couldn't risk
jeopardizing my career.
And then, finally, someone found me
sitting alone in a stairwell…
This is Kang Si-woo.
…hyperventilating and in pain.
Hey, Mom. Hi, yeah, it's me.
Apparently, Han-gyeol is not doing well…
[Young-hun] He sat me down
and gave me a serious talk.
Mom, the kid is sick.
Uh, I'll take half the day off…
[Young-hun] He just told me to stop…
to stop working right away
and to take care of myself.
I walked out that very same day,
leaving him to deal
with the launch presentation
I had stubbornly insisted on doing.
Someone from the company
emailed me recently.
And asked me to clear up
the misunderstandings about him at work.
That's when I found out
about the rumors about him.
Yeah,
someone who doesn't smile often,
a man of few words,
and doesn't apologize.
He is Three-No-Man.
To some, he may be
the worst boss imaginable.
But to me,
he is a unicorn of a boss
who actually saved my life.
I can't wait to see you,
Mr. Kang Si-woo.
[Soo-jin] Si-woo.
[Ji-yoon] Why are they…
Did they choose to stay friends
after breaking up?
But…
Why am I feeling this way?
[pop music playing]
[Ji-yoon] Do I? Mr. Kang?
So then, if you got married
and then divorced,
what would you call your ex-husband?
Where are we, in Hollywood?
[Si-woo] We will run
a second round of recruitment.
-Hello there, sir!
-I'll do it.
No. I-I mean, I'll try.
[Ji-yoon] They may have a crush.
Taking on a true man of mystery…
will give you a whole new thrill.
Is there a meeting I wasn't aware of?
WHAT MAKES YOUR HEART FLUTTER?
[Ji-yoon] Do I make you laugh? Do I, sir?