He swore to me and my mother
that the surgery was a success.
But after my mother got off the operating table,
not long after, she hemorrhaged and couldn't be saved.
I'll never forget the agonizing look
on my mother's face in that hospital bed.
And it's all thanks to your father.
Mitral valve:
severe stenosis.
Aortic valve:
moderate stenosis,
with moderate regurgitation.
Complicated by atrial fibrillation.
Her mother was only 47 at the time.
She simply couldn't undergo lifelong anticoagulation.
Complex aortic root reconstruction surgery
was the only option that could maximize
the patient's quality of life.
I once thought something went wrong
during the surgery itself.
But as the attending physician,
from start to finish,
did he ever speak up? No, he didn't.
That surgery took me a full five hours.
I remember every single detail clearly.
Every metric, intraoperative and postoperative,
was within controllable limits.
Even if her mother
were here today questioning me in person,
my answer would be the same.
I made no mistakes.
I didn't make a single mistake.
She had severe oral issues before the surgery.
At every consultation,
I reminded you over and over again.
Her condition
could very likely lead to postoperative infection.
And what about you?
What did you do?
Just so this case
could make it in time for your Specialist certification,
you chose to turn a blind eye.
You think this is the outcome I wanted?
This isn't what I wanted either.
Unexpected outcomes can happen to anyone.
You've spent your whole life chasing
a perfect surgical success rate.
Do you know why I left Pingjin back then?
Because after that surgery,
I finally saw you for who you really are.
You're too obsessive.
If she'd just waited a few more months,
if she'd waited until her periodontitis
had completely healed,
she could've had the surgery.
But your father,
it was your father who told my mother
the chance of postoperative infection was negligible.
But it was that exact negligible chance
that took my mother's life.
I hate your father to the core.
I've hated him for ten years.
But I hate myself even more.
Why didn't I convince my mother
to just wait a little longer?
Wait?
Could her condition afford to wait?
You knew her condition back then!
Every day of delay added more risk!
You don't need to explain anymore.
You can call me selfish and obsessive,
or say my skills are inadequate,
but I will never allow anyone
to question my professional integrity.
I, Jiang Zhaohe,
have always been open and aboveboard.
Unlike you,
deliberately placing that girl
right next to my son.
What exactly are your intentions?
This is just fate.
Fate?
Let me tell you,
don't you even think about letting my son
stay here with you,
to become a
freak like you!
Feier
Uncle Jiang
What are you doing here?
Why? Now, whenever I...
Whenever I close my eyes,
I...
I think of my mother.
I think of her crying out for help.
That kind of despair...
You could never understand.
Tang Yi.
Deep breath.
Deep breaths. Deep breaths.
If
I hadn't met Director Zeng,
I might
have spent my whole life
unable to move past
my mother's passing.
He told me
that hatred
and regret shouldn't consume my entire life.
Although nothing can be changed,
but
when my mother and I
had nowhere to turn for help,
the only one who gave us hope
was also your father.
We've
met before, haven't we?
Mom
Tang Yi
Don't touch me!