What are you doing?
There were so many people around just now!
Jiang Tiancai, have you lost your mind?
Yes, I've lost my mind.
In the past thirty-plus years,
I've never been this crazy before.
Do you know what the worst
side effect of PEP is?
Not dizziness, nausea, fever, or rashes.
It's that every single night, I dream
of you cooking in my kitchen.
So there's no chance of any Reconciliation.
I want you to know, crystal clear,
that I...
am in love with you,
Tang Yi.
Old Jiang
Who's this?
Do you know him?
I've never seen this professor before.
Jiang Zhaohe.
The only one in the country to win
the Golden Scalpel Award for Special Contribution three times in a row.
A leading professor in Cardiac Surgery.
A Cardiac Surgery expert.
What's he doing here?
Son.
If work has worn you out,
let's go home.
Have your mom make you
your favorite Red Braised Pork.
We can play a few games of chess.
Your son Xiaochun misses you so much.
He asks for you all day long.
Enough. Stop nagging.
Let go.
Our son still has work to do.
Why didn't I
think of that?
No wonder Dr. Jiang
is so accomplished at such a young age.
He was born with great genes.
It's because of Dr. Jiang's father.
With a great dad,
he doesn't have to work hard
to get everything so easily.
Truly enviable.
What are you doing here?
If I hadn't come,
how could I see you here
acting like someone else's son?
That's because you failed as a father.
Otherwise, your son
wouldn't have to seek that bond with strangers.
Tiancai.
All these years,
how much I've sacrificed for you,
you know very well.
I also know
that because of your grandmother,
you resent me, you hate me.
I won't hold that against you.
But you're an adult now.
You can't keep ruining your own future.
Sacrifice?
The sacrifice you speak of
was dumping seven-year-old me
on my frail, sickly grandmother
to go pursue further studies,
gone for five whole years.
Or how, on the rare times you came home,
all you cared about was whether I was
following the path you laid out,
never caring about what I actually wanted?
Just because, during the college entrance exam,
I didn't meet your expectations
and study Cardiac Surgery,
you think I'm ruining my future.
So if I decided right now
to stay at this hospital
and be a dentist for the rest of my life,
wouldn't you feel you have no successor?
So this is how you take revenge on me?
Using the hands of a genius surgeon
to do this kind of work?
What's wrong with this work?
Isn't it better than the
scheming and plotting on the operating table?
Back then, on her sickbed, your grandmother
grabbed my hand and said,
"Don't let him follow my path."
Looking at it now,
she really was worrying for nothing.
You have no right to mention her.
The name Jiang Zhaohe,
to me,
means nothing more than a stranger.
If it weren't for those so-called...
so-called pursuits of yours,
Grandma wouldn't have left me so soon.
Pursuits?
My pursuit
was to bring our country's medical technology
up to international standards five years sooner.
You know what?
I have a Clear conscience.
And you?
What is it that you pursue?
What I pursue,
you'll never understand in your entire life.
Tiancai.
Sorry, I didn't know you had company.
I'll just go.
Tang Yi.
Perfect timing.
Let me introduce you.
This is my girlfriend, Tang Yi.
Didn't you say the surgery was a success?
Then why is she gone? Why?
Tang Yi.
Stop right there.
Jiang Tiancai, let me tell you.
The only one who belongs by your side
is Lin Fei'er.
You're of equal standing, and know each other inside out.
She's the perfect match for you.
Ignoring a child's malocclusion,
thinking it'll fix itself with adult teeth,
is a huge misconception.
A child's malocclusion
not only affects their facial appearance,
but may also impair chewing function,
affecting digestion and absorption.
It can even have negative effects
on the child's mental health.
Parents
should take their child's malocclusion
seriously,
and promptly seek
help from an Orthodontics specialist.