You don't need to explain all this to me.
I don't understand your dental jargon anyway.
It's all too convoluted.
My request back then was very clear.
Just to get dentures, a restoration.
But this Dr. Jiang of yours,
he's blinded by greed.
He insisted I get,
get, get, what was it called?
Maxillary Alveolar Bone Graft Surgery.
First, put in an artificial bone,
and when conditions are right, do a...
called, called
Dental Implant Surgery.
Everyone, listen to this.
What kind of nonsense is this?
I've already asked my doctor friends.
They said this kind of surgery
is extremely risky.
And the recovery period is long.
The main thing is the cost,
it's outrageously expensive!
Look at you people!
You're just in it for the money.
You don't care whether we common folk live or die!
You don't care if we live or die!
That's right, that's right!
I explained very clearly at the time.
Dental implants
and removable dentures both have pros and cons.
It was after fully understanding the pros and cons
that you chose the dental implant option yourself,
and signed the Informed Consent Form.
All of my treatment procedures
are legal and compliant.
Don't give me that.
Legal and compliant, my foot!
I was just conned by you people back then!
If I hadn't seen the news,
I'd really have thought you were
some saint who saves the dying and heals the wounded!
I...
How can your hospital
even hire such an unscrupulous doctor?
How are we supposed to
feel safe getting treatment here from now on?
You must give me an explanation today.
Otherwise, none of you are leaving.
None of you are leaving!
E-Everyone, please stop arguing!
There's no way Dr. Jiang would be
the kind of person to hit a patient's family member.
There must be some misunderstanding here.
Let's talk this through calmly.
Could someone be deliberately smearing him?
Everyone, please calm down first, okay?
That's just too wicked.
We'll definitely give you all a solution.
Qi Yue.
Didn't your second brother in Pingjin
invest in some new media companies?
Could you do me a favor?
and see if there's any original footage?
I will definitely give everyone a satisfactory answer.
Sure, I'll go check.
Everyone, please go home first.
Director Zeng, you'd better keep your word.
You must give us an explanation.
I will, I will.
We must fight for our rights.
We can't let others bully us.
This isn't over, I'm telling you.
I'd rather have a different doctor see me.
It's no use if I'm the only one who believes you.
Take a break from work for now.
Don't worry.
This matter,
the hospital will investigate this thoroughly.
As long as we all have a clear conscience,
I won't let anyone be wronged.
Remember,
A man
must be adaptable.
Don't worry.
The truth will definitely come to light.
If before that whole thing happened,
I had met you,
and you used your
made-up psychology
to analyze me inside and out,
maybe
none of this would have happened.
How is that made-up?
It's genuine expertise.
But,
back then,
did you already have designs on me?
Who was having designs on whom, exactly?
Got the guts to flirt, but not to admit it?
I— Who says I wouldn't admit it?
What I was doing was...
What are you doing here?
What?
Not going to invite me in?
Your girlfriend keeps you on a tight leash?
Is it inconvenient?
Why are you blaming this on me?
You two talk.
I'll go out to buy some things.
This is truly ridiculous.
I prided myself on being
the person who knows you best.
But I never imagined
you'd actually fall for someone like her.
If you came here just to pick a fight,
you've seen enough.
Please leave.
I only came to tell you
Even though I don't believe the nonsense online,
I also won't let you become
what you are now.
Daniel,
as long as you're willing to go to Lyon,
you can leave all of this behind.
In a new environment, no one will know
about what happened before.
You can still start over and be yourself.
I've told you already,
I'm not going.
Give up on the idea.
Have you lost your mind?
Do you know that once you finish your training,
and return home,
what kind of future awaits you?
Can you stop acting on impulse?
I've thought it through clearly.
Why?
Just because of Tang Yi?
Then what about all our years together?
Or are you saying
you never loved me?
Love?
What is love?
I used to think that between us,
there was once love.
It wasn't until you went abroad
that I realized what we had was just
compatibility,
habit,
and responsibility.
There was never any romantic love between us.
Don't tell me
that you and Tang Yi have romantic love.
How long have you even known each other?
Three months?
And you're so certain your feelings for her
aren't just a momentary impulse?
What does she even have?
She's nothing but
a lowly doctor with no background,
and no family connections, from the bottom rung.
What can she give you?
Open your eyes.
We're the ones from the same world.
In your world,
doctors have to climb the ladder.
They don't care who the patients are.
They weigh the pros and cons,
to boost research efficiency.
But in my world,
a doctor has only ever had one duty,
and that's to heal the sick and save lives.
The moment I met Tang Yi, I knew.
Y-your hand!
Let's disinfect it first.
It's fine, it's fine. Treat the patient first.
Let me bandage it for you.
It's fine, treat the patient first.
Okay.
She and I,
we are the ones from the same world.
Jiang Tiancai,
have you forgotten
who exactly was there with you in the lab,
through all those days and nights?
But did you know I never wanted
to set foot in that lab?
The moment I saw that research data,
I would
I would get a headache.
It was you.
You always wishfully believed
that doing those experiments with me
would make me happy.
Lin Fei'er, it was always you.
From start to finish, you were the one who dragged me into
a world that didn't belong to me.
We were never from the same world.
This is bad, Dr. Jiang.
Something's happened.
When did this happen?
About an hour ago.
Her neighbors brought her in.
It's...
Acute Submandibular Space Infection.
It's all my fault.
She hasn't come in for follow-ups lately.
I should've gone to check on her at home.
I...
You're still suspended right now.
Don't worry.
Dr. Chen is in there with her.
My son...
Dad has failed you.
I didn't keep an eye on Xiaochun.
And I didn't take care of your mom either.
Dad is to blame, Dad is to blame.
Dad is to blame.
Auntie Jiang was such a good person.
How could this happen?
Dad is to blame.
How is she?
Say goodbye to Auntie.
Oral diseases are highly prevalent among the elderly,
progress rapidly,
and their self-healing capacity is weak.
But losing teeth with age isn't inevitable.
As long as there are still teeth in your mouth,
you should keep brushing morning and night.
If you notice issues in your mouth like
red, swollen or bleeding gums,
bad breath, or loose teeth,
seek medical care promptly and treat them actively.
Otherwise, mild cases impair oral function,
while severe cases can cause systemic infections,
affecting your quality of life.