Hey, boss, how much for these conches?
Tang Yi!
Tang Yi, aren't you working today?
Why didn't the handsome guy come?
Did you two have a fight?
Why do you have so many questions?
Which one should I answer first?
Look what I brought you.
A teddy bear!
Do you like it?
I love it!
Tang Yi,
while you were away,
I brushed my teeth every single day.
That's amazing!
On Pei Xi's livestream,
I learned so much about dental health.
I want to be a doctor when I grow up.
That way,
I can see you every day, Tang Yi!
You're such a sweetheart.
By the way, how are your eyes healing up?
Any discomfort?
No, not at all.
My eyes are doing great.
Daddy said I should always remember
the person who donated their cornea to me.
When I grow up, I want to help others too.
By the way, sweetie,
can you answer one question for me?
Of course!
Have you ever been to Pingjin with Daddy?
Yes, I have.
I went with Daddy to pick up supplies.
Look, I even fell and lost a tooth!
A doctor took me to the hospital.
That doctor was really stern,
but his hands were big and warm,
just like yours, Tang Yi.
Dr. Tang.
What brings you here?
Master Zhou.
Daddy!
Look, this is what Tang Yi
gave me as a gift.
Dr. Tang,
if you have something to say,
let's talk over there.
Master Zhou,
that's not really what happened, is it?
Dr. Tang,
I know you're a good person,
and I know about you and Dr. Jiang.
But you're you, and he's him.
You don't need to defend him.
Master Zhou,
none of us believe
he would do something like that.
If there's been a misunderstanding,
we can clear it up.
But these rumors
will truly destroy his career.
There's no misunderstanding.
What you saw is the truth.
To save that rich person first,
he abandoned my daughter.
What gave him the right?
My daughter was so badly hurt,
her face covered in blood,
crying out in pain.
I begged him over and over,
but what did he do?
He's a cold-blooded, heartless scumbag.
He doesn't deserve to be a doctor.
But do you know what?
This "scumbag" you speak of,
he picked up a scalpel at twenty.
In Pingjin First Hospital's history,
he's the youngest attending physician.
He can work 24 hours straight,
performing eight major surgeries.
He'll fight tooth and nail
for total strangers,
standing up to renowned experts,
just for that one percent chance of a cure.
How could a person like that ever
treat patients differently based on status?
I apologize to you.
It really was my fault back then.
Your daughter's surgery afterwards
was completed successfully.
But my attitude was poor.
I didn't explain things clearly.
That was my fault.
Dr. Jiang.
This one next door is Director Qin's friend.
Come handle him first.
If vital signs are stable, send for a CT scan first.
Full scan of head, neck, chest, and abdomen.
Isn't there a doctor right here?
Doctor, hurry, hurry!
The patient is undergoing debridement.
Who let her pull open the curtain?
I'm a friend of your Director Qin.
My son is badly injured.
I want you to examine him first.
Mom.
I'm so thirsty.
There's blood inside the helmet visor.
But no open wounds visible on the face.
There may be intraoral injuries.
Don't remove the helmet.
What's the oxygen saturation?
Oxygen saturation is 88.
Open a third IV line. Prep for surgery.
Got it.
Doctor.
My daughter came in first.
Her internal injuries haven't been checked yet, I...
What are you doing?
You, take over the debridement.
Okay.
Hurry, doctor!
The reason I saved that person first
is because I judged
that your daughter's condition was temporarily stable.
But if that person didn't get immediate surgery,
his life would have ended.
I know that no matter what I say now,
it can't make up for
the pain your daughter suffered then.
But this is the truth.
In a doctor's eyes,
patients aren't judged by wealth or status.
Every life
we treat with respect.
I actually...
I'm the one who wronged you, Dr. Jiang.
I know you're a good person too.
I really didn't mean to hurt you.
I was just so angry back then.
Furious that my daughter had to suffer so much.
I never thought things would turn out like this.
Later, I wanted to come forward and explain for you.
But I...
But after I saw those donations,
I really had no choice.
My mother was lying in the Intensive Care Unit.
Costing several thousand a day.
And my daughter had lost her sight.
I really had nowhere left to turn.
That money...
I shouldn't have taken that money.
I shouldn't have taken it. Don't do this.
I'm the one who wronged you, Dr. Jiang. Master Zhou.
I'm too ashamed to face you.
Please get up, Master Zhou. I'm sorry.
My brother found who was behind that news story.
Get up first, then we'll talk.
You should thank me
for not exposing what you did.
Master Zhou, please get up.
I'm so sorry, Dr. Jiang.
Suit yourself.
It doesn't matter anymore.
Get up, quickly.
I'm so sorry. Get up.
You're just going to leave like this?
What else should I do?
Wait around for you, the winner,
to come laugh at me?
It's all in the past now.
No one's going to dig up the truth.
You don't need to use your medical family
and golden child halo to show me pity.
What I, Chen Pei'ang, have done,
I own it.
All because of Tang Yi?
Maybe.
Before you showed up,
I thought I'd be the one
who'd stay with her till the end.
But reality is just that cruel.
You, so effortlessly,
took away everything I had.
She's her own person.
She doesn't belong to anyone.
Who she wants to be with
is her choice.
We competed fairly.
Fairly?
Is it really fair?
People like you,
are born at the peak,
enjoying the best resources,
basking in everyone's admiration.
And me?
I gave everything I had,
and the finish line I struggled to reach,
is just your starting point.
Do you know what having nothing means?
Do you know what "A slow sparrow should make an early start" means?
Have you ever seen your parents at 3 AM,
backs hunched over,
pedaling a tricycle to sell vegetables?
Have you seen your siblings groveling,
swallowing their pride to beg for loans?
Have you spent eight straight years,
sleeping only three hours a night,
hiding under the blanket in the dorm,
reading with a flashlight in the middle of the night?
You haven't.
You'll never understand.
Because you were born with everything.
Yes.
I admit it.
I'm jealous of you.
I'm insanely jealous.
I have no family background,
no connections, no network.
At my lowest point,
I had to split one cup of noodles into two meals.
I've struggled this hard for so long
just so I could say goodbye
to my old life.
Just so everyone I care about
could live a little better.
Just so I could stand a bit taller
in front of the person I love.
Is that so wrong? Is it?
Why?
Why can't I even be left
with this tiny bit of hope?
I...
I never thought you were beneath me.
And I never thought I was above anyone.
In fact, if I were in your position,
I might
not have done as well as you.
You have everything.
Nothing to worry about.
Of course you can sit there
and say all these noble things.
You only see the halo
of a golden child above my head.
But you don't see
how cautiously I live every single day.
Just because my father is Jiang Zhaohe,
from the moment I was born,
I was destined to follow in his footsteps.
I never had a carefree childhood like yours,
nor the right to choose my own interests,
not even the company
of family or siblings.
I have no time of my own.
And everything I do
is simply to be worthy
of being Jiang Zhaohe's son.
Every single day,
I'm careful,
working tirelessly, walking on thin ice.
I'm terrified of making the slightest mistake.
Because if I do,
my colleagues will think I got in through connections,
through the back door.
You think I'm not exhausted?
You think I don't feel
suffocated and miserable too?
I can't choose where I came from,
but I know how to navigate my future.
I do this
not to prove myself to anyone,
but so I won't have regrets.
What about you?
All your years of hard work,
just to surpass me?
There are countless people better than me.
Are you going to spend every day
living in comparison with them,
trying to surpass each one?
Believe me or not,
but I never saw you as a rival.
Everyone has their own path,
and all I need to do
is be better than I was yesterday.
That's enough.
My own path...
I used to think
that as long as
I had passion in my heart,
I could definitely help more people.
But the reality?
The reality is, no matter how hard I try,
I can't change that
deep-rooted prejudice and discrimination.
Eight years studying my field,
over a decade honing my skills,
and in the end, to others,
I'm less credible than
a plan a machine generates in three seconds.
What am I, Chen Pei'ang, really?
I'm nothing.
If everyone
ran away like you do,
how would our profession ever develop?
You think just the two of us
can change the ecosystem of this industry?
How will we know if we don't try?
Toothaches are just from internal heat.
Well, that's not always the case.
Dietary irritation,
poor oral hygiene,
excessive heart or liver fire,
oral infection...
all of these can cause toothaches.
If your toothache persists
or the symptoms get worse,
make sure to see a dentist promptly.
Don't put it off,
or a small problem could turn into a big one.