Dr. Jiang
Thank you
for all this time
you spent with us two old folks
playing house.
Regrets over missed chances
can never be made up for.
If back then,
I'd had the chance to say goodbye to Grandma...
The one I worry about most
is you.
Don't hold a grudge
against your father.
Get along with him.
Hurry up and...
and...
start a family.
Only then can Grandma
finally
rest at ease.
Dr. Jiang,
you are
a good person.
If
my son one day
comes back,
please tell him for me
that in
the kitchen,
in the southeast corner cupboard,
I left him
his favorite pickled vegetables.
Tell him to remember
to come home
and see his father.
No.
Grandma.
Grandma!
My dear.
Let's go home.
Come home with me.
Elder Chun, Younger Chun
are still waiting for us.
We've made up our minds.
This way, we can help more people.
If I hadn't been suspended,
I could've saved her.
By the time Auntie Jiang was brought in,
it was already too late.
It shouldn't have ended like this.
I reminded her again and again
to watch Uncle Ge's oral condition.
But I never thought to examine her.
It's me.
It's my fault.
If I'd just been a little more careful,
maybe none of this
would've turned out this way.
Tiancai.
Jiang Tiancai.
Jiang Tiancai, look at me.
Look at me.
No one wanted this to happen.
Auntie Jiang had diabetes
with submandibular space infection.
Complications like that
are inherently hard to prevent.
And it progressed so rapidly.
We did everything within our power
to give her the best care.
How is he?
Listless.
I've never seen him like this before.
Then do you...
really believe what the news is saying?
Of course not.
I found the original video you wanted.
We all know that patient's family.
It's Mengmeng's Dad.
After a tooth is fractured or knocked out by trauma,
avoid touching the tooth root directly,
or wrapping it in tissue or similar items.
Place it in saline solution or milk,
or under the tongue.
Within the Golden Thirty Minutes,
replantation can be achieved.