Dr. Tang.
Do you really think you know Daniel?
You only know you lost your mother ten years ago.
But do you know what he went through that night?
The grandma who raised him was dying.
And his father
was at your mother's operating table.
Because of your family,
Uncle Jiang missed
the best chance to save his own mother.
Stop torturing yourself.
What's done is done.
There's no going back now.
Your mother's spirit in heaven
would never want to see
you like this.
Daniel.
I wasn't wrong to tell her the truth.
If the two of you
can't even be honest with each other now,
then the road ahead
will only get narrower.
So I should thank you?
For your pathetic vanity
and possessiveness,
how far are you willing to go
before you finally stop?
Am I really that despicable in your eyes?
Yes.
I can't accept this.
We've known each other since we were seventeen.
Studying, exams,
graduation, work,
which stage of your life
was I not by your side?
Just that one time.
I was selfish just once, ten years ago,
and now you want to erase
fifteen years of what we had?
All those years you spent abroad,
did you ever dream of Grandma?
Even just once?
A woman who loved you as a granddaughter
had just closed her eyes and passed away,
yet for your so-called opportunity,
your so-called future,
you turned and left without hesitation.
You didn't even consider
giving her a proper farewell.
Lin Fei'er, just admit it.
You and Jiang Zhaohe
are essentially the same kind of person.
I loved Grandma no less than you did.
But I believe
if you were in my place,
you wouldn't give up your future
for sentimental attachments either.
Am I right?
Claude Bernard University Lyon 1.
A fellowship in Head and Neck Surgery.
I recommended you to Professor Baidi.
He's already agreed.
As long as you're willing,
you can fly to France by month's end.
Professor Baidi is chairman of Europe's
Head and Neck Surgery Association.
He takes one apprentice every three years.
Do you know how many people
dream of an opportunity like this?
Don't tell me you're not tempted.
I'll pursue opportunities on my own,
but not right now.
Professor Baidi is nearly seventy.
If you miss this chance,
who knows when another will come.
Jiang Tiancai,
where's your ambition?
What about your former dreams?
Are you really willing to spend
your whole life stuck in this place,
fixing teeth, filling cavities,
wasting your time away?
I want you to think this through carefully.
So you and Dr. Jiang are just over?
Could you be any more annoying?
She's already a mess inside right now.
Don't make it worse.
Just go, hurry up.
Get going, get going.
I'm leaving.
Don't let Lin Fei'er drive you apart.
When it comes to relationships,
only the two of you get to decide.
As long as you both think it's worth it,
who cares what others say, right?
If only it were that simple.
This knot between us,
I'm afraid it can never be undone.
Doctor, doctor!
Doctor!
It hurts so bad, doctor!
Check my wisdom tooth, doctor!
Take a look at this wisdom tooth!
It's killing me!
Just yank it out, hurry!
How much have you had to drink?
Extractions aren't advised after drinking.
Not recommended.
We can't pull it.
How will I drink with my buddies then?
Come on, come on, hurry up!
Just pull it out already!
My buddies are waiting on me for dinner.
Sir.
Alcohol impairs coagulation function
and affects recovery and anesthesia.
No matter what you say today,
I cannot perform the extraction.
Let me just examine you first, okay?
Alright.
Open your mouth.
The position of this wisdom tooth
is tricky, not easy to extract.
How about I give you a painkiller first?
After you go home, for 24 hours...
Sir!
Tang Yi!
Somebody help!
Sir, are you okay?
Someone help, hurry!
Call 120, quick!
Hurry!
Mom...
Suspected esophageal variceal rupture.
Easy now!
Call 120, hurry!
Careful!
Tang Yi!
Tang Yi, are you all right?
What's wrong?
Medicine... medicine...
Medicine.
What medicine?
Where is it?
Medicine.
What medicine?
Tang Yi, Tang Yi!
How is she?
Suction!
Get the suction, hurry!
Move aside!
What happened to her?
It's okay, it's okay.
Tang Yi.
It's all right.
It's over now, it's over.
There's no way we're breaking up.
Not in this lifetime.
It's all right.
Don't move.
Let me hold you a little longer.
Thank you, Jiang Tiancai.
Thank you for coming into my life.
Thank you for saving me,
again and again, without hesitation.
Remember this,
I'm not Jiang Zhaohe,
and you're not your mother.
I don't care what happened before.
But from now on,
you're not alone anymore.
Since you once
pulled me out of the darkness,
I'll never abandon you.
Then, Dr. Jiang,
from now on,
please take good care of me.
Our deputy director spot is still open.
Is Director Zeng considering Dr. Jiang?
By seniority or by ability,
it should be Dr. Chen's turn, right?
He's Director Zeng's direct protégé.
If Director Zeng really had that in mind,
he would've announced it long ago.
Look how much time has passed,
and not a single word.
On the surface, Director Zeng demoted Dr. Jiang
to General Dentistry,
but secretly he's grooming him,
preparing him to surpass everyone else.
You can't tell me you didn't consider
the risk of facial nerve injury too.
You two, switch places.
Continue the surgery.
But this was clearly Dr. Chen's
plan to begin with.
Dr. Chen.
Jiang Tiancai.
You forced me into this.
Dr. Jiang.
There are photos.
He hit someone!
Look, isn't that him?
Yes, yes, that's him.
If you're gonna date, date a male doctor
who can bond with kids like that.
We're at work. Stop being so mushy.
Fired from Pingjin First Hospital for
assault, that unscrupulous Dr. Jiang
has miraculously transformed
into a rising star at a dental hospital
on the southeast coast.
It's him! That's him!
Jiang Tiancai has no medical ethics!
Unscrupulous doctor!
What are you doing?
And this guy's still a doctor?
Wisdom teeth are lucky teeth. Don't pull them if you can avoid it.
Don't be fooled!
Recurring wisdom tooth decay and swelling,
food debris always stuck while brushing,
half-erupted and stalled,
overgrown and extended,
or causing damage to adjacent teeth.
If you encounter any of these,
pull, pull, pull them out promptly!
Don't let a small issue cause big trouble!