Still won't persuade him to go to Lyon?
Persuade him?
The most important thing in our field
is respecting the patient's chief complaint.
If he wants to stay, he has his reasons.
Ten years ago, very few hospitals here
could do complex dental implant surgery.
And imported materials cost a fortune.
But now?
Materials are produced domestically.
Prices have come down.
People can afford dental care now.
Watching Jiang Tiancai face those patients
with that sincere smile,
isn't that more meaningful than
receiving an invitation from Lyon?
No matter what you say,
I won't give up.
I've loved him for fifteen years.
Even if the two of you get together,
I won't just sit back and accept it.
Actually, every single paper of yours
on postoperative analgesia optimization,
I've read several times.
I kept wondering,
how do you manage to deliver anesthesia
with such precision?
An anesthesiologist who can keep patients
fully conscious and pain-free in surgery,
for us in oral surgery,
is nothing short of a guardian angel.
There's no need to flatter me.
No, no, no.
I'm not flattering you at all.
I often think,
if I could use the latest technology to
help a kid with Congenital tooth agenesis,
restore their confidence and their smile,
so they stop hiding their smiles in shame,
then I'd feel truly proud of myself.
I hope we can both become
the brightest light
in our own fields.
Take care,
Dr. Lin.
As you wish.
Satisfied now?
Chen Pei'ang just left,
and you couldn't wait to promote me.
You're throwing me into the fire.
How am I supposed to face anyone?
You little rascal.
Stop acting like you're the victim here.
You think I don't know?
That training opportunity in Lyon,
you gave it up for Dr. Chen.
Why the General Dentistry Department?
Maxillofacial Surgery,
or it's off the table.
Young man,
don't mistake the platform for ability.
Talented people
shine wherever they go.
To recognize and correct one's mistakes
is the greatest virtue, after all.
After all, in his field,
he's a rare talent.
So you're that sure
that after he comes back,
he won't fight you tooth and nail again?
I choose to believe
in the power of belief.
Dr. Jiang,
your follow-up patient is here.
Go on then. I'll look around.
Okay.
Come on, let big brother take a listen.
It's okay.
There's just
a little bug in your tummy.
I'll help you get rid of it. Let's go.
Hey, Jiang Tiancai.
It was just a simple oral examination.
Why did you make it hurt so much?
This wisdom tooth of yours,
is just like you,
ugly, crooked, and savage.
If I didn't apply some force,
how could I get a clear look?
Your skills are clearly just subpar.
Don't go around saying that.
If anyone hears,
how will I save face as Deputy Director?
Then give me some hush money.
Use an ice pack for tooth pain.
Jiang Tiancai!
The rate of oral diseases in our country
is rising year by year,
and affecting younger people.
What does this mean?
It means our task as dentists
is getting increasingly difficult,
and our responsibility ever greater.
We must not only improve clinical skills,
but also promote oral health awareness.
Qi Yue.
Really going to the Prevention Center?
The work there isn't easier than here.
I feel public education really suits me.
I'm definitely going.
Public education really suits me.
Tech like the implantation robot, AI,
and digital doctor—these high-tech tools,
are actually gradually transforming
our traditional treatment methods.
Making treatments more precise
and efficient, while also
improving patients' comfort
and satisfaction levels.
I can not only precisely analyze
a patient's oral condition,
and provide personalized treatment plans,
but also read faces and minds,
gauging their emotions and needs,
to offer them the most attentive care.
Look, our little buddy is here.
I believe in the near future,
you'll all learn from our buddy here.
A true protégé of Director Zeng.
The student has surpassed the master.
But I think,
Precise and powerful as this machine is,
what's even more precious
is still us humans.
It's us, every Chinese dentist,
because we have warmth and empathy
that can never be replaced.
Car accident casualties
are about to arrive at the hospital.
All department doctors,
please prepare to receive patients.
Car accident casualties
are about to arrive at the hospital.
Let's go.
All department doctors,
please prepare to receive patients.
Car accident casualties
are about to arrive at the hospital.
All department doctors,
please prepare to receive patients.
As of 2026,
Registered Dentist practitioners in China
have surpassed 350,000.
They are working tirelessly
on the front lines of national oral health.
With expertise and compassion,
they strive to help every patient
smile again.
Guided by the Healthy China 2030 strategy,
over the next five years,
China's dental healthcare industry
will see even broader horizons for growth.
The dawn of public oral health management
is already in sight.