Ah!
You weren't going to throw a
barbecue party, so we prepared one!
- Ta-da!
The guesthouse manager's final schedule:
A barbecue party!
Hey, no one said
anything about night shifts.
What else do you want me to do?
Have fun!
You have to party your hardest to raise
Badam Stay's brand value, you know?
Let's go.
- Cheers!
(Episode 6: My Everyday View)
[Some drunk conversation]
I started writing novels
because of my mom, but...
Mom...
I came back because I
wanted to be comforted.
I don't usually think
about mom anymore, but...
What am I supposed to do now...
I'm dying from this hangover...
How could you not expect that when you
drink like that and have work the next day?
You're quite diligent, Boss.
Of course.
Boss, I'm here to see the property.
We listed it just yesterday,
and we got an inquiry right away.
Please take your time looking around.
It's not as neat as the pictures.
Looks a bit tacky, too.
Who's the manager here?
Yes, well, Yoon Jio over
there is the manager.
Hmm, what's the average
monthly revenue here?
Due to the nature of the
hospitality business, there's
a big difference between
peak and off-peak seasons.
No, I'm asking for the average revenue.
I judge everything by the numbers.
I absolutely despise it when people
just gloss over things with vague words.
I could tear out all the tacky stuff,
remodel it to look luxurious,
and brand it with a premium image.
Then it'd be passable.
Looking at it, the view out front
seems to be worth some money.
It seems like you'd get
along well with our President.
Your mindsets are similar,
and even the way you speak.
- I'm like that?
- She's totally the female Cha Dokyung.
I'm that obnoxious?
Actually, it'd be better to just demolish
the building and run it as a vacation rental.
You're going to demolish
Badam Stay entirely?
Well, if I can make more
money by doing that, I should.
Don't tell me you're an amateur who clings to
unprofitable things in the name of "value"?
- Excuse me!
- So,
Have you made some money?
You keep going on about money, so I
wonder just how much you've actually made.
Money?
I've made plenty. I could buy this
place in cash right now, you know?
Our boss says about 5 billion
won would be appropriate.
What?
Do you have that much?
Why would a tacky place
like this cost 5 billion?
This place is worth that much,
but seeing how you can't recognize
it, your taste must be terrible.
If you don't have it, get out.
What?
The audacity!
Ugh...
Ma'am! Ma'am!
Even a beautiful view... doesn't it
get boring if you see it every day?
Who knows?
I have a dilemma.
After spending a few days here...
Struggling to survive in the rat race?
I'm getting sick of it.
So you're going to quit
your job and run away?
With a view like this,
I think it'd be okay to run away.
Five years ago, I saw this
ocean and made a decision.
To stay here.
But is it running away?
Shouldn't it be called a challenge instead?
Courageously taking on a challenge
for the happiness of my own life.
What if money can't protect you?
What?
What if money is what
actually torments you?
Isn't that why you came here, Jio?
To be happy?
Try valuing yourself more.
Then, even the most ordinary
things will become special.
That view...
I don't think I'll ever get tired of it.
Even if I see it every day.
That's a relief.
You said it, didn't you?
That there must be a
reason why we switched.
You said it was just like
a car accident before.
You became me,
and I became you.
"Whenever the moonlight
scattered on the freezing waves,
we turned our heads to capture
the evening stars in our eyes."
It's a line from a poem I
memorized when I was young.
It must have left a deep impression,
seeing how I still remember it.
What does it mean?
What do you...
think it means?
Hmm...
To not be afraid
and be honest with your feelings?
Like being born on
completely different planets,
there are two people who
are different in every way.
Can those two fall in love?
That's nonsense.
Unless their souls switch with each other.
I'm back!
We're back to normal!
What the...
We really are back!
Huh?
Mother...
Are you sure you don't need to answer it?
Now...
I want to try living the way I want.
How do you want to live?
In a beautiful and quiet place...
with a clumsy guy,
running a guesthouse or something.
What do you think?
Sounds perfect to me.
President,
I'm working here now too, right?
Secretary Ha...
No, Assistant Manager.
Don't make any mistakes
and do your job well.
Yes, President. I mean...
Boss Cha Dokyung.
Ah, Ms. Author, congratulations
on making your deadline, too.
Ah,
I thought you were playing around all day.
When did you finish writing?
It's my style to write while I play.
Ah...
Now that I'm leaving, I feel sad.
You're coming back next year, aren't you?
Sounds good.
Let's drink until we drop tonight!
Boss,
to commemorate our fresh start,
why don't you propose a toast!
Please do!
For a new life has been turned on...
Switch!
- Switch!
- This is it, this is it...
- Ah, this is so good.
Ah, ah...
How could you do this to me?
Was I wrong about you?
Ha, this is totally...
Ah, this is a total betrayal, a betrayal...
Such a betrayal...
Ah!
"Check In to You"