Get ready.
I'll win your heart in
three...
two...
one...
I have a hundred tricks
to win, win your heart
Add another hundred
Even when you're ready to leap,
I'll always be ready to love
I'll use a hundred more tricks
to win, win your heart
Again, you're running from me
Following you around
is making me lonely
Again, you're mad at me,
But why do you have to look so lovely?
Oh Baby
Told me not to love, but I already fell
Told me not to follow,
but you've attracted me so well
Baby, I’m crush on ya
I need a way to flirt with you, yeah
I have a hundred tricks
to win, win your heart
Add another hundred
Even when you're ready to leap,
I'll always be ready to love
I'll use a hundred more tricks to win,
win your heart
Hello there, my darling
If you were a laundry,
I'd be your Rinse Charming
Ready for love,
I have two shoulders for you to lean over,
Even though they feel heavy,
carrying my own beauty (Yep)
I know, I'm just your type, aren't I?
You're so hot like fire (Huh?!)
Because my heart burns for you (Right!)
I have a hundred tricks
to win, win your heart
Add another hundred
Even when you're ready to leap,
I'll always be ready to love
Baby, I wanna tell you something…
I love you!
I have a hundred tricks
to win, win your heart
Add another hundred
Even when you're ready to leap,
I'll always be ready to love
I'll use a hundred more tricks
to win, win your heart
But we already agreed
that we'd never let
the people at the hotel know
that we are...
Dating?
I was wondering if you're interested
in taking Japanese classes with Mr. Yu.
Mr. Yu...
Gimm, the new intern…
Gimm, Gunklao Tangwatthanakul.
This Gimm
is totally Fu's type.
That's so nice of you
to treat us to snacks,
unlike some intern here, right?
What?
Moo's getting banned?
Moo and I
are in a relationship.
Huh?!
Moo!
Why are you walking away from me?
Moo,
everyone knows
that we're together already.
Hello there, Mr. Fu.
It's still inappropriate, Fu.
We're at work.
Don't you care about your image?
Forget my image.
I only care about your feelings.
I know what's happening around here.
And you're willing to sacrifice it?
The most worthwhile sacrifice
is the one that lets me love you.
You've bestowed me
the truest state of your heart,
one that's ever so meaningful.
I wouldn't trade you
for the world!
Fu.
Was that his hand or his foot?
That's one hell of a strike...
Seeing you smile
is enough to make me happy.
Though from now on,
whatever I'm gonna do,
I'll let you know beforehand.
Let me kiss you.
What was that?
So refreshing.
Hah, I'd better get back to work.
Oh!
Did I...
bruise your cheek with that kiss?
Let me see. There, there...
- Mmm!
- Fu!
Gotta go.
I bet that's worth it.
It is from the very first one.
Bye-bye.
Hello, Mr. Fu.
Hello.
Which part...
do you specifically
want to learn about today, Mr. Moo?
Gift, you can act normal around me.
I'm still the same brother to you.
Mr. Moo... I meant, Little Moo.
Uh...Mr. Little Moo,
you're too kind.
But if you insist,
I will take great care of you.
Come on.
Let's go.
Right this way.
Is this you acting normal now?
It is.
Friends,
surprise!
Shocker.
I'm having a heart attack.
Hey,
you guys already knew?
- Duh!
- We...
- We were waiting to see
when you were gonna tell us.
I... I'm really sorry
that Fu's love
broke down the walls
that engulfed my heart
into bits, shreds, and pieces.
Like, I genuinely
couldn't help falling in love.
Uh, that means
our plan
was a failure.
Oh, no. Big yikes.
Mm.
Can you shut the hell up?
Oops...
Your happiness
is overflowing from your mouth.
It's pissing me off!
From now on,
I hope you don't bring
any more headaches our way.
Hm?
Oh, there will be none.
None at all.
- Huh?!
- Papa is coming back tomorrow?!
What's the rush?
Something's up.
Or maybe...
this is about
the new son-in-law of the Dong family?
Welcome back,
Papa,
Mama!
Fu!
I miss you so much, dear.
- I miss you too, Mama.
- Are you doing well, my dear son?
- Are you?
- I am.
How about you two?
We are.
I miss you so much.
There weren't any problems
at the hotel while I was away, right?
None at all, Papa.
Everything's been fine.
Mm.
I've put a new
marketing strategy to the test,
and right now, our occupancy rate
is at a very satisfactory level.
Well done, my dear.
I know you can do it when it comes to work.
But I'm more curious about something else.
About...
Oh, about that boy?
His name is Moo, Papa.
No wonder
you weren't interested in Gimm.
Gimm...
is like a good brother to me.
A capable one at that.
I believe, in the future,
we'll probably still be doing business together.
That's good, Fu.
So where is Moo?
Introduce him to us, would you?
Oh, wow...
Not bad, not bad.
Papa, Mama,
allow me to formally introduce you to him.
This is...
Moo,
Li Muying.
Hello.
Alright.
Your name is Moo, isn't it?
Do you have time this evening?
Join us for dinner, would you?
Fu.
- Hm?
- Will your papa like me?
Who wouldn't like you
when you're this adorable, hm?
Fu, I'm serious.
Moo,
don't worry about it.
If I love someone,
my family will too.
Ever heard of the saying,
"Love me,
love my dog?"
Fu, I'm not a dog.
Fu!
Whoa, Tee!
You really dressed to the nines, huh?
Hey, Tai,
why didn't you warn him?
Jeez, Fu.
It's our family gathering, after all.
Besides,
the Dong family's eldest
son-in-law is here too,
so I had to go all out.
Ready, eldest son-in-law?
Let's go.
Papa, Mama, your Tee is here!
Mama!
While you were gone,
I missed you so, so much!
I hope that was true.
You weren't just going out
and neglecting school,
were you?
That boy does it all the time, Mama.
There!
What about you, Tai?
How have you been?
Has school been intense?
Well, it's going okay.
I'm minoring in Japanese,
and I did pretty well
on the recent quizzes.
Mm!
It's good that you're spending
your time learning languages, dear.
It'll only help you going forward.
So...
you are...
Moo,
Tai's friend, right?
Yes.
We went to the same university
and were in the same faculty.
Oh...
You're in the Faculty of Hospitality.
Mm!
So you're working in your field, then, right?
I am.
So, how do you think
the hotel should set its ADR?
How about during the high season?
Uh...
I believe
we should compare our ADR
with those of our competitors.
I also believe our service
will provide a good experience for our guests.
Therefore, we can set our ADR
seven to ten percent higher.
What is ADR?
It's basically the room rate.
Papa, you don't have
to worry about the hotel.
Today,
we're having dinner together.
Let's have a nice moment, shall we?
We don't get to see
each other very often, right, Papa?
Right, everyone?
Mm.
That's right, dear.
Alright, if anyone
wants anything else to eat,
go ahead and order it!
Papa's treat.
Then, I'd like one more Peking duck.
Mm.
- Alright.
- The whole thing's mine.
- Come on, come on, let's eat.
- Alright, let's eat.
Moo, what about you, dear?
What would you like to eat?
Uh, I'd like a bamboo pith soup, then.
Eat up, kids.
Eat up, eat up.
Yeah.
I'm so happy.
Here's your bamboo pith soup.
Papa, do you like
stir-fried chicken with cashew nuts?
He definitely does.
Eat up, darling.
How was it?
What do you think?
I'm nervous as hell right now.
Hey, come on.
It's gonna be fine.
What's that?
"Come on", my ass.
I hope your papa doesn't hate me too much.
He won't.
He's just acting tough, that's all.
Tai,
don't be such a know-it-all.
Papa...
Just go for now.
Now that I've seen Moo,
I can see why you chose him.
He's adorable, isn't he?
Very much so!
Tai!
What's wrong?
You look like you've seen a ghost.
It's Papa!
Let me be frank with you.
Well...
I don't want you two to be together.
It's not that I'm disgusted or anything,
but Fu is an executive.
For him to be with just an intern,
it's...
it's just too different a world.
If you understand,
you should let him go.
I do understand.
But sir,
I myself
won't be an intern forever.
One day,
I will be the owner of a hotel
no less grand than Golden Peony Hotel.
And I promise
I won't be a disgrace to Fu's name.
You're a confident one.
Honestly, I don't know what the future holds,
but at least
I believe it's possible.
Though if you want me to let go of Fu,
I can't do that.
To me,
letting Moo go
is just as impossible, Papa.
Because Moo...
is the one my heart belongs to.
Please give us a chance.
I...
will prove myself
to be worthy of your trust, sir.
Here comes Tee Lek's dish!
Wow, dessert is here!
Go on, scoop some for Moo,
so he can eat more.
Of course.
Here you go.
There.
There!
Tee, go easy on it, or you'll choke!
Look at you!
Ahhh!
Ooh, oh, oh...
Fu has already grown up, darling.
Let him follow his own heart for a change.
At least for this.
All this time,
he's never asked for anything,
and he's always been a good boy.
Maybe you should give them a chance.
Fu is my son.
I know exactly what kind of person he is.
You don't have to tell me twice.
Are you okay, Moo?
I am.
Why would you ask that?
Even though Papa is strict...
don't leave me, please?
Then...
let's be together forever.
How does that sound?
Thank you, Moo-Moo.
I never get lonely because of you.
Are you home alone today?
Yeah. Why?
Then...
You perv.
Just kidding.
Well,
I just wanted
to introduce myself to your family.
When everyone's home,
I'll bring you back here again.
Can't we just do a trial run today?
Fu!
Good night, Fu.
Moo,
I'm gonna kiss your cheek now.
Good night.
I'd better go.
Hey,
it seems like Fu wants to meet my family.
And what's the problem?
I'm embarrassed!
My family
gets so freaking chaotic
whenever we get together.
Plus, they're all weirdos.
Do you think
Fu will be able to accept that?
I don't think he's gonna see it that way.
Who knows?
Maybe he might even
get along well with your family,
since you said they're all weirdos.
Mm.
You know?
Apart from being weird,
he's also very lonely.
Lonely?
Ever since he was a child,
he's always been alone.
Before our family got to where it is now,
Papa and Mama
had to fly to Hong Kong for work so often.
That's why he spent
most of his time with Mimi,
which is why they were so close.
Is it delicious?
It is, it is.
Your food is the best!
I gave it my all!
Eat up, dear.
Wow, you've got great skills.
Keep pressing.
I want you to be
with your Fu-Fu a long time, Mimi.
Mimi will stay healthy
so she can be with you a long time!
But once Mimi passed away,
Fu's whole world
was consumed by loneliness.
Fu, where is Mimi?
Mimi is gone.
But since he was the eldest brother,
he had to put on a brave face,
so he could
take care of his little brothers.
He never had the chance
to enjoy his childhood,
never had time to be weak,
to be fussy,
or to be affectionate with anyone.
Until he met you.
So...
don't worry about it.
But...
I am worried about one thing.
- Lhee!
Whoa...
Jeez...
You're taking extra Japanese classes.
And what's this?
Your lover gave it to you?
Are they also Japanese?
Japanese or not,
it's none of your concern.
Give it back.
Hurry.
Is everyone present?
We're having
a physical fitness assessment today.
Everyone, partner up and get in line.
Start.
Tee, wanna be my partner?
No.
Hey, Tee. Wanna be my partner?
- You can be with James!
- Come on, dude...
You have so many friends,
so why pair up with me?
As if you have any friends to pair up with.
Is your baby really Japanese?
Is their name Doraemon?
Why aren't you saying something?
Flustered?
Tanjiro, Gojo, Nobita,
Conan, or Arale?
Cut it out!
Or what?
Ow!
Jeab, I...
Shit, Jeab is legit bleeding.
Tee's mouth must be impossible
to pry open; it didn't even bleed.
Fu!
- Hm?
- I've brought you hot cocoa.
Oh, thank you, Moo.
Have a seat.
Uh, Fu. So...
This weekend,
my dad will come to visit home,
and...
my mom will also be there.
As for my older sister,
she's free, so she wants to come as well.
So I'm thinking that you...
I'm coming.
I've always wanted to meet your family.
Shit,
how am I gonna deal with Lhee?
What did you say?
Huh?
Oh, nothing.
I just said...
Sri.
Sri?
Sri's rice porridge shop is really good.
- Oh...
- Try it out if you have time.
Yeah, let's go. Anywhere you want to.
I'm hungry. I'm gonna get off work now.
Let's go to Sri's rice porridge shop.
Whoa...
Little Chicken,
Little Chicken, Little Chicken!
Here.
Are you feeling better now?
Well...
Yeah, I am.
Is there anything you want to vent about?
You can talk to me.
Well...
I want to change schools, Yu.
At school, there's this kid
who always messes with me.
At first, I didn't care that much
because he actually
had a decent side to him.
But it has been getting worse and worse
until I can't stand it anymore.
Wait,
has he done anything harmful to you, Jeab?
This is...
from an accident, Yu.
Yu,
am I just running away from my problems
if I want to change schools?
I think so.
How about...
you try talking it out with him once more?
Okay, Yu-sensei.
Let's go.
Let's give it one more strike.
I'm already exhausted.
Strike the punching bag, not me.
Okay.
It's on you this time, okay?
Let's go.
Guys,
do you think It's impossible
to pry open my mouth?
- No, you're just foul-mouthed.
Whoa...
In unison, too.
So,
what makes you think it's impossible?
I don't know.
Maybe because a friend told me.
Well,
what did you really want to say?
Well...
"Sorry", I guess.
What?
You can say that, after all.
Yeah,
you're right.
What?
Are you in love?
Aha!!
In love?
That's nonsense.
Oh, look at him. "That's nonsense."
Hey, Tai.
My turn now.
Go on.
Moo seems very worried
about his older sister.
That Lhee girl,
is she really that terrifying?
Terrifying doesn't begin to cover it.
Moo's sister
is so damn brutal!
- Whoa, snacks.
- Yeah, take it all.
They're my favorite.
How did you know that?
- Moo-Moo,
- Thank you so much.
mine is better.
- This one is.
- This one is better.
- Oh, flowers.
- Take it.
- Please take it.
- Thank you so much.
I really love this kind of flower.
- Take it.
- Oh, this one.
Please don't take theirs. Mine is better.
Hey!
You opportunists!
How dare you
get handsy with my little brother?!
You're dead!!
Whoa,
that sounds terrifying.
You have to be really careful, Mr. Fu.
That bad?
Yeah, that bad.
I've been pursuing Moo for so long,
but I never knew about this.
In the past,
Moo wasn't serious about you,
but now
you'd better have
emergency services on dial
because you're prolly
not gonna make it
out of Lhee's den alive.
Just a tiger's den
already scares me.
Lhee or not,
I will...
win her heart.
Just you wait,
Lhee!
- Arghh?!
- Argh!!
Morning, my love.
Wow...
You're dressed like
you're going to Fashion Week.
But why did you buy
three bouquets of flowers?
The first one
is for you,
my beloved.
The second
is for the woman
who gave birth to the love of my life.
And the third
is for your beautiful older sister.
Well, well, well.
How do you know I'm beautiful?
You haven't even seen my face.
You look like you're
going to Fashion Week with him.
Hello, Lhee.
Hello there.
You really are beautiful.
Exactly how I imagined.
Mm-hm!
Such a sweet talker.
And handsome too.
No wonder...
my little brother Moo
is head over heels in love.
Lhee!
Here you go, Lhee.
Moo isn't the only one
who's head over heels in love.
Even I
am also...
religiously head over heels for Moo.
- Jeez!
- Fu, what did you just say?
Enough, enough.
I'm going to explode
hearing this as a single person
Go, Moo.
Help Mama set the table.
Are you sure?
Of course, dear. Hurry up now.
Mama is inside...
And he's Fu, right?
Yes.
I'll take care of him.
No worries.
And who is the other bouquet for?
Uh...
It's Mama's.
Don't you know
Mama is allergic to jasmine?
Uh...
I...
I apologize. I didn't know.
And who were you calling "Mama"?
Is she related to you?
Is she your mom?
She's not.
Then don't call people that.
We're not family or anything.
Let's go inside,
dear Fu.
- I'll take care of you.
- Right.
The food is served!
Wow!!
Whoa,
look at you all dressed up,
- Oh, this is nothing, Father.
- my dear daughter.
Right, honey.
Every son in that family is handsome.
With how good he looks,
I wonder how he ended up
with our son, Muying.
Papa!
Come on now.
Eat up, Fu.
I gave my all into this meal,
especially this sour curry.
It's my special recipe,
spicy and flavorful.
Thank you, Mama.
Yes, Auntie.
Goodness, what do you mean "Auntie"?
We're family now, so just call me "Mama."
Right, Lhee.
Totally!
Why hold back?
Here,
I'll serve you some sour curry.
This is Mama's special recipe.
Lhee,
Fu can't eat spicy food.
Oh, this is definitely bad.
Everyone in our family eats spicy food.
With this,
are you even going to make it as a couple?
I can eat it, Mama.
But it's spicy.
Very spicy.
Fu...
Mm-hm!
This is delicious, Mama.
Good job.
You must really like it, huh?
Here,
- this entire bowl is for you.
- Lhee!
- Hurry up.
All for you!
Come on, then. Eat up if it's so good!
- Ooh, this massive bowl
- Maybe he likes it spicy, after all.
- is all for you!
- Take this fish. This one is much spicier.
I'm so proud.
Fu actually ate it all!
Right, Mama?
Fu seems...
to be filled with so much happiness
that it's overflowing from his mouth.
Absolutely delicious, Mama.
Oh, you can even look up this share?
Sure can. Nowadays,
you can even buy fractional shares
through mobile banking apps, Papa.
No need to invest in them
in tranches anymore.
- How interesting.
- It's very convenient.
Honey, are you seeing this?
- Yeah.
- Mm...
Wow, seeing how well you get along,
you might as well spend the night here, Fu.
No!
Where is he gonna even sleep?!
Well...he can sleep in Moo's room.
Or do you want him to sleep in yours?
No!
I mean...
It's just that
our house is so, so small.
How is Fu even gonna sleep?
I'm just concerned
that he won't be comfortable.
Actually,
I'm fine with it.
I can sleep anywhere, really.
See?
This is nice.
That way, before going to bed,
you can teach me more
about these technology stocks, son.
With pleasure, Papa.
I have all night.
Since you can sleep anywhere...
And this jasmine bouquet...
Thank you. I love it so much.
It smells so good!
Here.
Take a shower here.
This is your towel.
Let me give you a peck.
Fu, what are you doing?
Someone could see us.
You can't resist it, huh?
Fu, what the heck are you doing?!
I'm leaving.
He really can't resist it, huh?
Resist what?!
Lhee!
You.
Don't even so much as think about
spending the night alone with him.
Huh?
Lhee,
are you gonna share the bed with us?
The three of us in one bed?
The hell are you rambling about?!
I mean,
I'll have my brother sleep next to me.
As for you,
go sleep by yourself.
And don't hold your breath
thinking you'd get to do my brother.
Don't worry.
You can relax and sleep in your own room
because I will
sleep downstairs in the living room.
So please don't worry that
I'll sneak over to Moo.
You have my word.
What's back there?
Oh, just scratching a mosquito bite.
So many mosquitoes here.
Lhee, what are you doing?
I miss you, that's what!
Let's sleep next to each other
as loving siblings do.
I already gave her my word
that I would sleep
downstairs in the living room.
Though,
don't worry about me.
I can sleep anywhere.
Lhee,
I know you're worried about me,
but I'm already a grown-up.
I can take care of myself.
You don't have to worry.
My Moo-Moo!
Since when did you ever grow up?
You're still a baby.
Tonight, though,
keep me company,
or else I'm gonna be so lonely.
Okay, okay, got it. I can't breathe.
Let go. I'm all squished up now.
Okay.
So, do you know how to use a condom?
Lhee!
It's important that you know how.
You have to think long and hard
before getting into it,
you know that?
Don't worry about me, Lhee.
Mm, mm.
Come on, go to sleep.
You must be really sleepy now, huh?
- Whatever you say.
- Yeah.
If you can't sleep,
just turn to face me.
That's gonna make it even harder.
Moo!
Don't excite love until the time is ripe.
Fu!
Why are you down here, Moo?
Sleeping next to you, of course.
Is that a good idea?
And...
isn't Lhee gonna throw an insane fit
if she finds out?
Mm, you're right,
I'd better go, then.
Weren't you scared
Lhee's gonna throw a fit?
Once you've entered a tiger's den,
it's not gonna be easy
to escape.
When I said "sleep,"
I meant it literally.
Don't get funny ideas.
Jeez...
Look how you shut me down.
I won't do anything to you.
But if I'm going to,
I'll tell you first.
Right.
You're not getting so scared
that you're never coming back here?
Who is?
No one here is scary.
Everyone in this family is lovely,
especially...
this one...
and this one...
Especially you.
Fu,
from now on,
you don't have to be lonely anymore.
You can get affectionate
or fussy with me anytime you want.
You mean it?
Not too much, though.
I guess...
we have to kiss now, huh?
Moo!
Don't just kiss anyone randomly.
Chinese tea pouring
is both an art and an etiquette.
We only fill the cup to two-thirds.
Two-thirds...
The first infusion
is for rinsing the tea leaves.
Rinsing the tea leaves
with the first pour...
First infusion is for rinsing the tea leaves...
After we pour it,
we need to offer the cup with both hands.
Offer the cup with both hands...
Start pouring from the right
to the left.
Okay?
Okay.
But...
will this really win your Papa's heart?
Please, Mr. Moo.
Right.
Let's start with the basics.
This is how you handle the pot.
Mr. Moo,
look at me.
Look right in my face.
Wow...
I saw sparks
in Mr. Moo's eyes
every time he said that name.
Besides, I can hear his heartbeats
going,
Thump-thump,
thump-thump, so loud and resonating.
Khem!
Should we go to a cafe together?
So, can I win your heart?
I'm not holding back anymore.
Mr. Fu is gonna turn into an unwanted dog!
I shouldn't have let them meet, should I?
Get ready.
I'll win your heart in
three...
two...
one...
I have a hundred tricks
to win, win your heart
Add another hundred
Even when you're ready to leap,
I'll always be ready to love
I'll use a hundred more tricks
to win, win your heart
Again, you're running from me
Following you around
is making me lonely
Again, you're mad at me,
But why do you have to look so lovely?
Oh Baby
Told me not to love, but I already fell
Told me not to follow,
but you've attracted me so well
Baby, I’m crush on ya
I need a way to flirt with you, yeah
I have a hundred tricks
to win, win your heart
Add another hundred
Even when you're ready to leap,
I'll always be ready to love
I'll use a hundred more tricks
to win, win your heart