MY ROYAL NEMESIS
CLOSED TODAY
Boss, is that a woman right there?
I can see just fine. Drag her out. Raze
everything to the ground!
-Yes, boss!
-What the hell?
-Huh?
What's going on?
Who the hell are you?
I'm Cha Se-gye, I'm in charge of Chail.
I don't know you, should I?
-Hey! Come on! Hey!
-Get him! Get him!
-Hey!
-You're not goi--
-Get him, damn it!
-Hey! Stop him!
Hey, come on!
Get him already! Come on!
Oh! Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Stop now! Police! Cease all operations.
-Shin Seo-ri.
-Hey!
Are you okay?
-Cha Se-gye.
-Yeah.
What is it?
It's too bright.
It's hurting my eyes.
Shin Seo-ri.
EPISODE 13
TWIST OF FATE
-What's going on? Is she all right?
-I think she needs assistance. She really
I don't know, I just saw her on the
ground, it's--
-Has she been there for a long time?
-doesn't look well. Someone must
-Dan-sim, can you hear me?
-come help.
-Oh. She's opening her eyes,
-Are you all right?
Dan-sim!
My name is Seo-ri. Why is she…
Your breathing has stabilized
considerably, and your overall numbers
look fine, sir. As long as there are no
secondary infections or rebleeding,
you should be discharged the week
after next.
Sir, I don't know anything about it.
I have nothing to do with Mr. Cha's
company or your accident. My only
intention was to work with Mr. Choi
for mutual benefit. That's it.
And if you continue to keep your mind
completely at rest, your memory should
gradually recover too.
I see, thank you. I will keep that
in mind.
Contact the Commissioner General and
tell him that I want to see him.
Are you okay?
What?
I just want to know if you're okay.
You're like a ghost. Nothing gets
past you.
What can I do?
I'm not able to turn back time. It's no
good getting angry or crying over it.
I have to focus on the present
and just do whatever I can.
What is it? Has something happened?
Cha Se-gye.
I've always felt, all this time, life was
a punishment for me.
Each day I…
I felt I was being punished.
That pigheaded child. I can't believe she
threw herself into the river.
That wretch has no fear. Darn it.
We have already signed her away into
slavery, but her senses have taken
leave of her and she doesn't even
know her own name. What are we to do?
What do you mean, what are we to do?
She can be a slave if she doesn't
know her name. Send her off as soon as
she gets up!
For goodness sake.
Why had I ever been born if the
only thing awaiting me was punishment?
Ugh, the miserable face on that girl
is getting on my nerves. If you
keep that up after you're sold off, you
won't last long.
Hey, hey, where are you going? Damn, you
wretch!
Hey! Lock her in the shed and don't
give her a drop of water.
If that was how my life was going to be,
I'd rather…
Open this! Open it!
The lowly wretch is soon to meet her end.
Ugh, these are the end times indeed.
How dare that lowly wench do something
like that?
I'd rather…
Who knows? It could be black magic
to bring about the Queen's death.
SACRED SITE OF
THE ILLUSTRIOUS GRAND PRINCE CHEONGHEON
Not have been born at all.
Even when I landed here, although I told
myself I'd consider it a gift and
make it out to be something of a… a
second chance of sorts,
It still felt like another punishment.
I wondered what kind of suffering
this life would bring.
But do you know what's interesting?
I think I've smiled a little more
since coming here.
Since meeting grandma and since meeting
you my mind's been put at ease a little
for the first time in my life.
So I've decided to call it even.
I'm going to think of it as a
reward. I'm going to think of it
as getting all the rewards I missed out
on all at once.
Cha Se-gye,
let's never part and grow old together.
I won't let you go.
I won't let you go anywhere.
Se-gye, I'm the one who's not going.
There's no reason to go back now.
Because I'm exactly…
where I should be.
She had a high fever overnight, but
we administered some antipyretics
and she's much better now. Even so, the
wind is cold, so try to go in soon.
Grandma.
It's your grandaughter.
It's me. Your grandaughter is here.
Won't you look at me, at least?
Young lady.
This man right here, is he… is he your
boyfriend?
Yes, I am her boyfriend.
What a tall and handsome young man,
just like my husband. He wasn't
much good at making money, although he
really had a lovely face.
I'm good at earning money as well, ma'am.
As I said last time,
I'm a successful business man.
This boy sure knows how to talk the talk.
Pretty confident for a man who's lost
everything.
Young lady, who are you?
Why are you being so good to me?
What do you mean? I'm his girlfriend.
Don't cry.
It's okay.
What was all that yesterday? Telling me
to come there out of nowhere.
No other option. They came without
warning. It shook me up too.
Well, you should've kept me in the loop.
Same with your backroom deal with
-Inspector Lee.
-How dare you call it a backroom deal?
Make a deal with me.
Don't tell me you're trying to
make a plea deal with an active
duty police officer?
Just sharing info. From what I've seen,
the cartel inside the police force
runs as deep as sweet potato vines.
When it comes to guerrilla-style combat,
timing's key. Gotta strike while the
iron's hot. And speaking of timing,
I need you to work off site. Keep
an eye on yesterday's restaurant.
Don't know when they'll come back.
It'll be good for her to get some
fresh air rather than just staying
in her room all day.
Could I have a word with you, Ms. Shin?
We just wanted to let you know that
her meds are gonna be…
You have high standards, young man.
Very high.
You sure have picked a good one.
What are you saying?
How do you know when you pretty much just
met her right now?
Just met her right now? She's my child
that I raised with my own two
hands. Hey, there is something I'd
really like to say.
Oh, okay, just wait here. I'll go get her
right--
No.
Not Seo-ri, you. I have something I
want to say to you.
So, it wasn't a spirit possession, but a
reclamation? Not a forced occupation,
just a triumphant return?
At just 12, you landed in Joseon
and lived as a court lady until you were
executed by poison, at which point
you returned to the present day.
I've never come across a case like
this one before.
It's essentially like discovering
a whole new continent. Oh, now I get it.
That's why I thought that transcendent
vision I had was odd. She had
your looks, but it didn't seem like she
was you.
Must've been the girl.
Anyway, the conclusion I've come to
is that I never have to experience a
transcendent vision ever again nor be
possessed by a spirit.
Congratulations, Your Highness.
No, no, no.
Do not address me as "Your Highness"
anymore. I'm Seo-ri, alright?
Shin Seo-ri. That's my name now.
A-ha. Shin Seo-ri? Oh, yes. This really
is the start of a new life for you.
If I am to make a proper fresh
start, I need to prune the
rotten branches and get some things in
order.
His Majesty the King has issued
his decree. Huibin Kim, you have
committed the most heinous crime of
disrupting the order of the royal court,
and as such, you shall be put to death
by poison.
Is it a crime for one to have loved His
Majesty? I must see the King. Allow me a
proper audience with him.
Force it down.
You wenches! You unhand me this instant!
Bring His Majesty here!
Bring him here at once.
I shall not perish like this.
Bring it in!
So you are truly determined to kill me
and rid yourself of me? Very
well. Let us die together today.
I will have my revenge.
Wow, you totally killed the poison
drinking scene. The dopeamine
hit is unreal. It feels like you've
experienced that.
Practice makes perfect, they always say.
It's thanks to me if rating soar.
Noona, the director said he should bring
you back in season three as the twin,
with just a mole on your nose.
Dying young really creeps me out though.
Next time, I'm living to an old age.
Makeup team. Could you wipe the blood off
Seo-ri's lips please?
Look at you, all excited, Shin Seo-ri.
Hey, you. Bring me some water.
Oh. Oh, gosh.
I appreciate it.
Where's the wrap party for Seo-ri's
last shoot?
Wrap party?
Haven't you been invited?
Oh, uh…
Whoa, no way. After looking out for you,
she's suddenly decided she doesn't like
you anymore?
Wait, what do you mean looking out
for me?
You don't know? She's the one who got
you your role. It didn't take her
long to flip after overstepping
when she was a substitute hire.
Shows how fickle she is. Who does
she think she is anyway, to tell me to
come to her wrap party?
Apparently, she's a family member
of the nurse. Security's been trying to
force her out, but they can't.
DEATH OF NURSE AN SEONG-HUI
I DEMAND THE TRUTH
Why is she here rather than at Biojei?
It must've been Cha that leaked the info
to her.
Get rid of her…
before the word gets out.
Yes, sir.
Yeah, but she never would've said that
had you been there.
Is he still coming or is he gonna bail?
-You did a great job. Seriously.
-You really did a great job. Gosh. It was
-You really did a great job.
-honestly good. This is so delicious.
-We need a toast. Seo-ri, make a toast.
-Go on.
All right, guys. Thank you for coming
to celebrate my completion of filming.
In all of your personal lives, and in
your work lives, I wish you health
and longevity, and great success. Now,
everyone, say, "Muyaho!"
-Muyaho?
-What?
-M-- muyaho?
-Uh…
-Muyaho?
Muyaho?
Muyaho!
Oh, muyaho!
Yeah, muyaho!
Yeah, that's right!
Cheers! Cheers.
Hell yeah!
Cheers.
Wow, that is so--
What are you all doing here? Are you
friends with Seo-ri?
Well, Gwang-nam kept asking us to come,
so honestly, it was kinda hard to keep
turning him down.
Right. I'm sure that's all it is.
Eat and drink up, everyone. Boss man's
got this.
Hey. Gwang-nam, quit getting drinks for
everyone else and drink with us.
Hey, yeah.
Let's do a cheers.
I gotta drive tonight, so you guys
drink my share for me.
Oh, wow. You're so nice.
What's with your voice? I really
love your voice.
My voice?
Let's toast with water.
-Come on. Cheers.
-Cheers.
Dude, seriously?
No. Not as much as he's had, not at all.
-Huh? What's this? What's this? Wait,
-What are they bringing in? Hey, what's
-what's going on?
-the deal?
Wow, this is nuts.
-Is it for us? Gift bags, no way.
-Dang, for everyone, or…
-Huh?
-Here you all are.
Cha Se-gye.
What're you doing at my wrap party?
I heard Biojei's brand ambassador,
Seo-ri, has just finished her last shoot
today, so I prepared gift bags for the
film crew.
Oh…
First of all, the Dynaestie Premium
three-piece set for your beauty. A Chail
-Conic Bluetooth speaker.
-Nice!
Oh, dang. That's amazing!
The full Chail Tech set comprising watch,
tablet, and also a headset.
I can't believe it.
-Shin Seo-ri! Shin Seo-ri! Shin Seo-ri!
-Shin Seo-ri!
-Shin Seo-ri! Shin Seo-ri!
Shin Seo-ri! Here they come
Shin Seo-ri!
This is so great.
-Shin Seo-ri! Shin Seo-ri!
Really, it's nothing.
Are you trying to bankrupt yourself?
Why are you throwing all this
money around?
I'm investing, that's all. This
industry's a small world. Could run
into these people again. That's why
you invest in stuff that will gain
compound interest.
Compound interest? You should worry about
yourself instead of spending your money.
When are you going to stop living so
carelessly?
What's this, Shin Seo-ri? Do you worry
about me day and night? I'll be busy
so we won't see each other. How will you
handle that?
Why do I keep seeing couples everywhere?
-Gwang-nam.
-Yes.
How long are you planning to work as
Shin Seo-ri's manager? Don't your
parents say anything?
They have been nagging me to move
home, actually. But I really
don't want to live in the countryside.
What's wrong with that?
Living in the countryside is my dream.
Kinfolk style.
"Kinfolk."
Kinfolk, my ass. Didn't you say
everywhere outside of Gangnam was
just a rural dump? And that you could
never live anywhere lower than the 20th
floor?
When did I say that?
Well, I only meant that the air
quality is bad in Seoul on lower floors.
Yeah, I have heard that as well.
I live on the second floor of a
-boarding house, and if someone smokes
-Oh. Really?
A cigarette outside, there's literally no
escaping it. And the room is so
-Wh--
-small that the smell lingers forever.
-It's the worst.
-Oh, you live in a boarding house? Why?
Why? Uh… 'Cause I'm, um… I don't have a
deposit?
So why in the world don't you have a
deposit? Oh, are your parents doing that
on purpose to teach you independence?
Independence?
Oh, nah, nah. Oh, no. My parents used to
always have about five million won
on hand, it's just they got scammed last
year while getting stuff for their
mini-mart.
Mini… mini mart?
Yes, they run a small mini mart.
The Thousand Nyang Department Store.
But in our neighborhood, it basically
counts as a general store.
Oh, Th-- Thousand Nyang, Thousand Nyang
Department Store. Nice.
Very nice.
Know what? There aren't that many
things that cost one 1.000 won
in the store. Prices have gone up so
much these days that most things
cost at least 3,000 won.
Ugh, God.
Why would you go around saying stuff
about me that you have no clue about?
I didn't… Well, you said yourself
on the phone that you were the son of a
department store owner--
Oh, so you were just eavesdropping
on my phone call then.
Mr. Baek, I'm offended right now.
And it's not even just today.
Your attitude's been offensive right from
the beginning. Well, I'm not gonna
put up with it. I don't want you as my
manager So you're fired as of--
I'm done with this! And I won't
do this any longer.
D-- did you just throw down the car key?
As manager?
What are managers? Tell me. Are we not
people?
Screw it, I hope you fail at life.
Mr. Baek! You won't get away with this!
Wh-wh- wh- why is he coming back?
Wh-wh-wh- wait. Wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait.
This goes back to the company.
Are you serious? Hey! How am I
supposed to get home?
Once Seo-jun's school documents
are sorted, would you take care
-of him until I get a nanny? And
-Yes, sir.
Also baseball tickets.
Two tickets for this weekend. Okay?
Seo-jun would like that.
Chairman Choi Mun-do, right? I'm
Inspector Lee Han-su from Seobu Police.
I'd like to ask you a few questions about
the death of nurse An Seong-hui.
I'm sorry, death?
I think he's referring to the case
that Cha Se-gye is involved in.
I can't think how I'd be able to
help you. I don't have much contact with
Se-gye.
I'll decide whether you have contact
with him or not. It's a simple
investigation, I'd appreciate your
cooperation.
I have no reason to help you with this
investigation. If you have questions for
me, issue an official summons.
Uh, Mr. Choi.
REFUSED QUESTIONING
Inspector Lee said, Choi Mun-do's initial
response has been to deny knowledge of
the case. He told the inspector
to issue a summons. I wonder if
that's just buying him time to prepare.
That was my intention. I want to see how
that busy bee moves now.
That busy bee?
When Mun-do was at Chail, they weren't
even indicted, despite all the corrupt
bids. That means the cartel is
very tightly knit. So that's where we
start with this. The very foundation of
Choi Mun-do's power, Chail E&amp;C.
INTERNAL POLICE ACCOMPLICE
KEY ACCOMPLICE
I just found out that the police
officer from Seobu Police Station
questioned Cha.
It seems Se-gye is upset with me. I guess
because I humiliated him in front of
his girl. Does he seriously think he can
pressure me with a nobody inspector?
Prepare a press release. "Former Biojei
CEO Cha Se-gye. Not an ousting, but
an escape. Sucked retail investors dry,
sold shares, and walked away with
over one hundred billion won." Use that.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Choi, check the internet right now.
(EXCLUSIVE) THE TRUE FACE
OF CHAIL CHAIRMAN CHOI MUN-DO EXPOSED!
CHAIL CURRENT CHAIRMAN CHOI MUN-DO'S
ALLEGED BRIBERY FOR CONSTRUCTION CONTRACTS
Choi Mun-do's a pro at manipulating
public opinion with rumors. Being on
the receiving end of it messes with
your head more than you think.
We're taking real action to try and
stop Choi Mun-do's key business, the
resort project. We'll use the fact
that he illegally hired thugs to acquire
ACT ON THE PUNISHMENT OF VIOLENCE, ETC.
ARTICLE 2, PARAGRAPH 2
the city of Jusan, which is just ten
kilometers away from the site,
is pushing to build an international
airport. He'll be hit from both sides.
Internally, by investors, and externally,
by the public. The construction
will then come to a halt.
But Choi Mun-do won't just sit there and
take it.
Of course he won't. He'll come after me.
So then it's a matter of who's worse,
him or me? The media won't know who to
attack more.
So how do you plan to get yourself
out of this?
I won't get out of it. Why?
I have nothing to lose.
The heirs to Chail, Korea's top
conglomerate, are embroiled
PUMP AND DUMP VS. BRIBERY
THE FUTURE OF CHAIL TAINTED BY CORRUPTION
accusations of bribery. Criticism of
Chairman Choi Mun-do is also mounting
ACTING CHAIRMAN CHOI MUN-DO,
ALLEGED USE OF HIRED THUGS TO SECURE SITE
Illegal land purchase. All of these
allegations are groundless. If you
suddenly demanded early repayment
based on fake news from an unknown
figure--
I hear they're going to build an airport
next to the site.
Just ten kilometers away.
Oh, that's…
It's a good thing I have connections
at City Hall. Otherwise, I wouldn't have
had a clue until they broke ground.
If they build an airport next to the
resort, noisy planes will be flying
overhead all the time. How's that
gonna work? Who would actually want
to stay there?
As far as I know, the airport's in the
concept stage. Where did you hear
about that?
I looked into it. Turns out the current
mayor of Jusan is running for
re-election, and securing an
international airport is her key
campaign pledge.
The mayor of Jusan?
Yes, the resort project will progress
without hiccups. We'll also put out the
groundbreaking schedule at our fiftieth
anniversary event.
I'll take that as a promise.
After Songjin, you'll support
Jusan City. After all, a resort is
better than an airport.
Her aide said it wasn't a key campaign
pledge until a month ago, however, she
suddenly changed her stance.
It sounds like…
there's been some kind of deal.
Ms. Jang. You talked like you couldn't
handle it, but you're crushing the
biggest three cardio workouts from hell.
I'm in your hands, alright? I'm
building up my fitness 'cause of
what you promised.
Of course. I'll pave the way straight to
the Blue House for you. You won't walk,
you'll fly right in.
Should we try some strength training
next?
Sure. Over here.
Mochang's got some serious pull. It takes
one word from you to get an
airport built.
You're always taking from me.
When are you going to start
-paying me back?
-Come on now.
Once Jusan Airport opens, I know all
your businesses will get spots in the
duty-free stores. Your jewelry
brand, your restaurants, and
your outdoor lines.
There's got to be something I get for it.
I wouldn't do all this work for you
just because I like you.
I like that mindset. I wanna keep
working as partners.
Yeah, sure, let's do that.
Songjin Resort, Chail's flagship project,
has hit a major roadblock. The city
of Jusan, located ten kilometers from the
site, has announced it's plan to attract
an international airport. This raises
serious questions about the suitability
of the location. Analysts say the
project will be extremely difficult to
move forward with unless the design
is overhauled.
CHAIRMAN CHOI MUN-DO IN DIRE STRAITS,
CORRUPTION SCANDAL, PROJECT ROADBLOCK
During his Chail E&amp;C days, Choi
Mun-do, who recently stepped in as
acting chairman for the company, is now
facing his biggest crisis since taking
the job. Some observers are comparing
Choi Mun-do's management woes to
CHAIL UNDER CHOI MUN-DO IN TURMOIL
FOLLOWING OUSTING OF CHA SE-GYE
Why are they dragging me into this?
Is this what they mean by "blowing
your nose without using your hands?"
And when did you butter up Jusan's mayor?
The more insignificant the politician,
the more they want to flip the game with
a shiny badge.
I just gently scratched that itch
for her, and her ambition took off
on its own.
Choi Mun-do has to be fuming this time.
You always reap what you sow. I'm just
collecting on all the bad karma mileage
that asshole has racked up.
Wow, now you're even showing up
unannounced? Really?
You're supposed to be busy.
Why are you sitting around at home? You
should at least watch something. Oh.
You wanna watch something? Hey, move
-out the way!
-Oh, it's Cha Se-gye.
No, it's not.
Huh? Yes, it is. I definitely saw you.
No, you saw wrong.
Hey, I saw it. It was definitely
Cha Se-gye.
No.
-Damn it.
What a surprise to see you here. What do
you want?
Fine. Well then, why don't we just
get straight to the point.
Yes, Se-gye. It's finally time for us
to properly join forces. As you know,
your grandfather isn't doing okay, plus
the company's now in a really awful
state, obviously you know. At times
like this, I say the family must
all support each other.
Think about it. Why is Chail called
Chail? Because it belongs to the Cha
family. But,
the head of the company is Choi Mun-do.
That's Choil, not Chail. The name
itself is a contradiction, right?
Right. We can't have Choil.
Right? We can't have that, can we?
But since when were we family? Aren't I
just the little thief to you guys?
Se-gye. Fine, I admit it. we actually
haven't been the closest aunts and
nephew. But when have we ever treated
you like that?
Oh, so I'm not a thief.
I'm just a jerk.
Hey!
Just watch your mouth, will you?
We're here to suggest we work together,
especially with father laid up.
At least get the story straight.
You're not here to work together,
you're here to beg. 'Cause teaming up
with an asshole's better than nothing.
Cha Se-gye! How dare you use
that langauge in front of your elders?
This is why I didn't want to come here.
I was willing to overlook your
mistakes because you're family, but your
attitude is rotten to the core!
Who's rotten to the core?
Cha Se-gye, why are you sitting here
listening to that nonsense?
-Oh…
-Just throw them out of here.
What the hell are you doing here? What?
Are you two together now?
What? You know this girl?
How do you two know each other?
You still haven't learned your
lesson after I beat you with taffy?
I guess I went too easy on you.
You got beaten with taffy? Oh, my God,
no.
What? Did you hit her?
What are you saying? She gave me
a one-sided beatdown.
You're not the type to get beaten up by
anyone.
Listen…
Calm down, Cha Se-gye. I didn't get hit a
single time. It's true your aunt's
the one who was completely owned.
That's what I said. I was the
clear victim, not her.
And yet, here you still have the nerve
to come crawling to harass your nephew.
What? What now? What-- What? What are
you doing? Why did you pluck that out?
Oh, crap.
A good beating's the best medicine for
an attitude problem.
You dumb thug, you! Fine. Come at me.
Come at me, come at me. I've got
backup today. Oh. Hey!
Hey, get out!
Jesus…
What is this? You had to defend me from
my own family?
Those aunts of yours. You'd think
they'd help their nephew. Cha Se-gye,
don't worry. I taught them a lesson, so
they'll leave you alone now.
I know, I was so scared. What would I do
without you?
How smooth.
Are you okay? We can't have you
collapsing again. You're warm.
I'm taking you to the hospital right now.
Okay, let's go. Since I'm starting over,
I should introduce myself.
Wait, what do you mean?
Let's go visit your grandfather together.
How are you feeling? The doctor
says you're recovering, but you
still don't have your memory.
I'm sure it will come back soon.
And if it doesn't, so be it. It doesn't
really affect my life anyhow.
You should keep an eye on the chairman.
I think that he might be up to
something shady. And I think he might be
lying about his memory too. The way
the police and the media move together,
I doubt this would be the work of
Cha alone.
As long as you're good, I'm okay with it.
-Just focus on getting better for now.
-Huh?
And stay away from newspapers.
What's the rush? We easily could've just
left it for a while.
You said your grandfather wanted to
see me.
Yeah, but he didn't mean while
he's in the hospital.
You're visiting together? Have you
forgotten already? I told you
not to visit him for the time being.
Yeah, well… I don't ever listen
to others.
If you care about uncle's health, you'd
better not say anything unnecessary.
It won't do him any good to hear about
the troubles at the company.
The elderly can die at the drop of a hat.
Let them in. If he has any decency,
he'll follow.
Wait here. I'll let him know.
I really owe you quite a lot, Ms. Shin.
Whenever I find myself in a jam,
you're there. I hope you have a good
visit.
Hold on. We have to talk.
Are you sure it's okay for us to meet in
private like this? Se-gye's an awfully
jealous guy.
You find this fun? Toying with people?
No one works for fun. This is just a
matter of survival.
I have no hard feelings toward you,
Ms. Shin, so don't hate me. The resorts,
well… that's something I've staked my
life on.
Yes, you don't care about the means
if you can achieve your goal.
I used to know someone like that.
They were just like you.
What happened to this person? Did they
achieve their goal?
He sure did. He ascended to a
blood-stained throne and ruled over
people like livestock, before withering
away all alone.
In history, he's recorded as a wise king.
Victors write history, anyhow.
Would you like me to tell you a
secret about life? Karma, be it good
or bad, always comes back to you.
What goes around, comes around, and your
own reckoning is only just starting.
Is that a threat?
It's a warning that I won't sit idly
by anymore.
Enduring it once was quite enough for me.
In this life, I will protect me
and mine, and I'll do that no
matter what.
A declaration of war.
Guess we'll see whether you can protect
yourselves in all this.
What makes you think you can just show up
unannounced at this hour to make an
introduction?
This is the first time I'm asking this
of you. So please, do it for me this
once and force yourself to smile.
You wait outside.
I won't leave. How do I know what
you'll say to her?
Do as he says, wait outside.
If he spouts nonsense, please come out.
That- that rotten boy.
I don't like you very much. You are
an orphan who has no one to rely on.
You're not the right person for
him. Listen, I'm not changing my mind on
this.
I understand. Because until
recently, I felt the same way.
Although, I can't help it. Now that
I've been given a new life, I just
can't imagine myself without Cha Se-gye.
I never want to let go of his hand now.
You've made up your mind. So then why are
you here?
To inform me?
Yes, I'm here to inform you I'll
make your grandson happy.
And I'll never leave him alone again.
You can trust me.
Sir, Mr. Choi is here for you.
The case was suddenly transferred to
Seobu Station. Said it came from above,
but I don't think it came from the
captain.
I'm sure it'll come back eventually.
And if it doesn't, then so be it.
Interesting.
Now, I think it'll be hard to
bury this if the investigation goes any
further. In the worst case, it could
even lead to charges. You should
start cleaning things up I think.
You're right. Some cleanup is definitely
needed.
I will have my revenge!
KINGDOM OF WOMEN 2 (FIRST RUN)
Look at that. The venom in her eyes.
FINALE
Oh, my gosh. I'm petrified she'll
appear in my dreams.
"Petrified?"
You wench!
She's very pretty to me.
Oh, you still recognize your
granddaughter? Even as you're losing it,
you're still blinded by love. She looks
like an angel in your eyes.
I'm here to frighten you.
Gosh, when did you get here?
The granddaughter's here. In real
life, you look like an angel.
Oh, I do?
-Yes.
-I'm not venomous now?
I will rip you apart to death!
Let's wait and see, Your Majesty.
Grandma.
What are you staring at? Something there?
The stop. Bus stop.
Where are you in such a hurry to
go? I just got here.
And I have a lot to share with you.
Why do you keep talkiing about the bus?
Your granddaughter's here. Speak to me.
Why can't you look at me?
What's this?
A glamping date. What do you think?
Isn't it awesome? I mean, this thing's
essentially a house on wheels.
Why put a house on wheels? Evacuation?
Why would we evacuate? This isn't
the Korean War.
Do you want to stargaze with me.
You can't ever find stars when you're in
Seoul. You'd have to go at least as far
as Gangneung or Sokcho.
Why go all the way there? This yard
here is absolutely perfect.
Perfect? What, the view of those
apartments?
The warmth of the fire here reminds
me of my childhood. One day, a tiger
appeared, and I ran away. I almost
fell into a lake and perished.
Dang, is… is this really the time
for that?
I meant this is the opposite of
that time.
The fire is warm, you're beside me.
Man…
After that wild detour through that
time and finally arriving here,
it's like I've woken from a dream.
I still can't quite grasp it, that I'm
back here. It's my home again.
If you can't believe it, think how
I feel. I dream about it every night.
Do you still have dreams about it?
Let's not. What a dumbass. I'm
totally not like him.
Of course not. You're a different
pereson. You were the first one to
look at me with kindness and fill up
my heart.
When I think of you. I feel like
I could fly…
but then I get scared I'll lose you.
My heart goes back and forth…
dozens of times a day.
But I don't really care at all.
Is love often like that?
Is this what people mean when…
they refer to love?
Hey, why did you have to beat me to it?
The man should be the first one to
say that.
What a boomer thing to say. Who cares?
I want… a do-over. I'm gonna splurge and
then make the most romantic--
You're gonna keep on do-- And coming
over here without--
Kissing me whe--
I'll keep doing it. If you save it up,
it turns to crap. Didn't I say that?
Stop it already, would you? Just stop it.
Take it inside. If you're gonna sit
-out here and rub it in, do it inside.
-Let's… Can I stay over?
How did we rub it in?
He showed up out of nowhere…
so I guess I have to come in. I have
no choice.
Did you turn off the boiler?
Is it broken? You're sleeping this way?
What? What's wrong?
You could freeze to death in here.
It's even colder than out there.
This is practically a balmy spring day.
When I stayed in the mountains,
I thought my nose would fall off from
the freezing cold.
Ugh, enough of that talk.
-We're going to my place.
-What? No, we can't. We've been drinking.
Ah…
See, you shouldn't have downed
drinks like that.
Cha Se-gye, come in here. Let's share
a blanket.
I'm not that cold.
I actually run pretty hot.
Always have.
Whatever. Your nose is red, you know.
Hey you, freeze right now.
-Huh?
-Hands up, right now. Come on.
How's this? You like it?
Who suggests hugging by… by yelling,
freeze?
I said it because your face looks like a
criminal.
What?
It's nothing.
Work's been rough lately, right?
Why don't you take a break? Go off on
a trip or something?
A trip?
Go abroad for a little bit breathe
some fresh air. Think of it as a bonus.
Starting tomorrow, guard the chairman's
hospital suite. You don't have to
pick up Seo-jun anymore.
SONGJIN GENERAL HOSPITAL
She must be at the bus stop again.
Should I have gotten a bigger one?
You're here. I was just about to
call you.
Is my grandma at the bus stop now?
Her condition suddenly took a turn
for the worse. She's been moved to
the ICU.
She had a seizure, so we moved her
to the ICU. We've gotten her through
the worst with medication. She's been
holding on for a long time now.
Listen to me very carefully. In life,
there will be storms with thunder
and lightning. When it comes, an
umbrella won't be enough for her.
Just stand and get wet with her.
You can endure a lot of things, if
you're not alone. Having someone helps.
So… can I trust you'll be there?
No matter what happens, you must
protect her.
You can't even die before her!
Yes.
Yes,
I'll protect her. I will.
Go get some sleep. I'll stay here.
No, I don't know when she'll wake up.
You should go.
I can't leave you here alone.
Wait here. I'll go get you some
clothes and something to eat.
Grandma. Grandma, are you awake? Are you
all right?
Should I… get the doctor? The doctor…
Bus… The bus s--
-What, Grandma?
-stop…
B-- bus stop? Y-- you wanna go to the
bus stop?
Where is…
the bus headed?
Where am I headed?
Why are you saying you're going
somewhere? You can't go right now,
there's… There's no time, there's…
grandma.
Where am I headed?
Grandma.
Come on. Come on. No, wait, wait, wait.
Wait.
Grandma. Grandma?
Grandma, where you're headed will…
Grandma, where you're headed will be…
Grandma, you look good today.
Yes, I'm feeling great right now.
Wanna make a run for it?
Run away? Now?
Quickly, now. Let's go.
-Where's her guardian?
-What is it?
-Goodness. Ms. Nam!
-Huh?
We'll sneak out of your room.
After them!
-Ugh.
-Oh, oh, Ms. Nam.
Ms. Shin!
People are running after us.
-Ms. Nam.
-But we managed to shake them off.
Damn.
-Hey, Ms. Nam!
-Where are they?
Ms. Nam.
Let's go.
Let's go. No one can stop us.
At the bus stop, the bus is waiting
for us.
You get in the driver's seat, and we
take off.
Let's go.
Oh, this is great. The sky is clear,
and I have you with me.
We drive along the mountain roads,
passing all the other cars. As we
speed along, the wind blows past us.
Every time we pull up at a bus
stop, people cheer for us, as they
applaud and smile.
All aboard.
-Hey, wait a minute.
-Come on in.
-Where are we going,
-Ms. Nam.
It's been awhile since I saw you.
Aw, thank you so much.
How are you doing?
Hello, hi.
Ms. Nam, where are we going today?
Somewhere nice.
Let's roll!
All right, everybody.
Yes, let's go.
-We're off! We're off! Yay!
-Let's go, let's go.
-All right!
-Here we go!
This is gonna be so great! Yeah!
Let's sing.
Yeah, yeah, let's all sing!
One, two, three, four.
The day when the sun shines brightly
will return. The day when the sun shines
brightly will return. I'm here.
The day when the sun shines brightly
will return. The day when the sun shines
brightly will return. I'm here.
Hey!
Forget all your sadness and loneliness.
Nothing is impossible if you try.
The day when the sun shines brightly
will return. The day when the sun
-shines brightly will return.
-Hey!
All right!
And so everyone…
happily rides together.
Happily?
Yes. happily.
And then we…
keep on driving until we reach the
end of the world.
There are no tears or sadness there.
Everyone blesses you with a smile.
They praise you for doing a great job.
They tell you this life was a success.
Of course…
it was a success. With this life, I was
lucky.
And that's the way you go back…
to where you came from.
To how you looked before.
Happily, with a big smile.
You're here, my angel is here.
Grandma!
Grandma.
Grandma. Grandma…
Seo-ri's here. Seo-ri's here now.
Grandma…
Seo-ri's here now.
-Mom. Mom!
-Hi! How was school?
Okay.
-Thank you.
-No, no, it was the-- It's on me.
Hello. Okay, bye.
-I can't wait. See you later.
-It's okay, I don't mind.
Your nanny's a bit busy, that's why
I'm here.
Okay.
Where is he? Is he in bed?
Um, he's not home at the moment.
What do you mean?
The nanny said your chauffeur picked him
up.
Get all the CCTV footage around the
school and track all his movements.
Search anywhere Seo-jun could've gone
SECRETARY SEO
INCOMING CALL
Where have you been?
At the hospital with the chairman.
Why are you there? Why?
The chairman wanted to see Seo-jun.
Uncle, what are you doing?
What? It it wrong for a grandfather to
want to see his grandson? You should've
brought him to see me sooner.
If it weren't for Seo, I wouldn't
even have known he was here.
Are you threatening me by taking Seo-jun?
Why are you going this far?
Yes. I always knew you were rotten
inside, but I didn't know the
full extent of it. I shot myself in
the foot by having faith in a beast
like you. You're not even human, so why
should I treat you like one?
Even animals cherish their own offspring.
Can't you see, a child is precious to
their parents?
Why do you keep harassing a kid who
grew up without his dad's love?
There's a limit to how much I
can tolerate!
If that's all true, you should've
taken better care of him from the start.
The scars you get as a boy last
a lifetime.
Nothing hurts so much as when your
child falls over. I felt like all
the blood was draining from my body
earlier.
If you hate me, you should've
come for me. Why'd you have to
involve my child.
You've issued…
a real threat. And you've crossed a
line you shouldn't have. From now on,
everything you have coming is on you.
Accept that.
She never wore them.
She saved them and they're not even that
special.
I wish she hadn't.
Are you sure you wanna stay here?
You haven't gotten any sleep yet or had
anything to eat.
If you're not hungry, at least have some
fruit. Wait here.
It looks like just an ordinary
painting, but in reality it
actually holds two secrets. Because in
Joseon times, it was rare to paint a
woman's face due to Confucian values
that kept men and women apart. And
that means this was painted in secret by
her lover.
That painting of the lady is intersting.
There was also a rumor about this
painting. Can anyone guess what it was?
It looks like something stopped it
from burning all the way.
-Seems mysterious.
-What was it?
-Can you explain what the curator's
-And in fact, there was quite the
-saying?
-scandalous rumor about him.
There are bad rumors about the owner of
the painting. Like…
-ghosts,
-Isn't that fascinating? So interesting.
Spirits, and goblins.
Interesting. So what happened? How does
the story end? Is it a happy ending?
Since the yaksha fell in love, there was
no way the story could have a happy
ending. It was a sad ending.
But apparently, the two lovers from
300 years ago, whose love was never
fulfilled, are going to meet again soon,
as if by fate.
Silent night, holy night. Today is
Christmas Eve. The last night we
can see the Star of the Temptress
from Earth has finally come.
Are we finally going to be done with
all this?
The wor-- last-- lea-- bittersw--
Ow, it's just-- Oh, no, please. No, no,
please.
Your Highness, pray, come back.
Silent night, holy night. Today is
Christmas Eve. The last night we
can see the Star of the Temptress
from Earth has finally come. The word
"last" always leaves something of
a bittersweet feeling. It seems
the Star of the Temptress also intends
to leave us with a meaningful farewell.
Appreciate it.
Tonight in the night sky, they say a
meteor shower will accompany the path of
the disappearing comet. How about
we join in for a moment on this final
journey of the stars as they rain
down like a shower?
-Hello.
-Hi.
Could this become a truly special
Christmas Eve we'll never forget?
Excuse me.
She'll be waiting for me.
Your Highness, pray, come back.
Please, don't die. Don't die, Cha Se-gye.
Don't die. Don't die, Cha Se-gye!
Blood pressure's still dropping.
85 over 55. Pulse, 130. Ma'am
please wait!
Stay calm. Sir, sir!
Blood pressure's still dropping.
Heart rate, 120. He's gone into cardiac
-arrest.
-CPR.
He will not die…
Your Highness.
You are…
not Fortune Teller Geum.
Do not worry.
You can save him if you sever the
cycle of fate.
"The cycle of fate?"
Your lover will always meet his death,
whether in Joseon or here. So go back
and save the Grand Prince, for fate
will not repeat itself.
All you need is to pay a small price.
Tell me. What is the price? I'll pay!
Whatever the cost, I'll pay it!
Even if it means that you can never come
back here?
Never come back here?
Yes. You will not be able to return
ever again.
It really is shining…
now that I"m with you.
You're the only one, Shin Seo-ri.
I will not let you be alone. You can
trust me.
Cha Se-gye, let's grow old together
and never part.
MY ROYAL NEMESIS
You can save him if you sever the
cycle of fate.
I'm back in Joseon.
You used to serve at Hyeon's quarters,
did you not?
Do you mean to say you are sending me
to the Grand Prince? He's still alive.
I can save him.
Do not drink it. It is poison. He is
trying to use me as bait.
What do you think you are to me?
Where's Shin Seo-ri?
Why, can't you find her? Maybe she's
run away.
Could you not make me wait any longer?
I can't breathe, Shin Seo-ri.
This time. I will save you.