EPISODE 10
A Chinese restaurant owner.
Better than I expected.
Hey, what are you doing?
We meet after ten years.
Even if you can't pretend to be happy,
shouldn't you at least offer me some tea?
I don't think we're on terms
to sit and have tea.
Hey, no need to be so guarded.
I just came to see how you were doing.
I was always curious.
The traitor to his country,
Jeong Ho-myeong.
How miserably is he living?
But here you are with a cute son
and doing better than I expected.
Good for you.
Leave my family out of this.
I didn't mean anything by it.
I was just happy to see
that a junior I was fond of is doing well.
Oh, right. Come to think of it
there was another junior I was fond of.
Team Leader Jo Seong-won, I mean.
What a shame.
If it weren't
for that pathetic sense of justice
he'd have a good position
at the NIS by now
and be living comfortably.
Instead, his leg is ruined,
and he's a drifter.
It's a real shame, isn't it?
Ho-myeong.
Ten years ago and even now
you could have just let it go.
Why do you have to make things
so complicated?
This time as well,
do you and everyone around you
have to be destroyed
before you learn your lesson?
This isn't like you.
- What?
- Coming here in person
and making threats
using my family and Jo Seong-won.
The Han Gyeong-wook I knew
at the National Intelligence Service
wasn't the type
to give friendly warnings
when something got in his way.
He would have just wiped it all out.
So why are you acting this way?
It suddenly reminds me
of something you drilled into me.
When infiltrating enemy lines,
maintain total situational awareness.
Especially, pay close attention
to the enemy's armaments.
Whatever the enemy might be holding
in their hands
never take your eyes off them.
You remember, don't you?
Yes.
I'm glad to see my lessons stuck with you.
But, Ho-myeong.
Do I really
need to be on guard around you?
Well, if you have something to hide,
then I suppose you should be.
You've changed a lot.
Making such pathetic threats.
Why don't you find out for yourself
if they're pathetic or not?
You seem to have a big misunderstanding.
I didn't
come here to negotiate with you.
I have no intention of negotiating either.
I'm simply informing you.
Since you seem to be in the dark
about something.
Good grief.
There's no point
in talking about this anymore.
Yes, I agree this conversation
has gone on for too long.
Fine.
If you're so determined
to see this through to the end
I'll give you what you want.
See you around, Ho-myeong.
Oh, right.
And give my regards
to Team Leader Jo Seong-won.
Ho-myeong. Hey, that man who just left...
That was Han Gyeong-wook, right?
I heard you were an NIS agent.
Did you know him?
So then
the person who framed the Director
and forced you to resign
was the other candidate, Han Gyeong-wook?
That's right.
Chairman Do of Heaven Capital
and Heaven Casino
and Candidate Han Gyeong-wook
are all in it together.
Those guys are plotting something
on Yeongseon Island.
That day, without any real explanation
I suddenly told you to stop
helping the victims.
- I'm sorry about that.
- Oh, no, Mr. Kim.
You only said that
because you were worried.
Right.
But, O-ran
I'm telling you this
because I'm truly worried.
Any further than this
don't try to do anything.
This isn't just a matter
of helping the victims.
If they find out about this
you and the others
who are interfering with their business
and even the people around you...
They will never leave you alone.
Jeong Ho-myeong came to see me yesterday.
Oh, yes, I heard.
About what happened
to your husband in the past...
He told me all about it.
He said he knows
exactly what kind of people they are.
He said he would
take care of Han Gyeong-wook himself.
For an NIS agent who's now a civilian
to push himself to take on Han Gyeong-wook
there's a sense of duty, of course.
But the desire to protect his family
must be the biggest reason.
Yes.
- It's been a while, Chairman Hwang.
- It's been a while?
A loyal scumbag like you should just
stay by Deputy Director Han's side.
What brings you all the way out here
on this old man's special day?
And you didn't even bring any tofu.
It's not like you plan on
living a clean life
so what's the point in you eating any?
Well, I guess you have a point.
I'll have to get some blood on my hands
to slit Deputy Director Han's throat.
Right?
What's with that look?
You let me rot in prison for ten years
and now you let me out.
So did you expect me
to bow down in gratitude?
Let's stop with the pointless mind games.
Aren't you curious
about why the Deputy Director let you go?
THE HOLY BIBLE
The Lord has spoken.
Proverbs 18:13.
"To answer before listening
that is folly and shame."
Right. Since the Lord has spoken,
I'll at least hear your reason.
So where's Deputy Director Han now?
ORAN CHINESE RESTAURANT
Mr. Kim.
Hey, O-ran.
What are you doing here?
What if those gangsters followed you?
With Dad and you holding out like this
without even closing up,
how could I not come?
Honestly, your father's so stubborn.
Where's Ho-myeong?
He couldn't persuade your dad,
so he slept here.
Hey, about yesterday.
You know Han Gyeong-wook,
the candidate for mayor of Imcheon?
He came here.
- Han Gyeong-wook?
- Yes.
To be honest, I was skeptical
about Ho-myeong being from the NIS.
But I think it's actually true.
It looked like he was here
to see Ho-myeong.
- What are you doing here?
- Gosh, you scared me.
Why are you here?
We need to talk for a minute.
I heard Han Gyeong-wook
was here yesterday.
He's the one, isn't he?
The one who framed you
and got you kicked out in the past.
Yeah.
Mr. Kim told me
that he's an extremely dangerous person.
Are you going to be okay?
I'm fine.
You, your father, and our Ji-woo...
I'll do whatever it takes to make sure
no harm comes to any of you.
No, I'm not worried about us.
I'm talking about you.
I'm asking if you'll be okay.
Is it okay for you to go up
against someone that dangerous?
What's this? Are you worried about me?
You're our Ji-woo's father.
How could I not be worried?
I've been thinking.
Just like you said, what if all of us
get off Yeongseon Island for a while?
I'll do my best to convince my dad.
No.
I can't go.
I have to resolve this myself,
no matter what.
- No, please don't say that.
- As you've probably heard
Han Gyeong-wook
is planning something on Yeongseon Island.
If that jerk actually becomes mayor
there will be far more victims
than we're seeing now.
I couldn't stop him ten years ago
but this time,
I have to stop him no matter what.
You remember, right?
What you said on the day
our Ji-woo was born.
You said you'd never let Ji-woo
grow up lonely like you did.
That no matter what,
you'd always be by his side
until he became an adult. That promise.
Keep your promise.
I'll find a way to convince my dad.
You just go and take care of
that Han Gyeong-wook guy
and come back.
I'll be waiting.
Okay.
- Did she see us?
- I can't look.
- Is she gone?
- Did she catch on?
How diligent.
Yes, go ahead.
What?
You just said that Han Gyeong-wook came
knowing everything.
Then shouldn't you be lying low for now?
I've bought us some time.
But I think we need to make a move
before he catches on.
Among everything you've found out so far
is there anything that could be
an immediate blow to Han Gyeong-wook?
Well, there's nothing decisive
but I'm starting to get the picture
of what Han Gyeong-wook is up to
on Yeongseon Island.
The Yeongseon Island development project.
It's not as simple
as designating Yeongseon Island
a special tourist zone to develop it.
I don't think its intentions
are so transparent.
You know that company,
Yeongseon Future Development
headed by Do Hyeon-tae?
I looked into it.
The investors
are foreign companies with ties
to the People's Republic of China
and Japan.
And every single one of these companies
is suspected of being involved
with the yakuza.
Isn't that strange?
Why would companies
tied to criminal organizations
jump into the Yeongseon Island
special tourist zone development project?
If they're tied to criminal organizations
this is no longer just a simple
development project.
There must be some other motive.
If I piece together everything
I've figured out so far...
Heaven Capital has been using
illegal debt collection tactics
on Yeongseon Island residents
to secure their land
and using the money
laundered through Heaven Casino
they've been steadily moving forward
with the project behind the scenes.
If Han Gyeong-wook gets elected mayor
he'll lift the regulations
on Yeongseon Island
and push this project forward
full-scale all at once.
So...
We need to do something before that
but there are no traces of Han Gyeong-wook
in either Heaven Capital or Heaven Casino.
I mean, if we could at least prove
that the money from both places
went to Han Gyeong-wook,
or find a record of it
we'd have something to prosecute him with.
You know very well
just how meticulous Han Gyeong-wook is.
It looks like
it will take some time
to secure solid evidence.
The election is right around the corner.
There's no more time to waste.
If it's too difficult for you
- I'll find the evidence my own way.
- Your own way?
I'll tell you after I have it.
Prosecutor, please continue
your investigation
of the people around Han Gyeong-wook.
Okay, I'll contact you right away
if I find anything.
Yes, understood.
Hey, Gang Beom-ryong. It's me.
Bring Bulgae and come
to the camper van right now.
- Chief Kim! Perfect timing.
- Yes.
- About what I mentioned before.
I think we need to speed things up.
Let's dig into the people
around Han Gyeong-wook.
Get all the details.
Prosecutor, I don't think I can do it.
- What?
- The Chief Prosecutor
told me to report your every move
to him without you knowing.
If you give me orders like this,
I have no choice but to report it.
But he told you to do it
without my knowledge.
Are you sure
you should be telling me this?
Because I work with you,
not the Chief Prosecutor.
Even if I get in trouble for it,
I thought it was right to tell you.
Then how about this?
Of all the people around Han Gyeong-wook
let's start with our Chief Prosecutor.
- Yes. What?
- Yes.
Our Chief Prosecutor. My goodness.
I was going to let it slide,
but his constant buzzing
is getting on my nerves.
We need to swat this fly.
You've done this before,
so you'll be good at it, right?
No, this is
completely different from that.
Before, I was tailing someone
connected to the case.
But now you're asking me
to tail my own boss.
It's not different at all.
Our Chief Prosecutor
is deeply involved in this case.
He's taking bribes from Han Gyeong-wook.
Why are you telling me a secret like that?
I'm just going to pretend
I didn't hear that.
I just want to keep my head down
and have a long career. You get me?
Chief Kim, wait.
If you want that long career,
you have to cut that rotten lifeline.
And make a new, sturdy,
and safe one for yourself.
Don't you see what's at stake here?
You'll approve my overtime, right?
But what's Mr. Jeong thinking?
He was so suspicious of him
and now he wants us
to bring Bong Je-sun to the camper?
Gosh, how am I supposed to know
what he's thinking?
Oh, right. Was everything okay
on Mi-kyung's end?
What's there to report?
Everything's quiet.
- Hey.
- Hello.
Hello.
- What's that?
- Oh, this?
You're working so hard
to help me get my memory back
so I wanted to help out somehow
and brought a few things.
You really overdo it.
What?
Hey, it's you, isn't it?
From the warehouse.
- The warehouse?
- Yes. Don't you remember?
You know, back when those
Heaven Capital goons dragged us away.
Woof, woof!
- Have you lost your mind?
- Are you trying to pick a fight?
No, I'm not trying to pick a fight.
I'm just glad you're okay.
I was so worried
that you'd gotten seriously hurt.
But you're tough, so you seem to be fine.
Stop talking nonsense
and get in while I'm asking nicely.
- Okay?
- Yes.
Hurry. Let's go.
Well, Chairman Hwang,
it's been a long time.
You look even younger
than the last time I saw you.
Isn't that all thanks to you,
Deputy Director Han?
You'll understand the business
once you see read that.
I'll give you 10% of the profits
and give you my full support
in rebuilding your organization.
What do you say?
I'd say that's
more than enough compensation
for spending ten years in prison.
You're not going to use some rat
like Yoo In-gu again
- to stab me in the back, are you?
- Of course not.
As long as the business goes well
why would I have any reason
to do something like that?
What is it?
The reason you're giving me
such a good offer.
You're as sharp as ever.
There's something
I need you to do for me, Chairman Hwang.
One of your men
is in cahoots with that same
NIS agent from ten years ago.
Did you know that?
Those two have the missing package.
So you're saying I should go to Beom-ryong
get that package
and bring it back?
I know it's not easy to get
a runaway child to come back.
If you can't do it, just say so.
Whether by carrot or by stick
all I have to do is bring him home, right?
And recovering the package
shouldn't be too difficult either.
Gosh, so I'm
going into business
with Deputy Director Han.
In return for this fine coffee,
let me give you a gift.
Prosecutor Gang in this photo here
came to see me a while ago.
You...
met with Prosecutor Gang?
She said she would catch the real killer
in Director Kwon Soon-bok's murder case.
I thought she was some kind of psycho
but given the circumstances at the time
I was desperate,
so I took her up on the offer.
I even told Beom-ryong to meet with her.
And?
He never reported back on what happened
so I just assumed it didn't work out
and gave up on it.
But it looks like
things progressed this way.
Right?
Prosecutor Gang.
She may have found out far more
about your shameful secrets
than you might think.
Joong-gi.
We're not far from the finish line.
You know that, right?
- Yes.
- But...
At a time when we should be
making our final push
why do stumbling blocks
like Jeong Ho-myeong or Prosecutor Gang
keep popping up?
I'm sure
I instructed you to clear the path.
I'm sorry.
Before that woman becomes
an even bigger headache
you take care of it on your end.
I'll take care of it
as quickly as possible.
What is it?
What did you drag us out here
to talk about?
Weren't you just complaining
about how this guy is not to be trusted?
Hey, you go on inside.
- What?
I said go on ahead.
The three of us need to talk.
Okay.
- Go where--
- Where else? Can't you see the door?
Want to jump in the water instead?
I'll be in there, then.
Man, those must be heavy.
You guys.
Now, don't freak out.
Are you serious?
You're saying Han Gyeong-wook
knew everything?
Yes.
He probably thinks we have the package.
I think he'll be back soon.
Well, then we can just
keep pretending we have it.
That won't last long.
He'll catch on quick.
You know what he's like.
Before that happens
we need to find some kind of evidence
of Han Gyeong-wook's wrongdoings
and strike first.
But we don't have much time.
Is that even possible?
We have to try.
If we want to find out quickly
we'll have to dig
into Heaven Capital or Heaven Casino.
But the casino's system
makes it hard to infiltrate.
However, the Heaven Capital business
seems possible.
After Yoo In-gu stepped down
Chairman Do
and that guy, Geum Kang-sik, took over.
- Kang-sik is in charge?
- You know him?
We know him, but...
We're too embarrassed to even admit we do.
Yes, sir.
Kang-sik, the shoes.
Here, sir.
- Thank you.
- When we were in the Hwasan Sect
he just shined my shoes.
He was really good
at shining shoes, though.
But he couldn't even manage
a single food stall properly
so he was the epitome of incompetence.
Perfect.
When an incompetent guy takes charge,
things are bound to fall apart.
If we can just squeeze Geum Kang-sik
we can find evidence
that Han ordered the money collection
or find a trail
of where the illegal funds went.
What's so hard about
shaking down Kang-sik?
- Let's do it now.
- You can dismiss Geum Kang-sik
but he's got the other boys.
And he saw what happened to Yoo In-gu,
so he's probably being extremely cautious.
I'm sure he is.
That's why that will be our Plan B.
We have a much more certain way
to take down Han Gyeong-wook.
A more certain way? What is it?
We just have to make Bulgae talk
and get the package.
Are you kidding me?
He says he can't remember anything.
How are you supposed to make him talk?
How many times do I have to tell you?
It's all an act.
Hey, look at him.
Does he really look like Bulgae to you?
Hey, at that K-pop dance place yesterday,
he was living like a total slave.
If he were Bulgae,
why would he live like that?
I also think you've got it wrong.
Do you have any idea how many spies
I dealt with at the NIS?
An act like that...
I just know it when I see it.
You're telling me that
dopey look on his face is all an act?
Just you watch.
I'm going to rip that
detestable Bong Je-sun mask right off him.
He keeps staring over here.
So they think this is funny?
Look at them, having a blast.
Oh, my stomach.
Are you all done talking?
Of course. Why else would we come in?
- Have you made your decision?
- What decision?
Whether you're going to tell the truth now
or keep pretending to be Bong Je-sun.
It's time to decide.
Mr Jeong, just as you're saying
I wish this amnesia were just an act.
I really do.
But I'm telling you,
I really don't remember a thing.
Is that so?
Then let me explain it to you.
What?
Agent Bulgae of the Ministry
of People's Armed Forces.
Dispatched to the South and overseas
for secret operations.
A human weapon trained in North Korea
for various special missions.
Rumored to be a master of disguise
and a Taekkyeon expert.
A legendary spy whose identity
has never been compromised.
A guy like that gets amnesia
and holes up in South Korea for ten years?
Does that make any sense to you?
Believe it or not, it's the truth.
So you're going to stick to that story?
Then I have no choice.
I'll just have to make sure.
Hey, what are you going to do
to make sure?
Watch out!
- Darn.
- Darn it.
What was that?
- What?
- Did you all see that?
You think Bong Je-sun
could have dodged that?
Are you crazy? What if you'd hit him?
Hey, is he a target?
Why do you keep throwing things?
You almost killed him!
I knew he'd dodge it. Because he's Bulgae.
Are you okay?
I don't even know how I dodged that.
I was so shocked.
I barely ducked
my head like this, but right here...
Gosh, it stings.
It's bleeding. I'm bleeding.
- I'm bleeding. Blood!
- What? You punk...
Hey! If you don't want a hole in your head
reveal your identity
and tell me where the package is!
- Mr. Jeong, please stop.
- Yes, you're way too worked up.
So, just because I dodged that,
I'm Bulgae?
Hey, look. You dodged it. See?
He dodged it. He must be Bulgae, right?
Why didn't you dodge this? Why not?
You're calling me Bulgae
for dodging something
most people would dodge?
You've really gone too far. Darn it.
I put up with the soda can. But...
But you throw a knife at a person?
What if I hadn't dodged it?
It came right at me.
Bulgae, my foot.
You can say it a hundred times,
but I still don't remember a thing.
What makes you think I'm acting?
You keep spouting nonsense.
Because none of it makes sense!
For ten years,
with no friends and no girlfriend
you put up with all the crap
at that small company
and spent all your time
looking after
that troublemaker nephew? Why?
If it wasn't an act you'd have
no reason to live like that. Right?
An act? You call this an act?
You think I enjoy living like this?
You think I enjoy any of this?
Nam-il is the only family I have
and I don't even remember
who I used to be.
Do you think it's easy
to get close to people?
The second someone asks
where I'm from, I'm speechless.
The small company? The power trips?
You think anyone enjoys
putting up with that?
At my age, I have no skills
and nowhere else to go.
I'm telling you,
I have nowhere else to go.
Honestly, doesn't he have a point?
What makes you think
Bong Je-sun can just get another job?
I feel the same way.
He said he hasn't dated once
in ten years. How pathetic.
And just look at him.
Who would ever like that face?
And accusing him of being a spy
just because he's unpopular
that just makes us as pathetic as him.
You.
You really...
I've had enough.
- Tie him up.
- What?
Who's he talking about?
Let's just talk this out.
Talk?
Don't you realize what it means
that Han Gyeong-wook came to see me?
You guys...
You saw the Hwasan Sect
get destroyed firsthand.
You want to be careless
and go through the same thing again?
- Are you okay?
- Yes. Gosh!
Does it hurt a lot?
So, what are you going to do?
You're not going to do
anything crazy, are you?
Oh no. That's... that's the truth serum.
Truth serum?
It's a drug used by the CIA.
Once you're injected,
you'll tell the truth within ten minutes
but there's a 50% chance
you'll spend your life drooling.
It's a deadly poison.
I didn't want to resort to this
but if you're going to keep this up,
I have no choice.
- You're kidding, right?
- I'm serious.
- Darn it.
- Hey, Jeong Ho-myeong.
Now you're resorting to drugs?
Are you human? Are you serious?
Shut it, you thug.
Bulgae.
This is your last chance. Think carefully.
I'm not doing this
because of a personal grudge.
If you keep lying,
the people of Yeongseon Island
the dance club members,
your nephew Heo Nam-il
and Prosecutor Gang will all be in danger.
So just tell me now. It's not too late.
You seriously think
that'll bring back my memories?
What are you all doing?
Have you all gone insane?
Are you just going to
stand there and watch?
That was your last chance. So be it.
Take one more step
and this thug will beat you up.
- Two steps, three steps, four steps.
- No!
Let go of me!
Wait!
Let go of me.
You're out of your mind. Stop!
I said let go!
You know I hate being touched, right?
- Are you with the NIS or the CIA?
- Do you even know what CIA is?
- This is dangerous!
- Do you know the CIA, you punk?
- Stop it!
- You lunatic!
- Let go of me, you punk!
- It's too dangerous!
Stop!
Do it.
What?
Just inject me with that syringe.
No matter how many times I tell you
I've lost my memory
you have no intention of listening.
Throwing knives at people
and threatening them with your crude talk.
What you guys are doing right now...
How is this any different
from what that Han Gyeong-wook guy does?
You might as well just inject me.
Inject me and...
Yes, go on and hear
what this so-called truth is.
Just do it. Inject me.
- Mr. Jeong!
- Do you still want to go through with it?
Look me straight in the eye.
You really...
don't have a single memory as Bulgae?
I told you.
How many times do I have to say it?
How many darn times do I have to tell you?
I don't remember.
So why are you calling me a liar?
- Hey, Gong-bok. Here.
- Okay.
That's enough.
Keep it up. You're doing great.
- You idiot.
- Just stop it already.
Fine.
Well, if he still denies it after all this
- I guess that's true.
- Yes. Mr. Jeong Ho-myeong.
- Are you okay?
- Yes, I'm fine.
- Does it hurt a lot?
- Yes.
Oh, and that shot from before?
It was this.
- What?
- What did you say, you fool?
Hey, Bulgae. No, Bong Je-sun.
My bad.
You're a good guy, so you'll understand.
Darn it, seriously.
- Are you okay?
- Thanks for saving me.
- Untie him, quick.
- Oh, yes.
That darn devil, Jeong Ho-myeong.
He tied this really tight.
A master of disguise
and a Taekkyeon expert...
Okay, let's think about this.
This guy who's some kind of
martial arts master or whatever
seems to be a trained North Korean spy.
The other is Gang Beom-ryong,
the former number two of the Hwasan Sect.
And the last one
is some agent from the NIS
who knows Han Gyeong-wook well.
What kind of combination is this?
What kind of scheme are they plotting
that brought these three together?
A North Korean spy
the National Intelligence Service,
and Gang Beom-ryong.
Oh, now that you mention it, ten years ago
Deputy Director Han
came to see Chairman Hwang.
He wanted to work together on a job.
A job?
He asked us to find him
a solid guy back then.
I remember Gang Beom-ryong
and Ma Gong-bok were assigned to it.
So...
- they acted on an order?
- Yes.
- So, what happened with that job?
- Well...
Right after that job, Deputy Director Han
and Yoo In-gu teamed up
and backstabbed the chairman.
So whether they succeeded or what...
I don't really know that part.
I bet that order was the ferry case.
And that must be when those three
and Deputy Director Han
got involved with each other.
Considering how Han Gyeong-wook
is still paying special attention to this
it seems like something major
must have happened on that ferry.
Darn, what could it be?
Mr. Nam, you said you had
a contact at the NIS, right?
- Yes.
- Okay.
Then can you find out
what happened ten years ago
- about this ferry case?
- Yes.
What?
It's Secretary Baek.
- Yes?
- Chairman Do.
You haven't forgotten
tomorrow's delivery, have you?
Of course not.
But what about it?
The Deputy Director says
he has something to tell you
and asks you to come in today.
Today? Yes, understood.
Something to tell me?
What a roundabout way
of telling me to hurry up with the money.
Mr. Nam, go to Mr. Geum's Capital
and get the bag.
What? The bag?
It's a green juice.
It's said to help with fatigue
and clear your head.
Here, drink this.
Fine, don't drink it.
It's not like I'm giving it to you
because I like you.
I'm sorry.
For being just Bong Je-sun
and not the human weapon, Bulgae.
You know
I don't think I've ever felt
as frustrated about my amnesia
as I do today.
The people on Yeongseon Island
and Nam-il could all be in danger.
I'm sure there's a clue
in my memories that could save them
so why did I forget everything?
I can't even remember the faintest detail.
It's not that
I don't understand you, Mr. Jeong.
If there's any other way I can help,
please tell me.
Then I'll do anything. Anything.
Well, isn't this lovely?
Hey, you guys stay here.
- Why? Are you going somewhere?
- Finding the package is a lost cause.
I have to go with Plan B
I mentioned earlier.
I'll head over to Heaven Capital
so you guys stay here
and work with Bulgae...
I mean work with Bong Je-sun
and make a list of places
where the package could be.
Places where the package could be?
Every single place Bong Je-sun went to
while he lived on Yeongseon Island.
Starting tomorrow,
we'll split into two teams.
One team will take Heaven Capital
and the other team will take the receiver
and comb through Yeongseon Island.
You never know.
We might find something.
- Okay.
- You can help with that, right?
Yes, I'll do it.
Open the cabinet next to the bed.
The receiver should be in there.
Things are a little tight this month.
I have to pay my guys too.
Just one more month.
Give me an extension.
You know perfectly well
that laundry payments
have to be delivered on time.
- You didn't know?
- I know. But...
Come on, just help me out this once.
These are Deputy Director Han's orders.
Our hands are tied, you get me?
See you around, President Geum.
Boss.
Did they really take everything?
The guys are really unhappy.
At least when Yoo In-gu was around,
our paychecks were never late.
Everyone's saying
the old days were better.
What are you looking at, you punks?
Get to work!
What? Yoo In-gu?
Which one of you bastards
said that crap? Damn it.
Hey.
Who do you think saved this organization
after Yoo In-gu nearly destroyed it?
The organization is struggling
and you're driving around
in a nice car by yourself.
The guys only say that
because it's what they see.
Hey, I take the bus
just to save money on gas.
Not me. It was the other guys.
Whatever. Forget it.
Hey, just keep the guys in line.
I'll figure out a way
to get them paid. Got it?
- Yes, Boss.
- Get out of here. Go away.
You're right on time.
Chairman Hwang,
this is Chairman Do Hyeon-tae.
Chairman Do,
this is Chairman Hwang Hwa-san.
I'm Hwang Hwa-san, Chairman Do.
I'm Do Hyeon-tae.
Could you be from the Hwasan Sect?
Oh, my.
For someone like you
to recognize an old man like me.
I'm honored.
Not at all.
- Please, have a seat.
- Yes.
We'll register Chairman Hwang
as a director
of Yeongseon Future Development
and he'll be in charge of
the Heaven Capital business from now on.
But we've been handling that
just fine on our end.
Why go through all the trouble?
We could just...
Chairman Do,
you have way too much on your plate
with the hotel, casino,
and the Yeongseon Island project.
We need to be efficient.
Think of it as going back
to how things were under Yoo In-gu.
How things were under Yoo In-gu?
Oh, and...
Let's wrap up the case
you were following as well.
That kind of work
is Chairman Hwang's specialty, after all.
Understood.
Having you here, Chairman,
takes a huge weight off my shoulders.
From now on, if you run into any trouble,
just say the word.
We're on the same team now, after all.
I'll give it my all. I'm here to help.
Thank you.
I look forward to learning from you.
Of course.
He thinks he can sideline me
by putting some washed-up
old geezer in charge?
I do all the hard work,
and that guy reaps the benefits.
What do you think, Mr. Nam?
I believe we need to take action.
If profits from Heaven Capital
start dropping tomorrow
it'll disrupt our cash flow.
It's not just about the money.
I have a really bad feeling about this.
No matter how I look at it,
this is a signal from Deputy Director Han
that he doesn't trust me.
If I just sit back,
I'll end up just like Yoo In-gu.
Surely Deputy Director Han
wouldn't do that, would he?
I know Han Gyeong-wook very well.
Keep the hitmen on standby.
And if you find even the smallest lead
on Deputy Director Han
tell them to contact me right away.
Yes, sir.
Hey, it's an emergency.
I said I'd pay you back right away!
Hey, hold on.
What's going on?
Long time no see, kid.
Boss!
President Geum Kang-sik.
Live long enough and you see everything.
Both you and Yoo In-gu...
Punks like you being called President?
What has this world come to?
Oh, yes.
Aren't you supposed to be in jail?
Why? You got a problem with me being out?
What? No.
That's not what I meant. Not at all.
- Kang-sik.
- Yes, Boss.
Now that I'm out after all this time,
I have a lot of questions.
What kind of questions, Boss?
How the world has changed
in the last ten years.
Especially everything that happened
with Beom-ryong and Gong-bok.
Tell me everything.
You mean Beom-ryong, sir?
That's right. Beom-ryong.
Didn't you hear me?
I need to know every detail
on what kind of trouble
that runaway kid got into
and who he was running around with.
Sure.
So, have you looked into the ferry case?
Just as you suspected.
An NIS agent and a spy
reportedly went missing on that ferry.
They were reportedly
looking for a package.
It contained information about a traitor
colluding with North Korea.
The package vanished with them.
A traitor colluding with North Korea?
A package?
So how was it all wrapped up?
Deputy Director Han took personal command
and he reportedly kept it
from leaking to the press or the police.
What happened to those
involved in the case afterward
was kept top secret, so nothing is known.
My goodness. Jeez.
The mole is Han Gyeong-wook. Right?
And that package
must contain his weakness.
- Deputy Director Han's weakness?
- Come on, can't you see?
This is exactly
Deputy Director Han's MO, isn't it?
When he fails to retrieve the package
containing his weakness
he takes charge
and buries everyone involved.
What do you think?
Doesn't this picture look familiar?
No, but...
But there's another very
interesting situation to consider here.
Ten years ago
the three people who disappeared
while looking for this package
suddenly reappeared, hand in hand.
What do you think that means?
It means that the package with
Han Gyeong-wook's weakness has surfaced.
Where are the hitmen now?
They're keeping an eye on the three.
There will be a time
when they take out the package.
Tell them to tail them
without missing a single breath
and do whatever it takes
to snatch that package at the right time.
Yes, sir.
The places Bong Je-sun went
are here and here.
Here, here, here, and here.
There aren't many, so it shouldn't
take long to check them all.
- The receiver?
- Oh, one second.
I can't read upside-down.
What does he mean, "not many?"
You've been all over the place.
All right. Here it is.
Well...
Aren't you hungry?
- I'm starving.
- I know, right?
You missed lunch
because you were helping me.
Seriously, who carries around ingredients
for chicken soup in their bag?
I told you.
I wanted to be helpful in any way I could.
Cooking is the only thing I'm good at
so I packed some just in case.
I'm glad they're coming in handy.
Gosh, that looks delicious.
So, how is it? Do you like it?
But there's no black pepper.
- Oh, I...
- No, but it's good enough.
I think it's delicious.
That's a relief.
You stood up for me earlier.
I was really grateful.
Hey, it was nothing.
I mean, Jeong Ho-myeong
isn't usually that rash.
He must be busy and feeling rushed lately
so he made a mistake.
- Was it Bong Je-sun?
- Yes.
- You should try and understand.
- Sure.
Still, it was a very dangerous mistake,
don't you think?
- Oh, it really was dangerous.
- Exactly.
I almost spilled everything myself.
- What?
Wait.
You saved me.
Hold on.
If it weren't for you guys,
things could have gotten messy.
This ten-year-long ill-fated relationship
and that darn package...
Once you get a good night's sleep
will all be gone.
What should we do?
Just tail him for now.
You need black pepper for chicken soup.
Hey!
Hey, Gong-bok.
Hey, Gong-bok, open your eyes! Wake up!
- Darn it.
- Gosh, my head.
- Hang on.
What the? Where's Bulgae?
Hey, the receiver!
The receiver?
Gosh, hold on.
The receiver is gone.
- What about the car key?
- The car key?
The car key is gone too.
Bulgae, that jerk!
Darn it! Seriously.
What's wrong?
Hey, Bulgae!
Looking for this?
Gosh, Mr. Jeong, Mr. Gang, Mr. Ma.
How... how did you get here?
As for me...
I thought I was starting
to remember something
so I came here for a bit.
Look at that disgusting face.
Well played. You're a really good actor.
Stop the act, you bastard.
Hey, cut it out. We're on to you.
I knew I should've used more of the drug.
Darn it.
How did you know to come here?
I knew you'd pull something like this
so I set up a little trick of my own.
Hey, give that back now.
It belongs to my son.
You darn scumbags. You dare mess with me?
Look at that.
He's finally baring his fangs.
Look at this two-faced jerk.
Gosh, your true nature is coming out now.
This is good. Very good.
Hey, your acting was really...
I almost fell for it.
Did you really?
Now, cut the crap.
At first, I wasn't sure.
But something about what happened
at the hospital kept bothering me.
A guy who ditches a tracker and runs away
suddenly comes back
and offers to help us with our job?
Why would you do that?
It was because
you didn't have the package.
You only knew
the general area of the package
not its exact location.
So I decided to run a little test.
A test? What kind of test?
Hey, why do you think I'd invite
a dangerous guy like you to our hideout?
I said go on ahead.
The three of us need to talk.
I'll be in there, then.
Man, those must be heavy.
Where did they hide it?
They've hidden it really well.
Jeez.
You must have needed this receiver.
Coming here... Jeez, now I get it.
So then...
provoking me like a madman was also...
I figured you'd move
as soon as you felt cornered.
And...
I also had a hunch
you'd ditch these idiots.
Hey, what's that supposed to mean?
If you knew that,
you should've told us beforehand.
Hey.
If you don't want to die,
hand over that receiver.
This guy... He still doesn't get it.
Hey, you think we have to give it to you
just because you ask?
Why are we listening to him?
Let's just crush him already.
Hey, Bulgae.
Why are you after the package?
That USB drive
with Han Gyeong-wook's weakness
is useless to you.
What you're after
is the North Korean slush fund
that Black Pearl brought.
Slush fund?
Slush fund? What are you talking about?
- I'll give it all to you.
- Mr. Jeong. But...
Hey, how much is it?
You can't just make a decision
on something important by yourself!
It's not like we need it anyway.
In return, you'll cooperate with us.
If you help us drive Han Gyeong-wook
out of Yeongseon Island
I'll give you the entire slush fund
after it's all over.
- And you expect me to believe that?
- Make your choice!
If you run away now
your nephew Heo Nam-il on Yeongseon Island
the K-pop dance club members
who helped you
and even Prosecutor Gang
could all get hurt by Han Gyeong-wook.
And you don't want that to happen, do you?
How would you know
if Han Gyeong-wook will hurt Nam-il?
Gosh, this idiot is so paranoid.
See for yourself
just how serious this situation is.
Come out, you rats!
What the hell are you saying?
Mr. Jeong, who are they?
I don't know.
They've been following us
from the camper van.
Hey, we've been tailed this whole time?
You think they were just tailing us?
You're the ones
who messed with the camper, aren't you?
You left traces all over the place.
Hey, did Han Gyeong-wook send those guys?
Sneaking around
and testing the waters like a rat
isn't Han Gyeong-wook's style.
Hey!
You should at least introduce yourselves.
Who sent you?
None of your business.
Hand over the receiver or whatever it is
that can find the package.
Then I'll spare your lives.
What kind of crap are these rats spouting?
Let's just take them all out,
Bulgae and these scumbags.
Hey, Bulgae.
Now make your choice.
You can either fight against us
or join us and fight against them.
SPECIAL THANKS
TO KIM SANG-KYUNG AND KWON YUL
Found it.
We've detected a signal
trying to decrypt the package.
- So it wasn't a bluff?
- Hey!
- Are you sure you can crack this?
- Huh?
- This thing isn't easy to open.
- It's almost done.
- It's 2%.
- Hey, don't touch it.
If you're trying
to pull a fast one on me...
We shouldn't be
fighting amongst ourselves!
The boss got out of prison.
Bring me that package.
What if they decide
to side with the thugs?
You want me to stab my boss
in the back after all this time?
- Go back to the convenience store.
- I'll step aside.
Boss!
- A family?
- Do whatever it takes...
Get rid of them all.
What if your family gets hurt first?
- Ji-woo?
- Dad.
You don't mind
never seeing your nephew again?
You think I'd let some useless emotion
hold me back now?
All I have to do is hand over the package?
Isn't it a shame?
After all your hard work.
I'm prepared.
Let those punks come at us.
There's nothing we can't do.
We have to finish this.