[You Have My Heart]
[Episode 11
Half Demon Bitter Fruit]
Th-th-this...
You thought hiding your aura
could fool me?
Your concern betrays you.
Little raccoon. Tell me the truth.
My Lady,
there's no need to beat around the bush.
I killed them.
I've wanted to kill those three
for a long time.
They lorded it over the academy
all day long.
Not just Li Mao,
who in this academy
hasn't been bullied by them?
Wang Renjie wanted to pass
the imperial exams with top honors.
If he actually did,
and became an official someday,
now that would be true injustice.
No one cared,
but I did.
Tell me in detail,
how did you kill the three of them,
and where did you hide the bodies?
I waited until they were dead drunk,
strangled them,
then tore off their arms,
and hung the bodies from the rafters.
Where did you hide their arms?
Search every corner carefully.
Don't overlook a single clue.
Not just Li Mao,
who in this academy
hasn't been bullied by them?
Wang Renjie wanted to pass
the imperial exams with top honors.
If he actually did,
and became an official someday,
now that would be true injustice.
Found them!
My Lord,
six arms were recovered from the well,
matching the wounds on the bodies.
The severed arms of Wang Renjie
and the other two have been found.
How much longer will you stay silent?
My Lord, I killed Wang Renjie.
You killed him?
Yes.
Okay.
Then tell me in detail,
where did you hide the severed arms?
I threw them away.
Where did you throw them?
I just threw them anywhere.
You don't know,
because you weren't the one
who hid those arms.
But someone else does.
Ji has already confessed.
He put the severed arms in the dry well.
At this point,
lying is useless.
Think carefully,
what did you see that night,
and what are you hiding?
That night, I did return to the academy.
I wanted to get some books
to study in the ruined temple.
Spare us!
We were wrong!
We'll never do it again!
Remember what you said today.
If I ever find out
that you dare to harm a single hair
on Li Mao's head,
I will come back
and tear off every pair of your hands
that you only use to bully the weak.
We were wrong!
I'll let you taste
what it's like to lose your limbs.
Spare us!
Ji.
Look at yourself.
You're neither human
nor demon.
You deserve to be trampled
underfoot by others.
If I were you,
I'd have bashed my head
against the academy gates long ago.
It would be better than letting
your mother see you like this,
so she wouldn't have to
worry over you day and night.
Ji. Ji.
I...
Ji...
I beg you,
please tell my mother for me again
that I'm reviewing my lessons.
Get lost!
Go kneel
and tell your own mother yourself!
I know.
Ji was just disappointed in me,
that's why he said those harsh words.
That night,
my mind was a tangled mess.
I had no mood to review my lessons.
So I bought some wine
and went to the ruined temple.
I never left after that,
until dawn when I went to school.
But I arrived too early.
I was a bit tired,
so I fell asleep outside the academy.
Are you on good terms with Ji?
Ji likes to keep to himself.
He keeps a cold distance
from everyone in the academy.
He and I
barely ever spoke to each other.
Except,
when Wang Renjie broke my leg,
I asked him to deliver a message
to my family.
After that,
we've only spoken twice.
When did you meet him?
Sometime between 7 and 8 PM.
Do you have anything else to say?
On my way to the ruined temple,
I came across a scholar.
He asked me for a bowl of wine,
so I invited him to the temple with me.
Do you remember what he looked like?
I really can't remember his face.
I only remember
he was dressed in white.
In the moonlight,
he seemed to be glowing.
Then
can he prove
that you stayed in the ruined temple
the whole time?
Yes.
He definitely can.
That day, I shared my wine with him.
Later...
Later I got drunk.
He also rested in the temple.
With him there,
he can definitely prove
that I was in the temple all night.
In that case,
then think carefully about his appearance
and draw him out.
Once we find him,
you will be cleared of suspicion.
My Lord.
I will do my best.
But My Lord,
I have one more request.
Could you go to my home
and tell my mother I'm safe?
Alright.
Lord Bai,
why not return to the county yamen first
and interrogate Ji thoroughly?
I'll go and reassure
that Tiger Spirit's mother
in your stead.
No.
Why not?
Lady Fufeng, you look unwell.
Your spiritual power must not have
fully recovered yet.
I'd better stay by your side at all times.
Lord Bai truly has a healer's heart.
I have some questions
to ask Auntie Li in person.
Besides, there is one more thing
I don't understand.
Humans and demons have coexisted
in Yin-Yang Crossing for centuries.
Are demons here
always looked down upon by humans?
Li Mao is looked down upon,
not because he is a demon,
but because he is a half-demon.
The human world values clans and surnames,
while demons honor bloodline and heritage.
Caught in between,
half-demons have too weak demonic power
to protect themselves,
and are more sensitive than humans.
That's why ancient books record
a ban in Yin-Yang Crossing,
forbidding marriage
between humans and demons.
The law may restrict actions,
but how can it restrict the heart?
Yet this sincere devotion
only bears bitter fruit in the end,
which the child must bear alone.
So Li Mao is that bitter fruit.
Aunt Li.
There are no signs of struggle
in the yard or the house,
and the lock wasn't forced.
It seems that an acquaintance visited,
and Mrs. Li opened the door herself.
Lady Fufeng.
If so,
from the academy to the Li residence,
how long does it take at the fastest?
For an ordinary human,
going through the West Street
and taking alleys to avoid the market,
it takes an hour at the fastest.
For a demon,
it would be even faster.
Aunt Li's time of death was
between 10 and 11 PM last night,
almost the same time
as Wang Renjie and the others.
After striking at the academy,
the killer didn't stop at all.
He went straight to the destination,
barely pausing to catch a breath.
Hu.
My Lord.
Master.
Li Mao's detailed household
registration has been retrieved.
Li Mao,
half-demon and half-human,
was registered in Yin-Yang Crossing.
His mother, Li Yun,
was a local washerwoman
in Yin-Yang Crossing.
His father, Mao Da, a Tiger Spirit
used to be a street performer.
He was abducted
into a wealthy merchant's mansion,
forced to perform limb severing
for entertainment,
finally died after a banquet
where he was cut nine times,
and his body was abandoned
in the wilderness.
My Lady.
Lady Fufeng.
My Lord.
Aunt Zhang witnessed last night
that Li Mao returned home.
Answering your honor,
I got up to empty
the chamber pot last night,
and I clearly saw Li Mao
knocking at the door.
When?
I got up during the Second Watch,
just as the night watchman
passed by my door.
That would be 9:45 PM, wouldn't it?
Are you sure it was Li Mao?
He wore Qiuzhi Academy's uniform robe.
who else could it be?
Did he have a severed arm?
I didn't notice that.
If he had both arms,
it doesn't make sense.
My Lords,
Have you delivered
my message to my mother?
We told her you're helping with the case,
and everything is fine.
So she doesn't need to worry.
Good.
Li Mao.
You often study late at the academy.
Your mother must leave the door
unlocked for you, right?
Yes.
My mother
always leaves it unlocked
for me every night.
You're also a filial son.
I suppose when you go back,
you wouldn't knock loudly,
for fear of disturbing her rest, right?
My mother works hard
washing clothes during the day.
I dare not wake her,
so I always slip in quietly.
Lady Fufeng.
Once Li Mao's drawing is finished,
please send it
to the county yamen immediately.
Lord Bai, you certainly gives me orders
quite naturally now.
Please, Lady Fufeng.
The case is urgent.
I must return to the county yamen
to interrogate Ji immediately.
My Lady, what's wrong?
You need spiritual power?
With a fever this high,
haven't you even noticed it yourself?
It's been a long time since I got sick.
I didn't even know.
After I finish interrogating Ji,
I'll take some medicine.
Th-this is...
A little magic arts
will suppress your illness temporarily,
but it'll only last half a day.
If you don't rest after tonight's work...
What will happen?
Then you'll just stay sick.
Thank you, My Lady.
My Lady,
that magic arts just now,
can you do it again?
It would be great
if it could last for a day.
Then you will die on the spot.
Is that good?
No, no, no.
Thank you, My Lady.
Master.
You've been spending day
and night with him lately.
You finally built up some spiritual power
to nurture your heart.
And now,
you've given it all back to him at once.
It's just adding a handful of fodder
to a working draft horse.
If he runs faster,
the case will be solved faster.
For me,
and for Yin-Yang Crossing,
it's a good thing.
Ji, that night between 9 and 11 PM,
after you killed Wang Renjie
and the others,
where did you go?
You went to Li Mao's house.
Who's there?
Auntie Li,
it's me, Ji.
Li Mao...
He was studying in the academy.
It got too late, so he stayed there.
He asked me to tell you
not to worry.
I see.
Thank you for your trouble.
I...
According to Li Mao,
the two of you barely spoke,
only a few words total.
Why would you go this far
for him?
Delivering messages,
and even
killing for him?
Because of Auntie Li,
she is my benefactor.
Back then,
I was just a stray kitten
without much intelligence.
How can such a skinny kitten
survive this winter?
Are you starving?
Did your mother leave before teaching you
to catch mice?
The master doesn't like pets.
I don't have a home
of my own either.
That year, some bullies caught me,
tied a rope around me,
and dragged me along the river for fun.
It was Auntie Li.
She was still unmarried then,
just a petite, delicate girl.
She rushed up to argue with them
and snatched me away.
She bandaged my wounds
and gave me food.
Fearing her family was too poor
to raise me well,
she begged others
to send me to a wealthy family.
That I have survived to this day,
cultivated a human form,
and learned to read and write,
is all thanks to Auntie Li's
kindness back then.
That time,
Li Mao asked me
to deliver a message to his family.
May I ask who you are?
I recognized her at first glance.
Over these thirty years,
she has aged a lot,
but it's definitely her.
I can't be wrong.
I am Ji.
So,
you are not the murderer.
Everything you did
was just to take the blame for Li Mao
to repay Auntie Li's kindness.
What are you talking about, My Lord?
I killed them.
What do you mean by taking the blame?
This is my deduction
of what happened that night.
You sneaked into the academy
and taught Wang Renjie
and the other two a lesson,
hoping to scare them,
so they'd never bully Li Mao again.
And later,
you ran into Li Mao outside the academy.
You spoke harshly to him.
It seemed like humiliation,
but was actually frustration
that he wouldn't stand up for himself.
You hoped he would rise up because of this
and learn to protect himself.
You couldn't bear it in the end,
and still went to reassure
Auntie Li for him.
But you never expected
that after Wang Renjie
and the others died,
you believed
that Li Mao was provoked by your words
to commit a grave mistake,
so you took the murder charge
on yourself.
If I didn't kill them,
how would I know
that the six severed arms were hidden
in the abandoned well?
Isn't this irrefutable evidence?
Cat demons
are born with a keen sense of smell.
The fresh smell of blood from the well
could be easily detected by you.
This doesn't prove
that you are the killer.
I am
the one who killed them.
Fine.
What about Auntie Li?
That woman who showed you kindness,
and gave you a new life,
could you really be so heartless
as to kill her with your own hands?
Auntie Li?
She...
She was killed?
Ji,
get up first.
listen to me.
I have determined
that Li Mao is definitely not the killer.
There is no way
he would kill his own mother.
You two covered for each other.
Your sincerity was misplaced,
which instead delayed
finding the real killer.
You need to be strong now.
Think carefully.
Are there any other details
or strange things
that you have forgotten?
Strange things?
If
I had to say there was something strange,
after I delivered the message that day,
I saw a person.
That person
was dressed in white,
looked like a scholar,
and had a very strange aura.
On my way to the ruined temple,
I came across a scholar.
He was dressed in white.
In the moonlight,
he seemed to be glowing.
A scholar in white.