[You Have My Heart]
[Episode 10: The Bloodied Arm]
It's already almost the third trip.
Lady Fufeng's secret chamber has been
completely cleared out by Lord Bai.
Is Lord Bai really
going to read all of these?
He's in seclusion, studying them himself.
He said he needs to
quickly understand all kinds of spirits.
Learn about spirits?
What's the point of just reading books?
If I take him out for a walk,
he'll know everything in no time.
Hurry up and go.
No, wait.
I'd like to ask for some money for drinks.
Go ask him.
Cheapskate.
Zuiwang Tavern?
That's right.
My Lord, did you bring enough money
with you?
Yes, I've got enough.
Good to hear.
The Zuiwang Tavern
is no ordinary tavern.
Humans and demons sit together here—
drinking and enjoying performances.
Didn't you say you wanted
to learn about the lives of demons?
This place is the liveliest,
and also the safest.
Let's go sit there.
Nice! Nice!
Are all the performers here spirits?
Mostly demons.
After all, each of them
has their own unique tricks.
But Lady Fufeng set the rules—
performing is allowed here,
but they must not use real demon magic,
and they're absolutely forbidden from
turning it into a way to make a fortune.
Why is that?
My Lord, think about it.
If every demon stopped proper cultivation
and came here just to show off tricks,
wouldn't Yin-Yang Crossing
fall into chaos?
And once they get a taste of easy gains
from using demon powers,
who can guarantee
they won't start to meddle
with that evil power in the future?
So you see,
most of the performers here
are low-level demons
just trying to earn a few coins
and get by.
It's basically
their first job after taking human form—
seeing a bit of the world.
So she didn't simply
ban everything outright.
Instead, she allowed this corner.
It gives them a slim chance of survival,
while also preventing them
from spreading and becoming a menace.
She actually understands
the art of governance.
My Lord, since we're already here,
have a drink.
Just a little drink.
Everyone!
My classmate here
is incredibly talented.
Today, why not let him
perform a bit for everyone
and liven things up?
Alright!
Renjie, you sure know
how to have a good time.
You said you were bringing us
to see some demon shows—
but I never expected
you'd also have
a whole live troupe of your own.
Li Mao, don't forget to thank Renjie
for taking you out to see the world.
Look at them up there—
those spirits are just doing
cheap little tricks,
and still getting
a full house of applause.
-You…
-Exactly!
You've got extraordinary talent.
Wouldn't it be a shame to keep it hidden?
Why not go up
and put on a show
to liven things up for everyone?
Yeah!
Exactly!
Liven things up!
Renjie, don't joke around.
I can't do that.
Are you really gonna
disrespect Renjie like that?
What do you mean you can't?
You were performing just fine in private—
now you're scared to go on stage?
Li Mao,
you used to show us tricks all the time.
Now you're backing out?
Don't you want to be brothers anymore?
Everyone!
Get up.
My classmate here is no ordinary man.
Let him show us a real skill—
how about it?
Good!
Hurry, hurry!
Alright, alright!
Come on! Come on!
Come on!
Move it!
Hurry up!
Show us. Come on!
Don't drag your feet!
Start already!
Do it!
Come on!
Don't be shy!
Li Mao, hurry up!
Start!
What are you being shy for?
Just do it!
Hurry up!
Start!
We're waiting!
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
Go on!
Show us what you've got!
Start already, what are you waiting for?
We're all waiting! Hurry!
Yeah!
Absurd!
My Lord.
What?
He called "My Lord"? Let's go—now!
Go, go, go!
Move.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Hey, you...
It's fine.
Everyone.
Everyone, don't be afraid.
I'm a gecko spirit.
My arm was just cut off—
it'll grow back
tomorrow.
So please don't worry.
But...
Doesn't that hurt?
I'm used to it.
You brat—
since when is limb regeneration
something you show off in a performance?
Lady Fufeng set the rules:
no bloody acts like this are allowed.
Did you forget already?
If she finds out,
you'll be held accountable!
Lady Fufeng?
Alright.
I got it.
Please forgive me this once.
Just don't tell Lady Fufeng please!
Fine, fine.
Alright.
I'm leaving.
You...
My Lord, this is...
Let's go, let's go.
Let's go drink instead—
everyone, disperse, come on!
Move aside.
This is terrifying...
Can one ever really
get used to the pain of losing an arm?
Bad omen...
So many scrolls...
Why not have Xiao Hu
bring them all over at once?
He's been working cases
with me nonstop lately.
He hasn't really slept in days,
so I sent him back
to rest early.
You've set your own rules—
coming here every night
to the Xiqianhua Mansion,
without even asking my opinion?
Fengling said
that staying close to you
helps restore
your spiritual power faster.
Until we find Bai Han,
I'll keep coming here.
But don't worry, My Lady—
I won't let it interfere
with official duties.
Was there bloodshed
at the county yamen today?
On the way here, I ran into a man
and helped him out.
A person?
You're sure
it wasn't a gecko spirit?
In Yin-Yang Crossing,
the wind can speak.
And it runs
faster than you.
Besides,
the wind doesn't lie to me.
My Lady, I just...
Afraid I'd punish him?
My Lady, he was only forced
by circumstance.
Since it's his first offense,
and he didn't cause
any major disturbance,
I hope you'll show leniency
and not pursue it.
Alright.
For your sake,
I'll let it go this time.
If you keep looking
so worn out like that,
and it actually costs you years
of your life one day—
I can't have people saying
I worked you to the bone.
Don't worry, My Lady.
I'll leave a final note
saying it was my own choice,
so it won't implicate you.
My Lady,
if I stay here,
will your spiritual power
really recover faster?
Otherwise what?
Do you think I'm keeping you around
because you're exceptionally handsome
and I just want to admire you every day?
Five drum beats.
Another murder case.
Lady Fufeng!
Lord Bai!
The scene inside is truly indecent
and a defilement of the sages!
Please, please don't be startled!
This was the son of the Wang family—
Wang Renjie.
I'll bring another stool.
And these were Hu Shanming
and Han Ziliang.
All three were students from the academy!
Hu.
The three victims all show ligature marks
around the throat from cloth bindings,
with the base of the tongue protruding—
clear signs of death by strangulation.
There is also a strong smell of alcohol
on the bodies,
and traces of liquor
in their mouths and noses.
Based on this,
they were likely heavily drunk
at the time of death,
around 9 PM last night.
In addition, their arms
were also torn off by brute force
while they were still alive.
Put it straight.
Shall I place it here?
The assailant subdued 3 drunk men,
tore off both their arms,
strangled them with cloth,
and then hung the bodies from the beams.
The killer is nearly sadistic—
this is beyond human capability.
A murder has occurred within the academy.
I ask all of you to cooperate
with the investigation.
It wasn't me.
No, no, not me.
Last night was the academy's rest day.
Did any of you hear anything unusual?
My Lord,
we all went to bed by 9 PM.
We didn't hear a thing.
That's impossible!
My Lord,
enexpectedly, Li Mao
didn't show up for his lesson today.
He's usually the first to arrive.
Li Mao?
There's no trace of corruption
flowing here.
Where is she going?
Liu Fengling,
what are you sneaking around here for?
Pretty impressive.
What exactly did you find?
So it really is you!
Your arm actually grew back!
Hey, you,
wake up.
You're Li Mao, right?
What are you doing hiding here
instead of staying at the academy?
I'm weak... I can't get up...
I just wanted to rest for a bit
before moving again.
I think you just don't have the strength
to run anymore.
You insolent wretch, Li Mao!
Why did you murder your classmates?
Class...
The three of them
are dead?
Since when did I say
three people were dead?
I haven't even drawn my blade yet!
What's going on here?
His breath is faint.
We need to get him
to Lady Fufeng immediately,
or he really won't make it.
Wake up!
Why is this demon
as fragile as paper?
Wake up!
How can you just pass out like that?
Li Mao!
Overwhelmed by fear.
His mind is in disarray.
I've used my spiritual power
to stabilize his heart meridian.
He's not in danger for now.
Thanks for your hard work, My Lady.
Lord Bai, you're not in such a hurry
to lock the demon culprit
in the county jail this time, are you?
My Lady, last time the mirror spirit
went out of control in the county yamen...
If it weren't for your intervention,
the consequences would've
been unimaginable.
We can't let incidents like that
happen again.
Lord Bai,
you are becoming increasingly adept
at governing Yin-Yang Crossing.
I can't keep dragging you down.
What is it?
It's nothing.
My Lady.
My Lady, you don't need
to be embarrassed.
I'm just helping you
restore your spiritual power.
A healer's heart is like that of a parent—
there are no taboos.
I'm not the one
who's embarrassed.
Lord Bai, your face is quite red—
for someone who claims to have no taboos.
My Lady, after Li Mao lost his arm,
in such a weakened state,
could he still kill anyone?
A gecko spirit is a low-tier demon,
timid by nature.
Its only ability
is limb regeneration.
Last night he had already severed one arm—
forget killing anyone,
even climbing onto the academy's beam
would've been difficult.
My Lady, that aligns with my thoughts.
When Li Mao heard
his classmates were murdered,
he blurted out
"three of them" immediately—
clearly something was off.
But the killer,
after committing the murders,
carefully staged the scene.
That suggests
a calm and highly disciplined mind.
It's impossible he would collapse
just from a few questions.
You're right.
But there's another possibility...
Corruption.
Like the mirror spirit—
if he was controlled by the evil power,
his power would surge,
and afterward he would lose his memory.
That would explain
why Li Mao
acted so differently before and after.
Well done.
As a reward,
I'll give you another clue.
Wang Renjie,
Han Ziliang,
and Hu Shanming—
what were they
usually like in the academy?
Renjie was a good person.
He often helped classmates
copy notes
and even treated them to snacks.
Yes, he had good grades,
spoke politely,
and was decent in character.
Han Ziliang's family
even funded our academy's library.
They were all very well-liked.
Even teachers
thought highly of them.
What about Li Mao?
Did he have any conflicts
with the three victims?
We're not really sure.
Not sure?
This is a murder case!
Withholding information
is punishable by law!
Well...
Sir, why make things difficult for them?
What could they even say?
Good that those three died.
They deserved to die!
Then explain—
how exactly did they deserve it?
They relied on their wealth,
excelled in their studies,
and were favored by the teachers.
But behind their backs,
they made fun of us—
lowborn demon-background students.
You sound very familiar with this Li Mao.
Are you friends?
Friends?
That coward?
He got bullied to death
and didn't dare say a word.
I look down on him.
If you're not friends,
why were you rushing
to find Li Mao this morning?
Lady Fufeng.
A civet has
a naturally sharp sense of smell.
You smelled his blood—
that's why you hurriedly switched form
and slipped out of the academy.
Hu.