Faculty of Business Administration 2-1 Faculty of Arts
Go Arts!
Go, go!
Pass the ball!
Great!
Jane!
P'Ohm, pass it!
Pass it! P'Ohm, watch out!
Oh shit!
We're screwed.
Do you know him?
It's P'Jane, the fourth-year student
with the same name as you.
The one they say is dangerous.
He's incredibly rich.
And incredibly talented.
And incredibly skilled, he can do anything.
Anyone can ask him for anything.
But he never gives anything away for free.
Everyone who asks him for something
will be indebted to him forever.
You can't escape even if you try.
P'Jane, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to.
Hey! What are you going to do?
P'Ohm, get up.
Can I have my ball back?
So that we can get back to our game.
Thank you.
You're pretty tough.
Are you ok?
I'm fine.
I know the truth, I taste the sin
It’s wrong but I don’t want it to be true
I’m losing all my discipline
You’re all I’m thinking of
and I’m breaking all the rules just because…
You’re a red flag but I’m colorblind
I know you’re dangerous
If it burns, let it burn me alive
I can't hold myself back, I’d cross every line
You’re a red flag but I’m colorblind
I know you’re dangerous
If it burns, let it burn me alive
I can't hold myself back, I’d cross every line
Anyone can tell me you're trouble
But being with you feels like paradise
I’ll be yours forever
Or maybe I’m just out of my mind
You’re a red flag but I’m colorblind
I know you’re dangerous
Woo!
Go on.
Jane! Ball!
P'Ohm!
Hey! Jane!
Jane!
Hey!
Fuck!
Wow, that's serious.
I think,
you should take a week off from school,
as the doctor suggested.
What classes do I have anyway?
I'm don't want to miss class.
The basic subjects,
and the electives.
Come on,
I'll take care
of those subjects.
In the meantime,
rest your leg and let it heal properly,
so you'll be ready for the next competition.
Our team finally won, you know.
Thank you so much.
If it weren't for you,
I would have been much worse off.
Okay...
I'll go get you some crutches.
Yeah, thanks.
(Did you hear the rumors about God Jane?)
(God Jane, )
(the 4th-year business administration student, right?)
(I've never seen a picture of him,)
(and he doesn't have a social media account.)
(Has anyone ever asked him for anything?)
( Did they get what they asked for?)
(There's nothing he can't do.)
(Is the person holding the ball in the picture)
(God Jane?)
(Someone dared to mess with God Jane.)
Hey.
Thanks, man.
Come on, let me help you stand up.
Okay.
Mr.Weerawit Wongruampiboon (Tee)
Be careful.
Almost there.
Hey!
Huh?
That's Tee!
Where did he go?
He didn't even show up for this match.
I didn't see him in class.
I haven't seen him for a week.
I don't know where he went.
I can't contact him.
I asked the student council.
They said they don't know either.
I really don't know
how long I'll have to compete in his place.
Come on, let's go.
Are you okay?
Yes, yes, yes.
(Mr.Thanaphat Phiboon-osoth)
Jane?
Come help me carry the stuff, son.
Yes, Mom.
Stop right there!
Your leg is injured
and you're still carrying heavy things?
Oh my god, I forgot.
Go, go, go, go.
Go sit down, son.
You won't get better if you don't sit down.
Come sit down.
Mom.
Go, go.
I'll do it myself.
Saying yes to things
without looking at himself!
Oh.
Dad, park the car.
How are you, son?
Is it still hurting?
Almost healed.
Um, Bandit?
Yes?
Trakarnta?
And Jane...
Uh...  Jane Aree?
Yes? Is that you?
You were absent from class due to illness.
I've already paired everyone up.
Sorry, man.
I wanted to be paired with you, but...
well...
The hell is wrong with you?
Oh, oh...
Don't worry, dear.
Don't worry.
We'll have another student joining us today.
But I think they informed me that...
they might be a little late.
Don't worry, dear.
Okay.
Ah...
There he is, your dance partner.
Jane Patrick.
Okay.
You... uh...
Jane, what?
Aree.
Jane Aree?
And Jane... uh...
Jane Patrick.
You two will dance together now.
And the dance positions are..
You, Jane...
Jane Aree.
Okay, let's do this.
Let me rearrange the positions a little.
You two.
Oh.
You'll be Little Jane.
And you...
Professor?
Big Jane, okay?
Little Jane will dance as the lady.
And Big Jane will be the gentleman.
Okay, baby?
You've got to be the little one!
Little Jane!
Ow!!
He bumped into me!
Stay still!
Sorry!
Alright, babes.
Now, we'll pair up according
to the class assignments from the last class.
Okay, pair up!
Good luck, little one.
Something like this, okay?
Can I dance with you?
Oh.
Sorry.
When turning around
Change your leg weight.
You've taken dance lessons before?
Yes.
I'm just here to get my grades.
But don't worry.
Dancing with me, you'll definitely get an A.
Ouch!
Are you okay?
From falling on the field that day...
Your leg still hurts?
You saw that?
Yes, I'm always looking at you.
You're always looking at me?
What?
What are you doing?
P'Jane, where are you going?
Sit down.
Why?
Hey.
What are you doing?
P'Jane, don't!
So elegant.
Don't step on my foot. Quick, slow.
I'm not going to.
Quick, quick, slow.
So heavy on the slow part.
P'Jane, don't.
Ow.
Why are you doing this?
You can tell me if it hurts.
Is that better?
Wow, it really does feel better.
How did you do that?
P'Jane, that's enough.
P'Jane!
Ok, that's perfect babes.
Come on.
Gather around here for a bit please.
And whoever is paired up,
will have to dance together on the final exam day,
okay babes?
Yes!
Sorry.
Remember this,
the first step might be hard,
but the next steps will definitely be easy.
For today,
I must say
thank you and goodbye.
Thank you.
Bye-bye baby.
See you next time.
Jane?
Can I have your contact?
Sure.
Let's add each other.
Let me see.
Is this your Instagram?
Hmm.
Everyone says he's a devil.
A man who can do anything.
But I like this picture.
You're a great artist.
You guys...
Yeah.
Big trouble!
Tee got arrested!
Huh?
See you later.
What the hell?
He used his position as university council president
to embezzle money from the volunteer camp.
Really?
Is that true?
Is this news real?
I can't believe it.
Damn, it looks so real.
Hey guys,
Why didn't you let us help you get it?
It's no big deal.
Seriously?
Did Tee really do something like that?
How long has he been doing it?
I heard they're saying
Tee got arrested
because he made a deal
with P'Jane about something
and he broke the contract.
What contract?
The position of student council president.
P'Jane or whatever her name is,
is he that scary?
I think he's pretty hot.
Handsome, rich, and has a great body.
And he seems smart too.
Khing.
If you let his outward appearance fool you,
you'll become another one of his victims.
Victim?
You're talking like he's a criminal.
I think,
there must be someone who's jealous of him.
So they made up rumors
to discredit him or something.
You don't know anything.
When you ask him for something,
and he comes back to take it back from you,
your life is ruined.
Is it really that bad?
And you, Jane,
what do you think of P'Jane.
You're paired with him today, right?
Damn you!
Not only are you holding hands,
you're even grabbing each other's feet!
We were going crazy!
It's nothing.
What do you mean nothing? What's he like?
Well...
He's good.
That's it?
That's all?
What else do you want?
Hey!
Shuuu!
What?
He's probably just here to drink.
Probably nothing to do with us.
He won't walk over here.
Really?
Yeah.
Don't overestimate yourself.
He's not coming over here...
Damn, he's here!
Come on in.
He's here.
What were you guys talking about?
I saw you looking at me.
Uh...
We were talking about...
How you danced so well in class today!
Really!
You danced so well!
Is your foot better?
It's better now.
Do you want a beer, P'Jane?
I'll get one for you.
No need.
I'll get one myself.
Aren't you going to dance with your friends?
Nope.
I'm not a good dancer.
What about you?
Aren't you going to dance?
I'm not a good dancer either.
That's not true.
You can do everything.
You're good at studying.
You're good at dancing.
Everything you do looks good.
You're good at everything too.
Good at playing soccer.
Good at drawing.
So why did you choose
to study business administration?
Why not art or animation?
Well...
My family owns a Chinese medicine shop.
So...
They probably wanted me
to study traditional Chinese medicine.
But I'm not good at it.
So I thought business administration would be better.
At least..
I could help manage things a little.
I've noticed you like doing things for other people,
haven't you?
If it makes other people happy,
then it makes me happy too.
But you don't look happy at all.
Why?
Actually,
I have a dream.
To become a famous artist,
to draw the pictures I love.
But I'm not as good as other people.
Those artists
who can still support their family.
It can come true.
I have a way to make you a famous artist.
Without you having to work hard,
without you having to struggle.
If you want to do it.
I can help.
No.
Is something that comes without effort
something to be proud of?
Do you care about pride that much?
Yes.
I'd rather be disappointed.
I've never heard anyone answer like that before.
You're much more special than I thought.
More special than anyone I've ever met.
I'm going to the restroom.
I'm impressed with you.
I want to get to know you better.
Jane.
I have to pee.
Can you go to the toilet with me?
Fine, let's go.
Let's go Put.
Hey? Are you ok?
Go on.
Jane.
I want to be straight with you about something.
I'm saying this
because I'm worried about you.
I...
Don't want you to get too close to him.
Why?
He seems like a great guy.
You..
Aren't you overthinking this a bit?
Go take a piss.
Believe me.
I'm your friend.
Jane, come on!
Hey!
Come on.
Get him!
Don't stop!
You can block it!
Do your best!
Don't let him get to you!
Yeah!!!
That's great!
Let's go!
Wow! That was a total one man show.
Because you're weak.
Hey!
You have someone coming to your games now?
He's just here to see the game.
Is he here for the game
or to watch who's playing today?
Oh, hey, Gap!
Yes!
We made it to the semi-finals!
Phew.
Honestly, I think this year
we're definitely going to get revenge
on the Sports Science team again.
Last year we lost to them.
So frustrating!
Yeah.
This year we have to beat them.
Of course! We have to!
Yeah.
Right?
You're such a brag.
Go.
You did great today.
My talented one.
Thank you.
Uh.. Excuse me?
Uh, um...
We're making content for a channel.
And we saw you
and felt that you guys are really cute.
We wanted to ask if we could interview you
for our channel?
Me?
Yes.
Uh...
And could we interview you too?
But if it's not convenient, it's okay.
No way.
Someone like P'Jane...
Never let anyone take pictures easily.
Really?
But I think he will.
Want to bet?
One thousand.
I'll give you two thousand.
You said it!
I think he'll do it.
If you're not comfortable,
I can do it alone.
You can interview us both at the same time.
Okay.
Then could you please move a bit closer?
You can get closer.
Okay, perfect.
Let's start.
One, two, three...
Get your money ready, you bastard.
Hello.
Hello, what faculty are you from?
I'm a second-year Business Administration student.
พี่มาจากบริหารปีสองครับ
I'm a fourth-year Business Administration student.
Hmm.
So...
How do you feel
about winning today?
I'm really happy.
Okay then...
I won't keep you any longer today.
Thank you.
Why are you smiling?
I'm not smiling.
Let's practice.
Sorry, P'Jane.
I hurt you again.
I'm not very good at dancing.
Look at me.
You keep looking at the floor when you dance.
It doesn't look graceful and lacks confidence.
More.
Don't be afraid of making mistakes.
Do you remember what you said at the bar?
Even if you try to dance
but make mistakes,
it's still something to be proud of,
compared to not having the courage to dance at all.
When you're with me,
I want you to be more confident in yourself.
Don't worry about whether you'll do well or not.
Like this?
See? You really can do it.
You did great today.
Let's call it a day for now.
P'Jane.
When will we see each other again?
Do you want to see me that much?
Then how about we go have a meal together?
After that, let me take you home.
Sure.
You're always secretly staring at me.
How did you know?
Because I've been looking into your eyes too.
Have your studies been tough lately?
Not really.
But next year definitely will be.
Right now, I just have reports to submit.
Then how about someday we find a quiet place
and work on our assignments together?
We can each do our own work, but sit together.
Would that be okay with you?
(Painting Competition - Grand Prize 200,000 Baht)
The person I trust the most.
Thank you.
(Painting Competition - Grand Prize 200,000 Baht)
What book are you looking for?
Maybe I can help.
Digital Business Management.
My professor assigned us
to present an online advertising campaign.
But I still can't think of a product,
so I don't know what kind of campaign to make.
Start with something close to you.
Is there any product you're passionate about?
My family runs a traditional Chinese medicine shop,
right?
So all I really know is Chinese medicine.
But...
Most of our customers are grandpas and grandmas.
Then why don't we try targeting a new market?
Don't think your customers can only be elderly people.
Chinese dramas are really popular right now.
A lot of young people watch them too, don't they?
Then let's try..
I've got it!
I'll give it a try first.
And if I get stuck, I'll come ask you.
What are you looking at?
Is there a ghost over there?
Not a ghost.
A demon.
What are you talking about?
You've gone crazy.
Jet!
Are you trying to kill me?
What's wrong?
Why didn't you knock?
I did.
Can you turn the music off first?
Hey, can I borrow this shirt?
Just a sec...
I'll get you your shirt.
I'll put it on for you.
I never thought
you'd would agree to be my model.
It's no big deal.
I'd do something like this for you anytime.
Thank you.
There's one more outfit.
One, two, three.
Can you hold it a little closer here?
Okay.
According to the survey,
over sixty percent of Thai people
are already familiar with watching Chinese dramas.
Members of Gen Z
primarily watch Chinese dramas
through digital platforms,
allowing China's soft power
such as Chinese herbal sachets
reach younger audiences more easily.
This creates an opportunity
for this Chinese herbal sachet
to be promoted online and ride this trend.
That's insane!
Seriously though,
how long did you spend preparing
for that presentation?
Your presentation was amazing.
I really want to know.
How did you pull it off?
How did you get him to agree
to model for your project?
You two seem way too close.
Is there something going on between you?
Or should I ask...
Are you secretly dating?
What nonsense are you talking about?
I don't like him.
When did I ever say you liked him?
Cut it out, Gap.
Ugh, my head.
Are you sure
you don't like him?
I said I don't.
What if he likes you?
Why would someone like him ever like me?
Enough already.
Stop encouraging him
to get involved with that senior.
Jane already said
he doesn't like P'Jane.
He's going to get himself into trouble
without realizing it.
You really don't like him, right?
Then I'm relieved.
I thought you two might've
had something going on.
So if you don't like him,
can you give this gift to him for me?
I like him.
Hey.
Then why don't you give it to him yourself?
Well...
Because I'm too shy.
I'm embarrassed.
What's the big deal?
Jane already said he doesn't like P'Jane.
So he can help a friend out.
Please?
Come on, bestie, help me out.
Just give it to him for me.
Please, please, please.
Okay, okay.
Love you.
Love you so much, seriously.
I'll make it up to you, I promise.
Go ahead and eat.
My treat.
If it weren't for you,
my presentation score wouldn't have been this good.
You know what?
The professor wouldn't stop praising me.
I even got the second-highest score in the class.
But I'm not surprised.
I told you that you could do it.
I'm proud of you.
Hey.
I'm thinking of entering that art competition.
The one with the concept
"The Person I Trust Most"?
How did you know?
I saw you looking at the poster in the library.
Yeah.
I've been thinking about it.
If I keep being afraid,
I'll never get to follow my dreams.
You're right.
So who are you going to draw?
The person you trust the most.
If I tell you now, it won't be a surprise.
P'Jane, I have something for you.
But you already treated me to a meal?
You don't need to give me a gift.
Well...
Actually, my friend asked me to give this to you.
Her name is Khing.
She's really sweet and fun to talk to.
I think you might like her.
Why are you giving this to me?
You really don't feel anything at all?
Bringing your friend's gift to me like this?
I understand now.
P'Jane...
Thank you, P'Jane.
(Aren't you coming to class?)
Your partner isn't here?
He'll probably show up later.
Just stretch first.
What the hell?
Hello.
Hello, oh!
Little Jane.
Big Jane informed me that he'd be absent today.
But don't worry, Little Jane.
We'll switch dance partners around today.
Be careful, dear.
Alright everyone, take your positions.
Find your dance partners.
And today,
I want to see a little more confidence.
Put some elegance into every step.
Ow!
Hey!
What ??
Ow!
Are you okay?
Hey!
Sorry, man.
What the hell are you playing at?!
Hey, hey.
I'm sorry.
Does saying sorry make it better?
Whoa! Hey!
What the hell do you want me to do then?
Hey, hey.
Calm down.
Don't do it!
Ref??!
What is it?
He started it first.
We won! Cheers!
Damn.
Our team won.
Aren't you happy?
I'm gonna head out.
Even if I stay.
There's nothing for him to talk to me about anyway.
Good luck.
Why?
Just because I gave him my friend's gift...
Was it really that wrong?
To the point
that he doesn't even want to see me anymore?
Seriously.
Why do you think he got that angry?
No filter.
No sugarcoating.
Don't worry about anyone's feelings.
I don't know.
Then let me ask you something else.
Deep down...
Did...
Did you actually want to give Khing's gift to him?
If you were him...
Would you be mad at me?
If I did that.
If I was interested in you?
Yeah, I'd be mad.
Hey!
It's because of you
that my team lost.
Get him!
Hey.
Hold him!
I already apologized.
Come here.
Let go.
But that's not enough.
I said let go!
Hey!
Get up.
Let go.
Stay still.
Think you're so tough?
Let me go!
What are you going to do?
Job!
Hey!
Let go!
Hold him down properly!
Stay still! Let me go!
Let go already!
You came at me hard.
So I'm going to hit you back just as hard.
Hey!
Arghhh!!
Shit! It's God Jane!
Let go,
if you don't want to get into trouble.
I'm outta here!
Hey, where are you running off to?!
Why the hell are you getting involved,
huh?
This is between me and him.
Job!
Hey!
Ow!
Aaaagh!
Jane.
P'Jane.
Where have you been?
I'll take you home.
Tonight I want to stay with you.
Can I?
What does this padlock lock away?
A secret.
A secret?
How do you really feel about me?
I'm so confused.
You're so mysterious.
I honestly don't know anymore
how you really feel about me.
What about you?
How do you really feel about me?
I don't know.
I just...
really like who I am when I'm with you.
You make me feel...
valuable.
I like it.
I like the time we spend together.
But I don't see how
I'm any more special than anyone else,
like you always say.
You know?
That's exactly what makes you special than anyone else.
I like you.
I like you too.
Will you be my boyfriend?
What if you don't go home
and stay with me at my condo for one night?
Stay the night with me.
But I have a psychology quiz tomorrow.
How about I tutor you, then?
I think we should study something else first.
I’ve already contacted someone who knows
about P'Jane ’s past for you.
P’Dan from Computer Engineering, right?
Do you need something from me?
You walk in with a warning sign
Just one look and already falling for you
My friends tell me not to cross that line
But I’m already out of time
I know the truth, I taste the sin
It’s wrong but I don’t want it to be true
I’m losing all my discipline
You’re all I’m thinking of
and I’m breaking all the rules just because…
You’re a red flag but I’m colorblind
I know you’re dangerous
If it burns, let it burn me alive
I can't hold myself back, I’d cross every line
You’re a red flag but I’m colorblind
I’d give up anything for you
Even if it burns, I'm willing to melt away
I can't hold myself back, I’d cross every line
You can paint me with all your darkest sides
And I’d still wear them like they’re paradise
If this love is a perfect crime
Then I’m guilty for life
You tell me, don’t be too emotional that’s rule no. 1
I’d give up everything to be your only one
Ooh
You’re the only one
I know the truth, I taste the sin
It’s wrong but I don’t want it to be true
I’m losing all my discipline
You’re all I’m thinking of
and I’m breaking all the rules just because…
You’re a red flag but I’m colorblind
I know you’re dangerous
If it burns, let it burn me alive
I can't hold myself back, I’d cross every line
You’re a red flag but I’m colorblind
I’d give up anything for you
Even if it burns, I'm willing to melt away
I can't hold myself back, I’d cross every line