[The Legend of Rosy Clouds]
[Episode 21]
[Duanyun Gate]
Your Excellency,
today, before all the officials, we are to
publicly examine the corruption case.
The whistleblower is Fan Yun.
Yet, at this crucial moment,
she's nowhere to be found.
Could it be...
Could it be that she has
a guilty conscience?
Then why hasn't she shown up yet?
Mr. Zheng, calm down.
Let me show you all
something first.
Bring them forward!
-What are these?
-No idea.
Your Excellency,
at Fan Yun's request,
I've brought these four chests
of suspected embezzled treasure.
That's so much.
It really is.
Too much.
Unbelievable.
Mr. Cai.
Come forward and take a look.
What do you think of this?
Your Excellency,
I know nothing about this.
You're the head of the Services Bureau.
Something this serious happened
on your watch,
and yet you're telling me
you knew nothing?
That doesn't quite hold water, does it?
Yes.
Problems did arise within my bureau.
I am willing to accept punishment
for my negligence.
You make it sound so easy.
You'll take responsibility for negligence—
then who, in your opinion,
should answer
for the corruption itself?
Your Excellency,
I truly know nothing about this.
It must have been Lord Lu.
He lined his own pockets!
Lord Cai,
even now,
you're still trying to
pin the blame on me?
Your Excellency,
I'm innocent.
may I say something?
Speak.
As far as I know,
the reason Fan Yun was able to uncover
the corruption in the Services Bureau
is precisely
that Lord Lu arranged for her
to audit the accounts overnight
and gave her full access.
If Lord Lu himself
were the one embezzling,
wouldn't he simply be
shooting himself in the foot?
Lord Cai, what do you think?
Your Excellency,
don't listen to Jiang Shu.
He's talking nonsense.
It must be Lord Lu
who broke the law for personal gain.
Your Excellency,
I too was deceived!
Lord Cai,
do you know what this is?
I don't care what it is.
This is a secret medicine I obtained
from the Sacred Rites Bureau,
called the "Truth Pill."
If you have a clear conscience, Lord Cai,
then take this pill
and recount everything
truthfully and in full.
If there's not a single lie,
you can naturally clear your name.
Just because you tell me to take it,
I have to?
Why should I?
But surely you'll listen to me?
I order you
to take the pill now
and prove your innocence.
Your Excellency,
this man Jiang Shu
wears that mask all the time
and never dares to show his true face.
We can't trust his words easily.
Fine.
Since His Excellency asks me to
take the pill, I will.
But if I take the pill today,
do you dare to take off your mask?
If I, Jiang Shu,
remove my mask today,
then you will take the pill?
Fine.
Then I'll show you
my true face beneath the mask.
When does this parade start?
Where is the top-ranked scholar?
It's not time yet.
What about second place?
Second place...
Haven't seen them either.
I heard there's also a female official
among those recommended this time.
A female official?
She's not here either.
Who's there then?
I got here before dawn
just to catch a glimpse of
the top three scholars
and share in their good fortune. Well...
You're far too impatient.
Still, that female official
really isn't here.
I heard the plague
spreading through Yong City
was caused by that very female official.
Every household in Yong City
is in mourning.
They're all waiting to
make her answer for it.
What nonsense!
Why would I lie to you?
You're every bit worthy of
being No. 1 on the Guanyu List.
I have only one word—
impressed!
-Yes, indeed.
-Yeah.
Indeed, he's quite a looker.
I don't deserve such praise.
Lord Cai,
are you feeling a burning sensation
in your stomach right now?
Once this medicine takes effect,
if you don't explain the full story
behind these treasures
within a quarter of an hour,
you will bleed to death
from your seven orifices.
By then, let alone me,
no one can save you.
Think it through yourself.
Listen up, Jiang Shu,
I won't be bluffed.
What evidence do you have
that this treasure
was hidden by me?
Here is the evidence.
Your Excellency,
this pouch contained the congratulatory gold
Tian Xing asked Lord Cai
to send back to his hometown
after passing the selection exam.
It was actually hidden inside
a secret compartment in the coffin.
Lord Cai,
playing all those tricks
to keep everyone away—
you were just afraid
the hiding place would be discovered, huh?
No, Your Excellency, this...
I remember this pouch
was originally in my residence.
It was Lord Lu.
He came to see me once,
and after he left,
the pouch disappeared.
I... I have no idea
how it ended up here.
Your Excellency,
if you don't believe me,
you can send someone to investigate.
That abandoned house and the coffin
are both under Lord Lu's name,
Your Excellency!
Your Excellency,
aside from my own residence,
I own no other property.
I've never heard anyone say
that this treasure
was hidden in an abandoned house.
Lord Cai,
how is it that you remember
that detail so clearly?
I...
Lord Cai,
your time is running out.
You'd better think clearly.
Your Excellency,
I...
where power is abused,
injustice is inevitable.
Even if Lord Cai is guilty,
there must be
witnesses and physical evidence.
Now Fan Yun
and Tian Xing
have both disappeared for no reason.
Those so-called receipts
and account books
cannot be verified either.
Doesn't that strike you
as rather suspicious?
The evidence uncovered
by Fan Yun and Tian Xing
naturally needs to be examined
in open questioning.
The auspicious time
for the parade has arrived.
We can't make everyone wait
just because of
those two people.
Yes, yes.
Please order the parade to begin,
Your Excellency.
The auspicious time must not be missed,
but now one of my officials
stands accused of corruption.
The truth
is just as important.
Tian Xing and Fan Yun have arrived!
-Your Excellency.
Please speak, Fan Yun.
Yes.
Your Excellency,
this account book
was sorted out by Tian Xing and me.
Every questionable transaction
has already been marked.
Please review it, Your Excellency.
Lady Fan, please
explain each entry
and answer everyone's questions.
Lord Zheng.
Does anyone else have any doubts?
Your Excellency,
yesterday, Tian Xing and I were taken away
by the Shi family.
They forced Tian Xing to marry
and wanted to kill me
as a sacrifice to the Spirit Immortal.
And all of this
was secretly instigated
by one of the officials.
The Shi family has been brought here.
They can be questioned at any time.
Lord Cai,
confess now,
and I'll count it in your favor.
I...
Just confess.
I confess.
I did
all of this.
All the treasure here
is bribes I've collected
over the years by abusing my position.
And it was also I
who incited the Shi family.
But Your Excellency,
all...
all the treasure is here.
I haven't spent a single coin.
Guards!
Take Mr. Cai away
to await sentencing!
Your Excellency.
Your Excellency, please spare me.
-Your Excellency, please spare me.
-Move!
Your Excellency, could you spare me?
Your Excellency!
Pass my order.
The auspicious time has arrived.
Let the parade begin.
♪ Chase the light,
let our dreams unfold wide ♪
♪ With bold resolve, ignite plain faith ♪
♪ Light them up ♪
♪ Let all wind and frost of days gone by ♪
♪ Turn to countless beams
of light within my eye ♪
♪ Await the sight of you ♪
Still brooding over your father?
Gao Ran told me everything.
His love for you
is actually much deeper
than you realize.
The reason he gave you the surname Yan
was that he hoped you would live
in your own way,
not just as another ordinary Fan.
And this plum tree—he planted it
because you loved eating plums.
Actually, in his heart,
you've long been a part of our Fan family.
Then...
since Father cared for me so much,
why
did he never tell me?
That brother of mine
has never been one to openly express
his likes and dislikes.
Actually, he doesn't like
the family either.
But there are only the two of us brothers
in this generation.
I left the family early on,
so he had no choice but to
carry the family on his shoulders.
The reason
he didn't let you take the surname Fan
was that he feared
you would be entangled
in all the burdens of the Fan family.
Do you understand now?
Thank you for the reminder, Uncle.
I finally
understand Father's deeper intentions.
The academician dinner is about to begin.
Your father is waiting for you there.
You should go.
I'll take my leave, Uncle.
Lord Zhao, a toast to you.
Lord Zheng, a toast to you.
Okay.
Cheers, Lord Li.
Lord Jiang.
I heard that Lord Cai has been
confessing his crimes
one after another in prison.
That Truth Pill of yours
is truly effective.
However,
the Sacred Rites Bureau never
gives its medicine out lightly.
How did you get your hands on it?
How could I possibly obtain medicine
from the Sacred Rites Bureau?
To be honest, Lord Lyu,
that pill of mine
is just herbal dregs
mixed with chili peppers.
Once you take it,
your chest naturally burns.
It's just that Lord Cai
had a guilty conscience,
so he fell for it.
So it was fake?
Not exactly.
It takes
both skill and talent to play the villain.
The more evil deeds you commit,
the heavier the burden on your conscience.
With that weight,
it's not easy to eat or sleep well.
The pill I gave Lord Cai
may well have been the very remedy
that finally eased his conscience.
Jiang Shu, oh, Jiang Shu.
I truly admire you.
Father,
let me offer you a toast.
Alright.
Thank you for raising me, Father.
Do you remember
the day I first came to the family?
Of course.
That day, you ate
three baskets of steamed buns
before you were satisfied.
I only found out later
that I'd eaten your basket too,
leaving you hungry all night.
That was nothing.
I wasn't hungry anyway.
Surnames aren't important.
What matters is
that we are father and son.
Good.
Hearing you say that,
I am
very gratified.
Come on.
Let me tell you,
it's actually good
that you have different surnames.
This way,
you have a chance
to marry Fan Yun.
Marry...
That way,
first,
there's no issue of propriety.
And second,
my adorable niece can marry into
our family.
Listen to Father.
Go on.
Your Excellency,
I can't hold my liquor any longer.
After this full cup,
I'll take my leave.
Alright.
You've worked hard today, Mr. Zheng.
Get some rest.
Thank you, Your Excellency.
Your Excellency,
we'll take our leave as well.
You're all leaving?
Fine then.
Officials,
you should rest early too.
Thank you, Your Excellency.
Why are you all just sitting there?
Let's keep drinking.
I'll go have a couple of drinks
with His Excellency.
Okay.
Cheers!
To Your Excellency.
To you, officials.
Are you looking for me?
You're here.
I... I just got back.
From a blind date?
That's all behind me now.
Yeah.
Gao Ran.
Are you leaving?
I've been sitting for too long,
just getting up to stretch.
That's good.
The banquet is just getting started.
Have a couple of drinks with me.
Welcome back.
Greetings, Your Excellency.
No matter what,
you've finally become
an official of Nine Cities.
Congratulations, Lady Fan.
Thank you, Your Excellency.
Next
is the assignment of duties.
Your Excellency,
I...
have a presumptuous request.
Sit down and speak.
I'd like to take part
in handling the epidemic in Yong City.
You want to go too?
"I want to go too?"
Who else wants to go?
After the parade,
Tian Xing requested permission to go.
No wonder
I didn't see him just now.
So he's planning to go
all by himself?
It's dangerous ahead. How could I possibly
let you go by yourself?
In controlling an epidemic,
two things matter most:
speed and stability.
Speed
means we must quickly
cut off the source of infection
and stop the spread.
I know medicine.
If I go, I can tend to the sick first
and reassure the local people.
Then what about stability?
Stability means
every treatment
must be based on solid evidence
after careful verification.
We can't prescribe medicine recklessly.
What do you need me to do?
The conditions in Yong City are too harsh
for developing medicines.
I can't take
all of Lord Jiang's books there,
nor can I carry all the herbs.
For those already infected,
we still have to rely on
Your Excellency and Lady Fan Yun.
If we don't have sufficient confidence
in handling this epidemic,
sending a large force there
will only make things worse.
I agreed to let Tian Xing go first
because it's his hometown.
He's more familiar with it.
I also need someone to take the lead
and open up the situation.
Yes.
From this point on,
even if there's only
a one-in-a-million chance,
we can't afford to ignore it,
nor can we delay.
That's right.
But...
you must have heard those rumors.
If I put you in charge,
I'm worried there could be danger—
even a risk to your life.
But Your Excellency,
the people of Yong City
are also in mortal danger.
It is exactly because of those rumors
that I must go there.
I'll go solve the problem.
This way,
not only can I
save the people of Yong City,
but I can also dispel those rumors
and become a role model
for future female officials.
It will also show everyone
that Your Excellency's policy
of opening
the civil service examinations to all
is right.
You really want to go that badly?
Actually, I guessed it long ago.
Whatever Fan Yun decides to do,
she'll see it through.
She never considers
how worried everyone else might be.
Well...
Your Excellency,
aren't you the same?
You're right.
That's why I say
that's one thing
we have in common as husband and wife.
Hus...
W-What husband and wife?
Just now, you addressed me as Lady Fan.
I'm your subject now.
Yeah.
Whatever our relationship is,
as long as it involves you,
it means something to me.
Alright.
Tomorrow, before all the officials,
I'll announce that you and Tian Xing
will jointly handle the epidemic.
Great.
Thank you, Your Excellency.
Whether women
can truly become capable officials,
we shall see
starting tomorrow.
Does...
it still hurt?
You mean here?
Or here?
Just a few days apart,
and you've already learned to tease me.
This wound healed a long time ago.
But this one
still hurts a bit.
Sorry.
Actually, last time,
I didn't know if I could come back.
I thought, what if I couldn't come back?
I should at least leave you something
so you would remember me.
Miss Wei, actually, every time you appear,
you leave a deep impression on me.
Then tell me,
do you remember
what I said to you here last time?
I knew you wouldn't.
Last time,
I told you my name is Wei Ying,
and "Ying" means firefly.
It was just like now—you sitting there,
and me sitting here.
Oh,
and also
that time I brought you
the sour plum drink.
I just wanted to add some
extra nutritious ingredients for you.
Who knew
your soldiers would end up...
You know what,
I might actually
have some medical talent after all.
Look,
all those strong,
sturdy soldiers of yours—
one bowl, and down they all went.
Oh, right.
Do you still remember
the first time we met?
♪ Wind sheds rain like tears ♪
♪ Over the whole town ♪
♪ At the second our gazes meet ♪
♪ Past memories roar one louder beat ♪
You see,
you don't remember either.
So how could I not bite you?
♪ Perhaps hearts long to seek ♪
I figured
even after the wound healed,
♪ Etch within our fingertips ♪
the scar would remain.
♪ Hear crisp footsteps echo clear ♪
And if it doesn't,
I'll just bite you again.
♪ Strike out
on a fearless dream's frontier ♪
♪ Though fleeting years rush
without delay ♪
See? See?
♪ A wisp of softness
tints your brow each day ♪
You've got
such an adorable dimple,
♪ Walk side by side with moon and sun ♪
yet you never smile for me.
♪ When all is said and all is done ♪
I
remember everything about you.
♪ We'll ride upstream and downs ♪
But you?
♪ When deep love dwells within our eyes ♪
You don't remember anything at all.
♪ Our burning longing never dies ♪
♪ Wander together through wind and frost ♪
♪ Don't let the sun down ♪
Wei Ying.
Wei Ying?
♪ Perhaps hearts long to seek ♪
You look so handsome when you smile.
♪ Etch within our fingertips ♪
♪ Hear crisp footsteps echo clear ♪
You must
remember me.
♪ Strike out
on a fearless dream's frontier ♪
♪ Though fleeting years rush
without delay ♪
♪ A wisp of softness
tints your brow each day ♪
It's hard...
♪ Walk side by side with moon and sun ♪
♪ When all is said and all is done ♪
to forget.
♪ We'll ride upstream and downs ♪
♪ When deep love dwells within our eyes ♪
♪ Our burning longing never dies ♪
The new academicians
have completed
their internship within the residence.
Starting today,
they will be assigned to various bureaus
for further training.
Fan Yun!
I order you,
together with Tian Xing,
to jointly handle
the epidemic in Yong City.
Yes, Your Excellency.
Your Excellency,
I have an objection.
The epidemic in Yong City
is spreading rapidly,
and the situation remains unclear.
How can these two newcomers
shoulder such an important task?
I believe
such a critical matter as epidemic control
should be entrusted to Lord Jiang.
That would be the more prudent choice.
Mr. Jiang now heads the Services Bureau,
with heavy official duties
and multiple responsibilities.
So he only needs to
assist with this matter
and provide support.
As for Tian Xing,
though young,
he has a solid medical background
and is also from Yong City.
He has already gone ahead of everyone else
to assess the situation there.
With him in charge of the epidemic,
we can be confident
everything will proceed smoothly.
Your Excellency,
I second that objection.
May I ask, Your Excellency,
what is the use
of sending
Fan Yun there?
Your Excellency, esteemed officials,
rumors have been spreading
that this epidemic
was caused by a woman holding office.
I believe
controlling the epidemic
is not only about treating the disease
but also about treating the mind.
That is why I wish to
go to Yong City myself
to dispel those rumors,
so that all under heaven
will no longer have objections
to commoners and women
holding official positions.
Well said.
Whoever started the trouble should end it.
Lady Fan, your courage and determination
have earned my respect.
I shall watch with great anticipation.
Zheng,
are you alright?
Done being at odds
with the Fan family's little girl?
Since the boat has already set sail,
rather than trying to stop it,
we might as well
let it ride the wind.
Only I wonder—is your wind
blowing east or west?
Whichever way it blows,
as long as it's strong enough,
it will
carry the boat ashore one day.
Lyu,
what's Zheng
being so cryptic about?
Explain it to me.
He means that
since Fan Yun's becoming an official
is a done deal,
just let her go and make a mess of things.
Epidemics have always been
difficult to contain.
If she makes even the slightest mistake,
he will impeach her.
And he will use that to prove
that women cannot serve as officials,
nor can commoners.
Please.
[Yong City]
The Spirit Immortal comes forth.
The people are saved from disaster.
The holy sect descends.
The sun and moon shine again!
[Chunxiu, Yong City Resident]
The Spirit Immortal comes forth.
The people are saved from disaster.
The holy sect descends.
The sun and moon shine again!
Thank you. Thank you.
[Zhu Luan, Yong City Resident]
I heard the Shi family nobles
left for Ling'an a few days ago.
Someone should be coming
to save us soon, right?
Let's hope so.
Zhu Luan!
I'm back!
Brother!
Zhu Luan!
You're back.
Have you been missing me?
Yes.
Have you been listening to your mother?
I have.
Good girl.
These are all the records
we've gathered so far
about the epidemic in Yong City.
They detail
the onset time of patients in each county,
the number of cases,
and their basic conditions.
Great.
These are
all essential right now.
Don't you have anything to say to me?
Tell...
tell you what?
Your Excellency truly plans ahead
with remarkable foresight,
embodies the virtues of a wise ruler,
and lays the foundation
for a flourishing age.
Your Excellency is truly amazing.
I'm not that amazing.
I merely...
Greetings, Your Excellency.
You're here.
Lord Jiang.
Perfect timing.
Fan Yun and I are just
studying the epidemic in Yong City.
This record here
documents the very first case—
it seems to have been
at the beginning of summer.
The symptoms include...
unbearable fever,
continuous groaning,
along with severe headaches and vomiting.
That sounds like
it was caused by some kind of poison.
But this record
shows nothing
unusual in his food.
However, soon after,
his whole family
came down with the same illness.
Not just one family.
It seems the entire village got sick.
Look here.
The spread went from isolated cases
to entire communities.
Could this disease
be contagious?
If it were spread through
person-to-person contact,
the outbreak pattern
should radiate outward.
But the later cases were
in villages even hundreds of miles apart.
It's almost as if the source of infection
can shift places at will.
Lord Jiang,
has Yong City ever experienced
an epidemic like this before?
Yong City lies in a hot climate,
with complex summer weather
and many kinds of snakes,
rodents, and insects.
Various illnesses break out
from time to time.
But I've never heard of one
this contagious before.
At the very least, we've now confirmed
this disease doesn't spread
from person to person.
That's a real blessing
amid the misfortune.
Didn't Lady Fan Yun
declare so boldly
that she'd face the challenge head-on
and dispel the rumors?
Why is she still in Ling'an?
Is she afraid?
See? Being an official
isn't so easy after all.
Commoners becoming officials
is already absurd enough—
what can a woman do as an official?
When it's time to face danger,
isn't it always we men
who stand on the front lines?
Blood!
You're bleeding!
Blood...
Lord Xu? Lord Xu?
Wake up, Lord Xu!
Lord Xu!
Help!
Stop laughing!
What is wrong with you guys?
Can't you see Lord Xu has fainted?
This is the Spirit Immortal Sacred Water.
The Governor's wife...
How has Lady Fan Yun
been?
Has anyone been
making things difficult for her?
Someone is maliciously slandering her,
saying the plague here
is divine punishment
for a woman holding office.
But trouble of that sort
is nothing she can't handle.
True.
Nothing can defeat Lady Fan Yun.
Lady Fan Yun is the strongest
and most optimistic person
I've ever known.
And now,
there is one more.
You.
How could I possibly be
compared to Lady Fan Yun?
Zhu Luan told me everything.
If you hadn't
held things together all this time,
this pharmacy would've become
a house full of the living dead.
You've done an incredible job.
You don't know
what I've done in the past.
No matter what you did before,
here in Yong City,
you're already someone
everyone looks up to.
The water's boiling.
What's this?
Miss Suyin,
do we have wine?
Yes.
Alum?