[The Legend of Rosy Clouds]
[Episode 22]
So you mean...
our current research plan
needs to be scrapped?
The letter indicates
that after Tian Xing
went to Yong City this time,
he found that the people there
were drinking the Spirit Immortal Water
laced with alum.
And when he had abdominal pain
and diarrhea as a child,
his sister would give him alum water,
saying it could stop the diarrhea.
That is to say,
the symptoms like
fever and fatigue in the patients
were a series of reactions
caused by the diarrhea.
So the diarrhea
is the main symptom this time.
Besides,
the samples brought back previously
had traces of being gnawed by rats.
So we have been
focusing our investigation
on the plague.
Taking all the previous circumstances
into account,
this epidemic
is a severe malaria outbreak
caused by mosquito bites.
This epidemic
is recorded in the books.
I remember
there are roughly 4 types:
first, toxic miasma from mountain streams;
second, wind-heat phlegm;
third, pathogenic factors;
fourth, heat toxin.
And among these four,
the most severe one
is heat toxin.
So I suspect
that this time,
it should be malaria.
That's right.
And it spread so rapidly
that it became overwhelming
in a short time.
Your Excellency,
we can handle it.
But...
you have to help me deal with someone.
Lord Jiang's collection of books
is indeed as vast as the ocean.
Tian Xing wasn't exaggerating
when he said he couldn't move them.
Your Excellency?
Why are you here?
I was afraid you'd be tired,
so I came to help you.
Okay,
let's look together.
Why can't we find it?
We've looked everywhere I should.
I don't think I've seen this book before.
This is...
Your Excellency, you're awake?
I... I think I found it.
Look.
Sweet wormwood prescription.
It's the sweet wormwood prescription.
I found it.
You found it?
Wei Ying, hurry!
Your Excellency!
-They found it?
-Fan Yun?
We found it.
It's the sweet wormwood prescription.
It's recorded in this book.
It says,
sweet wormwood...
Take...
2 liters of something...
Wring it out,
and then drink it all.
Look.
This ancient book
is incomplete
and blurry.
As for what the 2 liters refers to
and how it should be wrung out,
it's not clear.
However,
we can look throug
more medical books for reference
and see if we can reconstruct
the original text of this ancient book
and find the right way
to test the medicine.
Then let's not delay.
Wei and Yan, gather all the physicians
in Qi Residence as soon as possible
to work on this prescription together.
-Yes.
Alright.
I'll go with them.
You didn't sleep a wink last night.
Why don't you go back and rest first?
Leave the prescription to me.
No need, Your Excellency.
I'm not tired,
and I don't feel like resting.
I just want to find the prescription
as soon as possible
so that more patients can be treated.
I'll go now.
How is it, Sirs?
How do we prepare this prescription?
Traditional Chinese medicine
is usually
boiled in water.
However, this book
says to wring the herb out.
It should be a special method
used to avoid
destroying certain components
in the sweet wormwood.
That makes sense.
Handbook of Prescriptions for Emergencies
indeed records that sweet wormwood
can clear heat, cool the blood,
and relieve summer heat.
It can also be used to reduce fever
caused by yin deficiency and hot flashes.
However,
there are only ancient records
and no prescriptions or cases.
Nowadays,
malaria in Yong City is so severe.
Simple preparation methods
might not
bring out its medicinal properties.
-Right.
So,
we can handle the 2 liters mentioned here
according to this idea
by choosing some medicinal herbs
with strong effects
to mix with sweet wormwood.
That's right.
I heard
that some special components in this herb
can only be activated
by strong stimulation.
As they say, fight poison with poison
to cure the disease.
Then what kind of poison should we use
to mix with it?
Yes.
Well...
Gelsemium elegans,
oleander,
poisonous wine,
and datura
are all options.
Then let's
try them one by one.
♪ Our hearts reach for the morning glow ♪
♪ Our dreams fear no barren land below ♪
♪ What does it matter
if we fly against the wind? ♪
♪ We vow to live up
to our youthful prime ♪
♪ To walk alongside ordinary folks alike ♪
♪ Sharing the same ray of light ♪
♪ Fear no strange land nor dim twilight ♪
Turn down the heat.
♪ All for this boundless world ♪
It's almost done.
♪ To wear a robe of radiant glory ♪
Your Excellency,
it's about time.
Bring them all out then.
♪ Face the light,
gaze ahead with brave eyes ♪
♪ Let all darkness and hurt step aside ♪
Physician Li,
♪ It's unstoppable ♪
are the antidotes all prepared,
and are you sure everyone will be safe?
♪ Chase the light,
let our dreams unfold wide ♪
Yes.
Rest assured, Your Excellency.
Taken in moderation,
this medicine poses no threat to life.
♪ With bold resolve, ignite plain faith ♪
That's good.
Thank you all for your trouble.
♪ Light them up ♪
♪ Let all wind and frost of days gone by ♪
♪ Turn to countless beams
of light within my eye ♪
♪ Await the sight of you ♪
Physicians,
how is it?
This prescription is not right.
Physician Li,
what about yours?
Not this one either.
Physicians,
what about yours?
Not this one.
My Lord,
the pulse has changed.
It's this prescription.
Fan Yun!
Your Excellency!
That's wonderful, Your Excellency!
We found the medicine!
-Well...
-Great!
does this mean Yong City is saved?
Yes!
Yong City is saved!
-We did it!
-That's great!
We finally found it!
Next,
we just need
to gather the medicinal herbs.
[Juyun Pavilion]
Boss,
Lady Fan Yun went to the herb firm.
What?
Juyun Pavilion has everything.
Why did she go to the herb firm?
What do you think?
Those misers at the herb firm.
I went to negotiate a deal with them
several times,
but we couldn't agree on a price.
The price you offered
indeed wasn't very high.
But...
it was very fair.
They are just too greedy.
It's a rip-off.
I can't go this time.
I got it.
Wait.
I'll go take a look anyway.
Then I will leave this matter to you,
Mr. Cao.
You're welcome.
Tomorrow I'll send someone
to deliver the herbs to you.
Thank you, Mr. Cao.
Don't mention it.
Making the best use of herbs
is what our firm is all about.
Now that you need them to save lives,
we are naturally duty-bound.
You can take my carriage back first.
I knew it.
Fan Yun!
Why is he here again?
Zheng...
Young Master Lou.
Why are you here?
Is he making things difficult for you?
Making things difficult?
Why would he do that?
I told you that whatever you want to do,
I can help you achieve it.
Mr. Cao,
please hand over everything
that Lady Fan Yun needs.
And if I don't do as you say?
Then I'll buy this firm
at the price you previously stated.
Lady Fan Yun,
I didn't expect
you and Juyun Pavilion
to be so close.
I...
I didn't expect it either.
Then I've changed my mind.
I can't give you the sweet wormwood
so easily.
You...
I am Fan Yun, a newly appointed official.
I am here about the Yong City plague.
I ask for your assistance.
Lady Fan Yun
needs our sweet wormwood
to make a specific medicine
for the plague,
and the more the better.
As for this matter,
I originally wanted to make the decision.
But the arrival of Young Master Lou Qiyan
of Juyun Pavilion
reminded me of something.
What is it?
The biggest difference
between our trade and Juyun Pavilion
is that we operate through consultation
and shared governance.
We are not a one-man operation
backed by sheer wealth.
So for this matter,
besides persuading me, Lady Fan Yun,
you also need to persuade everyone here.
Sweet wormwood
is a good medicine for the plague?
Yes.
We have developed all the formulas.
However,
Qi Residence has limited raw materials.
That is why I came here
to ask for your help.
This is a good thing that benefits
both the people and ourselves.
We are naturally duty-bound to help.
But I heard
that the Yong City plague is contagious.
Yeah.
You just need
to hand over the sweet wormwood.
Juyun Pavilion
will handle the transportation.
No disease will infect you.
Actually, this disease
does not spread from person to person.
As long as we take
good mosquito protection measures,
there will be no danger.
Since it's safe,
-then we...
-Well...
This is a considerable expense.
I wonder if Qi Residence
has allocated special funds
to cover the costs
of our manpower and resources.
Didn't you see those boxes at the door?
We don't want to get involved with
Juyun Pavilion too much.
Regarding the expenses,
I have an unreasonable request.
I wonder if you
recognize this book.
This book is...
-Isn't this...
-Exactly.
This is an ancient medical book I found
in Lord Jiang's library.
There are also many annotations
made by Lord Jiang himself.
And medical books like this
are countless
in Lord Jiang's home.
Sirs,
as the top herbal medicine experts
across the Nine Cities,
I believe you understand
the commercial value
of these medical books
better
than I do.
Lady Fan Yun,
are you trying to pay us
with this medical book?
Not exactly.
After all, these books
are Lord Jiang's private property.
I cannot use someone else's property
for my own benefit.
Then what do you mean?
You can't
just let us feast our eyes on it, can you?
Lord Jiang is the assistant official
for the Yong City plague this time.
He said that
anyone who helps with this matter
can be considered an advisor.
By then,
you can go to his library
and borrow books at will.
There is such a good thing?
However, Lord Jiang also said
these books can only be borrowed,
not taken away.
So gentlemen,
you still need
to rely on your own abilities
to memorize them.
My Juyun Pavilion has many talents.
This little advantage is enough.
Young Master Lou,
are you trying to compete
for this matter as well?
Yes.
I did a rough calculation.
With Lord Jiang's medical books,
my Juyun Pavilion can develop
countless superior medicines.
When that time comes,
I won't even need to buy this firm.
I'll just open one myself.
This won't do.
But this matter
is related to herbs after all.
I think
these gentlemen are more suitable.
Yes, yes, we are more suitable.
Alright.
That makes sense.
Since we are the most professional,
why let it pass through others' hands?
I'll sign.
- I'll sign!
- I'll sign too!
We all sign!
Okay.
Those who are willing
to participate in this,
come over and sign your names.
-Let's go.
How was it?
How was what?
I used to disdain helping others.
When I saw people being vulnerable,
I even wanted to step on them.
But today,
you've already stepped on me.
Has the girl from the Fan family
made any moves these days?
Wei Sui sent word
that she had found the herb firm to help.
Right now,
the herbs
are already on their way to Yong City.
They found the herbs?
Yes.
It seems
to be sweet wormwood.
Who are you?
Do you know these
are Juyun Pavilion's carts?
You're exactly who we're here to rob!
Kill them!
Your Excellency?
Fan Yun!
Why are you here?
Did you sleep well?
Why are you here too?
Did you two come together?
-Of course not.
I came to see you.
I came looking for you.
Fan Yun,
something happened.
The sweet wormwood was stolen.
The sweet wormwood was stolen?
Can you not interrupt when I'm speaking?
It was Juyun Pavilion's convoy.
On the way to Yong City,
they were robbed by bandits.
Bandits?
But why would bandits
rob sweet wormwood?
So I was thinking,
maybe they weren't bandits.
So...
Zheng Yuan!
-Lord Lyu! Lord Lyu!
-Zheng Yuan!
-Lord Lyu!
Lord Lyu!
Our Master is unwell
and hasn't gotten up yet.
Please come back another day.
Tell that to someone else!
Tell him to come out and see me now!
Lord Lyu,
please go back for now.
I will pass this on to Lord Zheng.
No need!
Zheng Yuan!
I never thought
you would dare to do such a thing!
Withholding the sweet wormwood
and delaying the medicine delivery!
You are treating human lives like dirt!
Those are all fresh, living human lives!
They are the people
we defended with our lives!
Yet because of your selfish motives,
you abandoned them all!
You must have lost your mind!
Lord Lyu,
you have misunderstood Lord Zheng.
What is there to misunderstand?
Zheng Yuan!
I don't care what your reasons are.
Having done such a thing,
you are unfit
to be Lord Zheng of the Nine Cities!
You are even less fit...
to be my friend.
Wait.
It still doesn't make sense.
I don't get it either.
What exactly is his purpose
for doing this?
Why are you looking at me?
You and Lord Zheng share a deep
grandparent-grandchild bond,
and you understand each other well.
Share your thoughts.
Yes.
Tell us what you think.
Grandfather has always felt that
Fan Yun is misleading the public,
bewitching the Governor to promote
the national selection exam.
He wants to use this to ruin Fan Yun,
abolish the national selection exam,
and restore things to how they used to be.
I still feel something is wrong.
Gambling with the lives of the people
just to abolish
the national selection exam?
This doesn't seem like something
Lord Zheng would do.
Grandfather's way of doing things
this time
is indeed a bit crazy.
Crazy?
It's simply absurd.
Anyway,
the most important thing right now
is to quickly send the sweet wormwood
to Yong City to save lives.
But...
what is the best way to do it?
Right, Your Excellency.
We can use the beacon tower.
The beacon tower?
When trouble occurs at one spot,
help comes from all quarters.
If we light the beacon tower,
the other 8 cities will
receive the message at top speed.
Then,
they will
send the sweet wormwood over
as fast as possible.
-Let's do it right now.
-No!
Absolutely not!
Have you forgotten
what I promised Lord Zheng?
During the trial period
of the national selection exam,
if the beacon tower is lit,
it means asking for help
from major noble families.
In this way,
the national selection exam
will be abolished immediately.
But if you light the beacon tower,
you won't be able
to keep your official position.
Therefore,
no one can light it.
But...
So this was Grandfather's purpose
all along.
Now all the blame is placed on the reform.
That makes sense.
As expected of my grandfather.
What are you so proud of?
Is craziness hereditary in your family?
Our Zheng family has been brave
and good at fighting since ancient times,
producing generations of talents.
Our Qi family has a majestic aura!
Where are you going?
I'm hungry.
Anyway, our Fan family can't go hungry.
You Qi family and Zheng family
can take your time arguing.
What?
We are hungry too.
Alright.
I'll bring some good food back for you.
Once you're full,
you'll have the energy to argue.
Take your time arguing.
I'm leaving.
Take me with you.
It's not on the way.
I'm not going back to my residence.
It is on the way.
You want to go to my house?
Don't bother.
Grandfather must have expected this.
He won't see anyone,
especially you.
I'm not going to see him.
Then where are you going?
To the beacon tower.
Aren't you afraid of affecting Fan Yun?
Why is it taking Fan Yun so long
to make food and come back?
Fan Yun!
Why did you lock the door?
Don't go to the beacon tower by yourself!
Fan Yun, hurry up and open the door!
Fan Yun's trick
of catching a rat in a trap
is really brilliant.
Are you a rat?
Whoever wants to go out is the rat.
I think staying here is pretty good.
Fan Yun!
Be careful!
I'll be waiting for your good news.
Stop being glib, will you?
Hurry up and help me open the door.
What are you waiting for?
Why should I go against Fan Yun?
What do you mean?
Are you taking Fan Yun's side on this?
Or should I take yours?
Do you know what it means
for Fan Yun to go light the beacon tower?
I do.
It means she is going over
the Governor's authority
to get medicine
for the people of Yong City.
What's wrong with that?
Fan Yun will be impeached
and held accountable,
or even lose her qualification to be an official.
Do you know that?
That's exactly the result I want.
The door of my Juyun Pavilion
will always be open for her.
Do you even know
why Fan Yun divorced me?
Because she didn't want
to live with you anymore.
Then what about her training
at the Commerce Bureau?
Studying day and night,
preparing for the selection exam,
and trying desperately
to pass her internship?
If all she wanted was freedom and leisure,
why did she have to take it step by step,
braving difficulties and dangers
to get here?
Do you think what you can give her
is what she wants?
Does she want what you can give her?
She wants neither!
Neither of us can give it to her!
Only what she strives for herself
is what she truly wants.
That makes some sense,
but not much.
Stop nagging.
Hurry up and help me open the door!
I really can't run anymore!
Fan Yun!
Fan Yun, stop running!
Your Excellency, stop chasing me!
If you stop running, I'll stop chasing!
I can only stop running
if you stop chasing!
I'll stop chasing.
So you stop running too.
Okay.
Then stop chasing.
And... and I'll stop running.
You tricked me!
Fan Yun!
Military zone!
No entry for plain commoners!
Fan Yun,
you're overstepping your authority!
I can punish you for this!
Come down right now!
Your Excellency,
we both know
that this is the only way
and the best way.
Then let me
light this fire.
No!
You can't.
For the national selection exam
and to abolish the old rules,
you have lain low for so many years.
And all these years,
you have been pretending to be...
Enough! Say no more!
Fan Yun, I'm telling you.
If you light this fire now,
it will be a crime of overstepping.
Not only will your political career
end again,
I...
I'm just afraid I won't be able
to protect you, you know?
But if you light it,
the political careers of all the commoners
who have already passed the selection exam
will end.
A year ago, I
didn't even have the right to stand here.
But today, I
can use this torch
to save millions of people.
This is what I have always wanted to do,
and the meaning of my being an official.
Your Excellency,
saving Yong City,
reforming the selection exam,
and pacifying the Nine Cities' affairs—
there are so many things
waiting for you to do.
So this fire today
must be lit by me.
Sacrificing one Fan Yun
to save a governor who truly wants
to change the Nine Cities...
I think
it's worth it.
♪ Face the light,
gaze ahead with brave eyes ♪
♪ Let all darkness and hurt step aside ♪
♪ It's unstoppable ♪
♪ Chase the light,
let our dreams unfold wide ♪
♪ With bold resolve, ignite plain faith ♪
♪ Light them up ♪
♪ Let all wind and frost of days gone by ♪
♪ Turn to countless beams
of light within my eye ♪
♪ Await the sight of you ♪
Fan Yun!
No regrets once the piece is played?
No regrets!
Your Excellency,
being your subject
is my honor.
♪ My heart is unwavering ♪
♪ My dreams become wings ♪
♪ What does it matter
if we fly against the wind? ♪
♪ The most ordinary desire ♪
♪ Is worth lighting up ♪
♪ With my life ♪
♪ From then on ♪
♪ Time left a glimmer of hope ♪
♪ Take it as the glory of my journey ♪
♪ Face the light,
gaze ahead with brave eyes ♪
♪ Let all darkness and hurt step aside ♪
♪ It's unstoppable ♪
♪ We chase the light and travel together ♪
♪ Not considering how long the road is ♪
♪ When looking back,
I'm still young and stubborn ♪
♪ Let all wind and frost of days gone by ♪
♪ Every place I've been to ♪
♪ Shines brightly ♪
♪ Just as I expected ♪
Master.
The Governor urgently summons
all noble ministers to his mansion
within 15 minutes.
The Governor would give in so easily?
The fire on the beacon tower
wasn't lit by the Governor.
It was Fan Yun.
It was her?
It's not surprising.
It is something she would do.
Master,
can we talk to the Governor tonight
about
impeaching Fan Yun?
Ask for a leave.
You are not going to his mansion?
By order of the Governor!
All Masters must immediately
mobilize their forces
to search for sweet wormwood
in their cities and send it to Yong City.
Yes.
What about the rest of you?
Are you going to disobey the order?
Your Excellency.
I heard that Lady Fan Yun
lit the beacon tower without permission.
I'd like to ask
if she will be held accountable for it.
Your Excellency.
Lady Fan Yun hasn't shown up yet.
I wonder
if she is trying to escape punishment.
Lighting the beacon tower
was my doing.
It has nothing to do with His Excellency.
Your Excellency,
I can resign,
but not now.
I know
that all the ministers
may have some objections
to women becoming officials.
But since I have become a female official,
I want to take this responsibility
seriously.
Your Excellency,
I request
that before the plague in Yong City
is controlled,
you allow me
to make amends for my mistakes
and continue to do good deeds
for the people.
Make amends for your mistakes
and do good deeds for the people?
I'm afraid
you won't be able to make amends,
and your crime will be aggravated.
Your Excellency.
Enough.
I already know about this.
Lord Jiang has reported to me
and recommended Lady Fan Yun.
The top priority now
is to control the plague in Yong City.
I promise you
that when the plague subsides
and Lady Fan Yun returns from Yong City,
this matter
will definitely be handled
according to the law.
Your Excellency.
Although we really want
to accomplish this task,
we
are not capable enough.
What's the difficulty?
The Nine Cities is so big.
Collecting so much sweet wormwood
in such a short time—
aren't you making it too difficult for us?
Your Excellency,
you once said
you wouldn't
rely on us for this matter.
But now you're assigning us the task.
Isn't...
Isn't this going back on your word?
Yong City is in trouble now.
The Nine Cities being united
is what we should do.
I'm afraid I can't do this.
Please withdraw your order,
Your Excellency.
You...
Your Excellency, Your Excellency.
Your Excellency,
Lord Zheng has submitted a memorial.
Read it.
Lord Zheng has gathered
all the sweet wormwood
in Jing City and sent it to Ling'an
to make a modest contribution.
He hopes to alleviate the suffering
of the people in Yong City
and relieve your worries.
Now,
do you have any other objections?
Well...
Ji City
will follow Your Excellency's order.
Wang City
We will fulfill our mission.
Cover it tightly.
Don't let it fall out.
Miss Wei.
What do you mean?
It's for you to take with you on the road.
Everyone has one.
But yours is the most special.
I can see that.
Here.
Thank you, Miss.
But Miss Wei,
Yong City has always been dry
with little rain,
especially at this time of year.
We'd better simplify our belongings
and march fast.
I specially wove it
using Lanshan vines from Gao City.
It's very light.
Try it if you don't believe me.
I...
Being on the road
is not like being at home.
Be prepared for anything, just in case.
I don't know what you might run into,
so I prepared this for you.
♪ Wind sheds rain like tears ♪
♪ Over the whole town ♪
♪ At the second our gazes meet ♪
♪ Past memories roar one louder beat ♪
♪ Perhaps hearts long to seek ♪
♪ Etch within our fingertips ♪
♪ Hear crisp footsteps echo clear ♪
♪ Strike out
on a fearless dream's frontier ♪
Why are you ignoring me?
♪ Though fleeting years rush
without delay ♪
♪ A wisp of softness
tints your brow each day ♪
The strap is too tight.
I'll loosen it for you.
♪ Walk side by side with moon and sun ♪
♪ When all is said and all is done ♪
♪ We'll ride upstream and downs ♪
♪ When deep love dwells within our eyes ♪
Thank you.
♪ Our burning longing never dies ♪
Well...
I'm leaving.
♪ Wander together through wind and frost ♪
Don't forget to miss me.
Set off immediately!
♪ Every dark night fades at last ♪
♪ When fate resides within our sight ♪
♪ Gazing toward each other's
distant light ♪
♪ Why would heaven and earth
seek to be with you to save us ♪
♪ Don't let the sun down ♪
[Ling'an City]
The Governor is leaving the city
for Yong City
to eliminate the epidemic!
The Governor is leaving the city
for Yong City
to eliminate the epidemic!
Your Excellency.
Do we have to be so flashy
leaving the city this time?
Why do we have to make such a big fuss?
Once we leave Ling'an City,
there might be dangerous forces
staring at us.
Masters from all over the land
have a duty to protect the Governor.
So at a time like this,
the bigger the fuss we make,
the safer we will be.
Gao Ran!
Once we pass the Ling'an checkpoint,
move forward at full speed.
Yes.
Boss.
You're back?
Are you alright?
We're fine.
These bandits
were just after the sweet wormwood
we were escorting.
They didn't want to fight us
for real at all.
Did you get a clear look at their faces?
It was too dark.
I didn't see them clearly.
It's just that...
Go ahead.
It's just that their moves
were a bit like yours.
In other words,
they really work for the Zheng family.
So Miss Fan Yun's trip this time
is likely to be fraught with danger.