You don't have to talk.
Just listen to my heartbeat.
Will you let me set the rhythm
for us tonight?
MOM
Yes, Mom?
What? You're outside the house right now?
Why didn't you call me first?
What if I wasn't home?
It doesn't matter, Runch.
If you weren't home,
I'd just give this to the maid.
Don't worry.
I wasn't going to talk to your wife.
I'd never want to anyway.
Mom.
Where is she, though?
It's her day off. She's still sleeping.
If you hadn't come,
I'd still be sleeping too.
Since when did you start sleeping in?
Want to join us for breakfast, Mom?
I'm good. I already ate with your dad.
Do you want to eat now?
I'll reheat it for you.
-Just a second.
-It's okay, Mom.
What?
-I can do it myself.
-It's okay, honey.
It's your day off.
You should sit back and relax.
I'll handle it for you.
Who cares if your wife
doesn't take care of you? I can do it too.
Neen has a job too, Mom.
And it's not her duty
to handle these things anyway.
I don't expect her to do it alone.
What's her job?
Does she work as hard as my daughter?
Has that brat ever accomplished anything?
She's always dressed up all nice,
and just saunters around.
When will you stop criticizing her, Mom?
Ugh, Runch.
You're always blindly defending your wife!
Just admit you made a bad decision
and ended up with a bad wife!
How am I a bad wife?
Your daughter really loves me though, Mom.
Anyway,
what are you doing in my house this early?
Is that how sophisticated people
greet others?
And look at your clothes.
You look like a tramp.
Don't you have anything better to wear?
Or is this how rich kids like to dress?
Actually, I don't like
wearing these clothes.
But Runch…
Runch likes it.
She says they're easy to take off.
Yuck. Gross! Disgusting!
Enough, Mom.
And you slept in until late morning.
If I hadn't come today,
my daughter wouldn't get to eat.
Ugh. Mom, your daughter
can find her own food.
She finds it for me too.
Are you disabled?
Why do you have to rely on her?
I'm not disabled, Mom.
What I am is Runch's little cutie pie.
My goodness!
Are you that submissive
to this brat, Runch?
She's even more submissive to me
than you think, Mom.
She does everything I tell her.
Runch loves following
her wife's orders. Right?
-I can't take any more of this!
-Enough!
Mom, go home already!
Runch!
Did you just tell me to leave?!
That's not it.
But you really should go home.
Come on. I'll walk you.
Come on.
-Mom.
-You crazy brat!
Mom!
Come on, Runch!
Mom.
What's the matter with you, Runch?
Why'd you tell me to leave?
Mom,
that's enough.
This is exactly why
I told you to tell me before you come.
This is your house too,
so why do I need to tell you?
Why do I need permission?
It's not my house.
Rin's parents bought it
for our marriage. Don't forget that.
And that's why she has such a nerve.
Enough, Mom!
This is why I didn't want you to come.
Well, your wife started it!
No. Stop it, Mom. She didn't start it.
-Runch!
-Mom.
Please go home.
-Please. Please?
-Runch!
Fine. I'll go home for now.
Just because you asked.
Neen.
Let's go upstairs,
get changed, and then eat.
I don't want to.
-Aren't you hungry?
-Leave me alone.
And this house isn't yours alone.
Please ask me before you welcome a guest.
Stop letting that old loudmouth
come in and insult me!
It's happened too many times.
Neen.
-That's my mom you're talking about.
-So?
So she can insult me
but I can't do it to her?
Or do you only allow me to be insulted?
I'm sorry. Really.
That's just how my mom is.
She doesn't listen
when I tell her or warn her.
So you're telling me, warning me,
and disciplining me instead?
Aren't you tired, Neen?
You always fight with my mom
every time you meet.
Of course I am.
I'm tired of both you and her.
But you know what? She's only this way
because you're her enabler.
I hope you know that.
When your mom
does bad things, acts rudely,
or does what normal people wouldn't do,
please discipline her.
Because if you don't, I'll do it myself.
Fighting all the time can take a toll
on our mental health.
I can't stand this kind of environment.
Well, that old loudmouth
is always insulting me.
Your mom's like a crazy dog
who bites everyone,
yet you expect to have a peaceful life?
Neen!
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to yell at you.
You're angry because I insulted your mom,
but do you ever care when she insults me?
You're just so good at everything.
Everyone admires you.
You have a great career,
and you're good at your job.
You seem so great to everyone.
But you know what? As your wife
who's in this relationship with you,
I think you're the worst!
I regret it. I regret nothing more
than deciding to marry you.
If I could turn back time,
I never would've married you.
I'm sorry.
You once told me you wanted a divorce.
I want one too.
But for now, while we're still married,
can you be a good wife for me?
At least during this extra time
that my family asked for,
please pretend we still love each other.
Can you let me
break your mom's heart
just once in my lifetime?
At least just for a little longer.
Neen.
Are you sure about getting divorced?
Yes. We've talked about it.
I never expected to hear
you both say it so easily.
You're adults now.
You've matured.
But, oh well.
I trust that you've thought it over.
There's just one thing
I want to ask of you.
It's very important.
Don't tell anyone
you're getting divorced yet.
Not even your own family, Runch.
I want no one other than the people here
to know about this.
Another one of Iperis' restaurants
is about to open in four months.
The press will be present,
and so will our partners.
There'll be a big event
for our company and our family.
And we need to use
the public image of a stable marriage
for news stories about the event.
I want just four months.
Can you do that for me?
Sure.
Thank you.
I know it's hard.
But I promise you.
After four months,
no matter what your decision is,
I won't stop you anymore.
Natee.
Looks like
I'll have to divorce Neen for real.
Huh? Divorce?
Are you being serious?
This is a big deal, you know.
You two really love each other, though.
What happened?
Every time my mom and Neen meet,
it feels like I have to watch
two people I love
hurt each other repeatedly.
I want to defend both of them.
But in the end,
I could never do anything.
I could never defend either of them.
Neen's really tired, Natee.
She's already tired from work,
and my mom and I tire her even more.
She has to try to act tough
when she's actually
a really sensitive person.
Every time I see my mom insult Neen,
she's got that childlike look in her eyes,
like a child
who feels hurt and unaccepted.
I really love Neen, Natee.
I love her so much
that I don't think
I can ever love anyone as much.
But the more I love her,
the more I know
that it's because of me
that she has to suffer because of my mom.
I didn't ask for a divorce
because I fell out of love, Natee.
It was because…
I really love Neen,
so much
that I'd walk away
from this relationship myself.
This way, I won't hurt her anymore.
Why are you back so soon, honey?
Runch told me to leave
because of that brat.
Did you have a fight with Neen again?
How many times
have I told you not to do that?
If you keep this up
and Runch can't take it anymore,
just don't say I didn't warn you.
She may not speak a lot,
but you'd better watch out.
One day she'll run out of patience.
Runch has been aggressive
since they got married.
This is exactly why
I didn't want her to marry that brat!
I don't see how Neen is that bad at all.
And you too, Pong.
Why do you love
your daughter-in-law so much?
And don't you threaten me.
If Runch ever feels unhappy with me,
I'm still her mom.
You sure seem confident.
I think when people
have a family of their own,
they'll always prioritize their family.
That's why I didn't want her
to get married.
You want her to marry
someone you like, don't you?
At least then I can rest a little easy
if she marries someone
who gets along with me.
You always made sarcastic
and snide remarks
even when they were just dating,
just because you didn't like her,
and you didn't get your way.
Now that she's fed up
and starts retaliating,
you're saying she's the bad guy?
When was I ever being sarcastic?
Everything I said is true.
Neen's just a rich kid who's incompetent.
She'll only give Runch a hard time.
And she shows way too much skin.
How unladylike!
She's a clubber, and she's too bougie.
She's not ladylike at all!
I don't care how rich she is.
She's not fit to be Runch's partner.
She doesn't support Runch
in any way! Damn it!
My mom called
and invited us over for dinner.
Well, she does it every week.
But if you don't want to go,
then don't. I'll go alone.
I never said I didn't want to go.
My parents understand.
They know we're about to get divorced.
You don't have to pretend
you still love me
like you do in front of your family.
We aren't divorced yet,
so can't I have dinner
with my parents-in-law?
Suit yourself.
You're always in denial and unforgiving.
That's why she asked for a divorce.
Why are you always rubbing it in?
Look, wouldn't dialing it back
be better for your relationship?
You know what I've had to go through,
yet you two always side with her.
How many times has her mom insulted me?
She'd even insult
my parents and my brother,
yet Runch never defended me!
Hey. Runch is the mediator.
It must be tough for her.
But is it tough just for her?
Even my family
has never treated me that way.
They raised me so well
just for that old hag to tell me off!
It's tough for me too!
Well, look at her go. She just called
the mother of her dear wife an "old hag."
She's my ex-wife. Please get it right.
You aren't divorced yet.
We will be. Just you wait.
Try this, Runch.
I cooked today, you know!
-Thank you, Mom.
-Of course.
-You too. Dig in.
-Thank you.
Don't be shy.
Help yourself, Runch.
You look like you've lost a lot of weight.
You know that, right?
Yeah. Are you exhausted, honey?
Has work been rough?
Or are you not getting enough rest?
If you're feeling tired or burned out,
and you want to rest, you can tell me.
You know this is like
your second home, right?
Yes, Mom.
Runch,
no matter what happens,
I'll still think of you
as my second daughter.
I really love you
like you're my own daughter.
Thank you.
Come on. Dig in.
-I've got the sour curry too.
-Today's a good day.
I'd like to treat my sister-in-law
to a drink.
Sure.
But just a tiny bit, please.
Nai.
You're a strong woman.
I bet you aren't a lightweight.
Sure. But just a tiny bit, please.
A tiny bit's not enough.
You've got to go all out.
Nai, can you not?
It's okay.
Cheers.
Not too rough.
Two drinks and she's out cold?
You know she's a lightweight,
yet you tried to get her drunk.
Well, it can't be helped.
She asked my sister for a divorce.
She made my sister sad,
so that's what she gets.
You're acting like a child.
She hurt you so bad,
yet you still care about her?
On the day of the divorce,
will you really be able to take it?
That's my question.
You know you're a lightweight.
Why'd you drink so much?
Well, Nai asked me to drink with him.
It would've been rude for me to refuse.
That's what you're worried about?
Why are you smiling?
I'm happy to see that you care about me.
You got me all wrong.
This isn't me caring about you.
I'm scolding you.
If you scold me, I'll be happy too,
because it shows
that you care.
You can go home without me.
I'll call a driver myself.
What are you calling one for?
We're going home together.
Come on.
Just leave your car here.
I'll have my dad's driver
drive it to our house tomorrow, okay?
-Come on.
-You are just the sweetest, Neen.
We're in your room now.
Don't hug me.
We're not the same anymore.
Why not? I remember
you used to like it when I did this.
But right now, we're not…
Right now, we're not the same anymore.
Don't do this again.
Thank you.
What's wrong with it?
What's wrong with the car?
I can't start it. The battery's dead.
I have a meeting today too.
If you can't start it,
why don't you get in my car?
I'll drive you.
Let me go grab a coffee really quick.
Do you need anything?
No.
You're just buying coffee.
What's with all that chit-chat?
Honey!
What's taking you so long?
They had a couple of orders before mine.
What?
Why didn't you tell me?
You took so long I got bored.
This is unacceptable.
You have to make up for it.
Well, what do you want me to do?
Aw, honey. What you used to do, of course.
Come on, honey. Quick.
You are just the sweetest.
-There's my girl! Right?
-Your drink, Ms. Runch.
-Thank you--
-Whoa!
Thank you.
Let's go, honey.
Were you jealous?
I wasn't. I was annoyed, more like.
You seem so close. Do you buy from here
every day or something?
Yes. Every day.
Ugh. Did you want coffee
or did you want something else?
Well, coffee, of course.
There are so many other cafés.
Why'd it have to be this one?
Neen,
don't you remember?
This is our café.
Thanks for the ride.
I'll carry these upstairs for you.
You have a lot to carry.
Don't.
I insist. Don't oppose me.
-Ms. Neen! Hello.
-Hello.
-Hello, Ms. Runch
It's been a while. Where have you been?
I've been busy with work lately,
so I couldn't find the time to come.
That's a relief. And here I thought
you two were fighting.
It's just that you two
are the dream couple for me.
Heck, everyone in our office says
they want a relationship like yours!
I'll take care of your car for you, Neen.
I'll give you a ride home this evening.
Don't.
I can call a ride myself.
No way.
Don't forget, we're the "dream couple."
Don't disappoint everyone now.
See you this evening.
I tell you, if Runch hadn't married
the CEO's granddaughter,
she never would've gotten
to be our boss today.
You're right. Sometimes,
when she makes mistakes,
no one dares to reprimand her.
What kind of boss
has her team do her work for her?
And she's always quiet during meetings.
It's like she's being used as a prop
because it looks good for us
to have a female boss.
I wonder. Is she really that great,
or is it just because
her wife's an heir of Iperis' CEO?
I don't know.
But if I were her, I'd feel so insecure.
She got to marry the CEO's granddaughter,
yet she's still just
an invisible boss to this day.
No one really respects her.
Yeah. Whenever she walks by,
everyone just keeps doing their work.
No one wants to talk to her.
I guess she can't get along with anyone.
She's probably someone
who knows they're incompetent.
That's why she acts calm and quiet
to hide her insecurity.
Hello, Boss.
Would you like a coffee?
Something's wrong
with your car's electrical system.
It'll take days to fix it.
I'll give you a ride until then.
Don't.
I'll ask my dad for a new car
so I don't have to bother you.
For you, it's no bother.
This isn't the way back home!
Let's have dinner first,
then we'll go home.
I ordered your favorite dish. Dig in.
Why are you doing this?
What do you mean?
No one's watching.
Why are you being nice to me?
I just wanted
to do things for you like before.
Like before?
You know nothing's the same as before.
What do you want?
Are you playing mind games with me?
Are you playing with my heart?
That's not what I think.
I just wanted to us to part
with good memories.
There's no need.
All the good memories were gone
when you asked me for a divorce.
So stop being nice
and acting as if you know what I want.
I don't want to be familiar
with having you by my side anymore.
You probably don't want to see my face.
I'm off to work now.
Don't forget to eat all of it. From Runch.
You sure know me well, Runch.
See that dress?
I have one that's blue,
but I don't have a pink one yet.
-You need to get the pink one too.
-Yeah!
-So pretty.
-It's 10% off too.
-See? It's that one right there.
-It's on sale!
-Yeah!
-That's great!
-How great.
-Want to check out that store?
-Yes.
-Isn't that Neen?
It's her! Ging,
isn't that your beautiful daughter-in-law?
I don't think so.
-Hello!
-Neen!
Hello, Mom. Hello, you two.
-Hello.
I'm so glad to meet you, Neen.
Did you get even prettier?
Thank you.
Right, Neen. Ging wants a designer scarf.
She really wants it,
but she said it's too expensive.
It costs 35,000 baht.
Why don't you buy her one?
Of course!
You don't have to.
How can I not?
You're Runch's important person.
Of course I have to take care of you
as best I can.
Please, go for it.
Neen, you're so kind.
She's everyone's dream daughter-in-law.
Why are you quiet?
She's so sweet, isn't she?
Here, Mom.
Don't thank me, Mom.
It was my pleasure to buy it for you.
Oh, and you two.
Today's a good day,
so I bought one for each of you too.
Are you sure, honey?
Of course I am. I'm very sure.
Neen! Thank you so much.
I promise to handle it
-very delicately.
-Yeah.
And are you all going anywhere else?
We're heading to dinner next.
Dinner, you say?
Mom, here's my card.
Please treat your friends to dinner.
Choose whichever restaurant you want.
It's my treat, so please don't hold back.
If you'll excuse me,
I have to go take care of something.
See you later.
-See you later.
Ging, you're so lucky
to have her as your daughter-in-law.
Wow!
I've always wanted it.
It's so pretty.
I'm so happy she bought it for us.
-Why'd you come to see me, Mom?
-Peeracha!
Get out here! Get out here, now!
What's wrong, Mom?
Why don't you ask your cheeky wife
what she did to me?
You did that in front of my friends.
That was so demeaning.
You acted as if I'm living off of you.
How was that my fault?
I just wanted to treat
an old lady to dinner
so she wouldn't starve to death.
You!
Mom, that's enough. Let's get outside.
Stay out of this!
-Mom, please get outside!
-Runch!
Did you just yell at me?
You yelled at me because of her?!
How annoying!
Mom!
Neen…
Mom.
Get out.
Go.
Runch.
Runch, I didn't mean it!
3 YEARS AGO
Your shirt's all dirty.
Do you want to get changed?
It's okay.
It's almost time to clock out,
and I don't have a spare shirt.
But if your white shirt gets wet,
it'll be too revealing.
If you don't mind, you can borrow mine.
I've never worn it before.
I don't want to bother you.
Please take my blouse.
You'll get sick in that wet shirt.
Let me go get it from my car.
Thank you.
I'll give it back as soon as I can.
Can I…
have your email address?
Email?
It's easier to call me on my number.
Can I have your phone?
Done.
My name is Neen. What's your name?
My name is Runch.
Do you work around here?
Yes. Pretty close.
Nice to meet you, Ms. Runch.
Does she think having connections
and a rich wife means
she can act all high-and-mighty here?
Be a man.
There are many more things we can do
to make it look like
we really love each other.
Then do it all.
You know Neen hates my guts.
But you hate her too, don't you?
Cut it out!
Subtitle translation by:
Ramil Natnitiwitaya