Aemie, stay here.
Stay low.
Huh?
Why?
Music hits better when
you're ducking down.
What's taking Zeke so long?!
I look like an idiot sitting here
listening to music by myself!
Zeke, why is there
so much blood?
Please, I don't know what to do.
Don't leave me, please!
Don't leave me!
So...
What about the third target?
You have to kill
her as well, Young.
You really love
your husband, huh?
Love him so much?
How do you know that?
Ouch!
I found that to be
the safest and most suitable way
to put a distance between
you and my husband.
I love him.
And I always will.
I think we need
to remove all of this trash.
Yuck!
Okay, listen.
I'll tell you the signs
that you're in love, okay?
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
This is the first sign.
When you get a strange feeling
whenever he gets close to you
or stands near you.
That means...
you're already in love.
Come on, let's eat.
Why are you stuttering, wife?
Is something wrong?
No, nothing.
I'm just hungry.
Come on.
Uh.
Hubby, so...
so Fiona is your girlfriend?
Hey.
Oh no, are you okay?
You used to choke
on coffee only.
Now, even on water?
Fiona was my girlfriend.
It's just...
when she came to
the hospital, she said...
she's still your girlfriend.
What, she was there?
Did she do anything to you?
Ugh.
No.
She was actually nice.
She even offered
to take care of you.
Did you let her?
Of course not.
Huh!
You bitch!
Second,
If you get annoyed
every time you see
another girl approaching
or talking to him...
that's it!
Could that really be it?
Am I really in love with Zeke?
Woman!
Hurry up!
Why are you in such a rush?
It's only 6 a.m.
He's just like cuz.
Wait a second, Dong.
Go downstairs first.
I'll just get dressed.
Okay, okay.
What happened to him?
Why is he suddenly blushing?
Oh no.
Do I need to take him
back to the hospital?
What if something
happens to him again?
Zeke!
Zeke, wait.
Help!
Please, help!
What's the matter?
You don't want a ride?
You want to walk?
Well...
what if what happened
last time happens again?
I cannot promise you
it won't happen again.
But I can promise you...
that I will protect
you the best I can.
Third...
you feel like
you're always safe
whenever you're with him.
It's like—your whole world stops.
Like that.
Hey!
It's already 7:45!
Isn't our meeting at 8:00 a.m.?
Let's go.
Louie was wrong.
Liar.
Time didn't stop at all.
Hey!
Zeke, wait!
Sigh.
Exactly.
And then, there's this too.
Good morning,
Mr. and Mrs. Roswell.
Why are you still here?
Excuse me, Mr. Roswell?
I don't want to see your
fucking face anymore.
You cannot fire an executive
without any concrete evidence
on what you think I did.
Zeke.
The doctor said you're not
supposed to get stressed.
I'll handle this.
Leave it to me.
Evidence!
So it means,
there's a possibility
that you're guilty.
Okay.
We are going to give you
another chance to tell us the truth.
Were you the one who
stole the 100 million pesos?
I will not answer that!
This is harassment!
I agree with the CFO.
You cannot ask such questions
in front of the entire board.
That's...
unprofessional.
What the fuck is she doing here?
Let me remind all of you,
that you all work for
Roswell Corporation.
Roswell.
And my husband owns the company.
And by interfering
with his decisions,
you are doing the
company a great disservice.
You should be all
ashamed of yourselves.
My husband just
got out of surgery.
And as for you,
I am giving you a lifetime
suspension, Ms."Sagwa."
It's Sigua! You can't!
Yes, I can!
Because I am the CEO's wife
and I am giving you
a lifetime suspension.
It doesn't violate
anything in the bylaws.
That's my girl.
But that's the
same as firing me!
No, it's not.
You can't apply to
another company
while you're working here.
You're still required
to do your job as CFO
without bonuses,
salary, which means...
It's worse than firing you.
Why are you laughing?
Nobody's joking.
Alright, everyone.
Let's stop wasting time
and get on with the meeting.
Shall we?
This meeting is exclusively
for board members.
You're not needed here.
This meeting is
about the toy industry,
which I'm helping
your wife with, Ezekiel.
Oh, so she's actually
going to help me.
Oh, you don't know her.
No, I know her.
She's Fiona Stonehurst.
Such an idiot.
Why do you keep laughing?
You're starting to worry me.
Why?
Is there something
wrong with being happy?
No.
So there's nothing wrong.
Sorry to interrupt
your sweet moment.
But...
Shall we start?
Sure. Go ahead.
Sweet moments?
Why does it feel like...
like my heart is pounding?
Hey!
Oh no.
Why isn't it pink anymore?
And where are
all my Dollie dolls?
Hi, Aemie.
That's your desk over there.
Have a seat.
Hey, why is my chair like this?
It's like trip to Jerusalem.
Aemie, I threw
out all of your trash.
I wanted to make
it look a little more...
professional?
I dislike messy workplaces.
Don't you?
You're working here too?
Why? There are
plenty of empty offices.
Well, I thought it would
be nice if we could all
work together.
In one space.
So I can make sure
you're doing things right.
After all,
I am your company's
supplier and partner
for your new venture
into the toy industry.
You'll be dead
soon, Aemie Roswell.
Yaji.
Who is this Yaji person?
How does he know
I'm going to die?
Is he a fortune teller?
Oh no, what if
he's part of a cult?
So creepy.
So...
uhm.
Is Ezekiel coming?
I don't know.
You should've asked him, not me.
Bitch?
He's your husband.
You should know.
What the fuck happened here?
And what the hell
are you doing here?
Excuse me?
The last time I was
here, everything was pink.
And it was filled with dolls.
Yeah.
Zeke.
Fiona did it.
She changed the office.
Look, Ezekiel.
I'm sorry, but...
you don't have a choice.
I'm your partner now.
In fact, I supply the
toys to your company.
I did not agree to that.
In fact, I don't like you
working with my wife.
Well, your wife doesn't seem to
have a problem working with me.
Right?
Aemie?
See, and in fact,
I'm pretty sure I
did you guys a favor.
I mean, look at this place.
I know you like things
executive-looking.
Stop acting like you
know what I want.
What I don't like is how you
changed what my wife did.
Let's go.
Wait, wait, wait.
Uhh, if you're heading home,
can I hitch a ride with you guys?
My car broke down.
- No.
- Sure.
I just feel bad for
Fiona, you know?
She already got
scolded, and then...
her car broke down too.
Besides.
Maybe her attitude is so bad
because nothing good
ever happens to her.
We should take her home.
Otherwise, she might end up
changing even more things in the office.
Fine.
Great.
Maybe you wanna get
some food on the way home?
Ezekiel?
Are you hungry?
Yeah.
Honestly, I'm starving.
- Wife,
- But I...
I'm asking you, are you hungry?
I'm not hungry, Dong.
Okay, let's go then.
Wait, but...
I said I'm starving.
The hell I care?
Hey. Zeke, Zeke.
Let's just hit the
drive-thru for Fiona
because she looks really hungry.
I am starving.
Wait.
This meeting is exclusively
for board members.
This meeting is about
the toy industry...
which I'm helping
your wife with, Ezekiel.
Wife.
Are you sure you're
okay working with Fiona?
Uhhm.
It's okay.
She's annoying because she
threw away some of my Dollie dolls.
But the book I read said,
to "be professional," so...
it's okay.
Okay, then.
Uhh.
Zeke.
Where did you go earlier before
you came back to the office?
Lamperouge and I just dealt
with some business matters.
How about you?
Hmm?
I saw your face earlier
when I entered the office.
You seemed to
be deep in thought.
Is something bothering you?
Ah.
That?
Nothing, I was just...
just thinking about something.
About?
Uhm...
Maybe I shouldn't
tell him about Yaji yet.
I don't even know who Yaji is.
Yaji is actually a cute name.
Ah, it's about, it's
about the Philippines.
I want to help the
Philippines prosper!
So boring.
If I were a customer,
I wouldn't buy these.
Uhh.
Well—
Well, you're not a customer.
Zeke, tell me if
these look boring.
The designs I picked are
supposed to look mysterious.
Like Zeke.
You know you love someone
when you often compare them
or relate them to different things.
No.
Erase, erase.
They're interesting.
Hmm?
Ezekiel.
I think you should take a
look at these for consideration.
Oh no!
Those dolls look like they're
going to a Halloween party.
You know what?
I prefer my wife's choice.
Yay!
Huh?
What is this Yaji thing?
Why...
why does he keep sending
me daily horoscopes?
Let me reply.
Mr. Yaji.
Or, I don't know if
you're a miss?
Could you...
feng shui my and Zeke's house?
And my mom's house too.
So we can avoid...
bad luck.
Thank you.
Ahh!
P.S.
Thank you for...
sending my...
daily horoscope for free.
Send.
Yes!
Ezekiel?
You gonna go for lunch?
I'll join you.
You can't.
My wife and I have a date.
We're going to have
lunch at her mother's place.
Huh?
Yay!
I miss Mommy!
Let's go?
Come on.
Enjoy.
Ah, wait a second.
Here, here's the juice.
Here.
Thank you.
Mommy!
Baby Ae!
Zeke!
Glad you stopped by again.
Good afternoon, ma'am.
Mommy, you have
so many customers.
Dodong and I will help you sell.
Huh?
Really?
Is that okay?
Of course!
What?
Mm?
Wait.
You'll handle the grill,
and I'll take the orders.
You don't want to?
Okay, fine.
You take the orders,
and I'll do the grilling.
Hmm?
Fine, I'll do it.
Come on, go take the orders
so we can sell out all your...
barbecue.
Hurry.
Go on.
So you do want to.
Oh no, not like that.
Like this.
There.
Okay, guys!
I have good news for all of you.
Our barbecue is now
only 20 pesos per stick.
And we have a special promo.
For only 40 pesos,
it's buy one, get one.
My daughter is really amazing.
She's so good.
Gosh, this girl is ridiculous.
Hey, sir, you want to avail?
How many?
Three?
There, make it five.
She got that from me.
Here you go, sir.
Thank you!
Hi, Aemie!
Hey, Grace!
Feels like I haven't
seen you in forever.
I've been busy with school.
The last time we saw
each other, you were still single.
Yiee.
I'd like five barbecue
sticks, please.
Oh, okay.
Five barbecue sticks.
Dong, she wants
five barbecue sticks.
Zeke, three betamax.
Dong, five chicken intestines.
Hey, Dong, four more betamax.
Hey, Dong, six
more barbecue sticks.
You'll know you're definitely
in love with him
if, for you,
he's the most handsome man ever.
What are you staring at?
Huh?
Nothing, I was just
checking if you're getting tired.
Don't get ahead of yourself.
You might start
thinking that I'm thinking
you're handsome even
when you're all sweaty.
Okay.
Why are you smiling?
Well, it's because...
I love seeing my
special someone smile.
Is this his special someone?
How can a barbecue smile?
Oh!
Oh, it's your turn.
You first.
Hey, miss!
My order.
Wait, sis.
Hold on.
Why so mad?
Here, sis.
I hope your power gets cut off.
What? But we're paying our bills.
Over.
Why so angry?
Hey.
Momo, do you see what I see?
Of course, I'm not blind.
Not blind?
But I've been standing right
in front of you this whole time.
And you still don't
see my worth.
Hey, why are you here?
Shouldn't you be at the office?
Exactly.
Oh, Cuz, we're on a date.
Right, Dong?
Yeah.
Date?
Oh, we're so in sync, Momo.
Looks like we're
really soulmates.
Soulmate, your face!
- Go sit far away.
- There goes Momo again.
- Charcoal flavored.
- Wow, seriously?
Wife, are you
awake? I feel like...
you're hiding something from me.
Oh no! You know about
the last will and testament?
Yes. But not that.
I was beginning to think
you were getting threats...
Threats? Maybe horoscopes.
I don't have any enemies.
Okay, I guess I was
afraid for no reason.
So Dodong is scared of threats.
What if I scare Dodong now?
But I'm already so comfortable in my bed.
Oh, I know.
I'll just text him the threats.
This is a threat. I can
see you Ezekiel Roswell.
You should be afraid now! RAWR!
P.S.
This is not Aemie.
I hope he gets scared.
Oh no.
He didn't even get scared.
Unfair.
Why weren't you scared, Zeke?
Why would I?
I thought you were
afraid of threats?
Insane!
So now I'm insane?
Who's this?
Dong thinks he's a smartass!
You think you can scare me?
Nope!
Suit yourself.
I'm getting sleepy.
Wife.
Dong.
Have you already met
with the staff about lunch?
Oh, not yet, but it's
scheduled for next week.
Fiona and I just
need to meet first.
Oh, there she is.
Hi, Fiona.
- Hi.
- Shall we start?
I just need to speak
to Ezekiel first.
Okay.
Speak.
In private.
I hope.
Now she's asking for privacy.
It's not like Dong's
office is a public place.
I should call Cai.
Oh my gosh.
Fine.
Hi, Cai!
Hi, Aemie!
You called?
Nothing.
I just missed you.
You weren't there when
we went to the beach.
We had so much fun.
Sorry, I've been kinda busy lately.
I'm looking for something.
Oh, really?
What are you looking for?
Want me to help?
Ah, no need.
Ah, I can handle it.
Oh, by the way, how's work?
I heard you're entering
the toy industry.
Oh, yeah.
We're launching
within the month.
You should come.
- Huh?
- Yeah, of course.
I'll be there with my dad.
You know my dad.
If it's business,
he's always present.
Alright, I need to go to
class, Aemie girl.
Okay.
Alright, bye-bye. Take care.
Love, love.
Exciting.
I wonder what
Mr. Ferrer looks like.
Do you think he's handsome?
Maybe I should bring Mommy.
So she can have a love team.
Because as far as I
know, Cai's dad is single.
Right.
Ms. Aemie, this is urgent.
Mr. Roswell needs
to sign this ASAP.
Okay, I'll handle it.
Thank you.
What is it this time, Kate?
We need to talk about us.
There's no us.
I swear, I--
I never wanted to hurt you.
Then why did you?
Because...
Because someone told me to.
Actually, no.
Someone actually
threatened me to hurt you.
Look, I--
I don't know who they are, but
they held me at gunpoint
and they told me that
I need to befriend you,
make you fall in love with me,
and then...
take money from you and...
and break your heart.
I swear, Ezekiel. I was...
I was so afraid.
I didn't know what to do and...
that's why I broke up with you.
Even though I really,
really didn't want to.
Sorry.
So what?
If you think I will feel sympathy
for you because of that,
think again.
Zeke.
Wait, wait.
Please.
I love you and I swear,
I never intended to hurt you.
You have to believe me.
Get the fuck out of my life.
Do you really love Aemie?
More than me?
Are you a fool?
Stop comparing
yourself to my wife.
I love her.
You are nothing.
You love her?
Hmm.
Then maybe she should
know you're a mafia boss.
What will she think?
You think she's gonna accept it?
I doubt it.
Because no one will
accept the real Ezekiel.
Only I will love--
Say a fucking
word and I'll kill you.
Okay.
I won't say a word.
But only if you do
something for me.
I don't take orders from anyone.
You don't have a choice, Ezekiel.
Zeke?
Shit.
Wife.
Sorry for interrupting.
Wife, let me explain.
Let me explain.
Just let me go.
Please stay.
Wife.
Please.
Just let me go!
Zeke?
Shit.
I'm so confused, guys.
What is this feeling?
Why--
Why does this hurt?
What's wrong with me?
Why am I getting angry?
I feel like...
I want to hurt someone.
Am I a bad person?
Ouch!
Ezekiel is mine.
Stupid girl.
Are you really challenging me?
Gosh.
What are you laughing at?
You're just such a stupid girl.
Take a look at this.
The resemblance is...
pretty close.
Are you sure?
Cause...
I'm gonna buy it if ever.
Hello?
Oh no! Over the phone?
No, thanks. Let's do it
tomorrow. It's already late.
Hey, Moo!
You need to come over to
our house right now.
Because I don't have a map
of your house, I might get lost.
I'll send you the address.
Come on.
Let's eat.
I'm not hungry.
And I need to leave too.
You're staying here.
Why won't you give me
the right to do what I want?
Wife, please believe me.
I love you.
And...
Who are you talking to?
Fuck!
I need to fix this.
Why, Zeke?
You seem awfully happy with me.
That's gonna cost you.
I wanna ask you something.
What is it?
Why am I so emotional?
Just stab me with
this remote already!
Could it be...
that I'm pregnant?!