(Respect copyright)
ظآزMemories hold you back
from fulfilling your dreamsظآز
ظآزOnly by moving forward
can you find reunionظآز
ظآزEndings only mark new routesظآز
ظآزIt's all part of the sceneryظآز
ظآزTo the horizon's callظآز
ظآزYour journey hasn't startedظآز
ظآزTowards mountains,
chase the stars brightظآز
ظآزLet time embrace you
and wash away the pastظآز
ظآزPut every twist behind youظآز
ظآزDrift leisurely through timeظآز
ظآزMake headway against the windظآز
ظآزLet mountains bow to your paceظآز
ظآزRush towards a life without regretظآز
ظآزLet your nature burst freeظآز
=The First Jasmine=
=Episode 23=
What is this?
Her Highness discovered this item
while organizing His Highness's belongings.
(To Mo Jingli at Lishan Academy)
(Prince Ding's Mansion)
- Your Highness.
- Where's the Princess Consort?
She's in her chambers, Your Highness.
Okay.
Your Highness,
I noticed a strange matter.
What is it?
Now, the first thing you do upon returning
to the mansion is go find Her Highness.
Is this strange?
Your Highness, the person
over there seems to be Lady Su.
Been away so long, I forgot that
Dachu nights are damp and cold.
So I caught a cold carelessly.
I remember when I visited
the mansion as a child,
there was a twin-trunked tree here.
Why is there only one trunk
remaining now?
No idea. Perhaps it withered and died.
After all,
nothing lasts forever.
Last night, I happened upon Ms. Wen.
Coming here rashly
was really not my intention.
Actually, given my current status,
I really shouldn't meet you again.
I saw Princess Consort yesterday.
She is indeed elegant and steady.
I heard she hails from Lishan Mountain.
Must be extraordinary.
You have suffered a lot over the years,
having a tough time.
Now, seeing you're doing well
and having a happy marriage
with Princess Consort,
I feel very relieved.
You serve Princess Lingyun.
Can you be absent all night like this?
Thank you for your concern.
Ms. Wen has already sent word
to the posthouse,
saying I happened to run into
old acquaintances and took some days off.
I... I've been out too long.
Ms. Wen must be looking for me.
Your Highness, I shall take my leave.
(To Mo Jingli at Lishan Academy)
Li, how was your day?
I checked on the shop. All is well.
Your Highnesses, it is time to dine.
Let's go eat.
(Prison)
Now you're at this state,
yet you still plan to hold on?
This is nothing but a frame-up!
The Cangbei rebels want to sow discord
between the Dachu court and its ministers!
It's okay. You will talk one day.
Prince Ding! This is a frame-up!
I demand to see Marquis Muyang!
(Marquis Muyang's Mansion)
That day, it all started suddenly.
We had to deploy our agents
within the palace to surround him.
But I never expected
Prince Ding's legs had healed.
It's my fault.
Enough!
The die is cast.
What's the point of saying all this?
I am not blaming you.
Mo Xiuyao is extremely cunning.
Even I was deceived by him,
let alone you.
But the current situation is perilous.
Zhang Hengyuan is not tough.
He won't hold out long
under Mo Xiuyao's interrogation.
If he talks, we are all doomed.
What do you expect me to do?
Infiltrate the Jingzhao Prefecture prison
and silence him.
It is heavily guarded. I'm afraid...
It's the only way.
Rest assured.
I've already
arranged everything for you.
Once it is done,
you'll depart immediately
to Yunchuan to lie low.
I have already arranged a new identity,
manors, lands, and assets for you.
Once everything's passed,
I shall bring you back as my adopted son
to the capital openly and honorably.
Adopted son?
Yes.
All these years,
though I never voiced it,
I've been thinking of you in my mind.
You are my own son,
connected by bloodline.
How could I bear
to see you live far away alone,
without returning to your clan?
I swear,
when you return from Yunchuan,
you won't do those
dangerous tasks again.
But given the current situation,
I can trust no one but you.
Rest assured, Marquis Muyang.
I will kill Zhang Hengyuan.
Do you still address me
as Marquis Muyang?
Be cautious.
I'm waiting for your return.
Yes.
Zhao Ting.
Marquis Muyang.
Follow him.
If any mistake occurs, spare no one.
Yes.
Father.
What truly happened
at the palace that day?
Does it have anything to do with us?
Did Zhang Hengyuan get arrested
because of his corruption?
And you were left behind.
Did the Emperor and Empress Dowager
give you a hard time?
Alright, stop asking questions.
You sent Qin Cang to silence
someone. I can do that too.
Want me to...
Enough nonsense!
Don't get your hands dirty
with bloodshed.
Why?
No why. I said no, so it's no.
You just said to spare no one.
Do you mean to kill Qin Cang as well?
Father.
He is your son.
Remember, you are my only son.
(Jingzhao Prefecture)
Fire! Hurry! Fire!
Fire!
Attention! Fire!
Hurry! Go put out the fire!
You lot, go fetch water!
Fire! Hurry!
Qin Cang, you're here to rescue me
on Marquis Muyang's orders, right?
Come on, open the cell now! Let me out!
Come on!
Wait, you're not here to rescue me.
Marquis Muyang sent you to silence me.
I didn't say anything.
Marquis Muyang, why?
Who's there?
Help! Murder!
He is over there! Capture him!
Who's there?
Marquis Muyang sent me to help you.
How did it go?
You killed Zhang Hengyuan?
Qin Cang!
He's here to kill you. Run!
Qin Cang.
Qin Cang!
They couldn't have gone far.
They must be nearby.
Spread out and search.
That way.
Check inside.
(Marquis Muyang's Mansion)
Marquis Muyang, Zhang Hengyuan is dead.
Qin Cang was exposed,
so I've dealt with...
You summoned me early this morning.
You must've anticipated
that Marquis Muyang
would be coming today
to seek your forgiveness again.
Over these years, every time
he messes up, he puts on the same show.
I am weary.
The one who died in Jingzhao Prefecture
last night was truly his own son?
Even tigers don't eat their own young.
Marquis Muyang is beyond redemption.
What benefits could he obtain
from doing this?
I taught you before.
Attack the enemy, but watch yourself.
Marquis Muyang never grasps it.
Look at you. You're the same.
Well, you've never let me win once.
Marquis Muyang.
Let me announce it first.
Marquis Muyang!
It is just as you anticipated.
All of you, withdraw.
Marquis Muyang,
let me announce it first.
Marquis Muyang...
Your Majesty, I'm here
to seek your forgiveness.
Marquis Muyang, why seek my forgiveness?
What happened at Jingzhao Prefecture
last night was my doing.
You're so eager to silence Zhang Hengyuan,
even asking your own son to do this.
It seems the secrets Zhang Hengyuan knew
were potent enough
to shake your foundations.
Is his collusion with Cangbei
related to you?
Absolutely not.
Everything I have done is for you.
Marquis Muyang, mind your words.
Zhang Hengyuan and Lu Changfu
followed me for many years.
You know well how many
tasks they handled for me.
If I weren't afraid that Zhang Hengyuan
might blab nonsense in prison,
bringing up the past deeds
that would damage your reputation,
I would never have resorted
to such an extreme measure.
Over these years, for you and the nation,
I've made countless enemies
and few to trust.
Now, villains are taking them out.
Until last night, even my own son
could not escape.
In that case, Marquis Muyang,
accept our condolences.
Let bygones be bygones.
Bygones?
Can they be?
You may have forgotten that
Qin Cang's original surname was Zhou.
He was called Zhou Lang.
His birth mother was the daughter
of an Eastern Palace attendant.
I was afraid it would worry you,
so I hid his true origins
for many years.
Because I've always seen you
as the real sovereign.
I want to serve you with everything I have.
So I married the Kang woman.
Shut up!
What's the point of
your telling me all this now?
If you truly care for that child,
why did you send him
to do those shady things for you?
And why did you send
assassins to silence him?
Eight years have passed. Prince Ding
has grown more composed,
yet you grow increasingly arrogant,
blinded by desires and ambitions.
How foolish!
I am foolish?
I have spared no effort
and devoted my all.
Everything I've done is for you,
and Dachu, isn't it?
The wise mend their deficiencies.
The foolish offer others
their weaknesses.
Time has changed.
Marquis Muyang, you should
learn to move with the times.
Your Majesty dwells high above,
holding up the heavens.
Naturally, your hands remain spotless.
But what about my hands?
My hands are stained with filth,
marked with blood,
and burdened
by all those deeds from the past.
And now, you expect a mere
"let bygones be bygones"
to wipe it all away?
Marquis Muyang, never forget that
every step you took
was a calculated move.
You reached out your hand
not out of loyalty,
but because you saw the 'price tag'
and thought it was worth it.
Now, there's no need for you
to play a loyal man before me.
(Linjiao Courtyard)
You are such a busy soul,
always rejecting invitations.
What brought you here
into my quiet courtyard today?
An old friend returned from Lingnan
and brought me this box of Tuoluo cakes.
I heard you hail from Lingnan.
I thought you might crave this taste.
So I brought them to you,
hoping to bring you some pleasure.
How thoughtful.
Indeed, it stirs my homesickness.
You seem troubled today.
What do you think of Marquis Muyang?
Since you ask,
I will speak frankly then.
Marquis Muyang possesses
only an arrogant demeanor,
yet lacks true talent.
Stubbornness leads to betrayal.
Narrow-mindedness
brings one to a dead end.
He is nothing but rotting bones
in a tomb, bound for a swift end.
"Rotting bones in a tomb."
The most intricate webs of deceit
are entirely transparent
to your eyes, clear as water.
No wonder the Empress Dowager
favors you so.
Turns out I'm the idiot here,
still clinging to the ghost of the past.
Surely that is not the case,
Your Highness.
I am merely an outsider.
I said that only by observing
the game as an outsider.
Forgive any offense, Your Highness.
The Su family isn't
completely wiped out.
Her eldest brother, Su Huaizhong,
now trades silk in Huaizhou,
specializing in fine silk
from Song and Bo prefectures.
They say this year, he's taken
orders from a Persian caravan.
And her younger sister, Su Zuichan,
married a ninth-rank clerk
from Jingzhao Prefecture's
Bureau of Revenue,
who manages household registries
and land disputes in the west of the capital.
And her mom's dowry nanny, Ms. Wu,
is now a chef at Xiangyun Tower.
The Golden Thread Pastry
you praised last time is made by her.
Got it. Thank you, Senior Wei.
What are you doing?
Working.
You're rubbing that table raw.
Planning to stay forever, are you?
I'm not in your way.
As an assassin, you work here.
Where's your ambition?
None of your business.
Is Princess Ding here?
There.
Your Highness, something's
happened to Yusheng.
Princess Ding isn't back?
Not yet, Your Highness.
Any message?
N-No.
(To Mo Jingli at Lishan Academy)
Thank you, Your Highness.
I didn't expect you to come.
You're someone my senior favors.
If you're in trouble,
I won't stand idly by.
You are so kind.
No wonder you'd care
for someone like me.
He's my patron, and I'm his confidant.
Everyone here knows one rule.
In a place like this,
never take anything to heart.
Especially those impossible
and unreachable things.
Do you agree, Young Master?
You seem fine. I'll take my leave.
Take care.
If he comes to you again,
send word to me at Shende Shop.
Thank you, Your Highness.
What she said wasn't right.
What do you mean?
If you make up your mind,
you must go do it.
How can you know if it's possible
without giving it a try?
Your Highness.
Your Highness, we've finally found you.
Why are you here?
You haven't returned this late.
His Highness is so worried.
Everyone available
has been out to look for you.
Please come back with me.
Everyone, leave.
- Yes.
Say it.
What?
Where did you go?
I... went to fight.
Where? Why?
A brothel.
You? A brothel?
I went back as soon as I finished there.
Ye Li.
I really don't understand you.
You're always going somewhere
I can't place,
doing something
I can't quite figure out.
Do you even know who you are?
Do you know that a woman walking alone
at night could be dangerous?
Do you know how it feels waiting for you
at the mansion without any news?
You fought in a brothel?
With whom?
What if you encountered desperadoes?
What if an accident happened?
I didn't encounter desperadoes.
Ye Li!
I thought after all this time together,
you'd understand me.
I thought you felt the same about me.
But you...
Have you ever taken
our marriage seriously?
Perhaps we don't know
each other well enough.
We do.
What?
We know each other.
I know you've never given up
on yourself all these years.
I know you cannot bear
the injustice forced upon
Prince Ding's Mansion
and Heiyun Cavalry.
I know you seek to reopen the case
and destroy Marquis Muyang.
And I know
you understand me.
You know
I'm not a woman who's willing
to be trapped in the mansion.
You know I came down
the mountain for some reason.
You know I'm related to the deaths
of Lv Cheng and Lu Changfu.
And you know
I have liked you
for a long time.
I won't do it again.
I'm sorry for making you worry.
ظآزDeepest love is none other thanظآز
ظآزAligning my scars with yoursظآز
ظآزWhat was once let goظآز
ظآزWill heal together from now onظآز
ظآزFrom your silhouetteظآز
ظآزI see the same meظآز
ظآزIf dreams become illusionsظآز
ظآزWith you I journey and find solaceظآز
ظآزIn the sole abode of heartظآز
ظآزWe embrace and circle into a cornerظآز
ظآزAmong worldly entanglementsظآز
ظآزLove lightly brushes pastظآز
ظآزLike you, like meظآز
ظآزThe eyes are still clearظآز
ظآزNone better than you,
and none better than meظآز
ظآزLove can last until the springظآز
Li.
Did you have a nightmare?
I dreamed that I was all alone,
walking on a desolate road,
with nothing around.
It was pitch black.
It's okay. It was just a dream.
I often have dreams like that.
I'm scared every time I wake up.
I'm here.
I won't let you be alone again.
Really?
I promise,
no matter what happens,
I won't abandon you or leave you alone.
In life and death, we shall not part.
In weal and woe, we shall be one.
ظآزAmidst life's ups and downs,
turns and twistsظآز
ظآزLove has never strayed awayظآز
I trust you.
ظآزIn the end, we're together againظآز
ظآزCountless trials and pleadings,
right or wrongظآز
ظآزTry to make this love quietظآز
ظآزBut we fight backظآز
ظآزTo make it a tale to be toldظآز
ظآزSilently, we turn pain into joyظآز
ظآزYou reach out and pull meظآز
ظآزAnd I gently touchظآز
ظآزSmooth out the creasesظآز
ظآزSo we can tightly fit togetherظآز
ظآزWithout you, there's no meظآز
ظآزPassing by the worldظآز
ظآزPart of my broken selfظآز
ظآزFinds our places in an embraceظآز
ظآزFulfilling our wishesظآز
ظآزLovers remain calm and composedظآز
ظآزLike you, like meظآز
ظآزIt's like a fond dreamظآز
ظآزNone better than you,
and none better than meظآز
ظآزLove blooms at every spring and sunsetظآز
(I'm heading to Shende Shop)
Fun, right?
Yes.
Are you feeling hot?
(The intense heat from that day
was exactly the same as right now.)
(The stone blocks along the street
seemed to be melting under the sun.)
(The cicadas drone louder and faster,)
(so piercing as if they might
split the very heavens.)
It's so hot.
My lady, it is really hot.
Everything's prepared?
(After Mo Xiuyao saved me,
I returned to the capital with Mom.)
(For somehow, after we parted,
I often dreamt of him.)
(Qingshuang said I had fallen for him.)
(I didn't fully understand,
so I wanted to see him once again.)
(I heard he went to serve Duke Hua.)
(It so happened that Duke Hua returned
to the capital for his mother's birthday.)
(As a personal guard,
he would travel along.)
(I wanted to see him,
but didn't dare tell Mom.)
(So I hired an escort carriage secretly
and took a rough ride out of the city.)
(Duke Hua's forces were stationed at
Changding Camp, west of the capital.)
(Changding isn't too far
from the capital.)
- (Riding there)
- How about it?
- (would only take about two hours.)
- The road was blocked.
(But luck wasn't on my side.)
- (A recent storm had washed away the roads,)
- Let's go.
(blocking all carriages.)
(So I had to take a small path.)
(The heat was dizzying.)
(The fruit drink in my small gourd)
- (was running dry.)
- Drink it, My Lady.
(My throat was still
parched and burning.)
(My legs felt like lead,
making it hard to take another step.)
- (Yet a fire burned in my chest,)
- Let's go.
- (pushing me to move forward.)
- Go.
(I had a question.
I had to ask him in person.)
(Maybe my information was wrong.)
(When I arrived, they'd already left.)
(I didn't get to see him.)
(Looking back,)
(the small road from the capital to Changding
takes a mere four to six hours.)
(Yet in my memory of that summer,
that road stretched on forever.)
(The cicadas' chattering was deafening.)
Can I ask you a question?
Go ahead.
The day we first met,
there were so many people there.
Why did you just pull me
onto your saddle?
Did you like me back then?
You were about this tall.
Your face got wet with snot and tears.
What did I like about you?
No snot!
Your Highnesses,
what are you doing here?
Waiting for you to open the shop.
Please, come in.
(Preview)
We did have an engagement.
But we were just kids back then.
Barely even knew each other.
Things changed later, and we lost touch.
If one day, I am in your way,
would you kill me then?
Yao, let's make a bet.
I bet the sun vanishes tomorrow,
right at the Wu hour.
ظآزMemories hold you back
from fulfilling your dreamsظآز
ظآزOnly by moving forward
can you find reunionظآز
ظآزEndings only mark new routesظآز
ظآزIt's all part of the sceneryظآز
ظآزTo the horizon's callظآز
ظآزYour journey hasn't startedظآز
ظآزTowards mountains,
chase the stars brightظآز
ظآزBoth joy and grief
make the trip worthwhileظآز
ظآزTrying to catch up
to your own lost shadowظآز
ظآزWithin the wilds, echoes thriveظآز
ظآزClear mind leads to a clear pathظآز
ظآزBe grateful to your lossesظآز
ظآزMake your steps weightlessظآز
ظآزTowards mountains,
chase the stars brightظآز
ظآزLet time embrace you
and wash away the pastظآز
ظآزPut every twist behind you,
drift leisurely through timeظآز
ظآزMake headway against the wind,
let mountains bow to your paceظآز
ظآزRush towards a life without regretظآز
ظآزLet your nature burst freeظآز
ظآزUnbound by formظآز