I want you to get rid of that family.
What do you mean "get rid of"?
The Tagusari family…
Kill them all for me.
Mogi regretted it the entire time.
If only back then, I had stopped him…
That's enough.
Wait, I'm still talking--
I've waited 31 years.
That's more than enough.
Makoto.
Let me kill him.
They didn't run away!
They didn't even move.
Sakutaro and Yuka…
They didn't even make a sound.
That's what Mogi said.
What are you talking about?
Don't mess with us!
Could it be…
They were already dead?
You too? What are you going on about?
Minoru!
Why did you stop?
She's obviously just bullshitting!
It's true there's no proof.
But there's no proof our parents
were alive back then, either.
You're really going to believe that story?
You can't get revenge
based on speculation.
Mogi is the killer!
But…
If the story is true,
there's a new culprit out there.
Minoru.
That would mean Mogi isn't the killer.
So I have to look into it.
Just what on earth are you hiding?
Haruko Ashikaga.
I'll go check
the remaining people involved.
The ones who ordered Mogi to murder them
were the factory manager and Sasaoka.
Amagi from the Igarashi-gumi
might be involved too.
And also Mr. Koike.