(Previously)
At first, I didn't think I'd like it.
But the more I looked at
it, the more I fell in love.
And I think I'll love it
even more in the future.
Let's make this place our home.
Our home.
Of course you're going to love it.
Our home is called ChermChey.
I made this for you.
So you won't lose it.
It's a Phra Khun Phaen amulet.
This one is super charming.
Boom!
What's up, Joi?
Boss, P'Erng!
Customers are fighting in front of the
shop. One of our tables is already broken!
Damn it!
What's going on?
Calm down.
Stay out of this!
Go fight somewhere else!
Don't do this in my shop!
I think...
They're trying to wreck
the place, not just fight.
Who is that?
Hey.
Shit, how did In get here?
How do you know who I am?
Whoa, calm down, man!
I'm going to kill you!
I'm sorry, man!
Who hired you?
Mr... Mr...
Mr. Who?
Mr. Aten! Aten hired us!
Erng, hang in there!
Hurry, P'Erng! Let's go!
Hey, bro!
Let go of me!
Bro!
Can't you see what's happening?
Stop! Have you lost your mind?
Erng!
How can I calm down
when the place is on fire?!
Hia!
Erng!
May this place be filled
with joy and warmth.
Three years ago, I opened
a small bar with my ex.
I poured my heart into it
until it became popular.
Then we decided to expand.
You can imagine how
much I loved that place.
But then I caught him bringing
someone else into our bed.
Can I take over your bar?
I want to start a business.
I've already thought of a name.
Really? Let's hear it.
ChermChey.
I'm Cherm.
(Out-dated)
And you're Chey.
(Old-fashioned)
Let's take a selfie.
ChermChey is officially open!
At first, I didn't think I'd like it.
But the more I looked at it,
the more I fell in love.
And I think I'll love it
even more in the future.
Let's make this place our home.
Our home.
This notebook is ours.
To write down all our memories together.
What's this little girl's name?
She doesn't have a name yet.
Can you name her for us?
Earn.
Her name is Earn Earn.
A combination of In and Erng?
Yeah.
That's so cute.
"Chermchey"
(Episode 8)
- Watch out!
- Whoa!
Hey, Hia!
Why are you shouting?
I know you're awake.
You're just ignoring me.
Ouch.
I'm depressed.
I don't want to talk to anyone right now.
My heart is aching.
Because of the fire?
And last night...
Where did you go when the shop was burning?
I went to beat someone up.
I saw it on the CCTV.
Someone was lurking around the house.
So I went out to deal with him.
The guy who burned down our shop...
is the same guy who
started the fight last month.
But I couldn't do anything
to the guy who hired him.
Who?
Is it who you thought it was?
It wasn't Bom.
It was Aten.
Are you tired of me?
Tired of me causing all these problems?
Are you a soap opera actress?
Stop reading from a drama script.
Don't be stupid...
and try to push me away
to find someone better.
A "good person" and
the "person you love"...
are not the same thing.
And another thing...
None of this is your fault, Erng.
Aten is the crazy one.
Stop acting like a victim in a drama.
And go back to being
the annoying Erng I know.
I'm never breaking up with you.
Got it?
I'm not breaking up with you either.
Can you stop scolding me?
I get it now.
Well, you were talking nonsense.
I'm sorry.
I really love your sassy mouth.
If you hadn't just woken up...
I would've devoured you by now.
Save the devouring for later.
But as a devoted husband...
how are you going to handle this?
Do I look handsome today?
Yes.
But what does that have to do with this?
It does, because I dressed up to
meet P'On and my sister-in-law.
Did Aten think he was the
only one with connections?
What the hell are you doing here?
I came to apologize to P'Erng and to you.
I didn't know you were
Araya's younger brother.
What happened to your face?
My dad beat me. Araya
made one call to his secretary...
and my dad dragged me back home.
He was furious that I
burned down your shop.
I don't actually feel that guilty, though.
I'm just apologizing to get it over with.
Then you deserved...
getting beaten up.
I'm going in to apologize to P'Erng.
I don't want my dad to beat me again...
for dragging my feet.
I heard everything.
Consider your apology accepted.
Now, get out.
Can I stay in your room for a bit longer?
I don't want my dad's men
reporting that I'm insincere.
But you aren't sincere anyway.
Seriously...
why the hell did you do all this?
For the thrill, I guess.
Just for the thrill?
I really want to slap you, Aten.
You took everything from me.
You wanted Bom...
and he packed his bags to be with you.
What more do you want from me?
Is being this malicious
just who you really are?
Where did the sweet kid
I used to care about go?
Ever since P'Bom broke up with you...
he hasn't been the same with me.
Why, P'Erng?
Even though P'Bom chose me...
why did it turn out like this?
Even though I'm his official partner...
he never respects me!
That's between you and him.
It has nothing to do with me.
Stop dragging me into your mess.
It does. I was jealous of you.
The happier you were, the more I hated it.
Did destroying me actually make you happy?
Or...
are you hurting too?
You need to ask yourself
what you're really feeling.
Of course I'm happy. I
stole P'Bom from you.
It felt amazing.
People who are actually
happy don't act like this.
The Aten I knew...
wasn't like this.
I'm not mad at you about Bom.
But about the shop, I'm absolutely furious.
So apologize to me, you little brat.
After what I did, you
still call me your brother?
If we can get mad, we can forgive too.
I'm too awful for anyone to forgive.
I forgive you.
And so does Nok.
Everyone goes through a dark phase.
Let bygones be bygones.
If you know you did wrong...
just start over.
You don't have to hate yourself so much.
If you've learned your
lesson, you're still my brother.
And about Bom, you
weren't the only one at fault.
It takes two to tango.
I'm the only one who did nothing wrong.
I'm the innocent princess in all of this.
You say you're not mad, but
you punched P'Bom's face in.
Well, I was mad back then.
But I'm not mad anymore.
And what about you?
You love each other, but you
threw a wrench at his head?
I love him, but I was mad too.
Do you know how hard it
was for us to be together?
Then you have to take good care of him.
Wow, that's sharp. Who's both
beautiful and kind? Me, of course.
Are we good now, P'Erng?
Fix my shop first, then we'll be good.
Sure, I was planning
to fix it for you anyway.
So, we're good now, right?
Yeah, fine. But why did
your dad beat you so hard?
He wants me to break up with P'Bom
and to send me to study abroad.
I said I wouldn't go, so he beat me up.
I have a favor to ask.
Can you take me to see P'Bom?
I want to see him before I leave. Just
dropping me off near his condo is fine.
Must be nice to have money.
Hia.
Hia, dear.
Yes, dear?
Take off your headphones first.
I'm listening to an online sermon.
Can you call me in 10 minutes?
Just talk to him, I won't interrupt.
I don't want 10 minutes, I want it now.
Take Aten to see Bom.
They want to say their final goodbyes.
Love...
The more you chase
it, the more it runs away.
Try staying still and
broadening your horizons.
And you'll find love all around you.
The more love you give to this world...
The more you'll get back.
Your husband is so deep.
Deep, my ass.
He's just copying the
sermon and preaching to us.
Should I say "Amen" to that?
Up to you. I usually pay respect
to his chest before bed every night.
P'Bom, you're back?
Did I wake you up?
I was waiting for you, but I fell asleep.
If you're tired, go back to sleep.
I'm going to shower.
P'Bom.
I went to see my dad today.
I ordered someone to burn P'Erng's shop,
and half of it burned down.
So Dad called me in to teach me a lesson.
P'Erng's new boyfriend is the younger
brother of someone Dad respects.
What the hell did you do, Aten?
When will you stop messing with Erng?
Don't you even care about me?
You never grow up.
I've never grown up in
your eyes anyway, right?
Dad ordered me to stay
away from you completely.
Congratulations, P'Bom.
You don't have to suffer anymore.
You don't have to break up with me anymore.
And about P'Erng, I've cleared it up.
It's all over.
I'm not breaking up.
When I wanted to break up,
you held onto me for dear life.
Now you're just going
to dump me this easily?
Yeah, I admit I wanted to win Erng back.
I was just trying to spite you.
Because you treated me like a dog.
And when you chased me away like a dog...
Did you ever care? Did
you ever worry about me?
Where are you going?
Let's talk this through first.
Don't run away.
Can you stop picking fights?
You're annoying.
I told you before, didn't I?
If there comes a day I can't take
it anymore, I'll be the one to leave.
Does it hurt?
I'll get some medicine for you.
It's fine, I've taken care of it.
Don't be stubborn.
I'm not letting you go home alone anymore.
If you're going back, tell me.
I'll go with you.
Caring now is useless.
Next week, Dad is
sending me to New Zealand.
Can you not go?
Ten.
(Aten)
I'll wait.
Don't wait.
From now on, I hope you find someone good.
What are you doing?
Dancing to attract customers. On
opening day, I'll be right at the counter.
Erng.
Come on out.
Let's go.
Erng Erng.
When will Erng Erng finish choosing?
I still can't choose.
I don't know what to eat.
Erng, you've been here
for 10 minutes, sweetheart.
There are too many options.
So I don't know what to eat.
Or maybe this one?
This is good.
This one.
Can I have two minutes
to gather my thoughts?
Sure.
Okay.
I think I'm good now.
Have you chosen?
Can I say something?
What?
Stop being so cute all the time.
Yuck.
I want to throw up at your BS.
Ong, how are you here?
To buy cat food. It ran out.
Otherwise, my boy
won't have anything to eat.
Are you even awake?
If I weren't, would I
be out buying cat food?
I can't believe you.
Leaving the house looking like this.
You haven't showered
this morning, have you?
How did you sneak past
Mom looking like that?
Mind your own business.
Since I ran into you,
I'll ride back with you.
No.
Erng Erng is big. He
takes up the whole seat.
That's rude, Hia.
Why did you stomp on my foot? That hurt.
Don't be dramatic. I barely stepped on it.
Erng, don't go near him.
He's filthy and hasn't showered.
I'm clean! I've been in AC, I smell good.
Pay for me first.
I only brought money for cat food.
I'm going to kill you.
Go ahead, if you think I
won't burn your amulets.
Want to go at it?
You think I'm scared huh?
Charge this to that guy over there.
Sure, okay.
Is this all, Ong?
No.
Erng is sleeping over
at In's tonight, right?
You're definitely getting some action.
Oh, we've slept together
for many nights already.
Hey, do you guys have condoms?
I have a new kind to recommend.
It's great. I just tried it last night.
Very thin, smooth, and
uninterrupted in every position.
But you have to use lube.
If you use lotion, it'll break.
That's inappropriate. I'm leaving,
I can't listen to this, Hia.
Ouch.
What the hell are you saying?
What did I do wrong?
Hey, wait for me.
This is the place of Baan Saithong...
(Famous line from an old Thai series)
that I wanted to come to...
Erng, come help carry the stuff.
No.
If I have to carry things myself,
why have a boyfriend?
Okay.
Fabulous, right?
No.
If we don't carry things ourselves...
Then why do we have muscles?
Hia.
He's insulting me.
Ong.
Are you insulting my boyfriend?
Hey.
You little brat.
Good job.
Erng.
Aren't you going to help me carry things?
No.
Hurry up and follow me.
Mr. Hia Intha.
Don't let me find out.
I'm getting a cramp.
That's better.
Big muscles for nothing, fatty.
What did you say?
Don't bully me.
Who would insult my boyfriend?
My boyfriend is so small.
Hurry.
Coming.
Hey, why did you shut the door on me?
Erng is here, Mom.
You're here, dear?
Yes.
Have you eaten yet?
- I came to eat your food today, Mom.
- Eat as much as you want.
Ong, where are you going?
Going upstairs, P'Aon.
And where is your cat?
Aon.
You're so rude to your brother.
Why do you do that?
Mom, aren't you used to how In and Ong
talk to each other?
It gets much ruder than this, Mom.
Mom.
P'Aon is framing me again.
I know.
I've never seen them
talk rudely to each other.
Yes, Mom. P'Aon loves to frame me.
Mom.
Mom, why don't you talk
to P'Aon and In-In first?
I'm going to head upstairs.
I need to take a shower.
Oh, my goodness.
You went out looking like
that without even showering?
I'll go take care of it right away.
Right, you haven't showered
since last night, have you?
But I think it's been
since yesterday morning.
Ong doesn't like to shower, Mom.
When you get close, he smells so bad.
If your heart is clean,
you don't need to shower.
You can't do that, dear. You
must shower morning and night.
You can't act like
you're still living abroad.
Exactly.
So, are you going out again tonight?
And take it easy on the girls, okay?
We're worried about you.
Yor-sor-tor-lor (Abbreviation that means
he's always fucking girls without a condom)
How can you say that?
Don't say that! Mom is
right here. It's dangerous!
It's nothing, Mom.
In-In told me it stands for
'Your Personal Reminder'.
Is that so?
I really didn't know, Mom.
I only found out when Aon just said it.
Don't play innocent, In.
I helped you out today!
Mom, Aon is raising his voice at me.
Aon!
I'm angry with you now.
Mom!
You'll pay for this.
Mommy!
Wait.
Hey!
That's my mom!
What? Don't you want to be family?
Oh, Mom might see us.
She won't. She's already gone.
Hey!
What?
Stop it.
Erng.
Mom!
Hey, where are you running off to?
Where's the medicine?
Oh, right. You need to take
your medicine after eating.
I think it's in the
car. I forgot to grab it.
Give me the keys. I'll go get it.
No, stay here. I'll get it for you.
Hia, Hia!
Let me go with you.
I feel like stretching my legs.
Sure.
Let's go quickly, or
mosquitoes will get in.
Mosquitoes wouldn't dare enter your room.
They're probably scared
of your cemetery lip balm.
This is the real deal,
blessed right at the cemetery!
Hia, why are you running?
Watch out, this is my house!
What is wrong with you?
Come on, hurry up.
So, what about the ghost story?
You still haven't told me.
You want me to tell you right here?
Yeah.
How does it go?
When I was about 14 or 15,
a fortune teller walked past my house
and told my dad that
his son's luck was down.
- The Banana Ghost wanted him...
- Did you pee on someone's banana tree?
The Banana Ghost wanted him as her husband.
Whoa, seriously?
So my dad wanted me to
perform a life-extending ritual.
But as for me,
I knew I hadn't peed
on anyone's banana tree.
My dad was just super
protective of his banana trees.
He said, 'The ritual won't hurt. What kind
of man is afraid of sleeping in a coffin?'
I was so mad back then.
So I went around kicking
all of my dad's banana trees
and yelled at the fortune teller,
'I'm going to be a wife!'
'I won't be anyone's husband, I'm
not a man, and I won't sleep in a coffin!'
You actually announced that
in the middle of your house?
Of course.
So everyone found out I was gay.
And I had to run for my life
to escape my dad's kicks.
I barely made it out alive.
But the thing is,
my dad already knew.
He'd known since the day I was born.
I supposedly yelled at the midwife
and my dad, 'Congratulations!'
'You have a baby girl!'
But the reason my dad was actually mad
was because I kicked
and broke his banana trees.
So he threw bottles at me.
We didn't talk for days.
He sounds like a sweet dad.
But wait, where's my horror ghost story?
That's the end of it.
End of report.
And here I was, hoping for a real ghost.
I'm staying out of this.
Amen to that.
Hia.
Intha &amp; Akara
I used to think
that if Chermchey was gone,
I'd have nothing left.
When I saw the fire,
it felt like everything was being
ripped away from me at once.
My shop, my dreams,
and my sense of security.
But when I ran back and
saw Erng standing there,
I almost burst into tears.
I wasn't even worried about the shop first.
I was worried about him.
In the end, the only
things I managed to save
were a notebook and a single doll.
I stood there, watching my shop
burn down right before my eyes,
unable to do anything about it.
It hurt so damn much to watch.
Because the one who made him cry
wasn't me.
At that moment, I swore to myself
that I wouldn't let whoever
did this get away with it.
When I found out it was Aten,
I was angry,
but deep down, I felt more
exhausted than anything.
It felt like everything was just
looping back to the same old story.
After the fire, Erng
went completely silent.
No teasing, no arguing,
not even a single insult directed at me.
That's when I started to get really scared.
But luckily, our home wasn't destroyed.
The shop is still standing,
and we're still alive.
We just have to start rebuilding again.
When Hia told me our home survived,
I almost cried again.
I don't know when it happened,
but the word
'shop'
became 'home'.
And the person beside me became family.
Sometimes, I feel like I'm a jinx.
Anyone who gets close
to me ends up suffering.
But what made me angrier than the fire
was seeing Erng start to blame himself.
I absolutely hate it
when he talks like that.
Being a good person and being the one
I love are two completely different things.
Even if Erng is stubborn, foul-mouthed,
and always looking for trouble,
I'd still choose him anyway.
At first, I thought I'd hate him so much.
But seeing him cry, I just
felt sorry for him instead.
Because in the end, Aten is just a kid
who never got the love he actually needed.
People who are truly happy
don't go around hurting others.
The more he spoke, the more I realized
how deeply unhappy Aten really was.
Watching Erng talk to Aten surprised me.
Despite everything he went
through, he still chose to forgive.
Honestly, I'm not that strong.
I just know that if we hold onto hatred,
everyone's life will end up ruined.
In the end, things wrapped
up in a pretty strange way.
From almost killing each other,
we ended up listening to
an online sermon together.
Hia In always acts like a fake monk,
but honestly,
sometimes his words really do help people.
After that, life slowly started
getting back to normal.
I still get stressed and dream
about the fire sometimes,
but whenever I'm with Hia,
everything feels so much lighter.
And of course, just as life starts to get
peaceful, Ong shows up to ruin it immediately.
I'm starting to get used to
the chaotic life in this house.
A house full of crazy, annoying,
and hopelessly romantic people.
Seeing Erng talk to my mom felt so good.
It feels like the person I love is truly
becoming a part of my family.
I don't know what lies ahead,
if the shop will ever be the same,
or if the chaos is truly over.
But right now, at least I know
that no matter how many
times my world falls apart,
I don't have to stand alone anymore.
(Next Episode) Tomorrow, Erng and I
are going to the beach.
A relationship-building trip.
How does going to the
beach build a relationship?
Well, it works.
Erng and I fell in love
because of our trips.
I also just found out that
Erng is protective of me too.
Very, very protective.
I have to wear a mermaid
tail for a photoshoot.
Please be our photographer, Hia.
It's time for me to return the favor.