[Love Has Fireworks]
[Episode 32]
Hello.
Hello, Miss Qian.
We're sorry to inform you
that you do not meet
our company's requirements.
I see. Thank you.
[Clary Construction Investment]
[Jitonghui Securities]
[Zhimei Construction Investment]
[Little Smart Roams the Future]
Qian Fei,
it's okay.
This is only the 10th company
that has rejected you.
Keep trying.
[Hello, Ms. Qian Fei.]
[I'm HR from Xinzouqi Capital Co., Ltd.]
[I've reviewed your resume.
After a preliminary assessment,]
[we think you'd be a good fit
for our company.]
[We'd like to invite you to an interview
at 10:00 AM the day after tomorrow.]
[Please reply to confirm it. Thank you.]
[Jingjing]
Hello.
Hello, Jingjing.
Did you send my resume
to Xinzouqi Capital?
I've received their interview invitation.
No, I didn't.
That's weird then.
I know the companies I've applied to.
And I only shared my resume with you.
I remember now.
I once told Wang Ruohai about this.
He said his former boss
left the original bank
and started his own venture capital firm.
He's doing great
and hiring people right now.
He thought this company
would be a good fit for you,
and he could put in a good word for you,
so he asked for your resume.
Well, I actually...
I didn't take what he said seriously.
Never thought he'd actually get it done.
Okay, I see.
Alright, I'm hanging up.
Who is it?
Hello, are you Ms. Qian Fei?
Yes.
Here are your flowers.
Thank you.
No problem.
[Let's start over. From Wang Ruohai.]
[Blocked Contacts]
[Calling]
Wang Ruohai, what exactly are you up to?
I just wanted you
to take me off your blacklist.
Looks like it worked.
I don't want to talk to you.
[Bad Name Took Me Forever]
[Streamer Center]
Today's game stream is over.
But I'm in a good mood today.
If anyone wants a chit-chat,
I can chat with you for a while.
Prime Minister,
you're using your mother's account again?
[Bad Name Took Me Forever is live.]
I successfully joined the stream.
I can see myself!
[Bad Name Took Me Forever]
Jun, isn't this your mom?
Peng Fei, Peng Fei.
What's going on?
Look, it's Jun's mom!
It really is.
Ma'am...
No, I mean, Blue Baby Bear.
[Bad Name Took Me Forever]
[Streamer Center]
-Dang.
-Welcome to my livestream.
Meeting you in this way
for the first time,
I'm feeling a bit shy.
Miss Bad Name,
I am Blue Baby Bear.
[Bad Name Took Me Forever is live.]
Prime Minister and I
have always been following you closely.
I-I've sent you many gifts.
I've also been watching your livestream.
-It's okay.
-It's not awkward at all.
[Bad Name Took Me Forever]
They're having a good time chatting.
[Mom, stop messing around.
Get disconnected now.]
[You're making Bad Name feel awkward.]
[Prime Minister is dating Bad Name?]
[Bad Name, your mother-in-law
has found out about your true colors.]
Wait, what "true colors"?
[Come back to our side.]
I understand all this stuff
you say on the internet.
[Peak "mother-in-law & daughter-in-law"
livestream moment]
Ma'am, my fans are just
talking nonsense. Don't mind them.
Listen,
I'm not Miss Bad Name's mother-in-law.
[Hold on...]
But it's true
that Prime Minister is pursuing her.
[What did I miss?]
[No, you came at the perfect time.]
Why are you guys so hyped?
-If they end up falling out
-What are you doing? What is it?
because of your provocation,
[Bad Name Took Me Forever]
I... I will blame all of you.
Oh, my goodness!
Jun, what does your mom mean by this?
She has won
the mother-in-law over, hasn't she?
I thought your mom once said that she
didn't like daughters-in-law
from other cities!
Yes!
Now that she's won the first prize
in the dance competition,
the household registration issue
is settled, right?
-Exactly!
-Sir, please stop it.
I'm feeling so embarrassed!
Bad Name, I've learned a dance.
Let's interact a bit.
[I never saw this coming.]
[For the iconic moment.]
[So cute.]
[What is happening?]
[Laughing out loud
for the first time today.]
They're dancing! They're dancing!
It's trending in the top 30!
It's starting. Let's go.
[Get more people there.] [So cute.]
[So many people are watching.] [Don't
know this dance, but she's so pretty.]
The fans who like
Miss Bad Name,
please subscribe
[The madam is pretty cute.]
[Excellent anchor and beautiful anchor]
[Interesting] [Keep playing and dancing]
and hit the "like" button.
Don't hold back.
The stream is now in the top five!
Jun, your wife and your mom are
the model mother-in-law
and daughter-in-law of the internet!
Not bad!
I didn't expect this would happen,
not even in my dreams!
So nice.
Fei, Wang Ruohai is sending me
a barrage of messages.
Compared to how he used to be, I feel like
he's a completely different person now.
He claimed
that he sincerely wanted to win you back
and asked me to persuade you
to go to the interview.
To be honest,
I think he's trying so hard to help you
because he owes you in the first place.
You don't need to feel any pressure.
Most importantly,
you're making
a major career change this time,
and it's so hard.
Realistically,
I think you should
seize this opportunity he offered you.
I see. I will go to the interview.
Come on.
I told you not to drink so much.
But you just chugged it down.
You're really something.
Here, come on.
Alright, I'm leaving.
[Pretentious Li]
Li Yifei has been on this business trip
for quite a while.
It'd be great if he were here.
At least he would
wring out a towel for me.
[Pretentious Li]
[Qian Fei]
Li Yifei, are you that afraid
that I might cling to you?
[Class Monitor]
Young master, you finally called me back.
Hello, Qian Fei?
Monitor?
What's up?
You must come to be the bridesmaid
when Mei and I hold the wedding.
It's a deal.
I've been a bridesmaid 3 times already.
If I do it again,
I won't be able to get married myself.
Qian Fei,
what's wrong with your voice?
Are you sick?
Where are you?
I must be hallucinating.
Why does your voice sound
more and more like Wang Ruohai?
[Qian Fei]
Qian Fei?
Qian Fei.
Wake up, Qian Fei.
Wang Ruohai?
Why are you here?
Wake up, Qian Fei.
Are you okay?
Qian Fei?
Fortunately,
the patient is young and healthy.
If she had arrived any later,
it'd have turned into pneumonia.
Doctor.
You're awake.
It's okay.
Stay in the hospital
for observation for a day,
and the nurse will give you an IV.
Thank you.
[Qian Fei] [Missed Call]
I was having dinner
with my partners yesterday.
I drank a little too much
and didn't hear my phone ring.
You're awake.
Want to get up? Here.
What are you looking for?
Where is my phone?
I put it away,
so it wouldn't disturb your rest.
I'll let you know
if someone tries to reach you.
I need it right now.
Here you are.
Thanks.
I also forgot what I was going to say.
Just focus on your business trip.
[I also forgot what I was going to say.
Just focus on your business trip.]
Qian Fei,
what are you doing?
I got you some food.
Eat it while it's warm.
Here,
let me feed you.
Here.
-It's not bad, right?
-Give it to me.
Don't you need to work today?
I took the day off.
You're pretty good
at taking care of people now.
I remember
when we were together before.
I used to work late all the time,
yet you never came to pick me up.
Now
you're taking such good care of me.
You took care of me for 5 years.
I learned just by watching.
Actually, it's not that
I didn't know how to do it back then.
It's just that I knew deep down
that no matter how I treated you,
you would never leave me.
So I got lazy.
That's quite sincere.
Why do you make it
sound like I did something wrong
and gave you too much
of a sense of security?
Well, you did teach me a lesson.
Thank you.
Qian Fei.
If a man
feels like he can easily control you,
he will start to cherish you less.
Sometimes, he won't even bother replying
to your messages quickly.
Being busy is
just an excuse men use.
I don't want
to see you get hurt again.
Wang Ruohai,
did you check my phone?
Nope.
I just noticed the way you looked—
you looked like you were
waiting for someone's reply.
Can you stop making wild guesses?
Okay, fine.
You are sick.
If you say so, then so be it.
Mr. Li, come in, please.
You have elegant taste, Mr. Sang.
Come on, Mr. Li, take a seat.
Mr. Li, I heard you've been
on the Fulaxida project
all the time recently.
Yeah.
Looks like your skin's
gotten a healthier tan.
Fulaxida has also been facing
constant problems lately.
They've been stuck in the mountains.
Now, those minor shareholders
all think their money
has gone down the drain.
They keep calling me all day long,
wanting to track the project.
Meanwhile,
Mr. Sang, you have a better temper
and stay calm.
You're even in the mood for running.
Honestly,
I've heard a little about
what's happening in Fulaxida.
But I believe that
with your capability, Mr. Li,
you certainly won't let me suffer losses.
Not necessarily.
Take a look at this document.
It concerns your interests.
[Share Termination Contract]
[Party A: Sanglin Group Co., Ltd.]
[Termination Contract]
[Sanglin Group Co., Ltd.]
Mr. Li, what do you mean by this?
I mean exactly
what is written in this document.
Let's terminate the contract.
We're no longer cooperating.
Mr. Sang, keep the drama you staged
to yourself.
Fulaxida has never been,
and will never be,
a tool for you
to easily rake in money.
Understand?
Do you know
what you are doing?
I couldn't be clearer about it.
You want to kick me out, right?
Fine.
But before that,
I also have a contract
for you, Mr. Li,
to take a look.
[Sanglin Group Co., Ltd.]
Y-Yifei,
hear me out.
I really didn't know
signing that was a trap.
They told me that
if I signed this technical contract
as the legal representative,
it would be like adding a lock
to the project's funding.
So you signed it?
They said
this contract could be terminated
at any time.
Didn't you know that
the contract had been tampered with?
Yifei, don't... don't scare me.
I was wrong.
I'll accept any punishment you give me.
What should we do now?
But things are no longer
the way you think they are.
Explain it clearly, Li Yifei!
Don't tell me Fulaxida will end up
belonging to Sang Shiqi!
Today, I came to force Mr. Sang
to withdraw his investment in Fulaxida,
but I was actually
just trying to provoke him.
I wanted to see
the last thing up his sleeve.
Y-You mean
you already knew he wouldn't agree?
Yes.
And I made him expose
the real power behind him.
Who is it?
Liao Jinshan.
Are you sure?
Today, he took out that tampered contract
to force me to give in.
I can't be more familiar with this trick.
When Qiansheng Group
went public in the US,
Liao Jinshan used this exact trick
against my family.
It's just that I was
too young to take part in it back then.
I heard about it from my dad later.
Should I say you're lucky or you're smart?
All right.
Now that we know who our enemy is,
it'll be easier for us
to fight the next battle.
It's not over yet.
Besides Liao Jinshan,
there's someone else.
You... You mean there's one more mole?
Yep.
Only people familiar with my usual style
would clearly know that
I would use shares to confront Mr. Sang.
Oh, Li Yifei,
so you've been setting up such a big trap!
You even kept it from me.
That's not cool!
I have no choice.
Only by hiding it from everyone
can I catch the real mole.
Okay.
[Zhonggeng Global Creative Center]
Qian Fei, I've seen you before.
I saw you at the company entrance
when you were waiting
for Wang Ruohai to get off work.
I've seen you, too.
After founding Xinzouqi Capital,
you've made frequent appearances
in the media.
Having made a new venture capital firm
so competitive
in such a short time—
I think it's truly amazing.
Thank you.
We've all reviewed your resume.
[Xinzouqi Capital Co., Ltd.]
We've also conducted
background checks on your work history
and why you left He Jing Securities.
Frankly speaking,
even if we set aside
the reason you were dismissed,
I believe this incident
has a major impact on your career
in investment banking.
It's not devastating, though.
I think you could
transition into the back office
[Xinzouqi Capital Co., Ltd.]
or pass other qualification exams
to get back into investment banking.
But why
[Xinzouqi Capital Co., Ltd.]
would you choose
a small venture capital firm
like ours?
I've worked
at He Jing Securities since graduation.
It helped me grow significantly
and broadened my horizons
in the financial industry.
Especially in back-end data analysis
and front-end project preparation,
it allowed me
to accumulate a lot of experience.
As for the reason I was dismissed,
[Xinzouqi Capital Co., Ltd.]
I could have simply used
the company's internal adjustments
as an excuse to explain it.
But actually, regarding this incident,
the biggest lesson it taught me is that
when facing the industry's unspoken rules,
you either accept them and adapt to them,
or you step away from them.
And I chose
to stay true to my original intention.
I don't want to force myself
for the sake of my future.
So I chose to leave investment banking
and come here.
How do you know that
you can realize your original intention
here at Xinzouqi Capital?
Actually, before coming to the interview,
I investigated every project
Xinzouqi Capital has invested in
since its establishment.
Although I wasn't involved in them,
I could tell that
under your leadership, Xinzouqi Capital
is not just
a profit-seeking venture capital firm
but a capital bridge
with a forward-looking vision
and a sense of social responsibility.
Then how do you define
the essence of equity investment?
I think equity investment is
actually a relationship
between zero and one.
It's either zero or one.
There is actually no middle ground.
If you win,
you get returns.
If you lose, you lose everything.
There's only one way to win,
which is to help enterprises
create real value for society.
We're glad
to have you join us at Xinzouqi Capital.
Let's work together
to help more enterprises.
Thank you.
[Xinzouqi Capital Co., Ltd.]
Look, No. 9 and No. 10,
as well as No. 1,
have these field controllers installed.
The rest of them are still
under construction currently.
Are you exhausted
from running around the past few days?
Well, if so, you should go back first.
We're almost done anyway.
That's almost it.
Okay, thank you for your hard work, too.
Okay.
By the way, um,
Qian Fei has found a new job.
My wife called me.
She said Qian Fei's working
at Xinzouqi Capital now.
She's switched to venture capital.
Xinzouqi?
How did she get in there?
That's not something confidential, right?
I think it was because of Wang Ruohai.
He used to be the subordinate
of Xinzouqi's boss.
After hearing
that Qian Fei was looking for a job,
he put in a good word for her
with Xinzouqi's boss.
When did this happen?
In the last couple of days, I think.
What? Are you panicking?
It just occurred to me that
Qian Fei sent me WeChat messages
a few days ago.
I guess it was about her job hunting.
She must have been very helpless
at that time,
but I couldn't help her at all.
Hey, why are you being so indecisive now?
Actually,
I've always been sure
that I like Qian Fei.
But does Qian Fei
really like me, too?
Or in other words,
would she...
accept me?
Hold on, hold on...
Y-You two have lived together for so long.
Can't you even tell
whether she likes you or not?
Hey, when it comes to women,
aren't you an expert?
It's different now.
Liking someone and loving someone
are even more different.
I'm serious this time.
I want to marry her.
Then what are you doing here?
It's a long story.
I wanted to use this trip
to completely sort out
my thoughts.
I was nervous, after all.
But I happened to overlook one thing.
She couldn't possibly just stay in place
waiting for me.
There's nothing between us yet.
She has no obligation to do so, either.
Stop it.
All right, look.
Tell me how you feel
right now.
I never stop yearning to see her.
But there are no more flights today.
I'll fly early tomorrow morning.
I'll leave this to you.
I believe in you.
Okay!
You got this!
[Exit]
Help me book a table with a view
at an Italian restaurant.
At 5:00 PM.
For two.
Okay, thank you.
[Xinzouqi Capital Co., Ltd.]
[Pretentious Li]
Hello?
Landlady, I'm back.
Well...
Are you free this afternoon?
Let's have dinner together.
And I have something to tell you.
Okay.
Alright, I'll send you the address.
See you later.
At 5:00 PM.
Mr. Liu, let's go to No. 520 Flower Shop
in Lujiazui first.
Got it.
♪ No need to guess the ending
right from the beginning ♪
♪ Let the melody play
among the chords and the wind ♪
♪ And no need to demand
that yesterday keeps its promises ♪
♪ Leave some surprises in life
to the unknown ♪
Li Yifei wants to have dinner with me.
What is he going to tell me?
♪ No need to use a few fragments
of the past to define the whole story ♪
Maybe he wants to tell me
not to think too much.
♪ Somehow, a little heartbreak
awakens the poet within ♪
♪ There's also no need
to give up because of the past ♪
♪ I need some courage to get praises ♪
♪ I'll show you the wider world ♪
♪ It's only in blazing bright
that I am who I am ♪
♪ Quietly carry it all, like a harbor
sheltering your drifting soul ♪
♪ When you return to your peaceful life ♪
♪ The light at home glows warm
day and night ♪
♪ Stay forever by each other's side ♪
♪ Like the stars and the moon
hanging brightly in the sky ♪
♪ I'll show you the wider world ♪
♪ It's only in blazing bright
that I am who I am ♪
♪ Quietly carry it all, like a harbor
sheltering your drifting soul ♪
♪ When you return to your peaceful life ♪
♪ The light at home glows warm
day and night ♪
♪ Stay forever by each other's side ♪
♪ Like the stars and the moon
hanging brightly in the sky ♪
Isn't it weird to dress this formally?
Not at all.
It's about attitude.
Why did you
suddenly lose so much weight?
Did I?
Maybe it's due to the fever I had before.
You had a fever?
What happened?
It's okay. It happened a long time ago.
By the way,
this is for you.
Open it to have a look.
Do you like it?
It's quite pretty.
Oh, right, didn't you say on the phone
that you had something to tell me?
What is it?
Qian Fei.
I...
Actually, I...
Then let me go first.
Li Yifei.
I missed you so much.
I couldn't help
but think of your cheeky look.
Really?
Actually, I also want to say...
Let me finish first.
I would
often check my phone
to see if you've sent me any messages.
My mind is also consumed by you.
Whether I like it or not,
you are always there.
However,
I've also realized one thing.
You make me feel very insecure.
I hate waiting and guessing like this.
I don't like myself like this either.
But I like you.
♪ Whenever I look up ♪
Qian Fei...
♪ I ran into your eyes ♪
I'm sure I've fallen for you.
♪ Trying to catch that pleasant light ♪
I know I
have a lot of flaws
and shortcomings.
♪ To embrace that fleeting moment
of happiness ♪
I'm always self-conceited,
and I always mess with you
and get on your nerves.
♪ Sometimes I cry,
and sometimes I'm happy ♪
I really haven't been good enough.
But it's different now.
♪ Sometimes I feel
I've captured the sweetness ♪
I have a direction.
I know what I should do next.
Can you give me a chance, Qian Fei?
♪ Sometimes, I run,
and sometimes, I fall ♪
Let's be together.
♪ Sometimes I feel
that having you is the best thing ♪
Be together?
You disappear when you want,
♪ I've never loved anyone
like I love you ♪
appear when you want,
and say you love me when you want.
Now you want us to be together
just because you want to?
♪ Without any hesitation ♪
What? Do you think I'm a fool
who will just follow your orders?
It's not like that, Qian Fei.
I just wanted to
take this business trip as a chance
♪ I've never been loved like you love me ♪
to sober up completely
and figure out
what I really wanted
and what our future would be like.
♪ In short, I'll wait for my love ♪
But I realized I was wrong.
♪ I've never seen a bright sea like you ♪
I overcomplicated
a simple thing.
♪ Every minute is colorful ♪
Liking is simply liking.
I believe you feel the same way.
Neither of us can lie to ourselves.
♪ I've never experienced
such a warm love as yours ♪
♪ In short, I won't let go of my hand ♪
I admit that last time,
I did run away.
If I've hurt you,
I apologize.
I'm sorry.
You don't need to apologize to me.
Do you realize how selfish you are?
You... You can't hurt me again anyway.
I won't give you that chance again.
♪ I've never loved anyone
like I love you ♪
I've made my choice.
♪ Without any hesitation ♪
♪ I've never been loved like you love me ♪
♪ In short, I'll wait for my love ♪
♪ I've never seen a bright sea like you ♪
♪ Every minute is colorful ♪
Hello, we've finished
moving things out here.
Please take a look.
Okay.
♪ I've never experienced
such a warm love as yours ♪
♪ In short, I won't let go of my hand ♪
Thank you for your hard work.
You're welcome. Goodbye.
[In the next episode
of "Love Has Fireworks"]
Didn't you say you were no longer
obsessed with love
and can rationally think about
your future relationships?
You're completely hopeless.
[Daisy flower language: You're the love
I've hidden deep down inside.]
You've fallen in love with Li Yifei.
[I've figured out a plan
and will contact you later.]
I'm looking for someone.
Sorry.
Do you know which room the guest
you're looking for is in?