[Love Has Fireworks]
[Episode 31]
Didn't you say it yourself
at the venture capital conference
that rural revitalization
is a national strategy?
This is definitely
a new wave of the times,
right?
And its impact
is no less significant than
the Reform and Opening-Up era
my father experienced decades ago.
So sometimes I find myself thinking that
it doesn't really matter
whether Fulaxida
ever makes money or not.
Life is so short.
If I run into a wave this big
and don't even jump in,
wouldn't that mean
I've got less guts
than that old man of mine?
True.
And let me tell you something else.
Whether a company
can survive in the end
doesn't depend on how much capital it has.
Anyone can put up money.
What really matters
is the personal ability
of the project initiator.
So what I value most
is you, as a person.
Of course, him too.
2022.
One at a time. One at a time.
Because you two are like me—
sharp enough to spot
the business opportunities
of rural development
in such a restless city.
And for that, I truly admire you.
Yifei,
how are you...
so good at praising yourself?
Teach me sometime, will you?
See? I said you've got sharp instincts.
But anyway,
we're like-minded people,
right?
Look at this vast land.
What is this?
This is wealth bestowed by nature.
But in my opinion,
Fulaxida's strength right now
is still far from enough.
Still too slow.
In the future, we must develop this place
into a model zone for modern agriculture.
You want to raise funds now?
Didn't you disagree before?
What I disagreed with
was raising dumb money.
Because that kind of money is
as good as burned—
it won't leave you with anything real,
you understand?
What we really need
is smart money—capital that comes
with valuable resources and connections.
That's the kind of money I want.
And the more, the better.
Only that kind of capital
can turn this dream into reality.
I get it.
We're going after the right investors.
Exactly.
That's what Yifei said.
He's agreed to raise funding.
It really wasn't easy
to get Mr. Li to budge.
Isn't it just smart money?
I'll go prepare it now.
Okay.
[Sanglin Group Co., Ltd.]
Alright.
Now the big problem is solved.
Once Fulaxida goes public
through a reverse merger,
the shares I'm holding on your behalf
will multiply dozens of times.
But only if I'm still alive to claim it.
The situation isn't looking good.
I think we need to speed things up
before something unexpected happens.
I've done my best with my part.
The rest is up to you.
Don't worry.
We've been friends for decades.
Just leave it to me.
Come on,
have some water.
[Sanglin Group Co., Ltd.]
I know how you handle things.
But sometimes,
things just don't go as planned.
Better to be cautious, don't you think?
Is it connected?
Yes!
Is it working?
You know, you look just like
a lovesick teenager.
Where's that fire you had
when you were winning over
the villagers?
Pull yourself together.
It's all work.
My wife called me.
Qian Fei didn't even know
you'd come here on a business trip.
What's going on? Trouble in paradise?
Nothing.
Nothing at all.
I see.
Off to a bad start.
What nonsense are you talking about?
What do you know?
Let me tell you,
I used to be just like you.
Before, with my wife,
I used to just keep everything in my head—
thinking it over, imagining things,
blah blah blah, and all that.
But I forgot the most important thing—
feeling.
As long as it feels right,
that's all that matters.
I know.
You finance guys always like
calculating your returns and losses,
and planning for every contingency.
But love isn't rational.
It's emotional.
And I'll tell you this—
if fate has already planned a relationship
for the two of you,
then as long as your paths cross,
there's no escaping it.
Running all the way out here
still won't make a difference.
So, Mr. Li,
you're just
making things harder on yourself.
Keep an eye on things here.
I'll go take a look over there.
♪ What matters to me is what you need ♪
♪ Nothing more, nothing less,
I just hope it's something I can give ♪
Why is it you?
♪ What I cherish is what I have ♪
♪ Every little moment,
I hope you're there with me ♪
♪ Those fairy tales, sweet words,
and declarations of love ♪
♪ Are like fireworks
lighting up the night ♪
Cut it out! Let's fulfill the contract.
♪ Truths, lies,
and words said just for show ♪
Fulfill the contract.
♪ Feel like I'm walking on cotton ♪
♪ Harsh words, lies,
and words I can't make sense of ♪
♪ Pretentious words wrapped
in glitter and glamour ♪
♪ Dreams, madness,
and the words buried in my heart ♪
♪ Under your fiery eyes ♪
♪ What I dream of is being with you ♪
♪ Hand in hand,
taking life at an easy pace ♪
♪ What I wish for
is something that lasts ♪
♪ Day by day, holding you close
in a life that's simple and true ♪
♪ Those fairy tales, sweet words,
and declarations of love ♪
♪ Are like fireworks
lighting up the night ♪
♪ Truths, lies,
and words said just for show ♪
♪ Feel like I'm walking on cotton ♪
♪ Harsh words, lies,
and words I can't make sense of ♪
♪ Pretentious words wrapped
in glitter and glamour ♪
♪ Dreams, madness,
and the words buried in my heart ♪
♪ Under your fiery eyes ♪
♪ Those fairy tales, sweet words,
and declarations of love ♪
♪ Are like fireworks
lighting up the night ♪
♪ Dreams, madness,
and the words buried in my heart ♪
[Online Q&A]
I used
[Fulaxida, well done]
a small camera like this,
so experts could remotely guide him
in treating his son, over several months.
The results were excellent!
They're currently in Shanghai
for a follow-up visit
and will be back in a few days.
-How is that not the same thing?
-It's only been a few days,
-but you've lost weight.
-His son, Xin Ba,
could receive treatment and guidance
from international medical experts
in such a remote place—
what made that possible?
[Xin You]
Xin You,
it's me, Qian Fei.
I just came across a short video
about you.
How are you and Xin Ba doing?
Hello, Xin You.
You saw my message, right?
You're in Shanghai now?
I'm free. Yes, I'm free.
Okay, let's meet tomorrow then.
Okay, see you tomorrow.
I'm so sorry
you had to stay
and play with  my son for so long.
Not at all.
Seeing how well
he's responding to the treatment,
I couldn't be happier.
We should thank Yifei.
After you left,
specialists continued
treating Xin Ba online.
This trip here is for him
to meet the specialists in person.
They said
Xin Ba's social communication skills
have improved
and are now on par with kids his age.
That's wonderful.
That means
he can make more friends from now on.
I remember he and Ji
had a falling out once.
Yes.
And there's even better news.
Yifei's company, Fulaxida,
has chosen our county
as the site for its pilot farm.
It's boosted the economy
of our entire county.
Next time you come,
you won't have to worry about
your car breaking down
on those remote mountain roads—
there are logistics trucks
coming and going every day now.
Fulaxida is Li Yifei's company?
Well, it's just a side venture for him.
But
he must be a major shareholder
of Fulaxida.
Look.
This was taken before we left.
Yifei brought
his new technology consultants
to our village.
He said they were going to
develop some kind of livestream app
for cattle, sheep, and so on.
It sounded pretty interesting.
I heard Yifei's company
has a technical partnership
with Mr. Lu's company.
That way, consumers
can log into the app directly
to check the agricultural products
they've ordered—
from the moment of
planting or birth,
through every stage of growth,
all the way to their dining table.
Isn't that wonderful?
He's so business-savvy.
My God. He's done so much all this time
without me even knowing.
In the same amount of time,
with all my effort,
I only went from one to ten,
while he went from ten to fifty.
Looking at it that way,
you should be proud too.
In the same amount of time,
you improved tenfold,
and he only improved fivefold.
As for my son,
he went from zero to one.
Even that small step
already feels like a great miracle to me.
Fei!
Xin Ba.
I'm happy.
-Happy?
-Say goodbye to Fei.
We're going back.
You're leaving already?
He has to get back to school.
Our flight is tonight.
And we hope
you'll come visit us sometime.
Definitely.
I'll see you off.
Okay.
[Anti-Scam Center Alert: If you
receive messages on short video platforms]
[or instant messaging apps like iMessage
from someone claiming to be a leader,]
[or a contact who says they've changed
their phone number, please stay alert.]
[Verify their identity immediately
to avoid fraud.]
It's been so many days,
and he hasn't contacted me at all.
[Pretentious Li]
[WeChat]
[Another fruitful day]
It feels like everyone
is revolving around you,
except me.
Like I'm the one being kept at a distance.
Hello.
Honey!
You look so silly, but handsome.
[Microphone On] [Speaker On] [Camera On]
You're the silly one.
I came to the greenhouse
to adjust the equipment.
So you missed me?
I missed you so much.
Let me tell you some gossip.
What is it?
Li Yifei
came all the way here,
and he's been completely lovesick
over Qian Fei.
But he doesn't even realize it.
So that's how it is.
I'm about to meet up with Fei.
Should I tell her?
[Microphone On] [Speaker On] [Camera On]
No, no, no.
Don't get involved in this.
Just let things happen naturally
between them.
If outsiders get involved,
it'll put a lot of pressure on them.
Alright then.
Trust me, I'm right.
Okay, I'm hanging up.
So I had to put down my phone every day,
cook alone,
check job listings alone,
do chores alone,
and say goodnight to the wall.
Then you felt lonely
and asked me out.
Actually...
You two are really interesting.
You...
He...
Me, him, me, him... Come on.
Can you just finish your sentence?
Don't you think you're acting like
someone who's either in love
or has just had their heart broken?
Why do you say that?
Because I'm picking up a different
vibe from you.
What are you, a dog?
I just feel so embarrassed.
I thought
that kiss between us was just a dream.
Now he's avoiding me,
using a business trip as an excuse
to run as far away as possible.
How am I supposed to get out of
such an awkward situation?
Fei,
honestly,
I'm certain you like him.
I've never thought about it.
Never thought about it?
What about now?
Let me think then.
I wouldn't exactly call it "liking" him.
It's just that...
it's pretty boring without him around.
Maybe I've just gotten used to
cooking for him.
Okay then.
Let me help you sort out your thoughts.
Let's set aside
whether you like him or not for now.
First, you have to admit
that he's not from the same world as us.
Look at what he eats, wears,
and plays with—
none of it's in your league.
Then what league is he in,
and what league am I in?
You?
Needless to say,
you're in the grassroots league.
But him?
He runs in the rich,
handsome, elite league.
People like him
have countless ways to make money.
Lu Ze told me
that Li Yifei invested a huge amount
in Fulaxida.
He sold his house.
Went all in.
Tens of millions invested just like that.
I heard
that the house was
actually bought by his dad.
Later, the house appreciated in value,
so he sold it
and invested the money.
Now, isn't he so broke that he has to
share an apartment with me?
Let's not talk about him anymore.
Let's talk about your Lu Ze.
He suddenly switched careers
to go into agriculture.
How did you manage to
talk yourself into supporting him?
Qian Fei,
can you focus a bit?
Where's your attention
wandering off to now?
I'm talking to you about Li Yifei,
and now you're bringing up
Lu Ze and agriculture?
Haven't you noticed you always do this?
Whenever the conversation gets to
what you really care about,
you change the subject.
I don't know what's going on with you two.
Anyway, I think
you should just take it one step at a time
and leave everything to time.
Wait and see.
I'll listen to you.
Wait and see,
and let nature take its course.
Thank you.
Oh, right.
Our class monitor called and said
Saturday is
the fifth-anniversary class reunion.
Our student affairs counselor
will be there too.
He asked whether everyone could make it.
No problem. I'll definitely be there.
But I think
he must have also called Wang Ruohai.
If he goes too, will you...
Will I what? Of course I won't.
I worked with him at Shanlifang
for quite some time.
You forgot?
That's good.
Anyway, I'll be out of town that day,
so I won't make a special trip back.
Say hello to everyone for me.
You're not going?
Then...
If you're not going,
won't I be alone?
Dealing with Wang Ruohai all by myself?
Why would you have to deal with him?
Listen,
if he tries to get close to you,
it's easy to handle.
Just slap him across the face.
Problem solved.
Your project is really good.
Nowadays, young people in the villages
have all gone out to work.
In our village alone,
there's
a huge amount of farmland lying idle.
If you can use it
for pilot fields
and agricultural development,
helping farmers increase their income,
that would truly be a tremendous service
to the community.
Village Chief, rest assured.
The whole purpose of this project
is to increase
the overall income of the farmers.
I believe that.
How is it?
It's Mr. Sang.
Look, those plots over there
and over there.
They need a bit more water
and are very fertile.
Yes.
It's all excellent farmland.
Yifei, I really have to push you on this.
The farmers out there are all waiting.
You mean the financing, right?
Yes.
Didn't you say a few days ago
that we should start further financing?
Are you now...
Ma Li,
I still think
it's too early to raise funding.
No, Yifei.
What do you mean?
You keep flip-flopping—
saying yes to financing one moment
and no the next.
What are you thinking exactly?
The person you met with a few days ago
was Mr. Sang, wasn't it?
Yeah.
Was there anyone else?
And Mr. Liao Jinshan.
Li Yifei, just say what you want to say.
Why does this feel like an interrogation?
Don't meet with Mr. Sang anymore.
You can't tell who's trustworthy.
You're going too far.
Wasn't Mr. Sang introduced to us
through your connections?
If you're denying him now,
you're denying yourself.
I admit I misjudged him this time.
But this time, I'm absolutely certain
that Mr. Sang approached Fulaxida
with an agenda
from the very beginning.
I don't know why you say that.
Maybe you have
your own reasons and judgment.
But what I want to say is,
no matter what you've heard,
when the farmers caused trouble
a few days ago,
if it hadn't been for Mr. Sang,
you and your silver tongue alone
might not have been enough to handle it.
I know what you mean.
You're saying Mr. Sang
paid off those farmers,
and that's why they agreed
-to cooperate with our project, right?
-Yeah. Since you know all that, why…
Ma Li.
Do you know that the farmers' protest
was arranged by Mr. Sang
from the very beginning?
Mr. Liao,
you're here.
Why didn't you call me in advance?
Let's talk in the car.
I'm just about to head to a meeting.
[Information on the Weibo account "0.33"]
Mr. Sang, your acting is superb.
That was a well-executed setup.
[Information on the Weibo account "0.33"]
Mr. Liao,
here's the information
we dug up on the Weibo account 0.33.
Mr. Liao, you're indeed
a veteran businessman—
moving this fast.
What do you mean?
Hello.
I'll be at the airport in an hour.
Help me compile all the cases
from the past 10 years
at Zhizhong Investment
where shareholders
were removed mid-project,
and send them to me.
No problem. Piece of cake.
I'll contact you when I land.
[Summary of Materials]
[on the Mid-Project Removal of Shareholders
in the Zhizhong Investment Project Team]
[Qian Fei]
[Dear passengers, your flight CY3357]
[is expected to depart
in approximately 90 minutes.]
[Please arrange your schedule accordingly]
[to avoid missing your flight.
We wish you a pleasant journey.]
Class Monitor.
Qian Fei?
You're Qian Fei?
Oh my gosh!
Did you get plastic surgery or something?
How did you become t-this gorgeous?
What do you mean, plastic surgery?
Even if I wanted to, I couldn't afford it.
Stop staring at me.
Besides, if I'd really had work done,
you wouldn't be able to tell anyway.
This reunion's
been eye-opening for me.
Everyone's done well for themselves,
especially Wang Ruohai.
But after seeing you,
I can already tell—
you're going to be the biggest surprise
of the night.
No contest.
Don't just stand there.
Come on. We've been waiting for you.
Let's go.
Wait a moment before going in.
Wait here.
Everyone!
Everyone,
open your eyes wide
and take a good look at who's here!
Come in.
Hello, everyone.
Isn't this Qian Fei?
Yes, Qian Fei!
Hello, Professor.
Sit, sit.
I haven't seen her for a long time.
Qian Fei, come on, sit.
So? So?
-Let's eat. Come on.
-Come on, let's dig in.
Come on, let's eat.
Eat up. The food's getting cold.
Well, everyone.
Every year,
seeing all of you again
brings me so much joy.
We only
had one couple in our whole class,
so I hope the two of you
stay together forever.
Professor Zhang, your information
is seriously out of date.
The two of them...
Professor Zhang, you're absolutely right.
Looking back now,
our college days
really were wonderful.
Back then, the love
was just pure love.
As long as you were
looking at the person you loved,
you could do nothing all day
and still smile foolishly the whole time.
Well, Ruohai,
are you trying to be a poet now?
Yeah!
Good! Good!
Well, that reminds me of back then too—
also at our university—
when I met my wife.
She was wearing a red dress,
standing by a tree.
[Wang Ruohai seems kinda weird today.]
At that moment, I remember thinking,
"How could this possibly be winter?
Spring has arrived."
Spring has arrived.
M-My biggest regret
about my college years
is never having had
a passionate, all-out romance.
So, to make up for that regret,
I've decided to marry a classmate.
[That bastard didn't
do anything to you, did he?]
[No, he didn't. It's just…]
[Anyway, he seems to regret it
and wants to get back together.]
Mei!
We're going to relive our youth together!
They are getting married?
You even kept it a secret from us, huh?
You hid it so well.
You really hid it well.
W-We'd like to toast everyone.
Come on.
Congratulations.
To our friendship—cheers!
Cheers!
Come on, come on.
Don't drink too much. Sit.
Fei.
Is there really no chance
for you and Wang Ruohai?
I can see Wang Ruohai
looking at you so affectionately.
He's clearly trying to
get back together with you.
Impossible.
Look at Mr. Wang now,
-he's way out of my league.
-Well, Ruohai,
you're doing the best out of all of us.
I heard that
after he broke up with that rich girl,
he landed a job at an even bigger company.
He's even paying for tonight's dinner.
Mei, Mei.
Let's toast to our teacher.
Professor Zhang
really took good care of us back then.
Come on, cheers.
Raise your glasses!
I remember this
used to be your favorite.
Thank you.
I heard you're treating today.
Seeing how lavish this spread is,
things really have changed.
No, no.
It's just that, thinking back,
I never took you
to eat anything good back in college.
I-I originally wanted to treat you alone,
but I figured you wouldn't come.
So, thanks to our classmates today,
I finally got the chance to see you.
Then you really were overthinking it.
Don't do this again.
Come on, everyone,
I've created a group chat for us.
Everyone, send your phone numbers there.
Now we all use WeChat
and rarely call each other anymore.
If someone's WeChat account
ever gets lost,
we won't be able to reach them, right?
Please pass me my phone.
I just sent a red package in the group chat.
Go grab it!
Whoever gets the biggest one
sends the next round.
[Has everyone shared their phone number?]
[Wang Ruohai]
[Blocked Contacts]
It really is God's will.
Even my phone couldn't stand Wang Ruohai
and automatically blacklisted him.
Why did you blacklist me?
Before, too many unimportant people
and things
took up my time.
Now I just want to clear them all out.
So you don't even want to keep in touch?
Even just as friends?
I don't even want to be friends.
I asked around.
I know you're single now.
That's why I went to all the trouble
of organizing today's reunion.
I'd already prepared myself for the worst.
I just want to make it up to you.
Don't bother.
Look,
aren't we both doing just fine now?
To be honest,
if it were the old me,
I'd still want you
to feel guilty for the rest of your life.
But now,
I just want
to be completely erased from your world.
Before, when I had nothing,
I thought the other half I needed
was someone who could understand me,
be considerate of me,
and even help me with my career.
But now I've realized
none of that really matters.
What I truly want is someone
to share life's joys and hardships with.
Being with someone I love
matters more than anything else.
Should I call my landlady?
Is she asleep or not?
It's been so many days.
Why hasn't she contacted me?
Why is she so stubborn?
Is she mad at me,
or has she simply
never thought about me at all?
[Job Openings]
I've finished my resume,
but there isn't a single job
I want to apply for.
It hasn't been that long.
Taking a month or two
to find a job is perfectly normal.
Take it easy.
I used to be anxious
because I had a mortgage to pay
and debts to clear.
Now I'm anxious because I want to find out
if there's actually a job out there,
purely in finance,
that I'd genuinely like.
Why don't you ask your tenant?
He's in the same industry as you,
and he has a lot of connections.
Maybe he can help you.
That's true.
I'll ask him.
[Pretentious Li]
Our current equity structure
[Fulaxida Equity Distribution]
is still fairly well balanced.
I have 34%,
and you have 33%.
Together,
that's 67%,
over the majority control threshold.
What does that mean?
It means we have complete authority
[Fulaxida Equity Distribution]
over major decisions
like amending the company charter,
splitting or merging the company,
changing business scope, and so on.
But
if we dilute our equity,
even by just 1%—
say,
[Fulaxida Equity Distribution]
down to 66%—
we'd lose absolute control
and fall into relative control,
where the threshold is just 51%.
Past that point,
any major company decisions
would need shareholder approval.
Got it?
Let it sink in first.
[When will you be back
from your business trip?]
I can't take it anymore.
My brain's about to explode.
[Don't know yet.]
The business world is like a battlefield—
that's just how it is.
Memorize it. Hurry up.
[Don't know yet.]
My fault. It's my fault.
I shouldn't have given you
that stupid advice.
I just shouldn't have contacted him first.
At this point,
if I still can't tell
he's been avoiding me,
then I really must be blind.
Majority control threshold, 67%.
What about 51%?
51% is...
Don't look over there.
I think I should just go farm.
I'm tired.
You haven't recovered from gastroenteritis.
Go rest.
I'll do it in a bit.
I've been fine for ages.
Didn't I help her with the birthday event?
These notebooks are new as well.
Send them to the kids too?
And these clothes,
along with that old computer.
Pack them all up and send them.
Xin You said
the kids over there
really need these things.
Okay.
Then let's send this batch first.
Later, we can ask our friends
and coworkers to donate as well.
We should be able to gather another batch.
I alone can rally enough donations
to fill several truckloads.
Yeah, you're the best at that.
Of course.
Anyway, there's strength in numbers.
So, how's your exam prep going?
I already listed all my exam prep books
on Goofish.
Why?
You're not taking the exam anymore?
I thought you were seriously
preparing for it since you quit your job.
That's why I never asked.
How could you just decide not to take it?
See?
I told you she'd react exactly like this.
You knew all along?
You guys really don't need to worry.
It's a registration-based system now.
In the past,
any sponsor
could make over a million a year
and rake in huge signing fees.
Things are different now.
Besides passing the exam,
you can also get directly recommended
by an investment bank.
You mean,
once you join a new company,
you'll have them recommend you instead?
That's one option.
But you really need to think it through.
This kind of job isn't something
you can just find whenever you want.
You've tried before.
I can give you a research report
or something,
but beyond that, I can't really help you
with other companies.
Don't worry.
This time, I'm fully prepared.
The kid's all grown up.
As long as you've thought it through.
I still have a part-time job at the mall.
This is almost done. You guys keep at it.
Gotta go.
Your time management is...
Hold on, hold on.
What?
Take the trash out on your way out.
Remember to eat!
-Okay.
-Your stomach isn't very good.
I'll ask around for you on my way.
Okay, okay, bye.
Bye, be careful on your way.
I didn't realize I had so many clothes.
Let me see.
When you get the chance,
just pack up the clothes and shoes
you don't need
and send them to me.
Okay, hanging up.
Dang.
Auntie.
We bumped into each other again.
We really have a special bond.
H-How's your stomach now?
Are you feeling any better?
With a body like mine,
I've long since recovered.
Um...
Our program won first prize.
Did Jun tell you?
He told me.
I have to say, that day, I really...
I really admired you.
You were so sick,
yet you still gave it everything you had.
It was so touching.
I'm part of the team too.
I couldn't let my condition
affect you or the rest of the team.
And I certainly couldn't let
all the months Jun put into
preparing for the dance competition
go unrewarded.
That last part is
the most important, right?
That's
what mattered most to you too, isn't it?
You girl.
Well, I'd better get going, Auntie.
Come over when you have time.
I'll make you
those shepherd's purse wontons.
They're really delicious.
Okay. I'll definitely come
and try them sometime.
Okay.
Goodbye, Auntie.
[In the next episode
of "Love Has Fireworks"]
What exactly do you want, Wang Ruohai?
[Let's start over. Wang Ruohai]
I just want you
to unblock me.
Looks like it worked.
I had dinner
with some business partners yesterday
and drank a little too much,
so I didn't hear my phone ring.
I just wanted to use this trip
to really sort out
my thoughts once and for all.
Look at me.
Right now,
tell me,
how do you feel?
All I ever think about is seeing her.