[alarm beeps]
[theme music playing]
THIS IS A WORK OF FICTION
CHILD ACTORS WERE FILMED SAFELY
WITH SUPERVISION
Si-woo, why did you push back
on the ice sphere project?
I told you to just run the project
you prepared as Team Lead.
I couldn't just overlook it.
[chuckles] Classic Kang Si-woo.
Well, we were handing that project
to a task force anyway.
Use this chance to put a team together.
I'll make sure the plan stays on track.
You'd better.
Both of our careers are depending on it.
Earn that promotion
and you're on your way back to the States.
Ma'am.
But to do that.
there's something you really need.
People.
[carefree music plays]
That one's pretty tricky.
Should we try something else?
No way.
I need to get through it.
[grunting]
CLIMBING - SHOWER
TEA - SUPPLEMENTS
RECRUITING CHA JI-YOON
CREATIVITY, PEOPLE SKILLS
ROBOT VACUUM CLEANER
VACUUMING DUST
CHAMOMILE
[Ji-yoon] Good morning.
Good morning, Mr. Ko. Everything good?
Oh. Good morning, Ms. Cha
Huh?
[Young-sam] What the… What?
Why are you going that way? Wrong way.
Huh?
[groans]
Sr. Associate Cha Ji-yoon, checking in.
I'd like to apply for the task force.
["Hopping" plays]
I look forward to this.
I look forward to it too.
[workers chattering]
Hey, Ms. Cha! You…
["Hopping" continues]
[sighs] I made the right decision, right?
[Si-woo] Anxiety, unease, worry, doubt.
Mr. Kang.
Caffeine only makes those symptoms worse.
Chamomile, on the other hand,
contains antioxidants
with a calming effect.
That's why you should drink this.
CHAMOMILE
What I heard was
it stimulates the nervous system,
and therefore
has the effect of improving your focus.
This is all sugar, oligosaccharides,
and coconut oil.
The coffee content, for better or worse,
is just 13.3%.
Hmm. What's surprising
is that this little packet
contains 6.4 grams of sugar.
15% of your daily intake.
Two of them, 30%.
[Ji-yoon] Classic marketing tactic
that triggers consumer anxiety
by exploiting a weakness.
Could you pour me a cup?
Happy to.
[sighs] He reeled me right in.
The launch has been pushed a month.
A month? But we've already lost a week.
Yes,
because someone kept avoiding me.
With the time we have left,
we have to be able
to make the perfect ice sphere.
-Would that be possible?
-We shouldn't ask if it is.
We have to make it possible.
[whimsical music plays]
[Ji-yoon] Well, that's all well and good…
but how?
[groans] Ew. What is that taste?
EPISODE 3
SICK OR NOT, STILL CLOCKING IN!
[Ji-yoon] There isn't a single pen
or even a memo pad.
Not even a speck of dust.
WATER FLOSSER, HAND SANITIZER,
DEODORIZER, RUBBING ALCOHOL
I bet his teeth are pristine too.
It's super weird if he smiles,
and weird if he doesn't.
It's super weird if he talks,
KANG SI-WOO
[Si-woo]
Do you have something you need to say?
[Ji-yoon] There's no one else here.
Why is he using messenger?
I don't. Thanks for asking.
[keyboard clacking]
TAP TAP TAP TAP TAP TAP
[Ji-yoon] I've dealt with all kinds
of bosses over the last seven years,
but this guy's a whole new breed.
TAP TAP TAP TAP TAP TAP
[Si-woo] Please change your keyboard
to a silent keyboard.
It's distracting.
It's distracting. [echoes]
[Ji-yoon] Sure!
[thunder rumbling]
[Ji-yoon] I guess that dark cloud
gets bigger when he's working.
Let's go down to the lab.
-The test results are in.
-Test results?
[Ji-yoon] This is… It can't be.
As you said, Mr. Kang, freezing it
drop by drop from the bottom up
did make it clearer.
[sighs] It hurts my pride to admit it,
but I have to hand it to you.
How did you come up with this?
Just like ice spikes.
I figured freezing it slowly,
drop by drop,
like an icicle, would make it clearer.
-Wait, that's…
-[clears throat]
You thought that if you did,
you'd get shut down like at the factory,
or have your idea stolen
like it was today.
[Ji-yoon] Did I get played again?
I thought he'd be a bit different.
That's right, it was her idea.
[gasps] Ice spikes! How about that?
Do you mean reverse icicles?
Yes! Icicles are clear, right?
Can't we just make them like that instead?
[Si-woo]
The one you ignored at the factory.
[team lead]
Oh, of course. Yeah, back then.
That's right.
You mentioned it, didn't you?
[chuckles] Oh, gosh,
if we had just listened to you back then,
we wouldn't have wasted so much time.
Sorry about that, Ms. Cha.
Oh, it's all good.
Oh, right.
[sighs]
It's not there yet.
Let's recalibrate it.
Speed and temperature.
All right.
[Ji-yoon] I really can't tell…
if he's a good person… or a bad person.
[researcher] Ms. Cha.
Would you take a look at these over here?
Sure.
Draft a progress report
on how the project is going.
Where the project is and how we got here.
-Yes, sir.
-[Young-sam] Ms. Cha.
You think you can leave a few scraps
of paper and just walk away? Huh?
Ever heard of a proper handover?
I've already sent every single file
and document I had over email.
Did you forget about
the executive briefing on Monday?
I mean, shouldn't you have at least
drafted up a report before you left?
Isn't it standard for the presenter
to write the report?
On our team, the best person
for the job does it.
Oh!
You wouldn't get it.
You don't know what teamwork is.
Ms. Cha Ji-yoon
is now part of the task force.
If she's in a team, it will be with me.
She not done with the work
she's supposed to do for me yet.
You may be leaving,
but at least wrap up the work you started.
You don't actually think taking on
everyone's work makes you responsible,
or do you?
But it's just the work
Ms. Cha has always done.
Yeah, and it's the work
that you're supposed to be doing.
-Why, you little…
-[Ji-yoon] Hold on a sec. Please hold on.
I will get both the progress report and
executive report done over the weekend.
Would that be all right?
I believe I already told you
that we don't have much time left.
If I don't do it,
then he'll make someone else do it.
I don't want to cause trouble for others.
Taking on extra work causes trouble too.
Learn to prioritize and stay focused.
[Ji-yoon sighs] I'm the fool for getting
my hopes up, even for a moment.
GOO-WON
[No-ah] I guess you're still very busy
I'll head down to Pohang tomorrow.
What are you doing?
[No-ah] I feel so bad for Ms. Cha,
I don't know what to do.
Leave her be.
She dug her own grave.
I'm off.
[sibling] No-ah!
[groans]
[coworker 1] That's her?
I think that I would be eating at home
every day too. Wow.
Does she happen
-to have a boyfriend?
-Oh, geez.
[coworker 1]
Man, your sister's so beautiful.
My sister's engaged to someone.
What the hell, Da-ra?
What are you doing here?
And what the hell are you wearing?
I was gaming nearby
and thought I'd just swing by for dinner.
There's nothing good around here.
Hey. Isn't there a tteokbokki place?
How many times do I have to tell you?
Tteokbokki is a calorie bomb?
Well, fine, we'll go eat something else.
Let's go.
SPHERE ICE REFRIGERATOR
DEVELOPMENT
[relaxed music plays]
-♪ Way back home, way back home ♪
-[sighs]
♪ I'm the happiest when I clock out ♪
[music stops]
I just sent you the progress report, sir.
Right.
All right then. I'm done.
I'll be clocking out now.
What is it?
I'm done. I do go home too.
[curious music plays]
[Ji-yoon] 10:12 p.m.
I'm avoiding this exact time at all costs.
You should sit down.
I'm fine like this.
Right.
Do you always…
get off work and leave at this time?
-It depends on the day.
-Oh.
That's a problem.
[chuckles] I mean, that must be tough.
[sighs] This is awkward as hell.
[electronic voice]
We are approaching Wonam-dong.
-Next, Korea Corporation.
-Oh, Mr. Kang?
You're getting off at this stop,
aren't you?
Oh, no,
I did plenty of cardio this morning.
What?
I only get off here
on days I miss my workout.
Then when on earth do you rest?
Isn't working out a form of rest?
Huh?
[scoffs]
[chuckles]
Mr. Kang, you're so…
…so not compatible with me.
That's just impressive.
Hmm.
You really don't have to walk me home.
I'm not walking you home.
This is my way home.
Right.
[Ji-yoon] Should I move then?
But my lease isn't close to being up.
How long have you lived in this area?
-It's been about two years now.
-Mmm.
So you must have moved here
-while I was in the States.
-Mmm.
So you've always lived in this area too?
Do you live alone?
Good night to you.
Sir?
Sure.
Have a good night.
[sighs]
[groans]
I'm wiped. [sighs]
[groans] Just one day together,
and I'm already totally exhausted.
How am I going to cope?
Today is Friday.
Ah, I should be eating fried chicken.
Were you waiting long?
Mmm.
That's why I told you
not to come here unannounced.
So, Goo-won,
do you happen to know why I like you?
Because seeing you puts me at ease.
7 YEARS AGO
At first,
I regretted seeing you every single time.
[sighs]
I shouldn't have come.
I thought you were kind of clumsy
and uncool.
And that you were not really
my type at all.
Were you waiting long?
[chuckles] No.
-Ouch! Ah, that's hot!
-Are you okay?
God, that's hot!
[Goo-won] Here, use this.
[chuckles] Thank you.
Uh, you're the first guy I've ever seen
who actually carries a handkerchief.
Hold on a second.
When we first met it was raining out,
so I wanted to ask you out on a sunny day.
[gentle music plays]
I like you,
No-ah.
[No-ah] When you told me how you felt,
totally sober and with some random excuse,
it put my mind at ease.
Mmm.
[sighs] But now…
when I look at you these days,
I feel uneasy.
No-ah.
They say everyone gets cold feet
before marriage.
Let's think of this as a bump in the road.
But I just fell in love with someone else.
I'm sorry.
I didn't expect this either.
Did you cheat on me?
It's not like that.
She doesn't even know I like her.
And I'm not telling her.
But how could I keep seeing you,
when I'm feeling like this?
If we were to get married…
I'd just be lying to you.
Does your mother even know
that you cheated on me?
I already told you, I didn't cheat on you.
Since moving down here,
you've only come up to Seoul once,
even though I'm way busier than you!
But I always was the one feeling guilty
for not being there enough for you
and for making you feel all alone here.
I'm trying my best
to be as honest as I can.
You know me,
I'm a pathetically slow idiot.
This isn't easy for me to say.
If it isn't easy,
then you shouldn't have said a word.
You're losing me, but I'm losing you too!
Then you shouldn't have betrayed me then!
It's over, No-ah.
My feelings for you are gone.
[sad music plays]
[sighs]
[breathing shakily]
What do you think you're doing right now?
I'm begging you right now.
I'll forgive you but…
take it back.
No-ah, just get up.
Then just tell me
you didn't mean what you said.
What? She's on her knees, begging him.
What's going on?
[patron] Oh, my gosh. [gasps]
I'm sorry.
I'll carry this guilt forever.
I feel like she's crazy
That was so awkward.
[crying]
[in French]
You should cover up your tears.
[dramatic music plays]
[sighs] This will never, ever end.
Double duty. Serving two masters.
Not for the faint of heart.
[yawning]
[sighs]
[gasps]
It's eight o'clock?
My whole weekend's just gone like that?
Oh, no. Oh, no.
I can't let my Sunday evening
end like this.
[calm music plays]
[phone buzzing]
SEUNG-JUN
Hi, Seung-jun.
Is Ga-eul with you by any chance?
Why on earth would I be with Ga-eul?
[sighs] I knew this would happen.
[groans] Then where did he go?
He has nowhere else to go.
What are you talking about?
Well, I mean,
that punk pulled the deposit
from the place he was staying at
-to put out an album.
-What?
Well, he's been crashing at my place,
but my girlfriend showed up
out of the blue
Ji-yoon, he's a fool.
Ga-eul put everything into this album
to win you back.
♪ Only looking at you ♪
[guitar music plays]
♪ Only thinking about you ♪
♪ That kind of thing ♪
♪ Is so hard for me ♪
♪ Like a cat ♪
♪ I find myself running backward ♪
♪ Again today ♪
♪ But the truth is
I love you so much ♪
♪ My heart that beats so hard for you ♪
♪ And my lips are running ♪
♪ Toward you ♪
[gasps] I love it.
It's just so amazing.
-Really?
-Yeah.
We need to drop an album with this title.
Uh, no. No.
First, let's film and upload a video
so we can generate some buzz.
All right, sing it again. Come on.
It's not done yet.
What do you mean it's not done?
It's amazing just the way it is.
The chords are awkward,
and the lyrics are sloppy.
It needs polishing.
Argh, come on.
We just need to release this right now.
You. Do you know I'm on
the Product Planning Team or not, huh?
Just trust me on this.
Oh, geez. It's not ready yet,
Sr. Associate Cha Ji-yoon.
I have a good feeling about this!
[sad music plays]
[sighs]
See?
It's too late now.
[phone buzzing]
CHO GA-EUL
[Ga-eul]
I'm finally done composing our song.
Have a listen.
♪ I don't know when it began ♪
♪ Your gaze made every part of me ♪
[gentle music plays]
You are very late.
I'm sorry, sir.
[sniffles]
Is something wrong?
Oh. No, sir.
[sniffles]
[Sang-won] Ms. Cha,
could you send me
the executive report as well?
[Ji-yoon] Sure.
CHA JI-YOON
[Si-woo] Ms. Cha.
Ms. Cha Ji-yoon.
Yes?
Run a profit-and-loss simulation
adjusted for the new launch date,
and send the report over to me.
Yes, sir. Right away.
-Ms. Cha?
-Yes?
I think you're gonna need to
resend the file you just sent.
Why?
You sent me last month's report.
[chuckles]
I'll send it again right away.
Thanks.
[sighs]
[sniffles]
I can't take this.
I never make mistakes like these.
SALES PRICE
AND PROFIT STRUCTURE ANALYSIS
Ms. Cha Ji-yoon.
Yes?
Did you double-check the profit-and-loss
simulation before sending it?
Is there a problem with the report?
You missed a zero on both
the retail price and the wholesale price.
SALES PRICE
AND PROFIT STRUCTURE ANALYSIS
I'm sorry, sir. I'll revise it immediately
and resend it.
[sighs]
Let's step outside.
[coworker]
She's getting dragged away. Look.
-Oh, dear.
-Oh, poor thing.
They're looking. They're looking.
They're looking.
It appears that I misjudged you.
If I had known
that this was how you worked,
I wouldn't have offered you the job.
I'm sorry, sir.
If it's too much for you,
I can transfer you
to another team right now.
It's not, sir.
Making one mistake is enough.
Repeated mistakes are not mistakes.
It shows their lack of competence.
I will… make sure not to disappoint again.
Right. Make sure you don't.
[sighs]
[somber music plays]
DIGESTIVE DRINK
[doctor] It's boss-sickness.
Boss-sickness, you said?
The reason I came here
was just because of mild indigestion.
Your heart races
the second you hear their footsteps,
you want to hide
the moment you cross paths,
and you immediately get suspicious
when they show any kindness.
Your stomach is in knots
because of them too, right?
[chuckles] I mean,
I guess you're right, but--
Everyone comes here
with different symptoms,
and the same diagnosis.
It's boss-sickness.
Oh, right.
CLINIC CHART: PALPITATIONS,
DIFFICULTY BREATHING, INDIGESTION
No-ah?
[No-ah] Oh.
She has something similar.
Ms. Cha.
[No-ah] We were together for seven years,
but breaking up
didn't even take seven days.
Some people have crushes for eight years
and then start dating
in just eight minutes.
He walked off without even helping me up.
That's when I realized…
[sighs]
…it's really over now.
I think I always knew though
that it would turn out like this.
I just pretended I didn't.
Because you thought
that once you got married,
you would get over that.
I keep having the strangest thoughts.
"I don't want to be happier than you.
I just wanna see you
more miserable than me."
[both chuckle]
I guess we both really are sick.
I'm sorry, Ms. Cha.
Huh?
To be honest,
I never really understand you before.
How so?
You go straight home after work,
you don't really take care of yourself,
and you have no interest at all in men.
So maybe you are staking everything
on a promotion?
But that's not it either.
Ah, I can't even argue with any of that.
[both chuckle]
But no,
I think I had you all wrong.
I realized it when you stood your ground
with Mr. Ko on my behalf.
You knew I was lying and yet
you still chose to look the other way.
You work hard
not because you wanna get promoted,
but because you wanna protect your pride.
[sighs] They were all assumptions,
and I knew nothing about you.
Ms. Cha Ji-yoon, you're awesome.
[both chuckle]
Damn it, I have a soft spot for praises.
In that case, can I call you big sis?
-Big sis?
-Mm-hmm.
Anyone that's this cool is a big sis.
[both laughing]
You're here early.
Yes, Mr. Kang.
Good morning to you.
SPHERE ICE REFRIGERATOR
FINAL FOR REAL
SENT
MESSAGE RECEIVED
[Ji-yoon]
I've reworked the product concept
to highlight the icicle theme
we've been working on.
Once you sign off,
I'll share it with the PR team.
SPHERE ICE REFRIGERATOR
"THE AESTHETICS OF COLDNESS"
INSPIRED BY
REVERSE ICICLE TECHNOLOGY
You should also revise the schedule.
I've also copied the email
to the Development Team.
Okay. All right then.
[lively music plays]
-Wow.
-Well? It's clear now, isn't it?
How did you do it?
Well, we used a controller
so we could fine-tune
the cooling speed and temperature.
I think that this is good enough
to launch right now.
It's not ready yet.
-Wh-What?
-They have to be clearer.
Come on, it's a residential fridge.
How can we make them
any clearer than this?
C-Come on now.
Let's try one more time, Mr. Kim.
Whatever. [clicks tongue]
You got it! You got it!
[chuckles] Good luck.
Our development schedule
has less than two weeks left.
From here on out,
we need to focus on the final details.
If we were going to settle for that,
I wouldn't have formed a task force.
Then we'll have to push back the launch.
For better quality, we should.
[Ji-yoon] No matter what, I'm clocking out
right on time and ordering fried chicken.
I'm ordering cheese balls too.
Anyone who tries to stop me will pay.
Do you have plans tonight?
Huh?
With fried chicken and cheese balls.
No.
Then let's go for a drink.
Sorry?
Here you go. The highballs you ordered.
[jazz music playing]
Wow.
Those are super clear.
The ice for ice balls are very different.
Apparently, it's made by
slowly freezing it over 48 hours
at a warmer temperature
than standard freezers usually have.
Oh.
Please, try it.
Thank you.
Wow.
It's… It's so delicious.
[bartender] Well, now you're spoiled.
Once you've had my highball,
you won't be able to drink anything else.
This guy knows how to mix drinks.
From cocktails to highballs of course.
And soju bombs!
[Ji-yoon chuckles]
That's why I only drink it neat
anywhere else.
Once your standards are set high,
it's impossible to lower them at all.
Yeah, like with these ice balls?
Exactly.
Mr. Kang, you're being a bit unfair.
What?
So you're pretty much telling me
that you deliberately spoiled my palate
just to convince me, is that it?
I may have overstepped.
[chuckles]
I was joking.
So, now that I've seen it for myself,
I can see the difference. Mmm.
You're right, Mr. Kang.
Let's try our best
to make it super clear
in the time we have left.
Cheers.
[Ji-yoon sighs]
[Si-woo] Tell me. What happened yesterday?
Oh.
Sorry, that will never happen again.
You know,
breakups don't put food on the table.
Did you break up again?
Sir?
During your blind date
and that time you got drunk,
I recall you saying that you broke up.
So what I mean is,
after putting off the breakup forever,
now I finally got over it with…
So, what I'm trying to say is
that my breakup will no longer
be affecting my work or anything else.
Right.
Breakups are my strength.
[Ji-yoon] Mr. Kang might just
be someone who can actually understand me.
[gentle music playing]
A while ago…
[inhales deeply] …a friend of mine
wrote a song that was about us.
Mmm.
I really loved that song,
but he refused to release it to the world,
saying he wasn't done with it yet.
But then yesterday morning,
that friend sent me
the finished version of the song.
Each note in the song
was deliberately more
refined and polished than before.
But I still prefer the version of the song
I heard back then.
It may have been a little rough
and unpolished…
but it felt fresh at the time.
I kept thinking, "What if he had
released the song back then?
And if he had,
would things be different between us?"
Those regrets
just wouldn't leave me alone.
Is your ex-boyfriend a singer then?
Wait, that's not the point
I'm trying to make right now.
I know.
You're saying timing is important.
But at this stage,
quality is a priority.
So, does that mean
I can try doing it my way?
And what would that be?
You know that story, right?
Where the sun and the wind
bet on who can make the traveler
take off his coat.
Do you mean the fable?
Tell you what, you can be the wind,
and I'll be the sun.
[chuckles]
Not quite.
[researcher sighs]
[Jae-won] What? Why did it fail?
[groans] What's wrong with Mr. Kang?
Should we just say we can't do it?
Who says we can't do it? Let's try again.
-Go.
-Yes, sir.
["Hopping" plays]
COOLING PLATE TEMPERATURE
COOLING SPEED
GAS FLOW?
Wake up, everyone.
We have nine hours until the next test.
-Come on.
-[groans]
FINAL FOR REAL
[song ends]
Not quite.
Wait. Do you think
Mr. Kang's eyesight's failing?
They're identical.
It's mine that's failing.
-Happy?
-[chuckles]
[groans] Damn it.
Oh, Mr. Kim, you'll shatter a tooth.
[knocking]
Mr. Kang.
You asked to see me?
We need to vent the gas from the top.
Sir?
The reason the ice freezes opaquely
is because of traces of gas in it.
We freeze it slowly from the bottom
to let the ice crystals grow,
and then we let the gas out
through the top,
-just like I've done here.
-Oh.
Yes. That would
definitely make them clearer.
Hurry over and let the team know.
Sir.
Mr. Kang.
-Are you all right?
-Sorry?
It's nothing.
I'll let the development team know.
[Ji-yoon] Mr. Kang,
this one is very low in calories.
And this one's so yummy
that someone could drop dead next to you
and you wouldn't notice.
[lighthearted music playing]
Snacks that won't make you fat.
[chuckles]
["After Work" playing]
That's right.
The stress you get from earning money
is best relieved by spending it.
Bananas.
BANANAS
13,400 WON
Geez, if the price gap in these two
is this small,
how do people living alone
not feel cheated?
[scoffs]
[sighs]
[exclaims] Oh.
Oh. Mr. Kang.
Doing some grocery shopping?
Yes. How about you, sir?
Same.
Well, enjoy your shopping, then.
Thank you.
KOREAN MILK
2-PACK
If you buy the two-pack
it isn't any cheaper
You would save 14 cents per carton though.
Yeah, but if I buy a two-pack,
I never finish the second
before it expires.
Yes, you end up taking a bigger loss
just to save a few cents.
Yes, exactly.
-Do you…
[song continues]
Mr. Kang!
These are buy-one-get-one-free!
Pretty good deal, right?
Indeed.
Anything else you need?
Oh. The sparkling water that you like
is cheaper in bulk.
Let's go.
I'll take that.
[song ends]
[Ji-yoon] There isn't
a single speck of dust.
I didn't know you actually had a car.
I only drive when I have to.
Oh, I see.
Should we play music?
Sure.
[melancholic music playing]
Oh. That's Yoo Jae-ha.
It's quite an old song, but you know it.
Oh. My dad loved this song.
He would always play it at his store.
The woman I used to live with
also liked this song.
Would that be Ms. Choi?
My mother.
Sorry about that.
I promise I won't tell anyone
that you were married before.
It's all right.
I wouldn't have told you about it
if it bothered me.
You know that you seem like
a different person outside of the office?
What do you mean?
I mean you're actually quite friendly.
[chuckles]
I can't have
my only team member running away.
[chuckles]
I knew it. You just see me
as a corporate slave, right?
Well, that's you and me both.
I guess you're right.
We're corporate slaves,
serving the same lord.
Even so, your paycheck is definitely
a lot bigger than mine.
-Quite a lot bigger.
-[chuckles]
I wanted to ask,
what did you mean by that?
Sorry?
You asked if I was okay.
Mr. Kang.
Are you all right?
Oh…
I think that… that
you've always fought your battles alone.
So I felt like you must've been lonely.
Because even if
it's a path that you chose,
it must get lonely
if no one's there to support you.
Thank you
for saying all that.
I don't really have a choice.
As I'm the only person on your team,
I figured that at the very least,
I should be on your side. [chuckles]
[chuckles]
Thank you so much, Mr. Kang.
Thanks to you,
I saved a lot of money today. [chuckles]
I enjoyed it too.
Which floor are you on?
I'm on the second floor.
Oh, but I can take it from here.
[Ga-eul] I'll take them.
-[Ji-yoon] What are you doing?
-It's heavy.
I'll just leave it at your door.
Do you know who that guy is?
Yes.
My ex-boyfriend, Ga-eul.
Oh.
Right, well then
I'll get going now.
Uh… Would you mind…
staying with me just for a little while?
You're back home early for once.
Were you waiting this whole time?
Mm-hmm. I have something for you.
Would you mind leaving us?
I have to speak with Ji-yoon.
No, I can't,
I have something to tell her too.
Please go ahead.
He's my boss. We have to talk about work.
I'm Kang Si-woo.
[Ga-eul] Oh, what a shame.
I don't have a business card for you.
My name is Cho Ga-eul.
Yeah, nice to meet you.
Please take good care of my Ji-yoon.
And try not to overwork her.
Ms. Ji-yoon is not the type of person
to listen to me
even if I ask.
[Ji-yoon] "Ms. Ji-yoon"?
I'm well aware.
My Ji-yoon can be stubborn.
That's why I'm asking this of you.
You had something to say?
Go ahead.
Here. A ticket to my concert.
[tender music playing]
BAND GA-EUL 1ST LIVE CONCERT
[Ga-eul] Come see what I've been doing
for the last eight months
and also the kind of mindset
I've come back with.
I'm busy these days,
so I probably won't make it.
Please let her finish early
on the day of my concert.
Cho Ga-eul. Hey.
That's not for me to decide though,
but for Ms. Ji-yoon to decide.
Hear that? It's up to you to decide.
I'll be waiting.
I'm sorry, sir.
I know that was a hard favor
to ask of you.
Not at all.
Well, get home safely.
Sure.
[car door opens]
[door closes]
[engine starts]
[music fades]
[sighs]
BAND GA-EUL 1ST LIVE CONCERT
All right, let's wrap it up.
We're done with development.
[all exclaiming]
It's finally over!
Gosh, thank you for all your hard work.
Mr. Kang, you really are ruthless,
you know that?
Yeah, but still, we ended up with results
everyone can be proud of.
Thank you for all your hard work.
Shouldn't we be
celebrating this achievement
with good food and good alcohol today?
Don't you know
Mr. Kang doesn't do team dinners?
Let's go by ourselves and not
make things uncomfortable for everyone.
Let's do it. Let's go out.
Actually, it'll be my treat.
[chuckles]
Well, if you don't want to…
Who said we didn't?
-Let's do it! Let's do it! Let's go!
-[all chuckling]
Let's do it!
Let's go. [chuckling]
["Let Them Boys Play" playing]
-Cheers!
-Drink up!
I can't remember
the last time we did this.
Wow, we all worked really hard, didn't we?
Oh, we should've taken something
for the hangover before this.
Totally forgot.
I can go and get some.
Come with me.
Sorry?
Right. [clears throat]
-[Si-woo] We'll be right back.
-Hurry back.
Was the concert today?
Oh…
Yes.
Going to your
ex-boyfriend's concert. [sighs]
Maybe I'm old-school
but I can't understand why.
We were friends for a long time
before we started dating.
But doesn't all that usually end
when you break up with them?
Was it like that? When you broke up?
When it ended, did you just cut all ties
and never look back?
Yes.
Do you still have feelings for him?
Oh, no.
It's not that.
Don't know what it is
I'm feeling exactly.
Then you should go and find out.
Sorry?
Once you stop running from it,
you'll understand what you really feel.
[people chattering]
Everyone's here now.
All right, shall we…
have some fun?
[cheering]
[romantic music playing]
-♪ Right here, right now ♪
♪ Where I am standing ♪
♪ Where exactly is this place? ♪
♪ My beating heart ♪
♪ The footsteps I'm running with ♪
♪ Where exactly are they headed? ♪
♪ No one tells me ♪
[Ji-yoon] It was only natural for me
to fall for someone like you.
For someone like me,
who drifted through life as it came,
you were like a special being
from a totally different universe
♪ To have you by my side ♪
♪ Come closer to me ♪
[sighs]
We need Ms. Cha
to make things fun around here.
That's right.
Sorry, sir.
Why did you let Ms. Cha go home?
[sighs]
Right. [clicks tongue, inhales deeply]
I guess I shouldn't have let her go.
Shall… Shall we say last round?
When we'd add a song to this album,
I moved to a smaller home.
[crowd] Aw.
One day,
I was really craving bingsu,
but had no money.
So then, I took it from my girlfriend's
piggy bank, and she didn't know.
[people chuckling]
[Ga-eul] I made the smallest incision
and pulled off the perfect crime.
I thought that no one would ever notice.
But the next day,
the piggy bank was replaced…
with one you could just open
any time that you needed to.
[crowd] Aw.
[Ga-eul] So if it weren't for her,
I would've struggled too much
and may have given up on music.
I will play this last song
in the hope that one day I'll be able to
fill her piggy bank back up.
This is "Like a Cat."
[cheering]
[romantic music playing]
♪ I don't know when it began ♪
♪ Your gaze made ♪
♪ Every part of me breathe ♪
♪ This fluttering heart of mine ♪
♪ Was already ballooning up ♪
♪ Your lips and your breath
Made it burst ♪
♪ Only looking at you ♪
-[cat meows]
-[Ji-yoon] Oh, my God.
-[laughs]
-[Ga-eul chuckles]
-Aw, look at you.
-[Ji-yoon] Hi, sweetie.
-Oh.
-Oh, my goodness.
Go on. Eat it. Eat up.
In the future, when we're married,
let's live in a house
where we can have a cat.
We can just take this one home now
and raise it.
Ga-eul.
Do you not like marriage?
Uh…
It's not that I don't.
It's just too serious for me.
Also marriage and living together
are just the same.
Even without the contract,
we can stay together. And be happy too.
[cat meows]
♪ That kind of thing ♪
♪ Is so hard for me, like a cat ♪
♪ I find myself running backward ♪
♪ Again today ♪
♪ The truth is, I love you so much ♪
♪ My heart that beats for you so hard ♪
♪ And my lips are running ♪
♪ Toward you ♪
♪ I just look at you again today ♪
[Ga-eul] Heading to the winter sea.
I'll come back with a killer song.
Love you.
Jeong-sik founded a music school in Busan.
Going to check it out for a few days!
BUSAN MUSIC ACADEMY
Yes, that's the way. Let's see…
Seoraksan is calling me!
[employer] Great work.
Oh. Thank you.
MOUNT SEORAK WATER
Take care.
[Ji-yoon] I warned you,
you absolutely cannot be late today!
Are you off the bus yet? Where are you?
GA-EUL,
WILL YOU MARRY ME?
[commentator] The ball just keeps going!
The runner on second base heads to third.
[Ga-eul]
Ji-yoon, I'm heading off on a trip.
I know you said you had something
to tell me today. Sorry.
[commentator] …way back.
It's clear over the left field wall!
Oh, it's a grand slam!
It's a grand slam! Home run…
This sucks.
WILL YOU MARRY ME?
[Ji-yoon] What was the answer I was really
hoping to hear from Ga-eul that day?
Did I want to see a happy face,
or did I expect to see a troubled one?
What I probably wanted
was the end to our relationship,
whether that meant marriage or a breakup.
I don't know.
I just wanted Ga-eul
to be the one to decide.
[song continues]
♪ It's not easy ♪
♪ Even though I want it ♪
[song ends]
[phone chimes, ringing]
[Ji-yoon] Ga-eul.
In the end, we were different people.
I was always worried
about a future that never came,
while you
always sang about today.
I'll cheer for that dream
that you fulfilled out in the world,
without me by your side.
Goodbye,
my first love.
Let's start over.
I can't be without you.
Let's get married, Ji-yoon.
[cries]
[chimes]
[chuckles]
CHA JI-YOON 1. CREATIVITY
2. INTERPERSONAL SKILLS
3. POTENTIAL 4. UNIQUE ABILITY
[sighs]
SHE MAKES ME LAUGH
CHA JI-YOON
[grunting, breathing heavily]
[grunts]
That's right!
Yeah! Great work.
[Ji-yoon] Oh! Hold that, please!
You're here early.
Yes.
And your eyes are puffy.
[chuckles] Yes.
Are you back together?
No.
It's the final, final, final goodbye.
So
I assume that you're free this weekend.
[romantic music playing]
[heartbeat thumping]
[theme music playing]
He's just not very talkative, you know.
-There's no way.
-Ugh.
[Ji-yoon] He's actually very kind though.
Are you two perhaps…
Is there something between you two?
I'm asking you if you may have feelings
for Ms. Ji-yoon.
-[Si-woo] The launch…
-Whoa…
-…will be presented by Ms. Cha.
-Me?
A presentation?
[Si-woo] While handling
the product release presentation…
I like for things to be perfect.
And had a panic attack.
Would Ms. Cha become
another victim of Three-No-Man or not?