You two are acting strange.
Seriously, are you two fighting?
Should I put my arm around his shoulder
to prove that we aren’t on bad terms?
Where is Ko Song?
Where is he?
Ko Song has been acting strange lately.
Are you avoiding me?
I’m short-sighted. I can’t see the blackboard.
This is what you want, right?
Ko Song.
Can’t you just say what is on your mind?
I’m sorry.
Fine.
If you don’t want to talk to me,
then don’t ever speak to me again.
I like you.
I know what I did is wrong.
I’m scared.
I’m scared that you will hate me
more than you already did.
Why would I hate you?
I don’t know.
I don’t know what you are thinking.
After I did that,
you rushed out.
What am I supposed to think?
I don’t want to lose you, Orange.
You’re going to lose me
because you are doing this.
Listen.
I’m neither mad nor hate you.
Can you now tell me
how you feel about me?
I…
I’m still your friend.
Okay.
No, you don’t get it.
Do you really understand what I mean?
I get it.
Are you going to keep your distance from me?
No.
Can we go back to being the same, Ko Song?
Promise?
(No one understands how I feel
better than I do.)
(I keep thinking if it’s the right thing
to say what I’m feeling.)
(The society, the social context,
people around me,)
(And the guy in front of me.)
(Everything pushes me to overthink.)
Are you okay?
(To admit what I am,
it’s not solely my decision.)
(The easiest way to save this relationship,)
(it’s to go back to the way we used to be.)
My goodness!
What is this?
Ko.
Why are you all wet?
It was raining.
How am I supposed to stay dry?
That’s a weird question.
You’re getting sarcastic.
Hurry and take a shower.
If you get sick and miss school tomorrow,
I’ll punish you.
Yes, ma’am.
You should go take a shower,
otherwise you’ll get sick.
If you’re going to keep looking at him like this,
why don’t you go take a shower at his house?
Mom!
What?
Don’t tell me that
you want to take a day off tomorrow?
No, it’s not that, Mom.
So what is it?
Just hypothetically.
If my friend…
He…
Hey.
How long are you going to mumble?
I want to watch the drama.
It’s the final episode.
I want to see how the male lead
confesses his feelings to the female lead.
So spill it.
Okay.
If my friend does something
that he’s not supposed to,
but I’m not mad at him.
We talked, he apologized to me,
and I understand everything.
Is this story fictional or real?
That’s not the point, Mom.
Alright.
Do you mean it
when you said you weren’t mad?
Ko!
I wasn’t mad. I was just shocked.
Then just tell him that.
I already told him,
but he doesn’t seem to believe it.
You just need to tell him seriously.
You aren’t upset by what he did.
He doesn’t need to feel guilty.
You are okay now.
Something like this.
You should talk things out with him.
Don’t leave the problem for too long.
The longer you leave it unsolved,
the longer he has to live with the guilt.
He’s avoiding you
because he feels very guilty.
It means that he really cares about you.
Don’t wait for too long.
You should talk it out quickly.
Otherwise, you might end up
losing this friend instead of making up.
Ko!
I haven’t finished. Where are you going?
You haven’t told me who you had a fight with.
Ko.
Ko Song.
I’m really sorry for what happened that night.
Listen.
I’m not mad at you.
You don’t need to be scared of losing me.
You promised me that
you wouldn’t disappear again.
Don’t break your promise.
You asked me
how I feel about you.
To be honest, I don’t know.
I really don’t know
how I feel about you.
But this is what I know.
I don’t want to lose you.
I’m sorry.
Sorry for what this time?
You have apologized to me too many times.
I’m sorry for avoiding you.
I’m also sorry that…
Ko Song.
I promised you that
I wouldn’t disappear again.
You went to take a tutoring class.
You didn’t disappear.
Stop apologizing.
Let’s go back to being the same.
Smile.
Smile, Ko Song.
Why don’t you smile?
Will you smile or not?
I’ll smile.
Ouch.
Ko, Ko, Ko.
Mom.
Shh
That’s all.
Thank you.
It’s late. Why aren’t you sleeping?
You were soaked in the rain.
You may get sick.
I’ll go to bed soon.
Orange, you should go to bed,
or you may get sick.
I’m happy that we are now the same.
Bring me oranges tomorrow, my minion.
Yes, boss.
Good night, Ko Song.
Good night, Orange.
Ko.
Yes.
Why didn’t you go to school?
I have a cold.
Are you faking it?
No, I’m really sick.
If you don’t believe me,
do you want me to spread it to you?
Ko!
I believe you. Stop it.
You always pretend to be sick
when I ask you to go
and help me on the boat.
Did you get wet in the rain yesterday?
How did you know that?
I saw your friend also didn’t go to school.
Ko Song is home?
See? I knew it.
I saw him watering the plants
in front of his house.
Did you two plan this together?
I didn’t know anything about it.
I’m going in to get some sleep.
Dad.
Mom didn’t prepare a meal for you.
When you wake up,
you need to go out and buy it.
Ko.
You are home. Why don’t you buy it?
I’m sick.
It’s just an act.
Who are you looking for?
I…
I’m going to pick an orange.
Good job, my minion.
Here, eat it.
I have a cold.
Aren’t you afraid of being near me?
Me too.
Do you like oranges that much?
Always.
Eat it a lot.
Oranges have high vitamin C.
It’s good for a cold.
Then you should eat them too.
Let’s go out for a ride.
No.
We are sick.
We should be resting.
You are smart,
but how can you not know this?
Taking a ride is a kind of rest.
Come on.
Orange.
August.
Why are you sitting here?
It’s none of your business.
Assh*le, I asked
because I’m worried about you.
Boss Ko.
Ko Song, woo!
You are sick and still so hyper.
We need to act like we weren’t sick
to confuse the virus.
One more thing, I ate a lot of vitamin C.
Look.
I got the orange power.
You just want an excuse to go out.
Uncle.
Uncle, are you here?
You have a customer waiting here.
Why don’t you come inside?
I want everything on the list.
So you two become loving.
I remember you two were always bickering.
Nonsense, Uncle.
Please go in and get things on my list.
I won’t tease you.
Come on.
Be gentle, Achi.
I told you not to overdo during the practice.
Why?
Are you worried about me?
You know what I mean.
- That must hurt.
- Will those two Ko come to school today?
Right.
How are things between them?
Thanks.
Hello, my friends. What are you doing?
Do you miss us?
Where have you been?
I was sick.
But I’m fine now.
Did you two make up?
Yes.
It was typical of Ko Neung.
He gets mad to get attention.
Nonsense, Augar.
I’m the most reasonable person in the world.
What happened to your knee?
What did you write on it?
A…
A-eh-ya-eh-yah!
Why?
Huh?
You are reading Dragon Ball too much.
Yeah.
I’m really into it.
Tle.
Are you mad that I sat at Ko Neung’s desk
instead of sitting with you yesterday?
No.
I get it. You are probably confused
after knowing I wrote the notes.
You’re right.
I never thought
they came from the guy sitting next to me.
Right.
But I’m curious.
Why do you fall for a guy like me?
Why?
I am…
I don’t know.
I just like you.
I don’t need a reason for it.
You’re right.
I don’t expect you to like me back.
We can be friends like this.
August, bestie.
I’m back. Do you miss me?
Yes.
Now, let me go.
So how is it going?
Did you get a new note?
What note?
Come on, August.
Tle.
Please take care of him for me.
He’s currently in love.
I had an ice cream with him the other day.
He kept talking about the writer of the notes.
He has wanted to meet that person
since we were in Grade 10.
He said he thought about that person all day.
Go back to your seat.
Didn’t you promise you wouldn’t tell anyone?
Hey.
How dare you talk back at your boss?
I’m not afraid of you.
I don’t get it.
When you were mad at him,
it was so intense.
Now, you two made up.
You act as if you’ve never fought.
You want to know what happened
and why we acted like that, don’t you?
I don’t want to know.
He kissed me.
Huh?
And you can act normal around him?
I’m trying.
I want to believe him.
He said he didn’t mean it.
I forgave him for everything.
I’m trying not to think about it.
Can you really do that?
Not really.
I’m still thinking about what happened.
If you’re still thinking about it,
doesn’t it mean that you…
I’m not sure.
I just want the old Ko Song back.
I also don’t like that
I’m constantly thinking about him.
Ko.
What?
I used to have a crush on you.
Huh?
Yes, I had a crush on you.
Are you out of your mind, Augar?
Assh*le, I mean it.
You had a crush on me?
Hold on.
What the heck is this?
I had a serious crush on you. I mean it.
What’s with the face?
I said I had a crush on you.
It happened when we were in junior high.
I’m totally over you.
What the heck was wrong with you?
Yeah, what the heck was wrong with me?
How the hell did I have a crush on you?
Assh*le.
It was a shame in my life.
Why?
What’s wrong with me?
Do you really want me to list it for you?
Yes.
You are a troublemaker.
You always steal snacks from me.
You are self-centered.
You are very stubborn.
You are loud and noisy.
I wanted to kick your ass several times.
You are acting like our gang’s leader, assh*le.
You go around picking fights.
But I’m always the one
who has to handle the fight.
Are you scolding me, Augar?
Yes.
Do you know why I’m telling you this?
Why?
Because you didn’t even know
that I had a crush on you.
But you and Ko Song both know
that you have feelings for each other.
Are you saying I have feelings for him?
Am I wrong?
I’m not thinking of him that way, assh*le.
Stop talking nonsense.
People will misunderstand us.
He’s just a friend, just like you.
Okay, you don’t have feelings for him.
Don’t ever say that to him.
I don’t want him to misunderstand me.
Things will get worse this time.
Why?
Are you afraid that
if he knows you have feelings for him,
he will keep his distance from you?
Assh*le, I told you
I don’t have feelings for him.
Your actions don’t match your words.
How you treat us and how you treat him  is totally different.
And you dare to tell me
he’s just a friend like the rest of us?
Listen, I…
Don’t argue with me.
How long have we known each other?
You’ve only known Ko Song for a few years.
I can tell you are closer to him
than the rest of us.
How you treat each other
is more than just friends.
You need to admit it, Ko.
No.
Liar.
I don’t have feelings for him.
Reconsider it.
Augar.
Think again.
No.
You like him, jack*ss. You, idiot.
I’m going to play basketball now.
You, jack*ss.
Do I have feelings for him?
Why would I like him?
Do I like him?
No way, no.
Do I like him or not?
Do I like him?
Do I like him? Really?
Orange.
I don’t think so.
Who likes you? It’s not me.
You walk past it.
I walk past what?
Your house.
Why do you look so distracted?
No, I don’t.
I just want to exercise.
You know, take a walk.
Then why did you turn around?
I suddenly feel lazy.
Huh?
Yeah, I don’t want to do it anymore.
I’m going in. See you.
I like him.c
I don’t like him.
I like him.
Do you like him a lot?
Quite a lot.
Mom!
What?
You scared me.
You scared me too.
What are you doing here?
I’m going out.
Why didn’t you take a shower
when you got home?
Okay, Okay.
Okay what?
I’m going in the house.
You scared me
Don’t like what?
♪ How long had I been waiting for someone? ♪
♪ How many seasons had come and gone? ♪
♪ Before fate finally led you to me ♪
♪ And made my heart beat like this ♪
♪ I don’t know if this is love or not ♪
♪ I don’t know if you feel the same at all ♪
♪ Do you know I’m scared
and I don’t understand ♪
♪ How to handle the way I am? ♪
♪ Every time that we meet again ♪
♪ Something grows a little more each day ♪
♪ The closer we are,
the more I feel the love I’ve waited for ♪
♪ Might not be too far away at all ♪
♪ Even when winter fades I’ll still wait on ♪
♪ Till the final raindrop falls,
hope is never gone ♪
♪ As long as I have you holding my hand
as we walk on ♪
♪ I fear nothing if this season has you ♪
♪ I heard that love can never be certain ♪
♪ Like the sky and wind
that change with the seasons ♪
♪ If the rain brought you to love
but not to stay ♪
Catch it.
♪ If the rain brought you to love
but not to stay ♪
Ouch.
Kanin.
Krittin.
♪ Every time that we meet again ♪
♪ Something grows a little more each day ♪
♪ The closer we are,
the more I feel the love I’ve waited for ♪
♪ Might not be too far away at all ♪
♪ Even when winter fades I’ll still wait on ♪
♪ Till the final raindrop falls,
hope is never gone ♪
♪ As long as I have you holding my hand
as we walk on ♪
♪ I fear nothing if this season has you ♪
Which one do you want?
This one or this one?
This one.
♪ When the sky clears after the storm ♪
Bye.
Bye. See you.
♪ When the sky clears after the storm ♪
Here, Ko Song.
♪ We start our journey together and move on ♪
We will crash the bike.
We won’t. Trust me.
♪ We start our journey together and move on ♪
♪ Every story we go through turns into a memory ♪
♪ That reminds us  how far we have come along ♪
How are you doing?
Soon, it will be your last year in high school.
I can’t wait to graduate.
Are you sure, Krittin?
I won’t be easy on you this year.
Mr. Kong, why are you picking on me?
It’s the school’s tradition.
Grade 11 students will hold a farewell party
for your seniors.
Other classes are assigned
to prepare signage and boards.
Do you know what our class is assigned
to do from drawing lots?
It must be something bad.
You are assigned to perform a play.
See?
Can’t we draw lots again?
Why don’t you ask
the friend sitting next to you?
The class monitors were the ones
drawing lots.
No.
I mean, we don’t need to do it again
because we got the best duty.
Whatever.
You need to do your best.
Don’t ruin my reputation.
what you are going to do.
All of you have to participate in it.
Do not take advantage of your friends.
Okay?
Yes.
I’ll look forward to it.
See you.
Why are you smiling?
I’m just thinking of something.
Thinking what?
It would be fun to watch you perform a play.
No way.
Come on. Please perform it. I want to see.
Please, please, please.
If you perform with me, I’ll do it.
No.
If you do it, I’ll do it.
No way.
Does anyone have any suggestions?
I like watching a drama with my mom.
What about O-Negative? It’s pretty popular.
What about Cinderella?
I’m sick of it. They do it every year.
She eats the apple and dies.
She wakes up after being kissed.
It’s so boring.
Aren’t you talking about Snow White?
They are pretty much the same.
I have an idea.
Michael Jordan.
What about you, the two Ko?
I like…
I don’t know.
I’m fine with everything you choose.
I think we should ask our seniors
what they want to see.
We shouldn’t choose what we like.
Now, I know what play we will perform.
I don’t like it when he pauses
and lets us guess what he’s going to say.
Are you sleeping?
No.
Why?
Let’s go out to eat.
I’m hungry.
Let’s go eat noodles and wontons.
You act like you have been starving.
I’m hungry.
When I got home, no one was there.
I haven’t eaten anything.
Did they tell you where they were going?
They left a note
saying they would be home late.
And they left some money.
Don’t need to say anything
to make me feel better.
I’m used to it.
I know that.
But if it bothers you, you should talk to them.
Maybe later.
Are you ready for tomorrow?
Yes, I’m very ready
I’m looking forward to playing this character.
You are getting yourself into trouble.
You need to blame Tle for this.
He makes me do it.
The role is perfect for you.
I think you know the person best.
You’re right.
I’m close with him.
Just kidding.
Here.
A reward for a brave man.
Does it taste good?
Yes, but don’t need to give me another one.
Who is actually hungry here?
I’m going back to eating.
You can have my wonton.
The shop’s wontons are the highlight.
It’s delicious.
I told you the noodles here are the best.
Next is a play
performed by Grade 11 students.
The title is ‘Teachers, We Are Sorry.”
Didn’t I tell you?
If you are late, you will be punished.
Do 20 push-ups.
Do it now.
Good. You’re working together.
I’ll help you too.
What the heck are you doing?
You are scooping up water.
Are you kidding me?
Mr. Prateep.
These are students in my class.
Can you let it slide this time?
Sure, Mr. Kong.
But don’t let it happen again.
Then Mr. Prateep would say.
Don’t let me see you do it again.
Teachers, we are sorry.
Why are you so noisy?
Why are the Grade 12 students not here yet?
If they aren’t here, I’ll go take a nap.
Mr. Chon.
Hello, Miss Peung.
Why didn’t you say anything
when you walked in?
You often complain about your back pain.
I brought you a muscle rub.
Thank you.
Why do you need to come in and interrupt us?
I’m flirting with Mr. Chon.
Teachers, we are sorry.
Why do you keep apologizing?
Don’t you know it’s bad to do that?
It means you are making mistakes repeatedly.
Mr. Prateep.
No teacher would want to hear an apology
from their students.
We all want our students to grow up
to have a bright future and good goals in life.
We want you to have a stable career.
I hope that the Grade 12 students
will set a good example for their juniors.
This school is just a small beginning.
I wish you all the best
on the path you’ve chosen.
As representatives of the Grade 11 students,
we would like to thank
and apologize to the teachers
for all the good and bad things that we did.
This is so embarrassing.
I won’t forget that Tle made me do this.
You did a wonderful job, Augar.
Why don’t you do it yourself?
It would be easier to play Mr. Chon.
Then it wouldn’t be funny.
I still have another year in this school.
How am I going to face others?
My teammates will tease me about it.
Augar, don’t worry. I’ll protect you.
If someone teases you, I’ll punch them.
Are you going to do that?
Yes.
Oh, my eyes hurt.
The soap got into my eyes.
Which one?
How is it?
It’s better.
Shall we go?
I’ll help you.
Yes, Mr. Kong.
Do I look okay?
Yes.
You look really okay.
Seriously, how did you come up
with the idea for the teacher parody?
Isn’t it what you and your friend are good at?
Is that a compliment or criticism?
It’s a compliment.
You all did a great job today.
August, you look cute
when dressing like this.
Didn’t your friends go to have lunch?
Why didn’t you go with them?
Yeah, you’re right.
I haven’t had lunch.
You should go.
Why don’t you come
and have lunch with me?
I still have to clean up here.
No, I mean another day.
Do you want to have a meal with me?
Sure.
Okay. I’ve got to go.
Okay. Bye.
Promise?
Yes, I promise.
You did well today, Orange.
This is the first time I saw this side of you.
Did I really do well?
Of course.
So I deserve a reward, right?
You’re getting used to it, aren’t you?
If I do well, I should be rewarded, right?
What do you want?
What about oranges?
It’s too simple.
What about…?
I’ll buy you an ice cream.
No.
What about this?
Do you want to come to my room
to play games?
(I don’t know why I said that.)
(Maybe it’s because I’ve never wanted
to go back to the way we were.)
(Maybe because my brain is overthinking,
so my heart takes over.)
(Or maybe because I want to kiss him again,
intentionally this time.)
(But what I really want is that
he feels the same way as I do.)
♪ Will say "I love you" ♪
♪ Will say "I love you" so you know ♪
♪ No more watching from afar,
letting chances go ♪
♪ Will say "I love you" so you know ♪
♪ To make this worth the wait after all ♪
- When you like someone, you want to tease them.
- Boo!
- Why did you hit my butt?
- You should watch and see
if that person likes to hit your butt.
- Ko Song, I want to eat an orange.
- Every time I have a problem,
you are a light for me.