You weren't...
working, right?
Zen!
Ryo?
Why...
Why are you here?
Zen...
Stay over tonight.
What's come over you all of a sudden?
I missed you.
I missed you too.
I'm so cold.
You idiot.
Let's go upstairs.
Mm.
[Fake Fact Lips]
[Final Episode: It's a Full Moon]
Um,
when I called you earlier,
you said you were working.
Were you at the office?
Wait, is it for a guy?
Well, well.
Mm.
I just stopped by.
Why do you ask?
Nothing.
I just wanted to know.
Hey, don't you think it's weird?
What?
You've been acting weird all day.
Just say what's on your mind.
What about you?
Eh?
Is there anything you want to say to me?
It's always been me
doing all the talking.
You really do have a fever.
No, I don't.
You said you were cold earlier.
That's because of the fever, right?
And you obviously don't have any energy.
I already told you, I'm not.
You must be tired then.
You've been really busy
at work lately too.
I should probably head home today.
With me here,
you probably can't rest properly.
Wait.
We have a trip the day after tomorrow.
If you keep pushing yourself like this,
we won't be able to go.
No, I'm not!
All right. Just lie down, okay?
Don't force yourself to come see me.
I...
still want to stay with you,
even like this.
I want to treasure the time
we spend together.
But you don't feel the same, right?
No, I just
want you to take better care of yourself.
What's been going on with you
since earlier?
Careful.
I hate it
when you don't tell me you're hurting.
Aren't you hiding something from me too?
What?
I'm not hiding anything.
Then...
What about lying to me about being
at the office
when you were actually with Futami?
You're not even denying it.
Zen...
Are you happier
being with Futami than with me?
You...
Do you think something is going on
between Futami and me?
Is that how little you trust me?
You don't understand how I feel at all.
How could I?
You always act cool and composed
and never let yourself be vulnerable
in front of me.
I...
hate not being needed by you
even more than not being able to see you.
You never tell me when you're upset.
Right now, we're not equals
in this relationship.
If things keep going like this,
I don't think
I can continue being with you.
He's been like that all day.
Yeah.
Did something go wrong with the project?
Ah. Did he get yelled at
by the supervisor?
That was you yesterday, wasn't it?
Yeah.
Mr. Shido would never get yelled at.
Then...
could it be something about his girlfriend
or something like that?
Why don't you go ask him?
No, no, no.
I can't do that.
-What are you afraid of? Go.
-You go.
Where is Mr. Iwao from Sales Section 1?
This is not Section 1.
Oh, it's not?
It's on the other side.
That way?
Go through there...
Okay.
Um... are
those documents for Section 1?
Ah, yes.
I'll take them over.
Thank you.
Ah, Mr. Shido?
Oh, here.
Ah. Sorry to make you
bring them all the way over.
It's okay. I was passing by anyway.
Hey,
do you know where Yotsuya is?
He took the day off.
I heard he has a fever.
Well, it's rare.
He'd been talking excitedly for days
about having something
to look forward to this weekend.
I'm a bit worried.
Well, I'll get back to work.
Good work.
Well, isn't that Yotsuya?
Eh?
Weren't you off today?
I only took half the day off.
I need to get off work on time,
so don't stop me.
Are you feeling better?
Yeah, more or less.
[Meet me in the meeting room after work]
Oh? Do you have a work dinner today?
No, I'm going home.
Huh? It's barely clock-out time.
That's exactly why.
You guys should get off work on time
once in a while too.
Have a good evening.
He must be feeling unwell.
No.
Maybe he's off to have a fight
with his girlfriend.
Eh?
Mm.
What are you doing here?
I was so busy after the meeting,
and I didn't even have time to tidy up.
Speaking of, why are you here?
Nothing.
Eh?
Yotsuya, you're here too.
The three of us are all here.
Ah.
Yotsuya, are you feeling okay?
Eh?
Are you sick?
Um...
I slept it off.
I only took the morning off
just to be safe.
Hmm.
It's rare to see
both of you looking so down.
What?
This guy
has been in a really low mood all day.
He even scared the juniors.
Ah.
This
suits me perfectly, right?
I got it yesterday.
I have to say, I've got pretty good taste.
Yesterday?
Yeah.
I went shopping with Shido yesterday.
What about you?
But since you only just bought it,
you haven't given it to him yet, right?
What are you talking about?
I'm leaving.
What are you playing dumb for?
You said you needed to buy something
yesterday, so I went along with you.
A present.
You even said you hoped he'd like it.
Eh?
Anyway, what are you two even doing here?
Right now...
Hmm?
Yesterday's gift shopping...
You just spoiled the surprise.
Eh?
What?
Hey!
I'm really sorry.
But since it's for Yotsuya,
you could've just told me beforehand.
Then I could've
helped you pick something out properly.
Shut up.
Stop talking.
Come on.
Sure, I messed up.
But do you really need to be this angry?
Seriously, did something happen
between you two?
Well,
normally, Shido,
you wouldn't get this angry.
You'd just fire back
with some cutting remark.
Oh, no. Zen is just...
Zen?
Why are you calling him by his first name?
Um... Well...
More importantly,
why did you buy Yotsuya a gift?
Nothing.
You two
became so close when I wasn't around?
It's so weird.
Weren't you
always butting heads before?
Well, we're
both adults now.
I'd say we've mellowed out.
No, it's still weird.
Alright, even if I give you that,
Yotsuya, you've always been
friendly with people,
so I can understand that.
Hey, I'm friendly too.
No, Shido,
for someone as stubborn as you
to change like this,
something definitely happened.
Wait,
are you two more than just rivals?
Shido,
what is Yotsuya to you?
Yotsuya is...
Ryo is...
-my boyfriend.
-What?
No way.
Seriously,
why did you suddenly tell him?
Sorry.
That's because you're imagining things.
Anyone would overthink it
after seeing
something that looked like a date.
Do you really think anything could
ever happen between me and anyone else?
Then,
what was that sudden showdown
with Futami about?
That was...
to see
who was more worthy of being
your rival.
What?
I couldn't help taking the bait.
Then...
you could've
just told me about
that kind of showdown sooner.
How could I?
And you, struggling like that
all by yourself—
you could've told me sooner too.
How could I?
Saying something as willful as
"Only I can be
both your boyfriend and your rival..."
Then
what about all the willful things
I've said to you?
That's fine.
Because it's you.
No, it's not.
We're in a relationship,
but only one of us has been holding back,
and only one of us has been
making all the effort. That's not right.
Well...
I'm the reason you've ended up
like this.
I kept taking your affection for granted.
Even though some feelings can't be
conveyed unless you say them out loud,
I kept running away from that.
So, I want to change.
I don't want you
to force yourself or hold back anymore.
Rival or lover,
there's only you. I hope you can trust me.
Mm.
I've been scared.
What?
I've been scared that my feeling of
wanting to be with you forever
might become a burden to you.
The more I thought about it,
the more I lost my composure.
Before I knew it,
I was already pushing myself.
I didn't even realize
that it was the same as not trusting you.
I trust you,
and everything about you, Zen.
Ryo.
From now on, I'll be honest with you
about how I feel.
Bring it on.
Whether it's jealousy or anything else,
I'll take it all.
"Bring it on?"
Is this another competition?
This is our way, right?
Well,
let's call it a draw this time.
No.
You won.
You've been
showing me your cool side this whole time.
But I'm very happy.
You said I'm your boyfriend.
Are you teasing me?
No.
You've always been cool.
I think
it's the first time
you've ever said that to me.
That's because
it's the first time I've said it out loud.
I've always felt that way.
That's why
I want to stay by your side forever.
Ryo!
Yeah?
I...
I love you far more than
you think...
Aaaah!
Oh no!
Yes. Well, tomorrow afternoon...
No, I'll find a way to finish it tonight.
Yes, I'm very sorry!
Yes. I'll hang up now.
This is bad. I need to get back now.
Even so...
you still think I'm cool?
Then...
tell me the rest
when we're alone together.
Are you really feeling okay now?
Mm.
I just overloaded myself with work.
I was just tired.
That's more like it.
If I...
couldn't prove
that I was worthy of being your rival,
I was afraid
I wouldn't be able to be your lover.
Since when did the man I chose
become so insecure?
Whenever it comes to you,
I always get insecure.
Why?
Well, obviously...
that's because I love you more.
What?
You don't understand.
Eh?
You
don't understand at all.
What?
I...
I love you
far more than you think.
It wasn't on a whim
that I became your lover.
I also love you very much.
I hope you know
I've been trying so hard
because I love you so much.
I love you so much.
I'm sorry I couldn't
say it before.
What can I do
to make you truly understand how I feel?
This is already enough.
Zen.
I love you so much too.
I know.
Zen.
Zen?
Why are you smiling?
Nothing.
Here.
Mm.
Futami called a bunch of times.
Ah, sorry.
It's okay.
I was going to tell him eventually anyway.
It's a full moon.
It is.
"The moon is beautiful tonight"—
don't you dare say that.
I won't.
I'll just say it directly.
That I love you.
Looks like we'll have good weather
for the trip tomorrow.
Come on.
Say it too.
It's been a long time since we've
gotten to spend this much time together.
I'm so happy.
Somehow...
I'm not quite used to this.
What?
Then I'll stop.
Don't.
Tell me.
Because we've finally...
By the way, what about your performance?
Shut up!
I came up with three more proposals
than this guy.
Churning out useless proposals
is just wasted effort.
Ah...
Darn it.
I'll just keep you company
while you sober up.
Since I didn't bring the T-shirt,
you could just head back home.
College life without me around
must be so dull for you.
Keep dreaming.
Bye.
You've become honest.
I knew it. I should just stop.
Why?
The mood just now was clearly
building up to an "I love you."
I don't know anything about
those kinds of moods.
If it's said too many times,
it won't feel as special anymore.
No.
It won't.
So...