Natsumi!
Sorry!
Hey!
-What are you doing? It's too dangerous!
-My daughter…
-My daughter is inside!
-What?
Natsumi!
LOVE-CHAN COOKIE
All right.
See you all later.
-See you.
-Good night.
What?
What's the rush?
I just have a feeling.
A feeling?
A feeling that if I stay,
I'll get caught up in work.
Don't jinx it at this hour.
It was peaceful today, wasn't it?
This is exactly when
sudden requests come in, right?
That's what you call a sixth sense.
It's said that the insular cortex
in the brain is involved in that.
The insular cortex?
It is a region involved in various
internal sensations of the body.
What seems like a hunch
is actually detecting and anticipating
a change, based on past experiences.
So there is a proper basis for it.
I'm done too.
Hey, wait!
See you.
Oh, good evening.
Hey.
Kerosene has been detected.
It has to be arson.
-Is this the body?
-Yes.
It carbonized due to high temperatures,
and then the house collapsed,
crushing the remains.
The skeletal structure
hasn't retained its original form either.
According to eyewitnesses,
five-year-old Natsumi Sata
wasn't able to escape the house,
and her mother, Haruka Sata,
reportedly went into the fire
to try and save her.
-Wait! Just wait!
-Let me through!
That is Haruka's husband, Yasuyuki Sata.
Excuse us.
We're the police.
Could we ask you a few questions?
What on earth happened?
Haruka and Natsumi are okay, right?
Where are they?
We're still investigating the details.
But we've found
burned skeletal parts.
Eyewitnesses report seeing
Haruka and Natsumi taken by the fire.
That's not true.
It can't be true.
Natsumi! Haruka!
Please calm down.
There's no way…
It's not true.
Sir.
I'm sorry for asking this
at such a difficult time.
Do you recognize this?
It's a wedding ring, isn't it?
This belongs to Haruka, correct?
I promise you.
The police will get to the bottom of this.
All the soft tissue was burnt away.
We have to handle this quite carefully.
I wonder if any teeth marks are left.
Can an accurate identification
really be made?
Regardless of the body's condition,
a piece of the truth is always there.
Let's begin.
Personal identification
proved to be extremely difficult.
However, this part,
although severely damaged,
appears to be the lower first molar.
This is likely
a metallic inlay restoration.
With this, we managed to match
the teeth marks with the dental charts,
confirming that the body
belongs to Haruka Sata.
You did a great job identifying it.
Even looking at the femur,
which withstood the most,
there is no mistake
that it's a female in her thirties.
So, what about the child?
About that…
We couldn't find her.
What?
Currently, the gathered remains
are for only one person, Haruka.
No way.
But Haruka went into the fire
to save Natsumi, didn't she?
A child calling for help inside the flames
was also witnessed.
However,
from those remains…
Since she was still a small child,
could it be that the bones
were completely destroyed?
Even at the maximum temperature of
a crematorium, fragments of bone remain.
It is impossible for absolutely
no trace to be left behind.
Did she completely turn to ash?
Even if reduced to ash,
inorganic matter
derived from bone remains.
It becomes a powder,
but some trace should still be left.
It doesn't add up.
Of course, I suppose
there is a possibility
that she escaped the flames on her own
and is alive somewhere.
There were many onlookers
around the scene,
and a fire truck arrived
on the back street.
Nobody witnessed a child escaping.
Then, where is Natsumi?
She vanished into the fire.
Is that it?
For now,
it's a mystery.
Kozue Tanahara.
You were the first caller
for yesterday's fire, correct?
Yes.
It seems you reported
that your friend jumped into the flames.
A friend?
Right.
Haruka and I have been partners
in badminton since we were young.
We were always together.
It seems like you did rather well.
What's this photo?
That was when we went
to a hot spring last year.
You were with Haruka
yesterday as well, correct?
Please tell us what happened.
Yesterday,
we were driving in my car
just to get a change of pace.
And then,
when I dropped her off at her house…
Help!
It's hot!
Mom!
Haruka?
Help me!
Natsumi!
-Hey! What are you doing?
-My daughter…
It's hot!
My daughter is inside!
It's too dangerous!
Natsumi!
I can't believe it.
You didn't find Natsumi?
Just to confirm,
Natsumi was left home alone?
Yes.
Where did you go?
We didn't really have any destination.
We just wanted to talk.
Just talk?
Like about what happened at kindergarten.
And about Yasuyuki.
Who is Yasuyuki?
Haruka's husband.
Yasuyuki and I
were originally high school classmates,
and I introduced him to Haruka.
So you were the one
who brought them together.
Are we about done now?
I have an appointment coming up.
You're not taking time off from work, huh?
What?
Your close friend passed away.
You must be shaken up.
Well, I'm busy.
More importantly, have Natsumi's remains
still not been found?
Please find them quickly.
Of course.
I'm counting on you.
We will do our best.
Natsumi was only five.
Leaving such a young child alone
just for a casual drive is strange.
-They could've taken her along.
-Well, that's true.
That's true.
And her friend died,
yet she didn't ask a single question.
"Why did she die?" "Who did it?"
People ask that.
Are you saying
you suspect Kozue is the arsonist?
Investigate Kozue Tanahara thoroughly.
Yes, ma'am.
The next batch has arrived.
All right.
What?
Are we checking all of this to see
if we find Natsumi's remains?
They said they had everything
that looked strange transported here.
This is definitely not bone.
Right this way.
These are Haruka's parents.
Is this
our daughter?
Most likely.
What about Nat-chan?
She hasn't been found yet.
Haruka would always send us photos.
Most of them were of Nat-chan.
She's so cute.
She took everything,
anything that could be a memento.
She often complained
that she had too many things at home.
Just the other day,
she brought a memento box to our house.
A memento box?
If it's all right, could we borrow that?
What?
It seems Natsumi's remains
still haven't been found.
Is it even possible not to find them
after searching this much?
I wonder.
Could a kidnapper
have taken advantage of the fire?
It's not impossible. But…
something feels off.
I forgot to mention.
I was staking out
Kozue Tanahara's apartment.
I know, about you and Haruka.
And you?
You're relieved, aren't you?
What?
You wanted to break up with her, right?
With this, the obstacle is finally gone.
You…
Aren't you glad?
It seems the two of them
were having an affair.
A witness report came
from Yasuyuki's colleague
that he brought a woman along
to his business trip destination.
Out of growing love and hatred
for her best friend's husband,
Kozue Tanahara killed Natsumi,
who became an obstacle, by arson.
Furthermore, she enticed Haruka
to save Natsumi,
causing her death.
So, what do you think?
Hey.
Couldn't this potentially be
a child's temporal bone?
It looks like an adult's cheekbone to me.
No, but, Haruka fractured a bone
last month from falling down the stairs.
If it's her cheekbone,
shouldn't there be a surgical plate?
Is it this one?
Hey.
It's this one.
MEDICAL RECORD
FIXED CHEEK WITH SURGICAL PLATE
FELL DOWN STAIRS AT HER HOME
FELL DOWN STAIRS
In any case, it's not a child's bone.
It's not, right?
-It's not.
-It's impossible!
Dr. Masumi.
It seems Natsumi's remains
really can't be found after all.
Is that so?
Huh? What's this?
Oh, it's Natsumi's memento box.
-So cute.
-Wow.
Oh, that's right.
Look.
What is that?
It's an umbilical cord.
Oh, from when Natsumi was born?
Yes.
I figured she would have kept it.
This will be useful too.
Useful?
To match Natsumi's DNA.
Please test if a sample can be collected.
Okay.
Ms. Kiryu.
Please go to the police station
and get the list of missing persons.
A similar case
might provide some sort of hint.
Right, I'm on it.
MISSING PERSON REPORT
I haven't been able to contact my daughter
for three days.
Her workplace says
they can't reach her either.
That is worrying.
Do you remember what
she might have been wearing?
Supervisor!
I'd have it sent to you
if you'd asked me about it.
I'm sorry.
So, how is the case going?
Any clues?
Where could Natsumi have disappeared to?
Ms. Dojima?
It's just…
The police
exist to protect people's loved ones.
People's loved ones…
Hurry up.
Yes, ma'am.
Here is the list of missing persons.
Thank you very much.
Well, I'm heading out for the day.
Oh? It's still early.
I'm going to meet a man.
What? A man?
Oh, wow.
Ms. Dojima met someone nice, huh?
Well…
That's not what she meant.
What?
He's a senior detective.
She says he always looked after her.
What she just said was also a teaching
from that senior officer.
Despite how she may seem,
when she was young,
she didn't do well in the male-dominated
police force, and it troubled her.
At that time,
she had failed to apprehend a suspect.
I heard you let the suspect get away.
I am very sorry.
What's wrong with that?
What?
You were protecting the family
present at the scene
and let him go, right?
That's fine.
We are here to protect
people's loved ones.
You're suited to be a detective.
You probably won't get promoted, though.
Just like me.
But that senior officer,
while trying to protect a child
from a random attacker…
was killed in the line of duty.
Since then, whenever something happens,
she goes to his grave.
I think he's the only person
Ms. Dojima can ask for advice from.
MAHO KIRYU
Dr. Masumi!
Look at this.
-Ms. Dojima!
-What?
Regarding Kozue Tanahara,
she's taking paid leave starting tomorrow.
Oh, really?
Do you think she intends to flee?
Seems suspicious, right?
-That's true.
-Also--
Tell me once you've found any evidence.
I have.
One hour before the arson occurred,
Kozue Tanahara purchased kerosene.
Why don't you bring that up first?!
Sorry!
We extracted DNA from both
the umbilical cord and the remains
to perform an STR analysis,
and there were ten mismatches.
Excuse me?
In other words, biologically,
there is no parent-child relationship.
What?
Dr. Masumi, what does this mean?
DENTAL RECORDS
Her mother, Haruka Sata,
reportedly went into the fire.
The gathered remains
are for only one person.
I have an appointment coming up.
We managed to match the teeth marks
with the dental charts.
Please examine the remains once more.
Could it be…
The pieces
might be coming together.
Hello.
Do you have a moment?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Sorry, I know you were about to go out.
Where were you planning to go?
Nowhere in particular.
A lot has happened,
just wanted to refresh myself.
Either way, what is this about?
We have found out
that the deceased body was not Haruka.
The victim's identity
is Miwa Tateno.
She is a high school classmate
of yours and Yasuyuki's.
Miwa's whereabouts had been unknown
since the day of that fire.
I haven't been able to contact my daughter
for three days.
MIWA TATENO
That is only natural.
Because
the body found at the scene of the fire
was not Haruka's,
but Miwa's.
As you are friends,
both of them were visiting
the dental clinic you manage.
Using your position,
you swapped the dental charts
and disguised Miwa's body
as Haruka's body.
I don't know anything about that.
That's nonsense.
The first thing I found strange
was the photo from the hot spring trip.
In that photo,
Haruka was not wearing a wedding ring.
It seems she hadn't worn a ring
for several years.
Then why was she wearing it
at the time of the fire?
That's what made me think.
Did someone perhaps
deliberately put the ring on Miwa
to disguise her?
There is only one person
who could make such a disguise
using a wedding ring
found somewhere in the house.
That would be…
Haruka herself.
That's not true!
It was me.
I did everything.
In this arson case,
the two of you conspired together.
So, why did you do such a thing?
Haruka visited several orthopedic clinics
over the past few years.
Her fracture from the fall
seemed unnatural,
and she had bruises that looked
as if she had been punched.
It seems Haruka was being
physically abused by Yasuyuki.
And you knew about it, right?
I already told you I did it!
Since I'm admitting to it,
just hurry up and arrest me!
The one who killed Miwa Tateno
was neither you
nor Haruka.
Isn't that right?
We obtained a warrant
and checked your dashcam.
On the day of the incident,
you two didn't want anyone to hear you
discussing the domestic abuse.
That's why you went for a drive.
You should really just go to the police.
The police?
But if I do that,
he really will kill me.
But you have to run away.
I can't.
No matter where I go,
he will chase me down.
Contrary to your statement,
Natsumi was actually with you.
And…
when you went to drop off
Haruka and Natsumi…
There we go.
What snack do you want?
What's wrong?
Natsumi.
-Yes?
-Wash your hands and go upstairs.
She's dead.
The police…
This is Miwa.
What?
You know her?
We were classmates in high school.
She comes to the clinic.
Why is she…
Anyway, the police…
Wait!
We have to do it.
This is your only chance.
Kozue?
Haruka…
You should die.
What are you saying?
We'll make it look like you died.
Then, you can be reborn.
And then,
you two immediately
went through with the plan.
First, you got Natsumi out to the car
in a nearby parking lot.
Then,
you put on the wedding ring.
And to completely burn away the body,
you doused her in kerosene.
Natsumi!
My daughter…
-My daughter is inside!
-What?
Of course, you could not fake
a child's remains.
Therefore, you reported
to the fire department
that you saw Natsumi
trapped inside the house.
There's a fire.
A girl is trapped inside,
and my friend went in there.
Please hurry!
And, she escaped from the back door
before the fire truck arrived.
She met up with Natsumi
and escaped in your car.
At first, we thought that you
and Yasuyuki were having an affair.
But that wasn't the case.
Kozue.
You…
were trying to protect Haruka
and Natsumi, right?
No!
Quit saying all this nonsense!
I did everything, it was me!
Haruka has nothing to do with it.
Haruka… Haruka is…
Your beloved partner.
Right?
She's the partner
you've been fighting together with
all along, isn't she?
I'm sorry.
Haruka, I'm sorry.
I couldn't protect you.
You were
about to go see Haruka
and her daughter, weren't you?
Could you tell us their location?
What will happen to Natsumi
if just the two of us are arrested?
At this rate, Yasuyuki will…
Don't worry.
I won't let that happen.
The police exist to protect
your loved ones.
We will protect her.
Please trust us.
Go ahead.
What?
You found Natsumi?
Yes.
Where is she? Please let me see her.
More importantly,
there is suspicion against you
for physically abusing Haruka.
What are you talking about?
I would never do that.
Sure, we've had a couple of
marital disputes before.
But anyone has those, don't they?
Either way,
please tell me where Natsumi is.
She is my dearest daughter.
I need to be with her.
I can't do that.
Why not?
Because you
are the person who killed Miwa Tateno.
You and Miwa had been having an affair
since last year's alumni association.
This way, please.
Thank you.
But she became dissatisfied
with that relationship…
What's wrong?
No, nothing. What shall we eat?
…and her behavior gradually escalated.
We have also found the message exchange
between Miwa and you.
On the night of the incident,
while Haruka and her daughter were away,
she seems to have barged into your house.
Cut it out already.
Since you can't seem to break up yourself,
I will tell your wife.
Stop joking.
I'm being serious!
Shall I just go tell her myself,
or will you divorce her?
Decide, now!
Or…
shall we die together?
After you ran away,
you must have been surprised
to hear Haruka died in the fire.
Eyewitnesses report seeing
Haruka and Natsumi taken by the fire.
That's not true.
It can't be true.
But upon seeing the wedding ring,
which she shouldn't have been wearing,
you realized the swap Haruka pulled off.
And then, you…
I know about you and Haruka.
And you?
You're relieved, aren't you?
The reason you went to see Kozue
was actually to get the whereabouts
of Haruka and your daughter, wasn't it?
I admit
that I ended up in that kind
of relationship with Miwa.
But,
I didn't kill her or anything.
There's not a single piece
of evidence, right?
Because it all vanished in the fire.
There is.
We've got evidence.
Where did you go after leaving the scene
following the murder?
Upon investigation,
we found out you went
to a home improvement center.
You purchased plastic buckets,
a shovel, and so on.
Also,
a large amount of industrial caustic soda.
WORKERS HEAVEN
RECEIPT
Originally used
for industrial cleaning tasks,
it seems it also has the effect
of dissolving skin and protein.
Did you intend
to dissolve and dispose of the body?
No.
That's…
That's not all.
Our colleagues were persistent
and examined the remains
over and over again.
When analyzing the internal structure
with a micro-CT,
we found a depression mark on the skull
that cannot be explained by heat.
It was a very small trace
that wouldn't normally be found.
But because of how skilled they are,
they were able to find it.
Next is the identification
of the murder weapon.
Next is the culprit.
They will not give up until they solve it.
I promised you, didn't I?
That we would get to the bottom of this.
We will definitely protect them.
Wait!
Yasuyuki admitted to the crime.
Of course,
you two also need to atone
for a serious crime,
but I think he will be in prison
for a long time for murder.
Thank you very much.
Really.
Not at all.
Kozue…
Thank you.
Finally, we're done.
Shall we take a break?
Yes.
Everyone, you all did such a great job.
Yes, we seriously did.
I'm really glad the case was solved.
I wonder if our investigation was useful.
I don't want to search
for anything for a while.
If you would like, please have some.
What?
Love-chan cookies.
-Cute.
-I've been hooked on them lately.
Cookies, huh?
Thank you.
-Thank you!
-Go ahead.
Since everyone overused
their prefrontal cortex,
the brain must be craving sugar.
I get that.
-I'll have one more.
-Go ahead.
You did a great job too, Ms. Kiryu.
Thank you very much.
Somebody's loved one.
Everyone
felt the same way, huh?
TAKASAKA FAMILY GRAVE
We are here to protect
people's loved ones.
You're suited to be a detective.
Why did you have to die so soon?
What you said before
about the meaning of a "loved one"…
In America,
they call the deceased a "loved one."
Does that mean someone…
who was important…
to someone else?
I feel like I've also…
managed to grasp
what that means to me, just a bit.
That
is a wonderful thing.
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot! It's a tie!
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot!
Okay, one more time.
Let's do it.
All right!
One, two! Rock, paper, scissors, shoot.
It's a tie.
Yes!
One, two! Rock, paper, scissors, shoot!
If he'd asked someone for help,
he might not have died.
Can you cook next week, too?
You can still start over.
Mr. Susaki wasn't alone, was he?
We have officially decided
to disband the MEJ.
Subtitle translation by: Maslin F.