MkvDrama.net
(This program is intended for mature audiences.
It may feature explicit content, violence, and strong language)
(All characters, places, and events
in this series are entirely fictitious)
Heh. You're finished, Irfan.
Hold on. Come here.
- Are you alright?
- I'm fine.
Go. Get going.
Easy now.
What should gonna do?
Mm... Easy.
Down!
=Love of Silom=
Shh!
Take them all out.
Wayu.
Can you stand?
Ugh...
You okay?
Krit, I hear someone.
Let's go. Can you walk?
- I can.
- Let's go.
Help!
Is anyone there?
Hey!
Help!
Don't! Don't come in!
It's locked, Krit.
I've got the victims.
They're on the third floor.
Search every room.
Then start the operation.
Hey, we're the police. We're the police.
Seal all the exits.
Don't let them get away.
What's going on?
I said what's going on?
You're about to get arrested!
You'd better hide well.
Hehe.
Oh! Sir.
The cops are burning this whole place.
Let's get out of here.
I've got a chopper ready for you, Sir.
Okay.
Surprise!
The chopper's late.
You can't get out in time.
There are two exits,
the front door and the back door.
We have to force them out.
So what should we do?
- Burn the building.
- Huh?
Isn't that dangerous, Captain?
Who said we're really going to burn it?
Once we've successfully rescued
the victims,
we'll use smoke bombs to force them out.
Send people to block both exits.
And around the whole building.
I'll go up to the rooftop.
In case they try to escape by chopper.
Wayu.
Be careful.
Haha.
Krit.
If you're so tough, come in!
Shoot, and we both die.
- Put the gun down. Don't touch him.
- You, put it down.
And let me walk away.
Put the gun down.
Hurry.
Oh, wow.
Bring Wayu to me, and I'll let you go.
- Bang.
- Wayu!
Haha.
Ouch.
You really love him, huh?
Wow.
A love affair between a spy
and a cop? What a cliche.
Sigh, since I can't have you anyway,
I'll at least leave you with a scar.
Wayu, throw!
Wayu, are you hurt?
I'm okay.
- Ouch.
- I'm okay.
Don't worry. I'm right here now.
Krit.
- I'm fine.
- Krit.
You're fine.
I'm glad.
Call an ambulance, please.
Krit!
Krit.
- Krit.
- Family can't come in here.
Please wait out front.
Can I go in to see him?
Family can't come in here.
Please wait out front.
Wayu, how is Krit?
He's been in there for two hours now.
He still hasn't come out.
- Ma'am.
- Darling.
Why don't you go sit down for a bit?
Hey, darling.
It's this kid.
He's the one who made Krit lose his way.
Sir, let's go sit down
and wait for the doctor.
Stop seeing Krit.
If you're a leech,
go cling to someone else.
Stop leeching off my son
and turning him into a freak.
It's disgusting.
Sir.
I don't know where you got
this kind of logic from.
But I've never once thought about
leeching off Krit as you said, Sir.
- We're together because we're in love.
- Love? Really?
You only love yourself.
If you really love Krit,
you should stay out of his life.
Let him live a good life.
- Not on someone with no future.
- Sir.
That's enough.
Wayu, go back for now.
No.
I'm staying here until Krit wakes up.
What are you still waiting for?
He is like this because of you.
If anything happens to him,
it'll be all your fault.
Remember that.
Calm down.
This is a hospital. That's enough.
- That's enough.
- Step outside.
Just step outside.
Here.
Thank you.
Hey.
Don't overthink it.
Krit's dad just spoke out of anger.
If Krit hadn't come to help me,
he wouldn't have to go through this.
If you get hurt
or anything happens to you,
Krit would be just as hurt.
Maybe it was like that before.
But not now anymore.
That's not true.
Krit never abandoned you, Wayu.
He's always been looking out for you.
Krit...
He hasn't moved on.
Wayu, just go back for today.
Wait until Krit's dad cools down,
and then come visit again.
I'll talk to him for you.
And I'll keep you updated
on how Krit's doing.
Even if I go back,
I still won't be able to sleep.
I'd rather stay here
until I'm sure he is safe.
Okay, that's fine.
Doctor.
- How is he?
- Doctor.
How is my son doing?
The surgery went well.
The patient is out of danger now.
During the surgery,
the patient lost a lot of blood,
and his heart stopped for two minutes.
So, we put in a breathing tube.
We managed to revive him.
Will this have any
repercussions for him?
From what I can see right now,
there's nothing to worry about.
We'll wait for him to wake up,
and run a full check.
Oh, okay.
- I'll take my leave.
- Alright.
- Thank you very much.
- Thank you.
Police have arrested Irfan Faruhanan,
also known as Ice.
A Thai-Malaysian national.
On charges of human
and organ trafficking.
He was also found in possession
of illegal drugs.
Ice was backed by Por,
who financed him from behind the scenes.
Wow, you're done already?
Thanks a lot for your cooperation
with today's questioning.
You're welcome. If you need
anything else, just let me know.
Sure thing.
If there's nothing else,
I'll get back to work.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
Hey, let's go grab
something good to eat.
Go.
Hey, you can totally trust me.
I'll take you to get something
seriously unhealthy.
Right, man?
(Rose)
(Krit's parents aren't here.)
(Visit whenever you want.)
Come to the hospital with me, yeah?
Are you going to eat hospital
health food or what?
I brought you some flowers, Krit.
So the room will smell nice.
I don't know...
if your parents
found out I brought them.
If they ever knew,
they'd probably be angry.
Why do we have to hide like this?
Can't people just care about
each other? Huh?
Relationships are one thing.
Being human is another. Right?
I really don't get it.
They're probably scared
I'll get back together with Krit.
What matters now
is the captain's health.
He still hasn't woken up.
Uh... Sorry, I didn't know
someone was here.
It's okay. Please go ahead.
Go ahead. Walk carefully, okay?
It's okay. I'm just dropping by
for a bit.
Besides, Krit hasn't woken up anyway.
Uh, are you a friend of Krit's
or his junior?
Uh, I'm his fiancée.
Once he wakes up,
we'll probably get married.
That's what my dad said.
Yes, yes.
If he wakes up, please tell him
that Mint brought him a melon.
- Yes.
- Okay, I'm coming.
Yes, okay.
That girl? Seriously?
But she's pretty cute.
But I think she's too young.
What do the adults even think?
Or is a good family name
all that matters?
I'm with you on this one.
You're a better match.
I'm serious, look at them.
You just fit him better.
She's pretty cute though.
Did you get hurt anywhere?
Hey. You're okay, right?
I'm alright, Mom.
Oh, dear. It's okay,
my child. It's okay.
After all that, you must've been
scared to death.
Yeah, right.
When Mom and I heard you'd been
kidnapped, we were so worried.
Why keep something this big
all to yourself?
I'm really sorry.
I've just had a lot to deal with.
I'm sorry too.
Yeah.
And the captain?
I saw on the news that
the captain was badly hurt.
Captain... He was shot.
But...
He's safe now.
He just hasn't woken up yet.
He'll wake up soon. He'll wake up.
He'll be fine, okay?
Don't think too much about it yet.
Good karma protecting good people.
You're not just stressed
about Captain not waking up, right?
What else is going on?
Tell us everything.
He is getting married.
What?
Wait, married? Married to whom?
And how do you know?
Sigh.
Well, today...
I went to visit him
at the hospital today and...
I ran into his fiancée.
What the heck?
Captain and I shouldn't have met at all.
Ending it like that
was probably for the best.
It's already bad enough
that his parents don't like me.
And now I've even met his fiancée.
Hey, it's really fine.
Good-looking people like you
can find plenty of partners.
Don't get hung up on just one guy, okay?
Really?
If he already has a fiancée,
why's he taking care of Singto?
What?
- Krit, right?
- Yeah.
You broke up with Wayu.
Why are you still looking after Singto?
I'm just keeping the promise
I made to Wayu.
But Wai, don't worry.
If Singto starts to improve,
I'll back off for good.
You still love Wayu, right?
If you still love him,
then why break up?
Why make things so hard?
Don't tell Wayu about this.
He doesn't need to worry about this.
He deserves someone good.
(He even hired a psychologist
to look after Singto at school.)
(And he secretly comes
to see Singto all the time.)
I'm sure Krit still loves you.
I really am.
About the marriage,
I'm sure it's arranged.
Rich people love marrying
their kids off for business.
Yeah. I've seen it in dramas.
Yeah, it might sound cheesy.
But you've got to listen
to your own heart.
You want to visit him, right?
Then just go.
If you want to do something
for him, then do it.
He's already done so much for you.
I think it's clear enough.
Now it's time for you
to be clear with him too.
Mm.
Sorry, no visitors are allowed
in this room.
Rose told me to come here.
Is she inside?
Rose didn't tell us anything.
Please step outside.
Oh, come on, Officer.
With a face like mine,
I couldn't hurt anyone.
Please let me in.
- No, you can't.
- No way.
I told you, I'm here on Rose's orders.
Let me in, please.
No, you can't.
Oh.
Wayu, are you okay?
These two officers won't let me go in.
Sorry, I forgot to tell them.
From now on, if he comes,
please let him in.
If anything happens,
I'll take responsibility.
- Okay.
- Sure.
Thank you for letting me in.
At first there was no guard, right?
Then why have someone now, Rose?
Krit's dad worried that Ice's men
or Por's might still be around.
So he had someone guard Krit,
just to be safe.
Yeah.
Then please look after him for me.
Today, his parents went back,
so the coast is clear.
I'll come back again this evening.
Thank you.
Bye.
Sleep well.
Aren't you bored yet, Krit?
Wake up and see me already.
Mm.
Hey, I've got something to show you.
See, am I awesome or what, Krit?
I've seen people doing this
for their partners lately.
I mean, for their exes.
But forget it, it's all good.
Current or ex,
I just made it for you.
Wake up and praise me already.
You know?
I'm waiting for you.
- Oh.
- Oh, Rose?
Where are you going, dear?
Not staying to watch over Krit?
Uh, I...
I'm just going down
to pick something up from the rider.
- I ordered some coffee.
- Oh, really?
I saw you bring a bag
and thought you were going home.
Oh, I just grabbed it on my way out.
- Hmm.
- Let's go.
Aren't you heading straight home?
You said you had errands.
He forgot his phone, that's all.
We'll hurry back for it.
You hurry down and get your things.
I'll see you in the room.
- Okay.
- Come on, let's go.
- Sir.
- Hmm?
I just checked and didn't see it.
Maybe you left it somewhere else?
I left it in the room.
But I checked just now, um...
It's not there.
- Maybe you left it at home.
- No.
I went to the bathroom
and left it there.
It's in there, I'm sure.
Let's go before traffic gets bad.
Sir, Ma'am.
- Hmm?
- I think...
Better to let Krit rest.
All this coming and going
isn't good for his health.
I think it'll be fine. I'm just grabbing
my phone and heading out.
- I mean...
- Rose.
What's going on? What's wrong with Krit?
Uh, no... Krit is not... Um, Sir...
Ma'am.
- Here it is, darling.
- Ah.
Good.
In that case, I'll go run my errands.
Anyway, look after Krit for me.
I'll be back soon.
- Sure, Ma'am.
- Tell me if you need anything.
- Let's go, darling.
- Uh-huh.
No need to rush, Ma'am.
I can take care of Krit.
- Darling.
- Wait.
Hello, Sir.
Why are you here again?
Can I take care of Krit
until he wakes up?
He saved my life, Sir.
I just want to repay him.
Ugh.
Sir, please just hear me out first.
If you want to repay him,
then don't show your face here again.
What else do you want? What do you need?
Your work always needs money, right?
Tell me how much you want.
- Is a million enough?
- Sir, that's too harsh.
Wayu just wants to be here
to take care of Krit.
Ma'am, please say something.
He really doesn't have
any bad intentions.
Sir.
I don't want money
or anything like that.
I just want to make sure he is safe.
That's all, Sir.
Have you forgotten already?
Who do you think made Krit
end up like this?
And now you're so worried
about his safety, huh?
- Sergeant.
- Yes, Sir.
Please give me a chance, Sir.
- Let me take care of Krit.
- Get him out of here.
- Come on.
- Sir.
Go.
- Go.
- Sir.
- And don't let him back in.
Understood.
- Go
- Sir.
Sir!
What do high-ranking officers like?
Status, image, classy stuff.
Luxury watches.
Tai, should I give the watch
the clients gave me
to Krit's dad?
Huh, yeah, that's good.
Then he'll know you've got a sugar mom.
It's not hard to trace those watches.
They can see who bought them.
There are only a few
in the whole country.
Next topic.
Social networks and parties, right?
He probably doesn't care about
the bar host scene or college circles.
He likes people who respect him
and follow orders.
And you keep arguing with him like that.
You'd call that following orders?
Then, things or activities
that show status.
Like guns and amulets.
Guns?
Then I'll buy a gun for Krit's dad.
I bet he'll love it.
Yeah, good idea. So he can shoot you
when you go see his son.
Can you stop with the digs, Tai? Huh?
So are you on Krit's dad's side,
or mine?
Here's my advice.
Just give up.
People their age
don't change their minds easily.
Just stop trying.
I feel sorry for you.
No. I'm never giving up. No way.
At least not until Krit wakes up.
- I'll take care of him myself.
- Wow.
Love really does make
people blind. Sigh.
Let me tell you something.
People at that level,
they don't need anything.
They just want to know
if you truly love their child.
That's it.
So,
being consistent might actually help.
That's good then.
I'll fight back with pure sincerity.
Yeah, that's how it should be, man.
- Please send the BP report for Room 3 quickly.
- Right away.
- Hello.
- Oh, hello.
I've brought fruit for everyone.
Thank you.
And...
Could you please change the flowers
in Captain Krit's room?
It's just that...
I was a victim in Captain Krit's case.
But right now,
they're not allowing visits.
So I can't go in.
I just want to repay Captain Krit.
Hmm, okay.
Alright.
Hello.
- Hello.
Could I trouble you to give
these snacks to Captain Krit?
- Sure.
- And also,
- could you please change the flowers?
- Sure.
Excuse me.
May I have your name?
- Oh, my name is Som.
- Oh.
May I call you Som?
- Oh, sure.
- Okay.
- Next time I'll bring snacks for you.
- Thank you.
Hello, Som.
- Hello, Wayu.
- Hello.
I brought salad rolls
and some fruit today.
Please share them around.
- Thank you so much.
- You're welcome.
- And the flowers.
- I'll do it just like before.
Alright.
- Just a sec.
- Okay.
Let me take a picture.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Hello.
- Hmm.
- Excuse me.
- Thank you.
The wound is no longer infected.
All bodily functions are normal.
But the patient isn't responding
to any stimuli at all.
What does it mean, doctor?
The surgery went well, didn't it?
So why is it like this now?
Even though the surgery went well,
it also depends on the patient,
on whether they're
strong enough to recover.
I'd like the family to discuss things
in case the worst happens.
Oh, darling.
Ma'am, please sit down first.
- Sit down.
- Please, just sit down first.
Easy now.
Take deep, slow breaths.
Slow, deep breaths.
Som, I'll go check that room for you.
- Please take care of it for me.
- Sure.
- Oh, Som.
- Hey, Wayu.
How's Captain doing?
Well, he isn't doing very well.
The doctor called the family
to prepare them for the worst.
When Captain's mom heard, she fainted.
She's being treated in a room nearby.
She was really shocked.
Then I'll leave these flowers
for Captain's mother, too.
And here's some fruit,
please help yourselves.
Yes.
Oh, you're awake. How are you feeling?
I feel a bit dizzy.
Who brought these flowers?
Oh, the victim in Captain Krit's case.
He brings flowers
for Captain Krit every day.
When he learned you were sick,
he brought some for you too, Ms. Pimjit.
Yes, Rose.
Krit's condition
has worsened again, Wayu.
Wayu, can you hear me?
I'll head over right away.
I want Norepinephrine,
4 to 250, IV, rate 5.
Yes, doctor.
What's happening?
Oh, the patient is having
a sudden drop in blood pressure.
The doctor will give medication to raise
the blood pressure. Excuse me.
- Okay.
- Darling.
- No. You can't come in yet.
- What's going on?
No, you still can't come in.
- Hey.
- Huh?
What's happening?
Krit's blood pressure dropped suddenly.
- The doctor is helping him.
- Excuse me.
Doctor, the medication is here.
Krit.
I'm safe now. You have to be safe too.
It's all set, doctor.
- Please keep an eye on him for me.
- Of course.
Sorry.
Hey, what are you staring at?
Get him out of here.
No, don't. Let him stay.
Please let him stay with Krit.
I'm begging you, please.
Krit.
You've always wanted
to see me, haven't you?
Well, here I am now.
You don't have to secretly
look for me anymore.
Please wake up and talk to me first.
You haven't even apologized to me yet.
I've only ever heard
about you from others.
You have to wake up
and tell me yourself.
You can't just die and run away
from me like this, Krit.
Krit.
Nonsense.
How could I die?
Krit.
- Krit.
- Call a nurse, hurry!
Yes.
Krit, are you awake?
Krit.
He's awake.
- Krit.
- Excuse me.
Let me check his blood pressure.
His blood pressure looks good now,
and his pulse is normal.
Darling.
Krit, you're awake?
Krit.
Ginseng chicken soup,
and some steamed pumpkin.
I ordered these specially for today.
They're all soft foods.
You'll be able to eat them.
Really? You call this "soft"?
Yeah, this is soft.
Eat up, dear,
so you'll get your strength back.
Is it too hot? If it is, let Mom
cool it down first.
Here, let me cool it down for you first.
No. It's fine.
- I can eat it.
- Okay.
Ouch, it's okay. I will feed you.
The food here is really good.
Take it slow, dear.
Slowly.
Wait.
Careful, dear. It's hot.
- Oh.
- Wait.
Yeah.
Let me wipe that for you, okay?
Okay, eat up.
- Yeah, eat up.
- Eat up, dear.
Dad, Mom, just act normal.
I'm not used to this.
- Hmph.
- Uh.
This is me being normal, you know.
- Ah, no.
- I'm normal too.
- Come on, just a little more, okay?
- Okay.
Mm.
Is it good, dear?
Okay, let's go.
Let's get you moving today.
Bend your knees.
Lift your hips a bit. Up.
Good. Mm.
Good. Now push your legs out.
Stretch them all the way.
Okay, up again. Do it on your own.
Very good. Ah.
Now push up to standing.
Straighten your knees.
Ah, very good.
- Can you manage?
- Oh.
Okay, it's fine then.
Let's do it one more time.
Can you manage?
Try it. Try again. Come on.
Straighten your knees. Push through.
Very good. Mm.
Mm. Sigh.
Step right, then left.
Step with your right, then your left.
Right foot first, then left.
Step right, then left.
Lean forward, press the cane, and stand.
Very good. Now tuck the cane
under your arm.
Good. Keep stepping like that.
Keep going.
Can you manage?
- I can.
- Okay.
You're so stubborn.
You just won't stay in your room.
So? Do you feel better now
that you're outside?
Yeah, a bit better.
At first, I just felt dizzy
and out of it.
But now I feel way better.
Just a bit more physical therapy left.
Soon I'll be back out catching
bad guys and putting them in jail.
How's your wound?
Does it still hurt?
A little, but way better than before.
Here.
When you were out of it,
Wayu came to see you every day.
He brought flowers
to brighten up the room.
Even with school so busy,
he still brought you flowers every day.
But your fiancée?
I haven't seen her once.
Pretty sure she only sent one melon.
So how come now I'm awake,
Wayu hasn't come to see me?
He comes, and they just send him away.
Your dad's chased him off
more times than I can count.
They even put cops at the door,
but he still kept trying.
He couldn't even get in to see you.
So he left the flowers with the nurses,
asked them to change them for you.
Wayu worries about you so much.
Hey! Take it easy.
What's wrong with you?
Captain's awake.
What are you stressing about now?
I don't know how to act.
I don't know what I'm supposed to do.
What do you even need to do?
Just act normal.
So what am I supposed to do?
We already broke up, and his dad
doesn't even like me.
Back when you were visiting him
in the hospital, sending flowers every day,
darn, you were really
going all out, man.
So now he's awake,
what is wrong with you?
What's wrong with you?
- Anyway, they called me for a client.
- Hey.
What now?
I'm booking you for the whole night.
Hey, what is wrong with you?
How are you going to pay for that?
Foei.
- What?
- Let me just sign first.
Just put it on my tab.
I'll settle it later.
Okay, deal.
Come on.
What is this?
Am I working for free today?
Ah.
Okay.
Since I'm working for free anyway,
I'll entertain you myself.
Come on, bottoms up.
Go.
You're not done yet.
(The First Night We Held Hands,
Season Five)
♪Look how long it took
to first hold hands♪
♪It's a miracle
we even found each other♪
♪Don't let us fall apart over
blind anger and misunderstandings♪
♪Look how hard we fought for this love♪
Krit.
I brought your favorite fruit.
I'll peel it for you.
- Mom.
- Hm?
I want to get out of here.
Mm. I know you're bored.
This evening I'll take you out
for a walk in the garden.
It's not that.
Well...
I want to leave the hospital.
Krit.
You only woke up a few days ago.
Wait until you're a bit stronger.
Mom.
I feel a lot better now.
And all my test results came back fine.
I do physical therapy every day,
and I can walk much better now.
- Here.
- Krit.
Don't do this. You're scaring me.
I can walk just fine now, Mom.
Let me go out, please.
I promise. I'll take
good care of myself.
What should we eat, then?
How about fried garlic pork
with a fried egg?
Oh, that again?
- You eat that every day.
- Come on.
- I just like it.
- I'm sick of it.
- Huh?
- What do you want to eat today?
Maybe noodles. Noodles sound better.
- Ugh, it's always this menu.
- Wayu.
- See you, Wayu.
- See you.
Krit.
Wayu.
I'm sorry.
For not telling you the truth back then.
But back then, I really meant it.
I wanted you to find someone better.
But now I know.
That my life means nothing
without you by my side, Wayu.
I don't know if it's too late.
But can you give me one more chance?
What chance are you asking for now?
(Kritsadawut Siriwatmontri
Nov 9, 19/Blood/Code 20839001)
Well...
I love you so much.
But I don't want us to go back
to where we were.
And if one day we break up again,
I'll hurt even more than before.
We're not breaking up again.
I won't break up with you again, Wayu.
Well, I just need a little time.
That's fine.
♪Please, I never wanted to leave you♪
♪And I never wanted to be this far away♪
♪But I accidentally did something♪
(Directed by Banchorn Vorasataree)
♪I just realized that without you♪
♪How much it hurts♪
♪Please, I never wanted to leave you♪
♪As you were♪
♪I won't♪
♪Start the fights like I used to♪
♪Please don't get tired of me just yet♪
♪Come back and let's be us again♪
♪Looking back on our story♪
♪Only when apart did I know♪
♪How deeply we're bound♪
♪My heart's this broken♪
♪I hate that♪
♪No familiar face is left♪
♪When we're far apart♪
♪I finally reflect♪
♪That it was me♪
♪Who chose the wrong path♪
♪One that breaks my own heart♪
♪Honestly, I never wanted to leave you♪
♪I never wanted to be this far away♪
♪But I accidentally did something♪
♪Said things in spite, so wrong♪
♪Shedding tears♪
♪Over the words of my own♪
♪Actually, I want you back♪
♪As you were♪
♪Even though
I always started the fights♪
♪Please don't get tired of me just yet♪
♪Why are you gone so much longer now?♪
♪Please, I never wanted to leave you♪
♪And I never wanted to be this far away♪
♪But I accidentally did something♪
♪I was wrong, crying as I apologize♪
♪I just realized that without you♪
♪How much it hurts♪
♪Please, I never wanted to leave you♪
♪As you were♪
♪I won't♪
♪Start the fights like I used to♪
♪Please don't get tired of me just yet♪
♪Come back and let's be us again♪
MkvDrama.net