How am I supposed to live
if I don't have you, Lal?
The worst-case scenario
is that Korn set up the company
under the name of his paralyzed friend,
used it as a vendor,
and sold everything to us
at inflated prices.
With all this evidence,
are you still going to deny it?
I've had time to think it over.
I only see you as a friend with benefits.
They've finished repairing your room.
You can take a look.
It's as good as new.
Um…
if there's anything you're not happy with,
just let me know.
I'll pass it along
to the person next door.
It's okay.
Thank you so much.
THANK YOU, LAL.
I'm sorry.
Lal.
Why weren't you answering your phone?
Huh?
Oh… I had a lot on my mind,
so I didn't hear it ring.
It's okay.
We stayed up all night
gathering the information.
Everything's ready.
I looked into it.
Mr. Tatsanai was in an accident
two years ago
and has been paralyzed ever since.
An accident?
Yes. He got hit by a car.
Here you go.
WE'LL GET THROUGH THIS TOGETHER.
So his wife took over the company?
I'm not sure.
But one thing's certain.
Mr. Tatsanai's wife
has the same last name as Korn.
Are they relatives?
More than that.
She's Korn's biological younger sister.
So he used her paralyzed husband's name
to set up the company
and take on those contracts.
Exactly.
That’s why Korn refused
to let us change vendors
even though this one
charges more than the others.
They're in cahoots.
Korn… you're going down.
Oh.
Thanks.
Ouch!
Lal.
Yes?
Ms. Nan would like to see you.
Oh, I'm about to meet her in her office.
Yes?
In the meeting room.
Dude.
Huh?
I thought it was an earthquake.
Why are you shaking your feet like that?
I'm scared.
What are you scared of?
You're not the one who cheated.
Exactly. We didn't do anything wrong.
We've got nothing to be afraid of.
Lal.
Lal, why is Korn here?
How are we supposed to talk
with him in the room?
Good morning, everyone.
First of all, thank you all
for taking the time
to attend today's meeting.
As you all know,
I place great importance
on transparency in the workplace.
After receiving a report
of a possible violation of company policy,
I couldn't simply ignore it.
Ms. Lal.
Yes?
Is it true…
that you and Ms.Wine are in a relationship
beyond that of coworkers?
Pardon?
I've received a report that you
and Ms. Wine, the Head of Accounting,
are in a relationship.
Well…
Lal, just tell the truth.
I…
Everyone else from the Sales team,
please wait outside.
Excuse me,
but that's not why we asked
to meet with you today.
We wanted to discuss Korn's corruption.
You made that story up
because I found out your secret.
That's not true!
I owe you an apology.
I've been hard on you in meetings,
so maybe you've grown to resent me.
And with several long-time clients
canceling their contracts lately,
you must be under a lot of stress.
But I never imagined
you'd try to bring me down like this.
No! That's not true.
I mean…
Ms. Wine,
we're discussing
your relationship with Ms. Lal.
Please take a seat.
(With all this evidence,)
are you still going to deny it, Wine?
Did you really think
I didn't know your girlfriend
has been digging into my business?
Whatever she's doing,
tell her to stop.
Otherwise, these photos
will stop her for me.
Whatever you do,
you can't outrun the consequences.
I'm smarter than you think.
I've gotten away with it once before.
Don’t you remember?
This world belongs to the winners.
The smarter person
always comes out on top.
Calling the horrible things
you've done "being smart"?
What kind of person are you?
Say whatever you want.
Your fate and your girlfriend's
are in my hands.
I always thought
you didn't like me
because you had bad taste.
Turns out,
this is the real reason.
What's that supposed to mean?
I'm just giving you a friendly warning.
If you want to keep your relationship going,
do your job and stay out of my business.
That's all.
And I won't lay a finger on you or Lal.
Everyone from the Sales team,
please wait outside.
That's not necessary.
They can stay.
I have nothing to hide.
Ms. Lal is the Head of Sales,
and you are the Head of Accounting.
A romantic relationship
between the two of you
is a violation of the company's
Conflict of Interest policy.
Here at our company, as executives
we are expected to uphold fairness
and transparency in everything we do.
I advise both of you to tell the truth now
before this proceeds
to a formal investigation.
If the company finds that
you have indeed violated company policy,
the disciplinary action
will be much more severe.
Ms. Nan, hold on.
But this matter is much more
complicated than it seems.
Shouldn't we appoint
an investigation committee
and follow the proper procedure?
I wasn't asking for anyone else's opinion.
Ms. Lal.
Ms. Wine.
Are the two of you in a relationship
beyond that of coworkers?
Lal.
Say it.
No.
Ms. Lal and I are not dating.
Are you certain?
We don't accuse people without evidence.
Then show me the evidence.
The two of you kissed.
Are you still saying
you're not in a relationship?
No. We're not.
Then what would you call it?
A coworker's kiss?
It was just a kiss.
It didn't mean anything.
There were no feelings involved.
Ms. Wine, if you're going to lie,
at least make it convincing.
People can kiss whoever they want.
It doesn't have to mean anything.
That's perfectly normal.
Or has that never happened to you?
I guess not.
You.
I've never seen Ms. Lal as anything
more than a coworker.
And I've already told her that directly.
Is that right, Ms. Lal?
Yes.
See?
I don't have feelings for her.
I don't love her.
So how could we possibly be dating?
We only talk about work.
I know nothing
about Ms. Lal's personal life,
and she knows nothing about mine.
We don't have any relationship
beyond work.
At most, we interact only when necessary.
To be honest,
I don't even like her.
She makes mistakes all the time
and is constantly creating problems
for me to clean up.
And she's always smiling,
even after causing trouble,
like nothing ever happened.
Just seeing her face annoys me.
So how could I possibly be dating her?
But I understand
why everyone would question me
because my actions have given people
reason to doubt me.
So I'll take responsibility by resigning.
Wait a minute.
You just said it meant nothing.
Yet now you're resigning
to take responsibility.
Don't you think
that's a little contradictory?
That’s because I won't let anyone
use this accusation…as a weapon
to stop Ms. Lal from doing
what she needs to do.
That's why
I'm taking full responsibility by resigning.
Even if you resign,
the allegations won't end here.
I will establish an investigation committee
and see this case through to the very end.
Good.
Jantra, could you please explain
the company's Conflict of Interest policy
regarding personal relationships
between employees or executives
and the company's vendors
or business partners?
The company's vendors
and business partners
must not be in romantic
or marital relationships
with the company's employees
or executives,
as this may create a conflict of interest
or allow personal interests.
Ms. Nan,
I hope Mr. Korn's case…
will be investigated
under the same standards
as Ms. Lal's and mine
because I believe
that fairness and transparency
are the most important principles
any executive should uphold.
That's standard practice
at the global companies
you used to work for, isn't it?
Ms. Wine.
I'll submit my resignation today.
Once you've formed
the investigation committee,
don't forget to call me in.
Wine.
Yes?
Why did you do that?
What did I do?
You resigned.
Why didn't you tell me?
Why should I?
Why are you taking
all the responsibility yourself?
I mean, I…
Ms. Lal.
How many times do I have to tell you?
We're nothing to each other.
I'm only taking responsibility
for my own actions. That's all.
Then I'll resign too.
If you want to let your emotions
outweigh your responsibilities,
that's your choice.
It has nothing to do with me.
But I do feel sorry for your team.
They've trusted you and followed your lead
through all of this.
And don't forget,
your family is still counting on you.
As a fellow team leader,
let me give you a suggestion.
Before you make any decision,
think a little more
about the people standing behind you.
Ms. Nan asked for a break first.
I'm sorry you all had to witness
something like this.
I really didn't know…
You don't have to apologize anymore, Lal.
You don't have to carry everything
by yourself alone anymore.
It's okay.
You've still got the two of us.
We may not be able to do much,
but we'll always be by your side.
It's okay, Lal. It's okay.
Tangkwa.
Yeah?
You’re close to Numnim
from Sales, aren’t you?
Give this to her. She'll need it.
Wine.
Proud.
These are the documents
our Sales team gathered.
And these are additional documents
from Accounting.
There were several cases where Korn
approved huge orders from this vendor,
causing serious overstock,
even though these products
weren't selling well.
However, he still approved
several unnecessary purchases.
Accounting found it suspicious,
so they forwarded everything to us.
As we said from the beginning,
the Sales team has no intention
of discrediting anyone.
We're simply doing our job
for the company's benefit.
You're pretty bold
to make such a serious report.
We have nothing to hide,
so we have nothing to be afraid of.
Excellent work, Sales team.
Management will investigate the facts
as quickly as possible.
We’ll set up an investigation committee
according to company policy.
Thank you very much.
I'll excuse myself now.
Ms. Lal.
Keep up this standard of work.
You all did an excellent job.
Thank you.
Everything seems to have worked out
so why don't I feel happy at all?
I guess we've just been through
too much today.
But we really have to thank Tangkwa
for bringing those extra documents.
Actually, it was because of Wine.
She assigned Proud to gather everything,
and I was just the one
who delivered it to you two.
So Wine already knew Lal and us
were investigating Korn?
I think so.
That's probably why she told Proud
to prepare all the documents.
Besides…
there's something Accounting
has been suspicious about.
What is it?
Ever since New's case…
I think New's insider
is still in this company.
Why do you think that?
The information New leaked
to our competitor wasn't old information.
It was newly updated data,
like the price from the new vendor
our company had just negotiated with.
That sounds like
we've got a long investigation ahead.
So what are you going to do next?
Lal just reported New,
so New's insider is probably
dying to get rid of her right now.
That's why we absolutely
can't tell the Sales team.
That one would charge in without thinking
and put herself in danger.
I want you two to help me with this.
Awww, Wine has been doing
this much for Lal?
Stay strong, buddy. Hang in there.
Maybe she's doing it for the company?
Tangkwa… Wine…
If opening your heart only brings pain,
then open a bottle with me instead.
What?!
Lal! Come on!
Lal.
You can't mope around
like stale leftovers all night.
Let's go have a drink.
No. I'm not in the mood.
See?
I told you.
Having a friend with benefits
is dangerous.
If you're not sure,
don't give away your heart.
Just look at you.
Yeah.
You were right about everything.
You warned me.
You told me,
but I was the one who gave her my heart
while she never wanted it.
I never thought I'd fall this hard.
If stopping myself from loving someone
were that easy,
I'd have done it a long time ago.
I can't deal with this anymore.
Lal… it's okay.
I just want to stop loving her.
I want to stop missing her.
Lal.
No love is ever easy, okay?
You've been with her for so long.
Of course you're attached.
But one day it'll get better
one way or another.
Alright?
I'm selfish.
I just wish she'd miss me
the way I miss her…
even half as much.
It's okay. It's okay, Lal.
Matching pajamas?
Yeah.
I thought they were cute,
so I bought them for us.
But I'm sorry I couldn't stop myself
from feeling this way.
What the heck?
Are you printing from your phone?
Yeah, but my phone's acting up.
Just share the file with me.
I'll print it for you.
Okay.
I just sent it.
Got it.
All set.
Thank you so much.
I'm glad to see you smiling again.
I like it when you smile like this.
Huh?
What's wrong now?
Did you press the red button earlier?
No, I pressed the green one.
That's exactly the problem.
Next time, press the red button instead.
By the way, are you going to
Wine's farewell party today?
Today?
She didn't invite me.
I don't think I should go.
If you're not going,
then come with me instead.
♪ Invisible to the eyes,
but feel it in our hearts ♪
♪ No matter where we orbit,
it’s you I’m thinking of ♪
Why's everyone so quiet?
Not having fun?
You’re having enough fun for everyone.
Come on! Get up! No more moping!
Get up! Let's go!
I can't be lively.
I'm too heartbroken inside.
You’re crying this much.
Is Wine resigning or dying?
Bas!
I’m sorry I'm late.
Wine.
I don't want you to leave.
You've taught me so much.
I only turned out this way
because you were so strict with me.
Otherwise, I'd probably still
be an airhead.
Well, you still are.
Bas!
Uh… I didn't know what to get you,
so this is just a little gift
from Nim and me.
Good luck on the path you've chosen.
Thank you so much, both of you.
I'm still mad, you know.
You resigned without telling me.
I'm sorry. Please don't be mad.
You're already capable enough.
You don't need me,
and I know you'll do just fine.
I still wish you'd stay.
Alright! Enough being sad!
Let's party! Come on.
Wine. Sit here.
Hey.
Hmm?
Tell Lal to hurry up and get here.
I'm typing!
Look how tiny my fingers are!
Then why don't you send a voice message?
Right. I'm an idiot.
Exactly.
Yeah. Hang on.
LAL, WINE’S HERE. HURRY UP.
It's a farewell party.
How could I possibly miss it?
One beer, please.
Sure.
I'd like wine today.
Red wine, please.
Certainly.
Do you like Wine?
Well,
I drink it sometimes.
That's not what I meant.
I'm asking you directly.
Do you like Wine?
Yes.
Why?
She doesn't seem like your type at all.
That's the thing.
Maybe I was just caught up in the moment.
So you've moved on now?
My turn.
Medsai, do you like…
lying with a straight face?
♪ From now on,
the word 'love' means nothing ♪
♪ Because you're the one
who destroyed it ♪
Which one's thicker?
Korn's face or Bangkok roads?
What?
Uh… your high notes are amazing.
Higher than a ghost's.
Yeah, perfect high notes.
Just right.
I'm tired. You sing.
Tired?
-Me?
-Yeah.
I can't sing.
I told you to sing so just do it.
Why the hell did he come?
Yes?
Bas! Come sing
“Why did you come?” with me?
Sure. I'll be Bird Thongchai.
You can be Jintara.
LAL, THE TROUBLEMAKER'S HERE. HURRY.
Numnim.
Yes?
I'm in the group chat too.
Ahh!!! Wrong chat!
I'll just leave then!
Just leave the group, not the party!
Tangkwa!
Come be Bird for me. Come on.
Fine.
Bird it is.
You think you can just
get away that easily?
What do you want from me?
Lal will still be working here.
I'm not letting her live in peace.
Yeah.
She'll definitely stay.
But you… probably won't.
You have no idea
what I've been through to get where I am.
I've dealt with loudmouthed women
plenty of times.
I used to be scared of you.
But now I keep wondering
why I was ever scared of you.
You're not scary at all.
You're just pathetic.
Wine.
What does that mean?
Save your questions for the courtroom
because there's no way
you're getting away with this.
Hey.
Making accusations like that?
You'll be the one getting sued.
Don't worry.
The evidence is already in the hands
of the people who need to see it.
At first, I had no idea it was you
REPORTING MISCONDUCT AND WHISTLEBLOWING
until Accounting sent over
the fraud documents related to Korn.
That's when I found an invoice
from the higher-priced vendor
with incorrect dates.
Accounting had to review
the application form
to approve the purchase request.
So what?
Wine would never let a mistake
like that slip through,
which means she never signed
that purchase approval form.
This is not Wine's signature.
If it's Wine’s signature,
I can recognize it
from even the tiniest details.
You picked the wrong person to mess with.
You messed with me
who was head over heels for Wine.
The company data leak,
the insider helping New…
It all makes sense now.
You're the Purchasing Supervisor.
You have access
to the company's confidential server.
And you were the one who told Korn
about Wine and me…
just to get rid of both of us.
I sent it.
Got it.
I saw that photo.
You saved Wine's story
so you could use it against us one day,
didn't you?
Korn, these two are secretly dating.
If you check the CCTV footage carefully,
you'll find proof against them.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
NUMNIM’S
STOP STEALING IT!!!
Let go!
You may get away today,
but you won't get away forever.
Hey, you think
you're the only one who can fight back?
I can fight back too.
Go ahead.
Come on.
You said this company was like
one family, just like in a TV drama.
I never thought
you'd be playing the villain.
My treat.
Thanks for helping me.
If I hadn't brought the Accounting team,
she probably wouldn't have believed me.
I helped Wine, not you.
Numnim, I told you I'm not going.
(Lal! Wine's disappeared!)
(And Korn too!)
What?!
Korn.
Stay still, Wine.
Where are you taking me?
You'll find out soon enough.
What are you doing, Wine?!
Stay still.
-Let me go!
-What are you doing, Wine?!
Let me go!
Wine!
Ouch!
There!
You like using force, huh?!
Lal!
You want to get run over?
Fine!
Lal!
Damn it!
Be my girlfriend.
Will you be my girlfriend?
What were you expecting me to say?
“Okay.”
I heard you've always wanted
to go to Japan.
An opportunity like this
doesn't come around often.
Whether you're gone for three months
or three years,
I'm not changing my mind.
SEE YOU IN YOUR ROOM.