If I liked Wine, why would I kiss you?
Even though
I still don't know your answer,
just being with you like this
already makes me really happy.
So, what are you going to do next?
I've already applied for a new job.
I'm waiting to hear back for an interview.
And don't tell them
why you left your previous job.
You don't need to damage your reputation
for nothing.
They might say it was your fault
for not being careful
and for letting him in yourself.
Mom…
It's not that
I don't understand you, Wine.
But society doesn't understand you
the way I do.
Whatever you do,
you need to be really careful.
The way you dress,
the way you carry yourself.
Remember this, Wine.
Not everyone
has good intentions toward us.
Don't trust people too easily.
I'm only warning you
because I care about you.
I don't want to see you get hurt.
Lal, you’ve been working here
for several months now.
How has it been?
Tell me about it.
I think I’m lucky to have a good team.
My subordinates are hardworking,
and they’re very capable.
There have been some other issues,
but only here and there.
Have the clients been complaining?
Yes.
For example, with documents,
if even one line is wrong,
we can’t just cross it out.
We have to send it back
and have everything signed again.
Or if the manager or supervisor
signs something differently
from what’s stated in the email,
the accounting and admin teams
won’t let it pass easily.
That’s why the workflow
hasn’t been that smooth.
Policies are one thing, of course.
But I think it’s pretty normal in an office
where most of the staff are women.
What do you mean?
Women tend to be very detail-oriented,
which I think is a good thing.
But sometimes they can be fussy
and turn small things into big issues.
Well, I’m not trying to criticize,
but based on my experience,
men make better supervisors than women.
Wow.
Is that really about gender,
or is it just a personal attitude?
Probably both.
I meant you.
Being this sexist,
is that just your attitude, Mr. Korn?
Since we’re already
talking about this issue,
let me ask you something.
The belief that
men are better drivers than women,
better at work,
more emotionally stable,
or better leaders than women…
Don’t these beliefs
come from unequal attitudes?
Sometimes I wonder
if the problem really exists,
or if it’s because
women are being stereotyped.
Whoa, whoa.
Lal, you’re taking this so seriously.
I was just expressing my opinion.
You don’t have to lecture me like that.
Oh, I wouldn’t dare lecture you.
Something like this should’ve been taught
by your parents, shouldn’t it?
Oh, Lal. You’re here too?
I was just about to leave.
Excuse me.
Wait, I’m leaving too.
Alright.
What a shame. It was just getting fun.
But I’ll head off first.
I need to go get my car.
I came here on a motorcycle earlier.
See you tomorrow.
Let’s go.
Excuse me.
Are they secretly dating or what?
It’s that obvious.
You think they were plucking
each other's itchy hair?
Why didn’t she tell us anything?
I feel slighted.
I thought we were close.
With a mouth as big as yours,
I wouldn’t tell you either.
Waaah.
And honestly, it’s her private matter.
She has the right to choose
whether to tell us or not.
But no matter what, she's still our Lal.
True.
Our sis is gorgeous, huh?
Even Wine surrendered to her.
Uh, from what I saw,
I think it’s the other way around.
Lal is totally losing in every way.
And what else is there that we don’t know?
Are you sure?
Mm. Of course I’m sure.
No.
I mean, are you sure you really like me?
We’ve come this far,
and you’re still asking me that?
Then what about Wine?
I like you, Tangkwa.
Is that clear enough?
Don’t mention others anymore.
TANGKWA AND I HEADED BACK ALREADY.
DON'T WORRY.
Lal.
Hmm?
I'm sorry I didn't tell you about Korn.
I was afraid you wouldn't like him
and that you'd end up
having problems with him.
He should know what kind of person he is
if people react to him like that.
But he's our boss now.
If you end up clashing with your boss,
work won't be easy for you.
So what?
Are we just supposed to accept
someone like that?
Come on.
Just listening to him talk tells you
how messed up his attitude is.
Lal, please.
Don't make an enemy out of him.
It's not just you I'm worried about.
I'm afraid your team
will get dragged into it too.
What if he tries something disgusting
with you again?
It's not that
I don't understand you, Wine.
But society doesn't understand you
the way I do.
Whatever you do,
you need to be really careful.
(The way you dress,
the way you carry yourself.)
But he's married now. He has a family.
And he told me himself that
what's over is over.
I don't think he'd dare do
something like that to me again.
Fine.
I'll try not to bite his head off.
No more trouble with him, okay?
One of your long-time clients
suddenly changed their mind.
Aren't you going to catch up with them
and find out why?
I was actually planning to ask today.
Looks like the sales team
has been spoiled for too long.
That’s why you've neglected your team.
So tell me, is everything delayed
because of the system
(or because of you?)
Here.
I bought you bubble tea.
I'm already feeling terrible,
and even this isn't helping.
That was the harshest scolding
we've ever had.
Here. Drink it.
Because she knew telling you
wouldn't help anyway?
We already fired New,
but the client still
went with another company.
If I were you, I'd start asking myself
what the real problem is.
Proud.
What exactly are you trying to say?
I'm just telling the truth.
If your boss keeps things
from you like this,
doesn't that clearly mean she doesn't think
you're someone she can rely on?
Hey.
Watch your mouth.
Are you looking for a fight?!
Come on then!
Don't, Numnim! No!
Get in here!
Proud!
-If you've got the guts, come at me!
-Come on.
You're tiny, but you're acting so tough.
What are you even doing?
Eh?
Don't take Korn's words to heart.
You take such good care of your clients.
Even when one of them was sick,
you personally delivered the products.
You never neglected them like Korn said.
He just started working here.
What does he even know?
Maybe…
my best still isn't good enough.
That's why my team got scolded
in front of everyone in the meeting.
But I think your team understands.
They've always understood me.
No matter what I do,
they'll always follow me.
That's why I want to protect them
as much as I can.
The reason I didn't tell them about you
was because I was afraid
they'd end up helping me keep it a secret.
Then they'd get dragged into this too.
I think you're carrying everything
on your shoulders by yourself.
It's still not enough.
I have to do more.
I have my team to look after.
My mom. My younger sibling.
I can't just let it go.
Oh!
What am I supposed to do?!
Bas? Numnim?
How long have you two been standing there?
Uh…
We just got here.
We were bringing you
some documents to sign.
Where are they?
The documents?
The documents…
Oh! The client's documents!
We were going to have you sign them,
but we forgot.
Yeah! We forgot.
All the required documents
have been submitted.
Okay.
Thank you.
Uh-huh.
We'll get going then.
I really, really love you, Lal.
I'm so happy for you.
Happy about what?
Oh…
She meant the documents.
Wine said everything had been submitted.
Come here, you!
Cheese!
Huh?
I wasn't calling you.
I meant the cheese. It's all over the place.
Well, I got startled.
You suddenly called me out
and then told me someone asked you
to be her girlfriend.
I just got asked out.
But what shocked me even more
was that it was incredibly hot Lal!
I'm completely confused.
When did you two even make this happen?
Why didn’t I know?
I'll tell you later.
But right now,
I need you to help me think.
So what did you tell her?
I haven't answered yet.
What?!
You still haven't answered?
Then what are you waiting for?
A purchase order?
It's just…
No.
I…
I don't know.
Give me your phone.
I'll reply for you.
Give it to me.
No!
Look at you, being so possessive of her,
and you're still saying you don't know?
Is it that you don't know
whether you like her
or you don't know how to answer
without getting shy?
That's exactly what's stressing me out.
I've never dated anyone before.
I’m scared. What if I say yes…
and I end up not being a good girlfriend?
Would we just end up breaking up?
The only reason
you're overthinking this so much
is because you really like her, isn't it?
Sure, breaking up would hurt.
But wouldn't it hurt even more
if you never even
gave the relationship a chance?
Then…
That’s true.
I can't imagine my life
without her anymore.
I believe Lal is just as scared as you are.
Who wouldn't be?
But I think the love she has for you
is greater than her fear.
So think about it this way.
If someone can find the courage
simply because she wants to love you,
can't you be brave for her too?
You’re overthinking, huh?
Where did you learn to talk like that?
(I hope you understand me, Lal.)
I do.
The reason I called
was because I wanted to know
what our company needs to improve
so we can provide
the best service possible.
(I went back and forth
on the decision many times.)
(But another company offered a price
that was much lower.)
(They clearly undercut everyone.)
(Their process was also much faster.)
(We didn't have to wait at all.)
I understand.
I'll bring this feedback
to my team and the management today.
Thank you so much.
Eh? You're all still here?
We've been doing some investigating.
Investigating what?
Well, our competitor has been running
a price-cutting promotion.
That means their costs
must be lower than ours.
So I asked a friend to find out
which vendor they're using.
It turns out the vendor we switched to
charges us twice the market price.
Really?
But the GM recommended that vendor.
He said they were trustworthy
and that we should
build a relationship with them.
I remember you telling me that.
-But—
-Forget it. Let me explain.
This is all thanks to
my nosy detective skills.
I searched the name
of the other authorized signatory
to see who he was.
And?
Remember when I stalked Korn's background?
He's Korn's classmate.
They went to the same university.
See?
I remembered Korn graduated from there.
When I saw the owner's profile,
I got suspicious.
Being nosy really does pay off.
Are you insulting me?
No.
So this is obviously collusion.
Actually, whether it's not
isn't even the point.
This violates company policy.
People with close personal relationships
aren't allowed to have business interests
tied to company operations.
But what I'm more curious about is…
we've worked with this vendor before.
So why have I never met this Tasanai guy?
Exactly.
Isn't that strange?
Bas.
Set up a meeting with this vendor tomorrow.
I want to talk to him.
You said she likes bread from my bakery.
I think she'll like this.
You didn't put fish sauce in it, did you?
Are you crazy?
Who pranks their friend like that?
LET'S TRY DATING, LAL.
That's adorable.
LAL: HAVE YOU GONE HOME YET?
So you really are dating Lal?
You misunderstood it.
It's just a joke card.
Lal and I are buddies.
That's a pretty unusual prank.
That's just how we mess around.
I'd like to joke around like that
with you too.
Wine, you know
this company’s policy, right?
No dating is allowed here,
whether it's real or just a joke.
If people find out,
that won't end well.
But I can help keep this secret.
Wine!
Oh, Lal?
You're still here?
Yes.
I'm looking into something important.
Did you find it?
I did.
Jackpot.
Great.
Wine, give me an update
on what I asked you to look into as well.
Wine.
Wine, did he do anything to you?
Let's go home together today.
Everyone else has already left.
I'll head out first.
See you at home.
Matching pajamas?
Yeah.
I thought they were cute,
so I bought them for us.
Sure.
I'll go change right now.
Oh! The bread.
Can I have some?
Of course.
I bought it for you.
Thank you.
Hey, Wine.
I'm starting to suspect Korn
and the vendor we're using know each other.
Why?
My team found out
they went to the same university.
Do you think they're in on it together?
I don't think you should get involved.
Why?
You don't have any proof yet.
If you start accusing him,
it'll only cause more trouble.
That's why I'm gathering more information.
But I think if you just
take good care of your clients,
have your team
follow up with them regularly,
and come up with interesting promotions,
that should be enough
to stop clients from leaving.
Yeah, I'm already doing all that.
But if we don't close that cost leak,
every promotion
just eats into our profits.
Then switch to another vendor.
One that has nothing to do with Korn.
Did he threaten you?
He didn't.
He said something to you today, didn't he?
I told you, he didn't.
That's not true.
I saw the way you acted around him today.
Something wasn't right.
If you're still
going to lie to me like this,
then I can't help you.
Why are you pushing me like this?
I'm not your subordinate.
If this is too much for you,
we can stop this relationship.
LET'S TRY DATING, LAL.
(I believe Lal is
just as scared as you are.)
(Who wouldn't be?)
But I think the love she has for you
is greater than her fear.
So think about it this way.
(If someone can find the courage
simply because she wants to love you,)
(can't you be brave for her too?)
Wine…
I'm sorry.
Sorry for what?
I crossed the line again, didn't I?
Not at all.
You said that to me again.
Wine.
I know my feelings
have been too overwhelming for you.
But I'm sorry I couldn't stop myself
from feeling this way.
I got mad at you and
you're still the one apologizing first?
How much guilt
are you trying to make me feel?
What did I do, Wine?
Did I make you feel bad again?
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
It just makes me feel like
I'll never meet anyone
who's as good to me as you are.
Isn't that a good thing, Wine?
It’s not good, of course.
How am I supposed to live
if I don't have you, Lal?
That's exactly my plan.
So you'll stay with me forever.
I'm sorry, Lal.
I'm sorry for saying that to you.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Lal.
So Korn's the one who did that to you?
Yeah.
Then why didn't you tell me?
He became our boss.
I was afraid you'd get into trouble
with him if I told you.
Wine, I'm way better
at handling people than you.
You know that.
Hey.
When something like this happens,
you have to tell me right away.
At the very least,
I can keep him away from you.
Aww.
Thank you.
Actually, the reason
I wanted to talk to you today
was because there's something
I need to tell you.
What is it?
It's not just about this?
Well…
I like Lal.
Not as a coworker.
So are you two going to date?
Yeah.
But the company
has a conflict-of-interest policy.
So are you going to quit?
I haven't thought that far ahead yet.
I want to talk to Lal first.
But if that's what it comes to,
I'm okay with it.
You'd really quit your job for her?
Do you like her that much?
Yes.
I really do.
I'm so happy for you.
You finally found someone
who could tear down your walls.
Mr. Tasanai keeps refusing
to meet with me.
His secretary says
he's overseas on business every time.
Who knows if it's really business
or even a world tour.
It's okay.
With the information we have,
I think I can talk to Korn now.
These are all the documents
my team has gathered.
As you can see,
this vendor's prices are extremely high,
which has driven our costs up unnecessarily.
Accounting has already flagged it.
Our profit margins have dropped.
But we already chose this vendor.
You also agreed to it in the meeting,
didn't you?
I did.
But that was before our long-term clients
started declining to renew their contracts.
Lal,
before you blame everyone else,
have you tried blaming yourself?
First you blamed the system.
Then the process.
Now you're blaming the vendor.
Have you ever actually solved the problems
within your own team?
I had a feeling that's what you'd say.
That's why I came prepared.
These are the current market prices
from other vendors.
As you can see,
our vendor's prices
are far higher than everyone else's.
I know sales performance
is my responsibility.
But the company's profits
are also my responsibility.
Replacing the vendor
would benefit the company far more than
replacing my team.
You need to look at the bigger picture.
Yes, they're more expensive.
But I believe their vision
is much stronger than the others'.
If we build a relationship with them now,
they'll eventually
give us better prices in the future.
What the hell?
Who on earth actually thinks like that?
Something smells fishy, doesn't it?
Definitely.
How do we catch him?
Yes!
My bubble tea is gone!
Awesome!
What?
Why are you happy
because your bubble tea disappeared?
We put laxatives in it.
Whoever suddenly makes a run
for the bathroom today that's our thief.
Why would you do that?
Why don't we just check
the security cameras?
Let's go look at the footage.
No, no, no! Please don't check the CCTV.
Yeah.
Some secrets are better left buried.
What secrets?
Uh…
Forget it.
Don't worry about it.
Come on.
Let's go catch the bubble tea thief!
Yeah!
Jantra, what's wrong with everyone?
Kate made banana dessert
with coconut milk for everyone
to celebrate winning the lottery.
It tasted great.
The coconut milk was a little sour,
so we thought it was refreshing.
It turns out it had gone bad.
Oh, crap.
If everyone's rushing to the bathroom,
how are we supposed to catch the thief?
I went through all that effort
setting up a trap.
Numnim,
you're a genius.
Lal.
Huh?
What are you doing here?
You don't have any client visits today.
Where are you going?
How do you know my schedule?
Wait.
Do you have feelings for me or something?
This is about Korn, isn't it?
Don't ask me like that.
I don't want to lie to you.
I told you to stay away from him.
What are you planning to do now?
Weren't you the one who said
we should follow company policy?
If we knowingly let someone
get away with wrongdoing,
isn't that like
letting cancer spread unchecked?
Then I'm coming with you.
Who knows
what reckless thing you'll do next.
Are you coming?
Yeah, I’m going.
Hello.
Did you make an appointment?
Oh, no.
I was just passing by,
so I thought I'd drop off
these documents for Mr. Tasanai.
You could've just sent them by courier.
That's okay.
I was hoping to meet Mr. Tasanai
in person too.
We've been doing business together
for so long,
but I've never actually met him.
Thank you very much.
He's been traveling overseas a lot lately,
so he's rarely available.
I see.
That's okay then.
Please give these documents
to Mr. Tasanai for me.
Of course.
Once he's signed them,
I'll come pick them up right away.
Sure.
Thank you.
Ow!
Should we head back?
I don't think he's coming in today.
People have to come to work eventually,
don't they?
Is he seriously
never going to show up at the office?
And if you do see him,
what are you going to do?
Arrest him?
I'll introduce myself first.
Then I'll get him talking
until he admits he knows Korn.
You make it sound so easy.
Come on.
Honestly,
even if we just get a photo of him
entering the office like a normal person,
that's enough to report this to the VP.
Plot twist.
The boss never comes to the office,
so the secretary goes see him instead.
I'm not letting this end in a plot twist.
Are we wasting our time?
Hello.
Here are the documents.
Is that the Mr. Tasanai
you've been looking for?
Mr. Tasanai is probably just a nominee.
Being paralyzed like that,
there's no way he could handle
these transactions himself.
Honestly, all the signatures
we've seen so far
were probably signed
by his wife or someone close to him.
The worst-case scenario
is that Korn set up the company
under the name of his paralyzed friend,
used it as a vendor,
and sold everything to us
at inflated prices,
while he had the authority
to approve the purchases himself.
So what do we do now, Lal?
Should we keep investigating?
This is as far as we can take it.
I'll report everything to management.
WINE, WANT TO GRAB
SOMETHING TO EAT THIS EVENING?
I WANT TO THANK YOU
FOR GOING WITH ME YESTERDAY.
SURE.
I HAVE SOMETHING I WANT TO TELL YOU TOO.
I'LL TELL YOU WHEN WE MEET.
Ms. Nan,
I'd like to report something.
Of course.
I'll be at the office
early tomorrow morning.
Come see me then.
LET'S TRY DATING, LAL.
Who are you waiting for?
With all this evidence,
are you still going to deny it, Wine?
Wine.
I’m sorry I'm late.
It's okay.
Are you hungry? Have you ordered yet?
You go ahead.
Okay. So what do you want to eat?
I don't think I'll be eating anything
because what I have to say
won't take long.
It’s about what you asked me
whether I'd like to be your girlfriend.
My answer is no.
I've had time to think it over.
I only see you as a friend with benefits.
And since you don't feel
the same way I do,
I don't think this relationship
is healthy anymore.
My room's been renovated.
I'll be moving back.
Thank you so much
for everything.
Wine…
Next time, press the red button, okay?
I've received a report
that you and Wine, the Head of Accounting,
are in a relationship.
Uh…
Lal and I aren’t together.
Friends with benefits are risky.
If you're not sure, don't risk your heart.
Lal!