That Table 4...
The people sitting there
are really famous in Korea...
They're huge food influencers.
[Park Ki Ryang / Kim Min Kyung]
Like they work for Michelin.
- You serve this to Michelin customers.
- Okay.
This is nerve-wracking.
Table 4, thank you.
- Hello!
Here's our welcome drink.
- Thank you.
- It's calamansi juice.
Ah, calamansi.
Do you have any recommendations?
Any particular preferences?
- We don't discriminate.
- Okay.
- Normally...
- Yeah.
People usually get the sea bream.
- Okay.
- Palabok is a popular choice as well.
Sisig is made from parts of a pig's head.
- It's a stir-fry with a syrupy glaze.
- Oh, really?
We'll take the entire page then.
- All of it.
- All of it?
- Yes, all of it.
- Well, there's more on the back.
- Oh, there's more?
- Yes.
Oh, I want the garlic rice.
We could probably share one garlic rice?
- Are the servings big enough?
- Yes.
- Portions are pretty generous.
- Really?
- We'll start with one for now.
- Okay.
- And order more later.
- Ah, yes.
Since we're here, we wanna
experience the whole menu today.
- Okay. So, all of it?
- Yes, all of it.
- Everything on the menu? Okay.
- Yes, yes.
- We'd appreciate it.
- One by one is fine.
- Certainly.
- Thank you.
- I got all these for you!
- Oh, for me?
- Of course!
- Is it my birthday today?
All menu.
Seriously? For real?
For real.
Gising-gising, one.
Wow.
Okay, Ji.
So that's one sinigang, one palabok,
one inasal, one fish,
one kare-kare, one sisig...
one garlic rice, one gising-gising.
[Basically, Everything...]
Basically, everything on the menu.
They're the mukbang guys, right?
Yes.
Okay.
[Kumusta]
[The Eve]
It's kinda chilly.
Hot soup would be amazing right now.
- We ordered soup!
- But that is...
Honestly, I can't handle anything too strong.
I've never tried it before. This is new to me.
When I visited the Philippines,
they told me about this dish.
In Korea, kimchi stew is somewhat considered
the "representation" of Korean food, right?
They say that sinigang
also represents Filipino cuisine.
It must be good then.
But I haven't tried it yet
because it was heavily seasoned for me.
The tanginess?
- The spices?
- Yeah.
Okay, sinigang.
- This is kare-kare for Table 4.
- Okay.
[Will it suit their taste...?]
Hi!
- Okay, this is kare-kare.
- Kare.
Excuse me, here's your sinigang.
- Sinigang.
- Yes.
I'll put this here.
Here's your bowl.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Garlic rice.
- Wow, this looks really good.
Garlic rice.
Is this similar to short rib soup?
- What is it?
- Right?
It's loaded with ingredients.
- Here, try it.
- Thank you.
Oh, it's warm.
I want to know how the soup tastes.
- I think I get what you mean by sour now.
- You get it, right?
Wow!
The meat!
That's pretty good.
The sourness is there,
but it's not as bad as I thought.
[All-Star Mukbangers Approved]
I think there's calamansi in it?
That's how tangy this tastes.
It feels like I'm abroad.
Calaman... Inasal up!
Table 4.
Thank you.
Oppa!
- Thank you.
- Sure.
Here's your inasal.
We'll clear these out.
- I'll clear it out for you.
- Put the bones here.
How's the food?
- It's better than I expected.
- Okay.
- It's not overly seasoned.
- Is that so?
I was thinking,
"Did they tailor this to our taste?"
- Right.
- It's really good.
I'll let the chef know about that.
- Oh, okay.
- Alright.
- Thank you.
The famous Korean mukbang celebrities...
They're losing it over how good the food is.
Okay, Chef, the mukbangers are
super happy with your food.
They're absolutely obsessed.
- They're happy.
- Okay.
- Good!
- Congratulations!
Can you guys slice
some calamansi while you wait?
- Okay.
- Yes, I'm on it.
- Which table, fish order?
- Okay, fish...
- Table number...
- Four!
- Four.
- Four, alright.
What?
- Is it heavy?
- It's just for the two of them?
Can they finish this?
- The mukbangers?
- Yes.
I guess so? Let them enjoy the feast.
Excuse me, this is...
- Oh, sorry!
- Thank you.
- Wow, sis.
- Take a picture.
- Sis, isn't this...
- Enjoy your meal.
Thank you. Isn't this good for four people?
This is how we enjoy the food.
The mukbangers.
They were shocked by the massive portions.
The fish is huge!
- They're only two. Can they finish that?
- Just the two of them?
- Yes girl! They're two girls!
- Just two?
- Oh, wow.
- Two!
- Two girls!
- Two people?
Yes, two people.
Is that sisig?
- Okay, here's your liver sauce.
- Okay.
- This is for your sisig.
- Alright.
Table number?
This is for Table 4.
It's still them!
What?
Sisig.
Okay.
My apologies!
- Sisig!
- Thank you.
Well.
Here!
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
- One more to come.
[This is light work]
Yes, one more.
[Mukbang Live]
[Mukbang Live ON!]
- Oh, there's tripe inside?
- It has tripe in it!
Wow.
This is crazy!
Wow, I keep reaching for this.
[Lost in the Sauce!]
Wow, sis...
I've never tasted anything like this before.
But the onion really gives it a kick.
It somehow elevates the entire dish.
It has a lot of shrimp in it.
Mmm?
This is delicious!
- You get that instant shrimp aroma and flavor.
- Right.
I absolutely love this one!
- Sis!
- What?
I swear, this is a feast fit for a king.
Okay, we're getting more customers, my friends.
We're getting more?
Hello, welcome!
Welcome!
- Hello!
- What?
[Kumusta]
Hello, come on in!
- Table for how many?
- For six, please.
[Kumusta Unstoppable]
For six?
[Stop]
Hold on, let me clear the table for you.
I'm so sorry for the wait.
Would you like anything to eat?
- It's free.
- Free?
- Thank you.
- Yes, you can choose whatever you want.
- This one.
- This?
- This one, this one.
- This is big, Choco Mucho.
- Choco Mucho! Yes.
- Yeah, this one is my favorite.
- Everyone loves it in the Philippines.
- It's good.
- We bring this to school.
- Choco's the best.
You can choose whatever you want.
Only one?
If you want more, it's okay.
[All Set]
This way, please.
Table for how many?
- For three.
Okay, please take a seat.
Wow, it's packed again.
This is busier than last night.
Yeah, it is.
[Full House Through The Rain]
Sorry.
One sinigang, one palabok,
one inasal, one kare-kare.
one inasal, one sisig.
One palabok, one kare-kare,
one sisig, one garlic rice.
It's never-ending.
This is good enough.
- Gising-gising!
- Okay!
- Sinigang, Table 1.
- Table 1, okay.
Palabok!
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
- Sinigang, can you just please wipe?
- Okay!
- Thank you!
- One at a time first.
- Take them one by one. They can be heavy.
- Okay.
Tables 3 and 5, coming up!
- Here's your sinigang.
- Sinigang.
Here's your sisig.
- Be careful, it's hot.
- Alright.
Here's your inasal.
Kare-kare!
- Kare-kare.
- Here.
Here you go.
Oh, it's innards!
I'll give it a try.
- Is it good?
- It tastes very nutty,
so it's really sweet.
- There's a lot of meat.
- Wow, that's a lot of peanut sauce.
That's really good.
There's a lot to eat.
- Wow, it's crazy.
- That's delicious.
- Is this sinigang?
- Yes, sinigang.
It looks good.
- It kinda reminds me of a Korean dish.
- Yeah.
- There are lots of interesting ingredients.
- I know, right?
Such a variety of ingredients in one dish.
- It kinda smells like tom yum kung.
- Yeah.
- It's good.
- Give it a go.
And let me know how it tastes.
I'll be the first to take one for the team.
- Is it good?
- It feels like tom yum kung.
Right? I visited the Philippines 20 years ago.
But I didn't even know
they had something like this.
Now that we know...
I know exactly what to order
when I visit the Philippines.
Woah!
That is amazing.
This somehow tastes very Korean.
Right. Two more...
We should've ordered four, one per person.
- Excuse me, Ji.
- Okay.
[A Moment of Peace]
There's a...
Ji, you know there's a proper way
to eat this Fudgee Barr?
Oh, I don't know.
So when you finish the cake,
you eat the paper also,
but you also spit it out.
What?
- Seriously?
- Seriously!
You can try it.
I did eat a lot of these but...
You're supposed
to chew on the paper and throw it?
We used to do that
when we were kids up until now.
No, I told him...
So...
I told him, when we were little kids,
after eating Fudgee Barr,
we eat the paper also.
And then we spit it out.
Eat the paper?
Yeah! No, I'm not joking!
I'll show you.
No...
No way...
She ate the whole thing.
Did you eat the paper, Ji?
I'm not joking!
I'm not lying!
- Seriously? But...
- I'm not lying!
Everyone but Francine
- is looking at her weirdly.
- Yes, oh no!
He said you're so hungry
that you even ate the paper.
[True or False?]
Then, can you talk to me?
What do I owe you? What do you need me to do?
- Just the inasal and fish.
- Okay.
Okay, that's all for the orders.
Last order, Chef.
Fighting!
- Let's go!
- Fighting!
Fighting!
- Yes!
Yes, I think we're good.
- Good!
Just keep going.
Okay!
Oh, my fish is nice.
Give it some love!
Some lovin'.
- Inasal is ready.
- Sweet.
- Okay, Table...
- Okay!
- Table 5, additional inasal, complete!
Okay, got it!
Let's say hi. Ask them how they are.
Not to chit-chat
but to really just ask them about the food.
Yeah.
Following up on the fish!
Yes, coming!
- I'll go with you. I'll take care of...
- Okay, go!
Okay!
Let's go!
Okay, let's go.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Thank you for the wait.
- Oh, no worries.
Here you go.
- It's our main dishes?
- Yeah.
Sea bream, salt-baked,
and then with a Filipino vinegar.
- Thank you so much.
- How was your meal?
- Very excellent.
- It was really good.
What did you like?
- I liked this one.
- Actually... yeah.
- Sinigang?
- Yeah, sinigang.
It kind of tastes like tom yum kung.
- Yeah.
- It's similar. Yeah.
- Taste is very similar.
- Thank you.
- Enjoy your fish. Thank you.
- Yeah, thank you.
Hi!
- Hello, hi!
- Hello.
- This is your palabok.
- Palabok.
- It's rice noodles.
- Palabok, rice noodles.
And I just want to say,
- thank you very much for...
- Thank you.
Ah, okay.
Thank you.
Thank you for coming.
How did you find out about our place?
- Kumusta.
- Actually, I'm from the Philippines.
- Oh, really?
- Before, before, yeah.
- Before for how long?
- For 9 years.
- How did you find the Philippines?
- I really liked it.
I really enjoyed it.
So I was looking for a kind of restaurant.
And maybe this can be significant for us,
and for me also.
So I recommended to him.
- The big boss will treat everyone today.
- Yes!
- Nice.
- Wow!
Do you work together?
Colleagues from which company? If I may ask.
Actually, we're a team
in charge of global business
at a company called NOL Universe.
- Okay.
- So, actually...
we offer mainly K-pop concerts
and travel products to foreigners,
- not to Koreans.
- Okay.
Interpark Global is a name that we show to...
It's a platform that we sell tickets
- and travel products for foreigners.
- Travel products.
- Oh, okay.
- Yes, so...
Maybe one day we'll be able
to purchase tickets from your site.
- Alright, thank you.
- Bye-bye. Thank you.
- How is your experience?
- It's good.
- Is the food good?
- Very delicious.
- You liked the sisig.
- Yes.
- How about you, sir?
- I liked this one.
- The inasal, and you?
- Me too.
The inasal also.
And the gentleman...
Ah, you liked the chicken.
So that's good to know
that you liked our food and...
Is it your first time
to experience Filipino food?
- Filipino food? Yeah.
- It's the first time.
It's the first time.
Is it something that you will
eat again in the future?
- Sure!
- Oh, sure, sure, sure.
We have to reserve... a plane ticket.
Ah! To the Philippines?
- Yeah.
- Manila.
- Just to eat?
- We have to.
Oh, thank you so much.
- Thank you very much.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
[Kumusta has been loved]
[But it is coming to an end]
I'm going to miss this kitchen.
Kind of.
Cute.
The food was so good!
- Thank you.
- Okay, take care.
- Bye.
Sign, please.
- Thank you.
Thank you!
Bye.
- Okay, we're done!
- Okay.
- Ding, ding, ding!
Congratulations!
Now we are done!
- Congratulations!
- Yey!
[Closed]
Great job, everyone!
- Thank you.
- Great job, everyone!
So we started with this restaurant
five days ago.
I can see how we have improved as a team.
So I just want to say thank you.
And we have a big event tomorrow.
It's the Philippine Day.
- Can we bring them back to the Philippines?
- I think we should give back, right?
Yes.
- For all their hard work.
- Yeah.
It's like we're bringing home to them.
Yes, I'm sure they super duper
mega over miss home.
- Oh, yeah.
- That's true.
So let's bring home...
- There, to them.
- Yeah, to them.
- Yes.
- So they won't feel like an afterthought.
- They've been part of it from the start.
- We ask them.
We are from the Philippine Embassy.
Filipino!
Oh, Philippines!
- Hello! How are you?
- Philippines!
- Thank you for coming!
- Yes, hello!
It's nice to see
Filipino cuisine here in Korea.
These are my favorite back home.
Really?
- We miss Filipino food.
- Yeah.
That's why we're here.
Very Filipino, even if it's in Korea.
Very Filipino.
We'll need to buy the ingredients.
At the same time, we'll have to buy...
- Decorations?
- Decorations.
To make it feel home.
Maybe it will be nice
if we have giveaways for the...
- Yeah!
- Right!
- For the Filipinos.
- Yeah.
- Let's go!
- Guys!
[Hyehwa]
- We're looking for a Filipino dessert
- Yes, sir!
- for our event tomorrow.
[Team Dessert: Jodi &amp; Arci
Where to?]
- Ah, this one.
- Hi, Jodi!
- Good day!
- Hello!
[Hyehwa Filipino Market]
[A place for Filipino immigrants
to share food and culture]
These are the Filipino products
that we have here.
- We're looking for dessert.
- Hello.
- You all look so pretty!
- Thank you so much.
Of course, we got it from you!
Ma'am is so cute.
- Bagoong? For the mangoes...
- Ay, there's bagoong.
That bagoong comes with bagnet.
Because I'm your fan, I will give you for free.
Oh, thank you!
Filipinos are the best when it comes to this.
Are there many Filipinos here?
Yes, we have lots of Filipinos here.
Like workers
and multicultural families like me.
All the best to you, ma'am.
- Yes!
- Thank you.
- How much do we owe you?
- "Owe," really?
- Just seven thousand.
- Seven.
Thank you, ma'am!
- Take care!
- Thank you!
Jodi, we're from Antique.
- Ay okay, thank you also.
- Can we take a photo?
Sure, come on over.
One, two...
- Hi, good day.
- Hello.
- Hello!
- Sure, please come here.
Come over here.
["The Silent Superstar"]
[Photo Requests at Every Step]
Thank you.
[Mini Fan Meet in Hyehwa]
Thank you. Okay!
- Thank you!
- Thank you, take care!
- Take care!
Thank you!
There we go! Let's see what snacks they've got!
Those are the ones already cooked.
There.
Okay, typical Filipino food.
- Thank you.
- You have your lumpia.
You have your chicharon bulaklak.
- Hello!
- Ay, oh my gosh!
- Ay, suman!
- Suman!
Suman and banana cue.
Let's go for the banana cue.
How much is one piece of this?
It's free for you.
We'll buy a few.
Please don't give it for free, we'll pay.
Really?
She's happy with you, she's enjoying it.
We want you to make money, ma'am.
You prepared all this.
- Do you want one banana cue?
- Sure.
- Let's share.
- This, turon.
Turon, okay. How much is it?
- Do you know how much 2,000 won is?
- Of course.
Just one turon, please.
- And this suman, please.
- How much is one?
It's 2,000 won.
Want four, Jodi?
Sure.
- Ay, here it is. Thank you.
- Thank you!
Ma'am, thank you so much!
- There! There are a lot!
- Sure, okay.
Cassava cake.
- Do you have?
- Ah, this one?
- Yes.
- Yay, we found cassava!
It won't spoil, ma'am. Unless it gets run over.
If it gets run over, it's ruined.
- How much is this?
- It's 11,000 won.
This is egg pie.
- Halaya, this is leche flan.
- This is ube.
Jodi, leche flan.
- We can do leche flan. Very Filipino.
- Yeah.
This is halaya, special.
It's 16,000 won.
- Both of them?
- Yes.
- Thank you so much. Take care, ma'am.
- Thank you.
Looks like we've got everything.
Isn't that amazing?
Even here, there are Filipinos everywhere.
Yes, right.
[Majang]
This place in Seoul is known for great beef.
[Team Ingredients: JP &amp; Ji]
- Oh wow!
- I think we need this.
Look at the marbling.
The short plate is this part.
Ah, okay.
- This...
- Short...
- There's a cow here.
- This one.
Yeah.
- Okay.
There is so much meat...
This is...
Is this leg?
Leg. Beef leg.
Wow.
Okay, for tomorrow, let's buy it.
- Ah, okay.
- For...
So maybe, we buy brisket.
With the fat.
- Fat. Yeah.
- Yeah.
Okay, where is it?
- Can I see?
- Inside.
With your bare hands? No gloves?
- Wow.
It's good.
- Good?
- Brisket.
Yeah, good because of the fat.
And it's so white.
And it's so red.
- Three.
- Three?
Do you have a...
- Fire?
- Fire? Now?
- Cooking? No?
- Now?
- You have a burner?
- Burner, yeah.
Can I eat the steak? Can I cook the steak?
- Now?
- Now.
I want to eat the steak now.
Ah, you can.
- You have fire?
- Yeah, yeah.
Where?
You have fire because you eat here?
Yes, you can eat.
- You eat the steak?
- Yes, you can use it now.
Okay, thank you.
Where's the striploin?
Let's go!
- Okay, okay.
- Okay.
Okay, turn on the fire.
I'm the sous chef for today.
Soju, please?
Soju.
Beer, please.
Soju is over there.
- Okay, ready.
Wow!
Do you like your meat rare or medium?
- Medium.
He's doing well.
Okay. I think it's okay.
Okay. Now.
All done now.
I'm in heaven.
- Should I try it?
- Get some.
- Papa.
- Is it still good without seasoning?
- Come and eat, sir.
- Papa.
It's also my first time.
Oh, it's really delicious.
Thank you for giving me this experience.
Ji, thank you for giving me this experience.
- Sure.
- It's good.
Welcome.
[One for Bro]
[One for Bro, One for Me]
Wow, this is...
- The beef is so good.
- Right?
[Team Souvenir, Janella &amp; Francine]
I finally have some fresh air.
I know!
And we're in Gangnam!
Oh!
Oh my God!
So cute!
[I Love Gangnam Style]
So colorful.
I know.
Wow! Finally!
So, we are in Gangnam!
Uh-huh.
Hello, Gangnam!
Should we take a picture?
- Let's take a picture here.
- Picture, yeah.
So that we have memories.
Okay.
One, two, three!
Cute, okay.
Cute.
- We can see the "Gangnam."
- Gangnam!
- Okay.
- So what's our agenda?
Shopping?
I really wanna go shopping, but I'm hungry.
Me too. I'm really hungry.
What can we eat?
What do you want?
I think it's really cold today.
- So, what if...
- We need something hot.
Something with soup.
- Shabu-shabu.
- I think...
this looks like a good place.
Shabu-shabu.
- Okay, let's go.
- Let's go, let's go!
[Target Locked]
Hello.
Wow, I think I want to devour everything.
- You choose your stock.
- Okay.
[Broth]
Additional.
[Beef]
Oh, you can get more beef.
[Fish ball]
Fish ball.
Fishcake, you want?
[Fishcake]
Let's get one? Or just make it two.
Two.
We should have this in Kumusta.
You're gonna lose your job
if we have this in Kumusta.
There it is.
It's delicious.
- Masi... what?
- Masisseoyo.
- "Where is it?" is "Eodiyeyo".
- Where is it?
Where's the... um...
Our souvenirs.
Ay, I think it's this.
So I think we have to give them
something cute
and something they can keep forever.
Or something they can use
whenever they want to.
[DIY Clothing Shop]
Okay, so it's Kumusta,
so should we put a letter K with...
- Minimalist, like Kumusta.
- Yeah.
But the letter K should be different.
One letter should have a different color.
- Like K or...
- Yeah.
If the T-shirt is white,
what color should the letters be?
- And if it's black...
- Kumusta.
Darker, so "Kumus..."
- Like that.
- Okay.
And for the black one, the lighter ones.
Or what if we jumble them?
Let's try changing the shape.
What do you think?
That's cute actually.
That's a good idea.
It's pretty!
Cute!
- Can I take a pic?
- It's okay, just take a lot.
Okay.
Three, two, one!
One more.
One, two, three!
Then let's go home.
Yeah!
Hello! Welcome back!
We went to the meat market.
- Meat market!
- Yeah.
Oh, poor piggy...
It's scary.
Oh my God!
[Pig Foot]
- Up here!
- High five!
Hey, that might be dirty.
It's okay.
- Hi!
- Fist bump!
- Fist bump.
Okay.
We have a surprise for everyone.
- Yeah.
- So we went shopping earlier.
It was a cute little shop.
And we got something for everyone,
like a token.
- Okay.
- Oh, cute!
So Jodi, this is you.
We dressed her up.
Because you're wearing pink.
- Because you're always in pink.
- Yeah.
Thank you!
Aw, thank you!
- And then, Janella, this is you.
- Yes.
- Since you're in red with your earrings.
- Thank you! It's a raincoat.
Chef! This is...
Ah, no, no, no!
- That's for Ji.
- Oppa Ji! This is you!
Thank you.
- Of course.
- I'm so sorry. It's not calamansi.
They don't have calamansi.
It's because you serve
calamansi juice to our customers.
- Okay, thank you.
- Yes.
And because you guys are matching right now,
- you guys are still matching.
- Yes!
- With the bears.
- Aw cute!
Yours, Chef, is popcorn.
[Matchy Bears]
That was the only food.
- Okay.
- Cute.
Yes, thank you!
Okay.
It's us.
- Thank you!
Here.
Sit down.
[Meeting in Progress]
So Chef, you said
we have lechon tomorrow, right?
[Lechon]
[A signature Filipino dish]
[enjoyed during festivals and events]
Do we already have the pig?
So, my chef from the Philippines
is gonna help us out to cook the pig.
- Chef Kim.
- Chef Kim?
Yes, Chef Kim.
Kumusta!
That's Chef Kim!
- Oh my God!
- The pig!
[Ta-Da!]
Hey, guys!
[Kim Yumol - Hero Chef]
My gosh, I can't look at it!
That's our pig.
No!
How are you guys?
I don't want to see...
[What a Bold Entrance!]
Her eyes...
Poor pig!
Welcome to Korea, Chef Kim.
How are you, Chef?
- Yes, welcome!
- Thank you. How are you?
- Thank you for being here, Chef Kim!
- Hello!
- This is everyone.
- Yes.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hi, Chef Kim.
My hands are dirty from carrying the pig.
- So, I'll just give you flying kisses.
- Okay, Chef.
- Francine, Janella, Jodi.
- Hi, Francine, Janella.
Ramona!
- Hi!
- Ramona.
- Hello!
- Hello.
So how many hours, Chef?
Yeah.
So this is around 25 to 28 kilos.
And it would probably take us
around 3 to 4 hours.
- To cook it.
- Yeah.
And we're gonna cook it outside?
Around this area, I think.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- So tomorrow, early start.
- Yeah.
And rock and roll!
Okay!
- Thank you!
- Fighting!
I'll do my best!
- You guys ready?
- Yes, we are!
- Let's go, guys!
- Here we go!
[The Last Mission]
[Philippine Festival]
[Closed]
Okay, let's go!
[Philippines Festival]
Let's do this!
Hello, Philippine Day!
[Hall Decorations]
[Clear]
[Personalized Cookies]
I hope they like it.
[Clear]
Kim, are you ready?
[It's Kitchen Time!]
Yeah, let's go!
[Let's Bring It Home!]
[Cheffies Locked In]
[Super Locked In]
[Flawless Kitchen!]
[Rustle]
[Rustle, Rustle]
[Next Up: Lechon]
Where's Oppa Ji?
When we need him...
He got tired.
Sorry, girl.
I'm so sorry.
I will pray for your soul.
Sorry.
Thank you for the food.
[RIP Chris P. Bacon]
So I'll remove the offals first.
- My only concern here...
- Yeah.
is tying the thing.
I hope it's secure enough.
- I know, because...
- Because if you don't tie it properly,
- the pig would be like this when we rotate it.
- Oh, I know.
[Pre-Roast Prep]
Okay.
Is that part of the spine?
This is like the joint.
It will go through the mouth?
Yes.
We make incisions at the ribs
so that it can enter...
Yeah.
There!
- Sorry.
- Okay.
Massage, massage.
It's okay, you can let go for now.
Okay.
No, I wanna support her.
What are you doing, Chef?
So we're opening this up.
Can I try?
Yeah, okay.
- This whole thing?
- Yeah.
So, I can sub the whole...
Okay.
Can I see? Can I see?
- Yeah, good.
- Yeah?
Okay.
This is a device.
Device?
Okay.
What are you doing, Chef?
So, if the pole enters,
- So, if the pole enters, we wrap it?
- It secures... yes.
It secures the pole inside the pig.
Ah, what if like this?
And then, there!
- Oh, okay.
- There you go.
And then we do it again.
- You want to do it?
- I'll try.
You should be careful, okay?
- There we go.
Is that right?
Yes.
- Yay!
- Okay.
- Okay, so we're down to two.
How's Kim with Ramona?
- Are they having fun?
- They're tying the lechon.
Oh, looks fun.
It's like you guys are in a lab.
Okay, so... there!
One, two, three.
Oh, wow!
Chef...
Your assistant is Arci Muñoz, Kim.
- She's amazing, actually.
- Ah, really?
So cool, so cool.
This chemistry is great.
So we need to put the pole in now.
Okay.
Oh, wait, wait.
I'll tell you... I'll lift it up.
- Go, Arci!
- Go, go, go.
Go, Arci!
- Push, Arci!
- Wait.
- Chef, don't put it down.
- I won't.
- There. Okay, go.
- Arci, push.
There you go!
Wait a minute.
What is this?
- Ji!
- Ji Chang Wook!
Hey, Ji Chang Wook!
- Experience.
- You should be the one doing this.
Why's it so cold today?
Hello!
- Hello!
- Wow, there's a cake!
- Hi!
It seems so real, right?
I've prepared a cake.
- Thank you!
Philippine Day!
- Thank you, Oppa.
- I'll get it. Okay.
[Philippines Day]
[Off to Work!]
Wow.
- Man, push.
- Okay!
Okay. Hold, hold!
Okay. One, two, three!
Okay, wait. Take it slow, Arci.
- Slowly.
- Okay, alright.
Okay, slowly.
Okay.
Move back a bit.
Okay, okay.
Wait, this is historical.
- Go, go, Arci.
- Okay!
No, no, go back.
Should I really be the one doing this?
This chef!
He's just laughing and taking videos of us.
Okay. One, two, three!
- Wait, wait, wait.
- Okay, push!
Go, Arci!
Just go straight.
I'll lift it up.
I eat Fudgee Barr.
[True or False 2.0]
Chef, do you eat the paper on the Fudgee Barr?
And then you spit it out?
You don't?
Just with White Rabbit.
When I was a kid, actually.
- Oh, see?
- Yes, it's like a childhood thing.
- Right? I wasn't lying!
- Which one?
- The Fudgee Barr paper!
- Chef Kim eats it?
Not now! When I was a child.
Not anymore?
Because Ji thought...
I was fooling him.
You swallowed it?
Because Chef Kim, they don't believe me.
- I think everyone went through that phase.
- They've never done it.
I said, maybe it's because I grew up poor.
- Is that really why?
- The one like this, right?
- Yes, and then you spit it out.
- And it's like so wet.
Classic.
Ji!
Ji, I'm telling the truth!
Fudgee Barr.
- She's not over it yet.
- No!
The paper!
Kid! When I was a kid.
I told you, I'm not a bad person.
Not that bad.
Just a little...
- Just a little bad.