Let's go to a PC bang.
No.
Wanna play League of Legends?
A league match?
No.
What about Overwatch?
Huh? That's...
Wait, is that Jihan?
Wait.
- Hey, what are you doing?
- Hey, hey, hey!
Nope~ not happening.
So why is our dear
freshman sleeping out here?
Ah... I got kicked out.
Kicked out?
Of your house?
Why?
I... don't really know.
When can you go back home?
I don't really know that either...
Then you've been sleeping here every day?
Pretty much...
Then you can stay at Hyunjun's place.
He lives alone near campus
I've crashed there a few times myself,
and it's decent. Pretty clean too.
More importantly,
what kind of senior would allow
his junior to sleep somewhere
this dangerous, right?
Uh... no worries if that's inconvenient
I'm kinda comfortable here too.
Come to my place after class.
See? Told you he's a good guy.
Uh... thank you.
Alright, have your assignments
turned in by next week,
and that'll be all for today's class.
Good work, everyone.
Wanna work on the assignment together?
The assignment?
I figured it'd be better
if we did it together.
Uh... sure.
I think it'd look better if
this side had a lighter tone.
And over here...
Is it okay for you to keep helping me?
What about your assignment...?
Mm... it's fine.
Should we blur this part a little more?
Like this?
Mm...
If you do this part
the same way as before,
it'll start looking too messy.
Oh, okay.
Wanna try it again?
Yeah.
Thank you, you really helped me a lot.
How long have you been drawing?
I've never really learned properly,
I just doodle as a hobby...
I didn't think it'd turn
out this good either...
Huh? Oh, it's you from before...
You know Hyunjun?
Yeah.
We just got acquainted recently.
Ah, I see.
Hi, nice seeing you again.
Yeah, hi.
Oh right!
This is for you
I still felt bad about
what happened that day.
Ah, really, it's okay
I was partly at fault too.
Anyway, what are you doing here?
Oh, nothing much
I was helping him with an assignment.
What about you?
Me? I came to work on mine too.
Wanna do it together?
We just finished,
so we'll get going first. Take your time.
You two are friends?
We're just classmates.
Your friend seems really nice.
Does he?
Hyunjun!
You left this behind.
Oh, right.
Excuse me.
It's messy, but probably
better than school.
Huh? No.
It's really nice in here.
You really live here alone?
I'll get you something to change into.
Not sure if it'll fit.
Thank you.
Want something to eat?
What should we have?
I don't really cook much at home...
But this looks so good.
Thank you for the meal.
Slow down.
Yeah, it's just so good...
I heard you helped with
Yunghui's club poster too.
Oh, yeah.
Though I don't know if I
was actually much help.
Oh right.
How do you know Yunghui anyway?
You two seem way too
different personality-wise.
Since we were really little,
our parents were close friends,
so we ended up going to the same
elementary, middle, and high school,
and somehow even the same college...
Ah... so you've known each other forever.
Sounds like he takes good care of you.
Oh, definitely.
Thanks to him,
I think I've adjusted to
school life pretty well.
That's good to hear.
If it's too cramped, I
can sleep on the floor.
If it's uncomfortable, I will.
No... no, it's okay...
Then let's just sleep like this.
Who's the person in that
photo on the coffee table?
You saw that?
I was just looking around...
My younger brother.
Really?
How old is he?
By now, he'd just be an adult.
Same age as you, probably.
You must've been really close.
We were.
But he died in an accident.
It's okay...
I'm sorry... I shouldn't have...
When I first lost my
brother in that accident,
all I could think about was following him.
He only had me,
and I only had him.
So I kept wondering if it was even right
for me to smile and keep living my life.
He must've been having
such a hard time without me...
He's living happily
I'm sure of it.
Really.
You don't believe me?
Thank you.
If I were your brother,
I'd want my big brother to be happy.
Live your life until then,
and when you meet again someday,
you'll have forever together then.
I can't quite figure you out.
Huh?
When I first met you,
I thought you were just some weird kid
but somehow you feel really familiar too.
Like just being around you is
comforting for some reason.
Let's get closer.
Okay.