MY ROYAL NEMESIS
-Is that a person?
-I think so.
-What the…
-Hey!
Excuse me!
-There's blood. Oh my God.
-Hello? We need an ambulance.
Someone has collapsed on the ground here.
Abdominal stab wound. Bleeding won't stop.
Prepare a transfusion and page trauma.
Cha Se-gye!
Do not die, Cha Se-gye.
Don't cry.
I need to get up.
I can't leave her…
Stay with us, sir!
-Blood pressure's still dropping.
-Not like this…
Heart rate, 120. I'll start fluids.
Start CPR.
You all must be weary
from the long journey.
This is a royal letter from His Majesty.
The Queen Dowager also sent
some restorative soup.
I anticipated a royal edict,
not a letter and soup.
I suppose I am not destined to die yet.
Drink it.
Die as a sinner.
Then the girl will live.
I must entrust you
to an unreliable promise.
Even if this is the end,
I cannot say it was a bad life.
A royal who could never be sovereign.
I was never destined
to live out a full life.
Still, departing this life with the one
I treasure most kept safe…
Is that not a rather
fitting end for a man?
What is the meaning of this?
You are a dead man anyway.
This manner of death is
His Majesty's will.
The tragic prince in exile
who fell to bandits
and vanished without a trace.
That is how history will remember you.
You scoundrel!
I will
save you this time.
EPISODE 14
MY ROYAL NEMESIS
Hey, Dan-sim.
Kang Dan-sim.
This is
the palace.
Hey, are you okay?
I am back.
In Joseon.
You can save him.
If you, Your Highness,
sever the chain of fate.
The chain of fate?
Your beloved is fated to die,
be it in Joseon or here.
So you must go back
and save the Grand Prince.
Then this fate will not be repeated.
You only have to pay a small price.
Hey, why are you in such a daze today?
You…
You wench.
What are you doing here?
Your clothes…
You were also a bond from a past life?
Hold on. Were you sleeping?
I never knew her in Joseon.
Did something change?
I am definitely inside the palace.
Where are we?
Where else? The Queen Dowager's quarters.
JAGYEONGJEON HALL
The nerve you have.
How could a palace attendant fall asleep?
The Queen Dowager's quarters.
Palace attendant.
The past has changed.
In that case…
I can change other things too.
Announcing His Majesty!
It is him.
Do not just stand there.
Open the doors at once.
Yes, of course.
You come in as well.
He became king in the meantime.
The Queen Dowager is still alive.
It has not even been a year
since his ascension.
She fell ill upon hearing
of the Grand Prince's death
and passed a few days later.
If the Queen Dowager is alive,
he must still be…
Around this time of year, the Grand Prince
would always fall terribly ill.
To think of what hardships
he must be enduring in that harsh place…
I can only be grateful that His Majesty
has heeded a mother's heart.
It weighs heavily on my heart as well.
I intended to send him a letter
within the coming days.
I will also have them deliver
the restorative soup
you prepared for him.
She shall deliver it safely.
Your Majesty
wishes to send me to the Grand Prince?
Yes. I heard you were once assigned
to Seonghyeon Pavilion.
Deliver it safely.
I am sure seeing a familiar face
should put him at ease.
And be sure to observe
the Grand Prince's condition closely.
He is still alive.
I can save him.
He was stabbed in the abdomen,
damaging his kidney.
We performed emergency surgery,
but he's in hemorrhagic shock.
Right now, he just needs to make it
through the night.
You are here.
You all must be weary
from the long journey.
He is still alive.
This is a royal letter from His Majesty.
The Queen Dowager also sent
some restorative soup.
I anticipated a royal edict,
not a letter and soup.
I suppose I am not destined to die yet.
I shall prepare the table shortly.
Why have you become so quiet?
I have longed for
that endless chatter of yours.
Your Highness
has not changed in the slightest.
It is as if time had stopped.
But you…
seem to have changed a bit.
Your eyes and spirit have grown stronger.
But why did you come?
I was taken aback
to hear that the Queen Mother would be
sending you, of all her attendants.
She shall deliver it safely.
Anjong must have sent me for a reason.
What does the letter say?
Is he asking how you are?
That is none of your concern.
Even if I am a sinner,
I would not show a letter
from His Majesty to a mere court lady.
I am bait.
He sent me here to use me as bait.
Then,
that must be…
You must not drink that. It is poison!
Poison?
Do you dare slander
Her Majesty the Queen Mother?
Do you not see?
I was used as bait.
To make you quietly drink
the poison and die.
What?
Bait?
Who do you think you are?
Just because we shared
some banter as "companions,"
do you truly think
that makes you something to me?
I was happy.
I was just a court lady
with no one to confide in but a stray dog.
I was happy when you offered
to be my companion.
You were the first
to ever peer into the heart
of this lowly court lady.
Compose yourself.
I have never once cared for you.
I have no need
for the affections of a mere court lady.
So bury them.
Me.
And your memories.
Did you know?
I like the rain now.
I have come to appreciate
its cleansing chill.
It reminds me that I am alive.
Now feel it for yourself.
This cleansing chill.
I am alive.
I survived.
Even when I thought I wanted to die,
I actually wanted to live.
I did not want to live as I had been.
But I did not want to die.
That is
what you awakened in me.
-My will to live.
-You--
Should this life be unbearable,
there are other ways to live.
You must find yourself a new world.
Be it Qing or another foreign land.
Anywhere but here.
You must escape from this place.
I thought your lips had grown
heavy with silence,
but they could not be lighter.
How you prattle on so thoughtlessly.
Then again, that is you.
Ever the same.
Did my brother send you?
Did he tell you
to bring his brother's head?
Just consider us bandits
who left empty-handed
after foolishly following
some soldiers and palace servants
into the mountains.
Would that not be better
for your peace of mind?
No.
This is your chance to flee.
No, we must go together.
There is no time. You must hide.
Did I not tell you?
I am trying to save you.
He will only live
if Your Highness survives.
-"He"?
-Yes.
He is
more precious than life to me.
I smiled because of him.
I was finally able to breathe.
Just as Your Highness once saved me,
I too wish to save him.
I cannot give up now.
You have found someone like that?
Now I understand.
Why your eyes have come
to hold such courage.
Do not worry.
I shall live.
I am so widely despised…
I will not die easily.
In the end…
No…
Shin Seo-ri.
Se-gye, are you awake?
Sir?
I'll go get the doctor.
Se-gye, are you okay?
What happened? Shin Seo-ri…
You shouldn't move yet.
You'll tear your stitches.
You were just moved from the ICU.
The doctor said you need absolute rest.
He just woke up.
How are you feeling, sir?
-Mr. Son.
-Sir.
Where is Shin Seo-ri?
Shin Seo-ri.
Why are you two here?
Stop wasting time with me. Go see Se-gye.
Go and talk to his doctor.
Tae-hee said she'd call
when Se-gye wakes up.
Is she his family? No, you are!
He doesn't even have his parents around.
He is your one and only nephew,
and you can't even look after him?
We didn't have
a father growing up, either.
You only cared about Jin-u.
You never even looked our way.
How can we show him love
when we never received any?
Why would you go bringing this up now?
You're upsetting Father.
Always going on about that damn grandson!
Father. We're your children too.
Stop living in the past.
Try looking forward,
or even just around you for once.
You should try it out one of these days!
Why that little…
When will he be able to be discharged?
You're quite impatient.
He just woke up.
We'll have to monitor him.
Sir?
I can't find Ms. Shin.
She's not at the restaurant
or at her place.
She's unreachable.
The police don't really have
anything either.
Nothing but suspicion
and circumstantial evidence.
Secure the interrogation room recording
and prepare a response.
Frame it as a wrongful investigation
and incompetent police.
-There he is.
-He's here!
Chairman Choi, regarding the nurse…
-Do you admit to the charges?
-Do you have anything to say?
Care to comment?
Mr. Cha Se-gye was attacked last night…
Where is Shin Seo-ri? What did you do?
Se-gye, you're awake!
Thank goodness.
Tell me where she is.
Hey, why would you ask me about her?
You should have protected her.
What, can you not find her?
Did she run away?
Then again,
I suppose there is always a dagger
hanging over those who stand beside you.
Anyone in their right mind
would run.
You son of a…
Se-gye, are you okay?
Seriously, I had nothing to do with her.
You'd better find her.
Before I do.
-Are you okay?
-Why you little…
Mr. Cha Se-gye!
Are you okay, sir?
-You piece of…
-Enough!
Sir.
We can file a missing person report,
but without foul play,
we can't investigate.
We could act right away
if an immediate family member filed…
She doesn't have any family.
Her grandmother passed away recently.
Please do something.
Mr. Cha.
You don't look so good.
Are you okay?
I suppose there is always a dagger
hanging over those who stand beside you.
Anyone in their right mind
would run.
Mr. Cha! Are you okay?
What are you even doing here?
I can't find her.
Did she really run away?
It'd be a relief if she just ran away.
As long as she's safe.
Sir, let's just…
I don't think you should be
worrying about Ms. Shin right now.
Let's get you back to the hospital.
Easy. Careful.
Why haven't the police made any progress?
I can't live with all this anxiety.
The police are still investigating.
Let's just be patient.
Goodness. Are you feeling okay?
Are you sure you should be
out and about like this?
I can't find Shin Seo-ri.
I think something happened to her.
But I can't find her.
Please help me, Grandfather.
We found Ms. Shin Seo-ri.
We found her,
but right now she's…
-Excuse me.
-Pardon me.
They say she's unconscious.
Are you her guardian?
What happened to her?
We thought it was temporary,
but she's not responding.
It took us a while to identify her.
You should transfer her
to a larger hospital for a thorough exam.
Shin Seo-ri, why…
I offer you my sincerest congratulations.
Your punishment has ended.
Now, you may be free from your pain.
Pain…
Sever every knotted thread of connection,
whether ill-fated or destined.
Then you shall never again lose
the ones you hold dear
or shed another tear for them.
You have endured enough suffering.
Yes.
I suffered.
It was agony beyond what I could bear.
You need not endure it any longer.
Until you are ready
to pass on to the afterlife,
you may simply stay here
and find your peace.
This is a reward
bestowed upon you by the heavens.
It is peaceful.
Not a breath of wind.
It is so quiet.
And so, the vixen
chose to remain in a place
that was neither past nor present,
neither the world of the dead
nor the world of the living.
Because the soul-piercing pain
drove away all her painful memories
and her fond ones too.
They say the human brain
shuts down when the pain is too much.
I guess that's what happened?
She endured until the breaking point came.
Even so, she should not have lost herself.
She needs to realize
that hollow peace is nothing but a prison.
What a profound story.
But, ma'am, when do you think
I'll land a lead role?
There's a time for everything.
When the time comes,
whether to move forward or to stay…
the answer will reveal itself.
Why isn't she waking up?
She doesn't even have any injuries.
This can happen
even without any physical trauma.
When the brain receives
a shock it cannot handle,
it shuts down consciousness
to protect itself.
A kind of escape mechanism, if you will.
Then what should I do?
I'm willing to try anything.
Just stay by her side and talk to her.
There's always a chance she can hear you.
Mr. Cha has had no recent contact
with the rest of the family.
His movements have been limited
to the office and the hospital.
The hospital? You mean that woman?
Yes, she's in a coma.
Keep monitoring Cha Se-gye
until the press conference.
Report any unusual movements in real time.
Life's really put you through
the wringer and then some.
Is your life just one big obstacle course
or something?
Yes, Ms. Hong.
Me? Where else would I be?
I'm at home.
How's the lawsuit
against the trolls going?
I won't show them any leniency.
Bye.
Hello.
Yeah, hi.
Have you quit yet?
Well, not yet, but I will.
Still, the courteous thing to do would be
to say goodbye to Ms. Hong in person.
Courteous? Yeah, right.
Anyway, you made the right choice.
No matter how I look at it, Mr. Baek,
you're just not cut out to be a manager.
Go find your true calling.
I must have been blind.
What did I ever see in that woman?
SHIN SEO-RI
Sir, you have a guest.
She said she had something
to tell you regarding Ms. Shin.
I see.
To tell you the truth,
I have been channeling a spirit recently.
When I finally came to, I was in a haze.
I couldn't tell what was real
and what wasn't.
I went to her place,
and they told me she hasn't woken up yet.
But I still felt like I had to come
and at least say something to you.
I don't know
what con you're trying to pull,
but you should get lost
while I'm still being nice.
Before I call the cops.
Please don't be mad. Just hear me out.
Even if no one else knows, you should.
Seo-ri went to save you.
To save your life.
She gave up everything and went back.
Get out.
Right now.
Oh, gosh…
Even if the whole world
doesn't know it, you should.
Seo-ri went to save you.
What a load of crap.
To save your life.
She gave up everything and went back.
Listen, Cha Se-gye.
When spring comes,
we should go see
the cornelian cherry flowers.
We can make flower pancakes
with the yellow petals.
In summer, we can enjoy
a yard spilling over with trumpet vines
with peaches in our mouths.
Or we can even go back to the sea
to look at the beach roses.
And in autumn, make me
a crown of chrysanthemum blossoms.
We can also go see
the autumn leaves while holding hands.
Let us spend
all four seasons together like that.
Shin Seo-ri.
How long
has this been here?
Mochang Group's new cosmetics line
managed to hit number one
in Eastern Europe. Sorry, Se-gye.
Se-gye.
Se-gye?
My apologies.
I didn't sleep well last night.
Please continue.
Is Ms. Shin still the same?
Isn't it hard to keep waiting?
Not knowing when she'll wake up
or if she'll even get better.
Please don't take this the wrong way.
I'm just saying this out of concern.
Waiting without an end in sight
drains the life out of you.
And waiting doesn't guarantee
the answer you're hoping for.
Se-gye.
Have you ever been
to the museum across the street?
They have an interesting painting there.
A buyer who stopped by recently
was really taken with it.
She said the painting looked like
it had a story behind it.
It's half burned,
but it's a painting of a court lady.
She looked like someone I know.
She bears a strong resemblance
to Ms. Shin.
The court lady in that painting.
Could this be a brine stone?
But I have never been to the sea.
It looks like an ordinary painting,
but this painting holds two secrets.
In the Joseon era,
it was rare for a woman's face
to be preserved in a portrait.
This was due to the Confucian belief
in the separation of men and women.
So, this painting
must have been done in secret.
It was a bit unreal.
She could be her doppelgänger.
Do you see this book at the bottom?
It is the Seonghyeon Pavilion Diary,
and it once belonged
to Grand Prince Cheongheon,
Anjong's brother.
The ill-fated prince who vanished in exile
after being swept up in a scandal.
When it came back to Korea
just a year ago,
no one expected it
to become this well-known.
History is written
by the victors, after all.
The page it is opened to
is the last record Prince Cheongheon left
before his disappearance.
It holds the truth, not the history
recorded in the royal Annals.
"A Record of the Jeongchuk Day
of the Tenth Month, Byeongo Year."
"The downpour that rattled the roof
through the night has ceased."
I used the collected rainwater
to tidy myself up early in the morning.
Today is different from yesterday.
She is coming here.
Are you on your way?
To me?
I sought to rid my mind of you.
Why are you coming to me now?
Rather than aching with longing,
hating me would serve your life better.
I must drive you away with cruel words.
Even if it breaks your heart,
that is the way to save you.
Bait?
Who do you think you are?
Just because we shared
some banter as "companions,"
do you truly think
that makes you something to me?
I was happy.
I was just a court lady
with no one to confide in but a stray dog.
I was happy when you offered
to be my companion.
Shin Seo-ri.
Even if this is the end,
I cannot say it was a bad life.
A royal who could never be sovereign.
I was never destined
to live out a full life.
Still, departing this life with the one
I treasure most kept safe…
Is that not a rather
fitting end for a man?
You must not drink that. It is poison!
To save your life.
She gave up everything and went back.
Did I not tell you?
I am trying to save you.
He will only live
if Your Highness survives.
He is more precious than life to me.
Can't we
just stop all this now?
Wow, it's snowing!
Mom, look! It's snow.
Snow in the middle of summer?
What deep sorrow brought this on?
More like freak weather.
It's still pretty though.
EMBRACING JOSEON ONCE MORE
Can't you please stop making me wait?
I…
can't breathe, Shin Seo-ri.
Come back.
Please…
He is alive.
Shin Seo-ri, look at me.
I'm right here.
Cha Se-gye.
No matter how dark the night is,
if someone is by your side,
it is a bit more bearable and less scary.
It is not about where you are.
It is about who you are with.
I harbor affection for you.
I just need you.
You're the only one, Shin Seo-ri.
Let me be your only one too.
Cha Se-gye.
No matter what happens
to us in the future,
just remember
that I truly hold you in my heart.
I will take that with me wherever I go.
And with that one memory,
I will flourish and not wither away.
Promise me.
I will make sure you are not alone.
You can trust me.
Don't forget that promise, Shin Seo-ri.
Protecting you. I gave you my word.
Your punishment has ended.
Now, you may be free from your pain.
No.
Sever every knotted thread of connection,
whether ill-fated or destined.
Then you shall never again lose
the ones you hold dear
or shed another tear for them.
No.
This is a reward
bestowed upon you by the heavens.
This is no reward.
Without pain, there is no happiness.
Without sorrow, you cannot feel joy.
I have no need for such a reward.
Then I shall give you
one last chance to choose.
You may go anywhere.
The past or the present.
Even the future or another world.
You can even go to a world
where you bear no trace of the vixen.
Where will you head to?
I have already made my decision.
I choose…
Cha Se-gye.
It is snowing.
Why are you out here getting snowed on?
You…
I missed you.
So much.
I am so glad you are alive.
Thank you for staying alive.
You.
How could you?
How could you leave me behind?
How was I supposed to live without you?
But I am here now.
Both of us are here
perfectly alive.
I really thought you were dying.
I almost died waiting for you.
I never even told you
how I feel about you.
I never had a chance
to tell you I love you.
How could you just leave like that?
You can do it now.
You can do it every day.
I love you, Cha Se-gye.
Look at you, beating me to it again.
You're seriously…
You and me for the next hundred years.
A hundred years?
I want a thousand. Ten thousand.
You're not going anywhere now.
Fine.
Deal sealed.
Shin Seo-ri, slap me.
Slap you?
We reunite, and that is what you want?
It just doesn't feel real.
I think I might be dreaming.
So hit me hard.
This is not a dream. This is real.
How is it? Nice and warm?
Yeah.
It's nice and warm.
You really are the Shin Seo-ri I know.
Unbelievable.
What took you so long?
Were you trying to torture me?
I thought you were dead.
"In the end, I could not save one.
I am the sole survivor."
"And now,
I truly have no one left."
But then I heard your voice.
In a place with no day or night,
your voice was clear as the sun.
You saved me, Cha Se-gye.
You pulled me out of there.
No, you saved me.
Both of us.
And him too.
The fact that I'm right here
in front of you is proof.
That we are alive.
They must be finding their way
along their own path.
Looking completely different.
You are not a boy. You are a girl.
That's a secret, kiddo.
Here.
What is your name?
My name is Dan-sim.
Kang Dan-sim.
Halt.
A composite sketch!
A comp-what now?
Hey, Park.
You should be carrying our bundles.
The ferry to Qing is that way.
You are forgetful.
I should have been more attentive.
It's fine.
Let's ditch those cops and run.
You really are
like a different person.
From your speech to your eyes.
I told you. I made a comeback
to my own body.
Anyway, let's scram. That way.
All right.
Let us scram, then. Quickly.
Bye!
They're probably out there living it up
somewhere we'll never know.
I'm sure of it.
I want to believe that.
Things never went the way I believed.
But I want to believe that.
I'm telling you I'm right.
I can guarantee it.
Okay. I will believe it.
Up until now,
I was busy scrambling to survive.
Now I want to live the way I believe.
Good.
Let's turn over a new leaf too.
No more giving people ammunition.
Let's just be good and kind.
No. We cannot do that.
Why be nice in this cruel world?
Want to be a pushover?
If someone betrays you,
you hunt them down.
Anyone who badmouths you
gets it back double.
We must be ruthless.
Wait, why?
Why are you so fired up?
Even more intense than before.
Turning over a new leaf too quickly
can be lethal.
After everything I did
to make it back alive?
I shall outlive them all.
In that spirit…
we cannot just let everything end
on good terms like this.
What's with that look? It's scary.
The reporters have arrived.
I'll be leaving
for the US branch right after this,
so go and pick up Seo-jun.
Until now, Chail deserved
every bit of criticism
for its incompetence, greed,
and the resulting scandals.
Times like these
call for decisive action
to carve out what's rotten.
Let me make this clear to all of you now.
Should further police investigation
be needed,
we shall continue to comply diligently
and maintain full transparency
until the full truth is revealed.
Is that to say you had no part
in any of these matters?
Legally, I may have no involvement,
but as family,
I feel very much responsible.
You cleverly sidestepped
the allegations made against you directly.
Is that the purpose
of today's press conference?
Which outlet are you from?
Please state your affiliation.
Affiliation?
I am affiliated with Cha Se-gye.
You dared to mess with my man.
You are dead meat today.
Get rid of her.
Stand back, you scoundrels!
Before I snap your wrists in half.
You should've left her alone
when she said so.
Now your wrists are broken for nothing.
What took you so long?
You should have run over.
Traffic was bad. What could I do?
Traffic in Seoul is a serious problem.
What do you think you're doing?
This is a press conference.
Yeah.
Just looking to have
some fun with the reporters.
Mr. Son.
RE: CHOI MUN-DO ABANDONS BODY
Can I ask all the reporters here
to check their phones?
-What is this?
-Hold on.
Cha Se-gye.
What is this?
Right.
I acquired them the day
you spread that power-trip video.
My word.
Their deepfake work
has improved again since then.
Looks real, doesn't it?
It really does.
It really is a scary world.
I suppose you could call this foresight?
30 MINUTES AGO
Our job is to represent
the company's interests.
Whether this benefits
or harms the company.
Let that be your guiding principle
as you cast your votes.
Effective immediately,
Choi Mun-do is no longer
the interim chairman of Chail Group.
He is just a private citizen now.
You have been notified
by the board of directors
of your dismissal
from the interim CEO position.
Naturally, your trial
will not be handled by Chail's legal team.
Who says there's going to be a trial?
Can't make an arrest without evidence.
There certainly is evidence.
Mr. Choi Mun-do.
Please come with us. You're under arrest.
This must be about the illegal video.
But it's a deepfake.
The police wouldn't move
this swiftly over a fabricated video.
Isn't that right, Inspector Lee?
Yes, your aide turned himself in.
It appears he recorded
and documented every task
you've ever given him.
The statements alone could fill a truck.
Such is life.
You should have hired better subordinates.
No. When the water upstream is dirty,
the water downstream cannot run clear.
Why are you so lost in thought?
This is the problem with the 21st century.
When you cannot deliver justice yourself,
it never quite satisfies.
It wouldn't be
the 21st century if we could.
What kind of Stone Age society
has you getting blood on your hands?
This will not do.
Any karma I can exact myself,
I shall make sure it is thorough.
Oh my God!
Who the hell left this here?
Damn it.
What the…
Reflect.
Shin Seo-ri, you crazy…
Damn it.
Right back at you, punk.
Royal Consort Kang,
the villainess with the poison refills?
Here is the real tea.
Court intrigue? Just Anjong's gaslighting.
The consorts and the Queen were victims.
Using women as shields for personal gain?
Posthumous decapitation is only fitting.
Perhaps that sounds too elegant?
Eradication is the answer.
Perfect.
-Jeez!
-Any grievances?
I can serve up some karma for you.
Enough already.
There's just no middle ground with you.
Ms. Hong.
Hey,
what kind of intern
submits their resignation offline?
A phone call would've sufficed.
I see.
Gosh.
Did you find a new manager?
I need to hire one,
but we're in trouble.
Word of Ji-hyo's temper
has spread all over the industry.
She's apparently number one
on the manager community blacklist.
I'm pretty sure the troll responsible
is an industry insider too.
What? And I'm a suspect now?
No, I was just wondering
if you knew of any potential suspects.
-It's not me.
-Right, it shouldn't be.
With a mouth like hers,
it was always
going to come back to bite her.
How is there still no progress
on the troll lawsuit?
Hey!
Did you block my number?
What the… Gong Tae-woo?
What are you doing here?
-Give it.
-Damn it.
Give it back! Damn it.
The call cannot be connected…
You really did block me.
Unblock me and drop the charges.
We're broken up.
Why do you care if I block you or not?
Wait, did you post hate comments about me?
You petty bastard.
No wonder there was always
a grain of truth buried in every post.
I'll see you at the station.
Get ready to be completely
and utterly humiliated.
Hey, Yoon Ji-hyo!
Damn it. Let go!
-Let me go!
-Knock it off!
I get that you're still not over me,
but you can't just take a dump
all over someone's life like this.
She's clearly not the one full of crap.
Who are you?
Let her go.
Article 260,
Paragraph 1 of the Criminal Act.
Any person who assaults another
shall be punished by
up to two years of imprisonment
or a fine not exceeding 5 million won.
What? Are you a lawyer?
Me? I'm not a lawyer.
Civil servant hopeful…
turned manager. Why?
This is all being recorded right now.
Want me to take a video too?
Should I go live
for the whole country to see?
-Hey, don't film me! Don't.
-Should I?
Hey.
You better drop those charges.
Article 283,
Paragraph 1 of the Criminal Act.
Any person who threatens another
shall face up to 3 years of imprisonment
or a 5 million won fine.
Damn it.
What a bastard.
What did I ever do to him
to deserve this?
What did I…
Damn it.
You did do something wrong.
You did indeed.
Seriously? Damn it.
It's wrong for you to look this pretty
even when you're crying.
Disproportionate self pity.
I'd call that a crime too.
So forget the hate comments
and all that other crap.
And focus on yourself.
Ji-hyo, you're a much better person
than you think you are.
Trust me. I'm a good judge of character.
Need more?
Here.
Go on, wipe your tears.
You came here alone without Se-gye?
Before the trial.
Right, that trial.
People are lining up
to send you to your grave.
Your aide, Director Jang,
and even your staff at home.
Just a line around the block.
That won't work on me.
I won't be in here for long.
What do you want?
Do you…
believe in fate?
Fate?
That everything is
predetermined and unchanging.
That nothing changes
no matter how hard you try.
Therefore do not dare
to dishonor your betters,
forget your station, or rise against them.
It is quite a garbage notion.
Created by those in power.
I do not believe in fate anymore.
Instead, I have come to believe
in the karma I have created.
Because you and I are living proof of it.
I was curious enough to come hear you out…
but you should save
your half-baked philosophy for Se-gye.
I can't listen to this anymore.
You really are clueless.
With such ignorance,
you will rot away in this cold prison.
After squandering your one chance
to rewrite your mistakes.
Chance? What chance?
The chance to save your corrupted soul.
Dad!
The chance to wash away
the greed etched in your soul.
Your one chance to become whole.
You blew that chance.
You can now ruminate
on that chance you threw away
in this cold prison
for the rest of your life
as it gnaws away at you
bit by bit.
Grandma.
How is it up there?
Are you resting well
in a warm, sunny house?
I'm doing well too.
REST IN PEACE NAM OK-SUN
Finding small joys along the way
with someone who stays by my side.
So please watch over me.
See how fully I live my life,
making up for lost happiness
with interest,
surrounded by warmth.
Fly freely, Seo-ri.
Jeez, did he call you again?
Why does Grandfather
keep calling you instead of me?
You should have answered his calls.
He said he is about to block you
because you never pick up.
Block me? As if he could defy
the laws of parental love.
It sounded like he was about to defy them.
You will be hung out to dry.
Why would I be hung out?
Father,
I've made my decision.
I'm getting a divorce.
I just submitted the papers.
Yeah. Divorce isn't anything
to be ashamed of nowadays.
Plenty of people do it two or three times.
Nothing to brag about, either.
Goodness, how did both my kids
end up divorced?
Grandfather!
Gosh. My sweet boy.
There you are. Are you back from school?
-Yes.
-Good.
We played kickball in PE today,
and my class won!
Well done. Excellent.
Wow, our Seo-jun is great at kickball too.
You're good at every sport.
Yeah.
Since when is kickball a sport?
What's so special about some kids
kicking around a little ball?
If you're going to be like this,
don't bother coming.
Why come here just to spoil the mood?
Hey.
I'm trying to start things off
on the right foot with him. What?
You bitch even when I show up.
"Bitch"?
No.
I meant, "hitch." Auntie misspoke.
You see, a hitch is
like a hiccup that stops you
and causes you to be late and stuff.
I see. It makes you run late?
Auntie, are you a hitcher?
That's right, she's one big hitcher.
-Hitcher.
-Hitcher…
She's a hitcher all right.
Some are disarmed by childlike innocence.
BIOJEI 2027 OPEN RECRUITMENT
Hello there.
"Your diligent and responsible man."
"I am Baek Gwang-nam."
Your diligent and responsible man…
K-beauty… The core of K-beauty.
I dream of joining Biojei to be
at the frontline of K-beauty…
That's not going to work.
Frontline? Are you going off to war?
Hey, I'm trying to rehearse here…
What?
Ji-hyo?
Does she work here?
Mr. Baek, are you seriously saying
this is your true calling?
Wait, what are you doing here?
-Are you here for me?
-No.
Yeah.
I'm here on business.
What a coincidence.
Like destiny.
Candidate 332, Mr. Baek Gwang-nam.
Yes, I'm here.
-You'll be next.
-Okay.
Please excuse me, Ji-hyo.
Don't go.
Oh, my.
Don't go. Work with me instead.
-What?
-I'll triple your pay.
Triple. Oh, my.
I need
a trash talker like you.
Damn. What a baddie.
Deal?
Some find meaning
in the calling of a name.
Congratulations, Se-gye.
You've reclaimed the number one spot
in the Eastern European cosmetics market.
Sorry about that, Tae-hee.
You must've had quite a run
while I was stumbling.
You don't look sorry at all.
You actually look happy.
How annoying.
Yes, I am happy.
So happy I almost feel guilty about it.
What about you, Tae-hee?
I'm going to give happiness a try too.
Thanks to a certain someone,
I now believe
that such a thing really exists.
Some carry hope for a new beginning.
Very well!
Let this day claim us both.
THE WOMEN'S KINGDOM 2
Let us see this through!
I mean,
that's just too much.
You can't claim cute,
pretty, and sexy all for yourself.
What's everyone else supposed to do?
Stop watching my old drama,
and help me run my lines.
Here.
-Your lines?
-Yeah.
Let's see. My 99th First Kiss.
What? Ninety…
Are you saying
you're going to kiss 99 times?
Are you nuts?
No, don't do it. Cancel it.
Cancel what? The shoot is in two days.
Who cares?
I'll buy up all the ad spots.
Just take out all the kiss scenes.
"My 99th Eye Contact" sounds nice.
Family-friendly.
You must be kidding.
Who would watch that?
Are you trying to ruin my career?
What the…
Then you can just live with me.
I never agreed to that. Slow down.
Time for your kiss scene with me.
What are you doing? Stop it!
-It hurts.
-Are you okay?
While others
find gratitude
for the smile of a loved one.
In this vast and boundless sea
we call life,
we survive
by holding onto whatever we can.
Come spring, let us go see
the cornelian cherry flowers.
We will make flower pancakes.
-Flower pancakes?
-Yeah.
And in summer, we can come
to the sea, just like this.
And eat some ostrea too.
We should plant
trumpet vines in your yard.
And eat a whole lot of peaches.
Are we only going to plant and eat things?
Autumn calls for chrysanthemums.
We should plant some.
And a persimmon tree to pick from!
Unbelievable.
Our yard is going to become an orchard.
We'll be able to open a fruit stand.
Seasonal fruit is so good for you.
You find the little joys in life
when you eat what is in season.
Really? Who said that?
My grandma.
My grandma used to say that.
You have to enjoy things
in their time to be happy.
Happiness doesn't earn interest.
That's true.
It really is.
I am done lamenting the world.
I am going to live freely.
Like a pure white frost flower
in the middle of summer.
Freely.
Sure. Freely.
I love you, Shin Seo-ri.
Empty tokens are meaningless.
Warmth is all you really need.
Having courage with every step
can keep you going in the end.
If you just hold on,
it will come to you, without fail.
You beat me to it again.
If you do,
a magnificent world
will unfold before you.
I guarantee it. You can trust me.
Subtitle translation by Justin S. Kim