"Lost To You"
(Episode 9)
If the countdown to the
rest of my life has begun,
I only want to run away with you.
Even if the destination is darkness.
Zhan Wang
I like you.
Zhan Wang, are you okay?
He'll live.
He just drank too much.
He got too emotional.
He'll be fine after some sleep.
Zhan Xu.
Is Zhan Wang really...
Don't worry.
The two of them
didn't hit each other too hard.
Hurry up and take him back.
He really hit hard.
Let me see your injury.
Does it hurt?
No.
But, Zhan Xu...
I'm scared.
I'm right here.
Haven't I always been by your side?
I'm afraid of their nasty words.
I'm afraid you won't be able to take it,
and you'll hide away by yourself again,
leaving me behind.
Don't worry.
This time,
it's my turn to protect you.
We're not going anywhere.
If we go,
we go together.
Zhan Xu...
I'm thirsty.
Xu Yuan.
I'm here.
Don't push me away.
I won't.
You're not allowed to choose Xiang Bei.
I only choose you.
I like your minty scent.
I know.
Xu Yuan.
This is Xu Yuan's room.
How did I end up back at Xu Yuan's place?
Zhan Wang.
I like you.
You're awake.
I made some hangover soup for you.
Come out and have some.
Does your head hurt?
That's what you get for
drinking so much yesterday.
Hurry up and drink some hangover soup.
Why am I at your place?
Last night...
You drank too much last night.
Bian Ye found you,
and then,
I brought you back to my place.
Did I...
say anything stupid?
No.
You were just a bit loud.
Drink the soup.
My head hurts.
I really can't drink it.
Just have some.
It's good for you.
We have to go to school after this.
There's an event at school today.
We need to help out.
Um...
Do you have any more mints?
My mouth tastes weird.
It's awful.
Here.
Look over there.
He's putting on quite a show.
A red-haired punk pretending to read.
Exactly.
I heard
he's been running to the
suspended school doctor, Zhan,
quite often lately.
One is gay,
the other is a punk.
Asking for advice?
Who are they kidding?
It's obviously that kind
of disgusting relationship.
Can you guys show some decency?
How is him reading any of your business?
What kind of person is Zhan Xu?
What kind of person is Bian Ye?
Who are you to judge them?
I'll say whatever I want.
What's it to you?
Don't tell me your jinx of a brother
is also gay?
You have a filthy mouth.
Spending your time gossiping
about others' private lives
doesn't make you any classier.
Everyone has
the right to choose their own lifestyle.
You don't have to understand it,
but at least learn to respect it.
Look who's playing the good guy now.
Weren't you the one
who pointed at him and called him gay?
Yeah!
Exactly!
And now we're not allowed to talk?
How ridiculous, shouting so loud.
Right?
If you have a problem, come at me.
Why yell at a girl?
I'm right here.
Say it to my face.
You're just a red-haired punk.
We're saying you're
just like that damn queer.
So what?
Shut up!
- You...
- Bian Ye.
Zhan Xu.
I... I didn't cause any trouble.
I know.
Why is he here?
Lately,
I know some of you
are very interested in me.
About my sexual orientation.
I have already resigned,
so it won't affect you anymore.
Bian Ye...
We are together now.
I was the one who pursued him.
I hope he can accept me.
So it's true!
Really?
I had no idea.
So he was the one pursuing him.
What?
This is really...
Calling him a damn queer was spot on.
Likewise,
this is also between the two of us.
Oh my god!
They're actually kissing!
This...
Oh my god!
They're being so blatant!
I can't believe it.
In broad daylight,
they dare to kiss right here.
I ship them so hard!
This is true love!
Come on, cheers!
To celebrate that we're still together,
and to celebrate
overcoming all our obstacles,
one by one.
Cheers!
To celebrate Lin Xia's
hand recovering so well!
To celebrate Zhan Wang's health improving!
To celebrate the great weather today!
And to celebrate that we're
all a bit braver than yesterday!
Cheers!
What the heck?
Why is mine just juice?
Mine too!
Minors only get juice.
No fun.
What are you looking at?
Eat up!
I'm starving.
Oh my god.
Today,
thank you
for not pushing me away.
Push you away?
It's just...
so sudden.
I was totally caught off guard.
But,
it actually felt pretty good.
When my brother kissed Bian Ye earlier,
someone's face
turned as red as a tomato.
You weren't any better.
Your eyes were as wide as saucers.
It was quite shocking,
but really satisfying.
My brother...
finally isn't hiding anymore.
Then what about us?
Boss,
The demolition agreements
for the other shops
have all been signed.
Now, only the Xu Family
Noodle Shop is left.
We've tried everything, but nothing worked.
The boys heard back that
the Zhan family has stepped in.
Are we still going ahead
with the demolition?
Tear it down.
Come on, another drink.
To bravery, and to the future.
To those messy,
yet very special days.
Cheers!
[Mom]
Mom?
Hello.
Are you a family member of Chen Meixi?
This is the hospital calling.
The hospital?
She just fainted and was brought in.
We need a family member to come over.
Which hospital?
People's Hospital.
Okay.
I... I understand.
Something happened to my mom.
The demolition crew came to
force her to sign again today.
They made her so angry she
fainted and was sent to the hospital.
Mom!
Don't panic.
I'll go to the hospital with you.
Where are the people
doing the forced demolition?
At the noodle shop again?
They said it must be torn down today.
We can't let them get away with this.
Lin Xia, go to the hospital with Xiao Nuo.
Xu Yuan, let's go.
Let's go.
Let's go to the hospital to help.
Don't think hiding in
the hospital will save you.
If you don't sign today,
the shop is gone.
18 million.
What are you doing?
I've already called the police.
Your demolition procedures are illegal.
A lawyer's letter will arrive tomorrow.
You little punk.
You're still wet behind the ears,
and you're trying to lecture me on the law?
Let me tell you,
around here,
my word is the law.
Get the hell out of here.
If you don't leave, we'll
tear you down with it.
Don't you dare!
Doing this the hard way, huh?
Beat them up!
Zhan Wang!
Run!
Get them! Don't let them run!
This way!
Fortunately, it's just a flesh wound.
No internal organs were damaged.
It's fine.
I used to get these kinds
of injuries all the time.
You do it.
Are you sure you don't
want to call Brother Xu?
Or go to the hospital?
I trust you.
I'm starting then.
Dr. Xu,
it hurts.
Is there any other way?
Just bear with it a little longer.
It'll be over soon.
You're hurt.
Let me do it.
Are you scared?
No.
You're awake.
Why aren't you sleeping?
Is your wound uncomfortable?
I was afraid that if I fell asleep,
you wouldn't be here when I woke up.
How could I leave?
I'll always be by your side.
Does your wound...
still hurt?
Are you hurting?
Did you like it?
Are you sleepy?
No.
I was just thinking,
how many times have we woken up together?
Have you counted?
The third time.
And this time is different.
I'm so scared.
I'm scared that we're dreaming right now.
I think even if it's a dream,
it's a
very beautiful,
very long,
and very romantic dream.
I don't want to wake up.
I don't want to wake up either.
Then, if
you had to set an
expiration date for this dream,
how long would you want it to be?
Ten thousand years.
Guess
how long I want it to be.
I can't guess.
No expiration date.
You're so bad.
Bian Ye,
we will always be together.
Let me carry your bag.
Sure.
They really have a great relationship.
They're inseparable.
It's good that they get along so well.
Xiao Wang even made a
special trip to bring me back.
I heard you got hurt.
Are you feeling better?
I'm fine, Auntie.
It's just a minor injury.
I even dragged you into this.
We're already family.
There's no such thing
as dragging anyone down.
It's just a pity
the shop was still torn down in the end.
I'm already working on a solution.
Auntie,
congratulations on being discharged.
Thank you.
You came too.
I'll go make something for you guys to eat.
Auntie, you just recovered.
Please don't trouble yourself.
It's no trouble.
I'll help Mom inside first.
I asked a friend
to find a storefront at the
east entrance of the town.
They're in a hurry to sublease.
The location is pretty good.
It's surrounded by long-time residents,
so there's a good base
of regular customers.
As for the paperwork and the initial rent,
I can...
It's fine, I have the money.
Just give me the landlord's
phone number and address.
That'll be enough.
Alright.
You're an adult now.
Solving your own problems
is a good thing.
[Folder containing documents]
Here.
Take it.
The place my second brother
found definitely won't be bad.
But
there's one more thing I
might need to trouble you with.
As for Lawyer Lu,
I've already spoken with him.
They demolished illegally
and intentionally caused harm.
Once the lawsuit is settled,
the compensation won't be small.
I'm your second brother.
How could I not know what you're thinking?
Thank you,
Brother.
I'm off.
Zhan Wang,
where did you get so much money?
Don't worry.
I have plenty of money.
Zhan Wang.
What's wrong?
Are you worried I'll squander it?
Then you'll have to keep a close
eye on the money from now on,
Housekeeper Xu.
Let's go.
[The menu for the restaurant]
Xiao Yuan-yuan,
I'm here!