Don't let the fire go out tonight.
Bears come around here often.
Thanks, Brother Wu.
You go into the mountains a lot.
Have you ever been attacked by a bear?
Bears aren't as tall as me.
They can't hurt me.
Do I really look like a bear?
I never used to think about
how I'd survive without a signal.
And now?
Being cut off from the world...
is absolutely amazing.
You don't find it boring?
It's like going back to
the Stone Age overnight.
"A Winter Sun Wakes the Wind in Spring Hills' Dream"
(Episode 5: The Wilderness)
Is that rumor about the rich woman true?
You actually believe rumors like that?
With your current standing, how
could you land a variety show?
Can't I get one on my own merit?
Does no one have any faith in me?
Everyone says Qinglang
won Best Actor on merit.
Why does no one believe in me?
No one at all?
I'm sorry.
Sister Lan found out what I did for you.
Oh. Did she give you a hard time?
No. Just wait for me to get back.
Okay.
Love you, baby.
I'll be waiting for you.
What's this?
Tea seed powder. It's eco-friendly.
You really care about the environment.
But have you ever thought about this?
Once we reach the village...
where people actually live...
and everyone goes back to
using detergent and shampoo...
the pollution will still wash
down the river to this very spot.
Just because I can't control the future...
doesn't mean I should
stop doing the right thing now.
At least I'm doing my part right now.
I won't have any regrets.
I can't believe he ran away with someone.
He's still not answering his phone.
It's probably just a bad signal.
I'm sure he's fine.
Are you warm enough?
Here's your strawberry.
Thank you.
Wenshu replied.
She can talk now.
Sister Lan.
Hello, President Xu.
You're too polite, Sister Lan.
Just call me Wenshu.
I don't eat sweets when I'm filming.
Oh, please.
I've been eating double
portions for every meal.
I've put on so much weight
these past two months.
I heard that Tony is coming.
When will he be here?
He'll be here shortly.
Watch your attitude.
I'll try.
Do you think I'm breaking out?
Let me see.
Sister Lan.
Kevin.
Sister Jialin.
You must be exhausted
after the flight and the drive.
I just got off the bus.
I wanted to make sure I came
to see Sister Lan right away.
Sister Lan is on a call right now.
Cavin, you might need to wait a moment.
Kevin.
Sister Lan is dealing with
an urgent matter right now.
Once she's done, I'll
bring her over to see you.
Oh, that won't do.
You've already taken such
good care of my boy here.
Brother Guo, please show Kevin to his room.
Sure.
Are you afraid of Kevin?
It's not really fear.
I'm under contract, so I
have to do what I'm told.
Our company isn't like that.
I know.
I'd heard that Sister Lan was
different from other producers.
But I didn't quite believe it back then.
I actually really envy you.
Having someone like Sister Lan.
If I could work under
Sister Lan for a few years...
I'd definitely make
it big in the future.
The other day, I saw her taking out
the trash and moving tables herself.
It's like she can do absolutely
everything on her own.
"Never pin your hopes on others."
Yes, Sister Lan told me that.
It's our company slogan.
It's hanging on the wall.
When I first joined...
and Sister Lan interviewed me...
she said something to me...
that I'll never forget
for the rest of my life.
I asked her...
if actors aren't allowed to date.
What did she say?
She told me...
"You can date."
"But as an artist..."
"if you rely on your
fans for a living..."
"you must have basic
professional integrity."
"You can't take their money..."
"while deceiving them at the same time."
"That's cause and effect."
"Everyone must bear the consequences..."
"of their own choices and actions."
"But as your elder..."
"I support you dating."
"You have the right to experience life..."
"instead of being bound by a label."
At that moment, I realized...
I'd probably never find...
a boss more
understanding than Sister Lan.
So, I signed the contract.
Besides, all of Sister Lan's
works reflect who she is.
I believe that artistic expression...
is a reflection of the creator's soul.
That's beautiful.
Yeah.
Let me ask you something.
Were Lang Di and Shi Yuhao together before?
How should I know?
Aren't you psychic?
Close your eyes and take a look.
Old Man Chang wasn't surprised.
He asked Old Man Qing,
"Where are they?"
"They went back to the sea."
Old Man Qing looked longingly
at the sunset glow and said,
"They're all out at sea."
"They represent every
loved one and friend..."
"who had ever crossed
paths with the two old men."
Old Man Chang held Old
Man Qing's hands in one of his,
and gently touched his face, saying,
"Yanyan, let's go back too."
Snuggled together under
the bright, warm sun,
they returned to the sea together.
That year, Old Man Chang was 116 years old,
and his lover was 129.
He had fulfilled his childhood wish.
From the moment he met his love at 16,
to 26, 36...
and finally to 116.
Spending a hundred years in this world...
sharing a hundred springs, summers,
autumns, and winters with his love.
That's a legendary kind
of happiness, isn't it?
By that logic,
I'll have to live to 118.
What are the main characters' names?
Old Man Chang and Old Man Qing.
I mean their real names.
Changyang and Qinglang.
You're lying.
Look for yourself if you don't believe me.
How long have we been out this time?
Who cares?
I don't have any work
until next month anyway.
Oh.
What are you drawing?
Counting down the days until next month.
Including today, we have ten days left.
This scar on your head...
From a fight when I was a kid.
You don't seem like the
type to get into fights.
You won't even argue with me.
Don't you need me to go easy on you?
If you didn't truly understand me...
you wouldn't be able to.
You have a fiery temper.
Before I used to
be worse than you.
It's like you have
firecrackers in your pocket...
ready to pull them out
and light them at any moment.
So why did you get into a fight?
Was someone bullying you?
I was backstabbed by my best friend.
They spread the rumor that
I was an illegitimate child.
I took on eight of them by myself.
I beat them so badly they
all ended up in the hospital.
Is that why you came to Molie?
Yeah.
But I realized the mountains
are cleaner than people's hearts.
So I decided to stay.
Jin Jin.
I've always treated you
like family, haven't I?
Sister Jialin, you don't
have to say it. I resign.
I was the one who told Shi Yuhao
about Lang Di's whereabouts.
Being a fangirl for a washed-up actor...
has more of a future
than working with me?
I don't care about my future.
I love Shi Yuhao.
I'd do anything for him.
He's a total scumbag!
Jialin, did you settle Jin Jin's pay?
This girl is so stubborn.
I want her to see clearly that
Shi Yuhao isn't worth
her sacrificing so much.
Jin Jin.
I hope you remember
the choice you made today.
No matter what happens in the future,
you must accept who you were today.
That's enough.
You only lost a job with me.
I don't want you to lose
the impulse and passion of your youth.
Jialin, have the accountant
pay her in cash later.
Sister Lan, I don't regret it.
Good.
Wow, happy wrap-up!
Happy wrap-up!
Great.
Thank you, Sister Lan.
Thank you for your hard work.
Go on.
Oh, look at my hands.
Look at my hands.
What do you want to do in the future?
You don't want to do just one
thing your whole life, do you?
Sticking to one person is fine.
Can you speak properly?
If you hadn't come to Molie,
I was planning to leave.
To where?
I want to see other forests.
I want to visit every forest in the world.
That's a great dream.
You support it?
Of course I do.
Don't you think it's crazy?
If I quit showbiz,
I'd be even crazier than you.
It's not working very well.
Let's charge it when we
get back to the guesthouse.
Being a caveman isn't easy.
I'm definitely going to get
scolded when I get back.
I promised Sister Lan a cameo.
Counting the days, they should
wrap up today or tomorrow.
I probably won't make it.
Sister Lan's new drama?
A remake of my movie from seven years ago.
I often hear people say
an actor's destiny will closely align
with the character that made them famous.
Is that true for you too?
Not really.
If it were that accurate,
I should have played a character
who wins Best Actor right away.
It would have saved me a lot of detours.
Shi Yuhao is quite like his character.
Cowardly and indecisive.
In that case, I'm quite like mine too.
I am brave,
steadfast in the path I choose,
and unwavering.
You too, right?
Tiantian.
Now that Grandma is here,
neither you or Langlang are home.
If you two don't come back soon,
Grandma is going to throw a fit.
Grandma, please stay a few more days.
I'll fly back.
Grandma, did my brother call home?
Huh?
Did my brother, Feng Qinglang, call home?
No. Is something wrong with your brother?
Your eldest grandson is missing.
He's hiding, and we can't find him.
- Really?
- Who's calling?
- My grandson.
- Don't tell Mom.
I have to go, Grandma.
Okay, okay.
Did he say what it was about?
Yes, he said he missed his grandma.
Hello, Brother Wenshu.
Did you find your brother?
Not yet. I shouldn't have
treated him like an adult.
You're not that old either.
Brother Wenshu, I have
a confession to make.
What is it?
Half a month ago,
I talked to Changyang about going into
the mountains for the spring tea season.
Later, I brought my brother along.
Thinking back on it now,
Changyang was the one who said the
mountains are peaceful and rejuvenating,
perfect for a relaxing vacation.
He also said he planned
to start a tea estate
to cater to out-of-town clients.
And most importantly,
he said, "I have a friend
who wants to come,
and I can host him."
Only now do I realize
he was baiting me into
bringing my brother here.
Back then, my brother had just announced
his participation in the
variety show with Shi Yuhao.
The two fanbases were
at each other's throats,
and my brother was extremely stressed.
So you suspect Changyang
planned this all along?
If nothing was going on between them,
I wouldn't suspect him.
But now that he's run off with my brother,
I feel really bad about
this, especially to you.
You don't have to feel that way.
Yes, I do. You've chased
my brother for three years.
If you hadn't invested in his movie,
he wouldn't have won Best Actor.
Professionally and personally,
I feel like we owe you.
Then think about how
you can make it up to me.
I've already thought of a way.
I'll ask Changyang for his best tea,
and sell it to you at the lowest price.
I'll help you make money.
Taking Changyang's money
and putting it in my pocket?
Moving money from hand to hand?
Exactly.
Then I'll help you win my brother back.
I'm afraid I don't have what it takes.
Changyang is too clever.
And you're far away abroad.
During my brother's days in Molie,
he pampered him down to his very hair.
He's more devoted than anything.
Don't overthink it. I don't blame you.
How many other people do you call "baby"?
I can't believe I invested 50 million
to get you variety show resources,
and this is how you repay me?
Sister Dan, I...
You're dropped.
[He's trying to call Qinglang]
I'm crying.
I actually cried.
Do you remember when
we were filming before,
I could never cry?
Today, I cried.
I found what Sister Lan talked about??
The fire in my heart.
Sister Lan always said the
fire in my heart had gone out,
but now I've found it.
I found it!
Qinglang.
Are you happy for me?
[Now he's calling his mom]
Mom,
I can cry now.
Listen... You can't hear it?
I'll make a...
I'll record a video for you.
[Now he's posting his crash-out on
Weibo, with the caption "Mom, look!"]
[His fans reacting, sharing
theories on his personal/work life]
My luggage is still in the car.
Get it tomorrow morning.
Why tomorrow morning?
I don't want to carry it. Do you?
I don't either.
What do you want to watch?
Your first on-screen kiss.
Turn it off.
It's not like I haven't seen it.
I'm not watching it with you.
How about the one you won the award for?
Why do you keep watching my movies?
There's a secret.
A secret.
A boy's secret.
Are we waking up early tomorrow?
No.
Ah.
I need to charge.
Does your charger cable fit my phone?
It's plugged in.
My phone is going to
blow up once I turn it on.
How long have we been
disconnected from the world?
72 hours.
Can I keep it off and stay
disconnected for another 72 hours?
No.
Hmph.
Feng Qinglang, you're an artist.
Don't forget how many
contracts you're bound by.
It's a pity you're not an actor.
The whole world is looking for me.
Sister Lan, Sister Jialin...
Even my mom.
Call Qingtian first
to see what's going on.
Okay.
If you don't show up soon,
everyone is going to call the police.
"Xu Changyang, the human trafficker."
Put Changyang on the phone.
Xu Changyang.
I can't believe I considered you a friend.
When did you start coveting my brother?
Was it before or after you turned legal?
Keep laughing.
You two will be crying soon enough.
Reply to whoever is
looking for you yourself.
[Unknown number calling]
I know it was my fault for not
telling you about the livestream linkup.
But I just wanted to surprise you.
What can I say?
Qinglang,
Are you listening?
I used my alt account, Ji
Zongjun, to interact with you.
He's gathering evidence.
He's really good at acting sincere.
So you were fooled by him back then?
I wouldn't call it being fooled.
Some moments were genuine.
I need to call Sister Lan back.
Feng Qinglang is finally back.
Sister Jialin.
Where is Sister Lan?
She went to look for you.
Where did she go to look for me?
President Xu gave Sister Lan
his brother's license plate number.
Sister Lan had someone track the location.
She has a general idea of where you are.
She and Brother Guo
are driving after you two.
I just tried calling Sister Lan,
but I couldn't get through.
I'll try calling Brother Guo.
I'll hang up now.
[The "can't connect" message]
There must be no signal.
Sister Lan.
You're back in reach.
Yes, I went off the grid.
As long as you're okay.
Where are you guys?
Send me your location.
Sister Lan.
Where are you now?
This is Xu Changyang.
Hello.
Hello, Sister Lan.
Don't worry, Qinglang is with me.
I'm familiar with the Molie area.
Are you still driving?
Yes, we're navigating to Xi Gui now.
It's not too far.
But the road is rough.
Don't drive tonight.
Find a place to stay for the night.
We'll head out first thing tomorrow
morning to meet up with you.
That works.
Lang Di, how could you elope without me?
And another thing,
hurry up and send me a
photo of that human trafficker.
The shippers are going to lose their minds.
Guo'er, find a place to stay nearby.
Sister,
Shi Yuhao just posted a savage Weibo.
[Yuhao just wailing away]
Call Jialin.
Tell him to release a statement
in the company's name,
announcing Qinglang's
withdrawal from the variety show.
Sister Lan released a statement.
Shi Yuhao's post is just to play
the victim and manipulate his fans.
Lately, people have started digging into
the financial backer behind Shi
Yuhao's variety show resources.
Some fans are linking Shi Yuhao's video
with Sister Lan's statement,
saying Sister Lan is heartless
and is cutting off Shi Yuhao's livelihood.
Sister Lan shouldn't have
released the statement at this time.
She's doing this to protect me.
She's drawing the fire to herself
to control the situation.
Everyone thinks Sister Lan
was the one who took the show,
and now she's the one pulling me out.
I feel like we're back to how
things were seven years ago.
Changyang...
Why are there so many people in this world
who talk nonsense
without knowing the truth?
Buddhism says reckless
speech creates bad karma,
and bad karma brings retribution.
Aren't they afraid of retribution?
They lack a sense of reverence.
Hello, Sister Jialin.
Guo,
where is Sister Lan?
She's driving.
Driving so late?
Why aren't you driving?
Oh, these winding mountain roads...
I don't dare to drive on them.
What's going on?
I found out a few things.
Jin Jin sent the recording
of her call with Shi Yuhao
to the variety show's investor.
If he wanted to bring Shi Yuhao down,
why didn't he send it directly to us?
He knew we wouldn't leak it.
It has no value to us.
You shouldn't have
drawn the fire to yourself.
Now that Shi Yuhao's dirt is out,
we should release the video we have too.
The behind-the-scenes footage you
saved on the cloud drive back then,
should be released if necessary.
If we push him too hard,
he might commit suicide.
When we were filming back then, he said
that because his friends
didn't understand him,
he almost committed suicide.
Poor kid.
Let him face his own karma.
Did your reshoots go smoothly today?
Did I tell you to post that?
Didn't you record the screen
because you wanted to post it?
But you didn't get my permission.
I'm your manager.
Does the company need your
permission to make decisions?
Now is the perfect time.
You called Qinglang,
and he didn't say a word.
And Xing Lan took the blame
for pulling out of the show.
Isn't this your chance to make a comeback?
To put it bluntly,
both you and Qinglang are
just puppets controlled by capital.
Playing the victim is the
only way to gain more fans.
Didn't I tell you
that before you post anything,
you must ask for my opinion?
Are you out of your mind?
Haven't you caused enough
trouble for the company?
The company is already being
merciful by not making you pay damages.
Drop this victim mentality.
The company has already booked
some commercial gigs for you.
Go home and rest for a couple of days,
and get ready to work.
I want to terminate my contract.
Do you have 15 million?
Back then, the company
forced me to split the CP fans.
If I hadn't split the fans so early,
I wouldn't have offended Sister Lan,
and my career wouldn't have stalled,
leaving me like this.
Shi Yuhao,
can you stop shifting the
blame to everyone else?
You had both a girlfriend and a boyfriend.
Why didn't you say so earlier?
Why didn't you tell us when
you couldn't hide it anymore?
If the company hadn't
helped you split the fans early,
you would have crashed even
harder when the scandal broke.
Did we make you offend Sister Lan?
When you were cursing and attacking people,
why didn't you take a look at yourself?
When things go bad, you blame the company.
But if things went well,
you'd run away even faster.
On that point alone,
you don't have a conscience
like Qinglang does.
He stayed by Sister Lan's side
through her toughest times.
If it were you,
you would have run away long ago.
The company knows you
have no sense of responsibility.
From now on, your affairs
will still be decided by the company.
Go home and cry a few more
times these next few days,
and post a couple more Weibo updates.
[Erxi Culture + Media LTD]
You were absolutely right.
He was indeed recording for evidence.
Since he couldn't beat me,
he targeted Sister Lan instead.
Brother Guo, have you guys settled in?
Not yet, Sister Lan is still driving.
Let me know when you arrive.
Brother Guo asked for my photo earlier.
I'll record a video for him.
What kind of video?
Hello, Sister Lan.
Aren't you recording this for Brother Guo?
My name is Xu Changyang.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I've watched all of your films.
Some critics say your films have regressed,
shifting from exposure to consolation,
losing their stance
just to evoke empathy.
But I don't see it that way.
Of course, my opinion
might be insignificant,
but no matter the form of expression,
it serves a purpose suited to its time.
A hundred years ago,
Lu Xun used his writing
to expose human nature.
That exposure was like a sharp scalpel,
cutting through the
rotting skin of the era.
But today, most people live in anxiety.
What this era needs more is
rebuilding after the exposure.
If we can only strip away the hypocrisy
but cannot help the
decayed wood regenerate,
the spirit of this world
will only perish faster.
I've watched your films,
and I can feel an enduring love in them,
one that is indestructible.
Although it's a kind of utopia,
and it's not entirely realistic,
it's like a lighthouse. With it,
at least we have the hope and determination
to reach the other shore.
Without it,
our lives would be even more of a waste.
After saying all this,
what I really want to say is...
your movies are the
reason I truly believe in love,
and believe that I can find and protect it.
How long did it take you to memorize that speech?
It just rolled off the tongue.
Jealous?
Send it to Sister Lan.
[Message from Qinglang + Shi Haoyu calling]
Sis,
It's Shi Yuhao, should I take it?
Yes.
(Qingtian: Don't let my brother
hear, find somewhere and call me back)
My delivery just arrived. I'll go grab it.
When did you order food?
I was worried you'd get hungry.
Is this a good time to talk?
Yes, I just stepped outside.
Sister Lan and Brother
Guo were in a car accident.
Can you bring my brother here safely?
I will.
[A series of heartfelt messages to Sister Lan
asking to let him handle his matters on his own]