DOCTOR ON THE EDGE
THIS IS A WORK OF FICTION
SOME SCENES WERE GENERATED USING AI
CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS
WERE FILMED SAFELY
Woo-hoo!
Let's go!
My, this is nice.
We beseech thee, mighty sea-spirit!
"We offer this ritual today
with all our devotion,
praying for safety and a bountiful catch!"
"We ask that you tame
the crashing waves and high winds,
and fill our nets to the brim
with many schools of fish!"
Is this your first time
seeing a sea ritual?
Oh, yes.
I haven't been to one
since I was little either.
It's just the way I remember it.
"May you also bestow your grace
upon us so that those who go out to sea
may all return to land safely!"
Please grant our wishes.
Please accept our humble offering!
- Was that a good thing?
- It's for good luck.
What's he doing now?
Every time they hold a sea ritual,
they store white rice in that pot.
It's a fortune-telling practice
for the coming year.
They say that if the rice
remains white without rotting,
that year will bring a bountiful catch
and safety for everyone.
Mmm.
:cue
So… how does it look? Huh?
Oh, come on. How is it?
A bountiful year it is!
All right!
- That's great.
- Yes, that's great.
Bless you all!
- Bless you!
- Give me a lot.
Give me a lot.
A lot.
Here's to a bountiful year of fish.
Jangsu, we're in for a year of plenty!
Gosh!
Here, bless you all.
Bless you!
- Oh, no!
Oh, no!
Wait. Please don't touch it.
- Oh, my!
-  Let me see.
The rice, the pot… How could this happen?
Goodness!
EPISODE 10
IT'S NOT OKAY.
Goodness…
I ruined the sea ritual
as the village chief.
What am I to do now?
It looked like just a pot to me.
That was no mere pot.
A year's worth of good fortune
for Pyeondongdo rested on that sacred pot.
I see…
Right. Weren't you moving
back into your house today, Ms. Hari?
Yes, today's the day.
My, I'm sure it couldn't have been easy,
what with the construction dragging on.
And you had your work cut out for you,
cleaning up the house every night.
We're done. Thank you for your patience.
-  Thank you.
- Have a safe trip back.
- Okay.
-  Goodbye.
Dr. Do.
:cue
Should we throw
a housewarming party today?
Mmm.
Whoa.
It's just the way I remember it.
How did you find the time to do this?
Hmm.
I brought you a housewarming gift.
Hmm? What is it?
It's fried chicken!
I pulled some strings with Mr. Park
since we're having a party.
- Here.
- Thank you.
I was actually going to eat with my hands.
It's good.
- Do you like it?
- Yes.
When I retire, I'm going to set up
my own fried chicken place,
so I can eat it every day.
Mmm.
But are you sure
they fixed these properly to last?
Why? Everything seems okay.
I'm just worried
they might have done a hack job.
I'm just a little bummed out
that you're no longer at the quarters.
What's there to be bummed out about?
This is even better.
What?
Well, the other doctors
are at the quarters, so…
What did you want to do if we were alone?
It's not like I wanted to do anything.
It was just inconvenient having to text
with a wall between us. That's all.
What do you want to do
now that there's no wall?
Stop teasing me.
If you want to do something,
feel free to do it.
There's no wall between us here
and we're all alone.
Oh, come on!
That's not what I mean.
You're getting a call.
Oh, it-it's probably a spam call.
- I've been getting a lot.
- Mmm.
I think you should get that.
Right.
- Hello?
-  Goodness, Dr. Do!
What took you so long to answer?
You have to hurry over
to the center right now!
Uh, okay.
:cue
PUBLIC HEALTH CENTER
Goodness,
it hurts so much.
What's the matter?
Here. Over here…
Let me take a look.
Goodness!
How about here?
So this spot is fine.
What about here?
No issues here either.
Oh! Oh, man!
Does it hurt when I press down
or when I let go?
I don't know.
- I'll try pressing again.
- Okay.
Oh, goodness! Goodness!
How long has it hurt?
For the past few days, I think.
The pain is killing
me, so please make it go away.
Pain upon removal of pressure
from the lower right abdomen,
a typical symptom of appendicitis.
My goodness, please help me.
You need to go
to a big hospital right now.
I'm not sure,
but I suspect you have appendicitis.
- What is that?
- Your appendix may have burst.
- I'll hail us a medical boat.
- Okay.
I'll give you a painkiller for now.
You can relax your hand.
The seas are too rough for a medical boat,
but a chopper is available,
so I requested it.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Hang in there, sir.
We're almost there.
They got here earlier than expected.
What a relief.
We're almost there.
Hang in there just a little longer.
An emergency dispatch
helicopter sent to transfer a patient
out of Pyeondongdo, Yeopoong-gun,
has crashed,
resulting in the death of the pilot,
Mr. Kim Hongcheol, who was 34 years old.
Fire authorities launched an investigation
and are going over the CCTV footage
to find out the cause of the incident.
Fire authorities believe the fatal crash
may have occurred
while the pilot attempted a risky landing
to save an emergency patient.
Meanwhile, the patient suspected
of having appendicitis
turned out to have nothing more
than an upset stomach,
adding to the tragedy.
It is a horrific incident caused by
a public health doctor's misdiagnosis.
In the wake of this tragedy,
concerns regarding the misdiagnoses
of incompetent public health doctors
are growing,
pushing Governor Ko of Yeopoong-gun,
to bow his head
and apologize on behalf
of the Pyeondong Health Center.
First of all,
I'd like to express my sincerest
condolences to Mr. Kim Hongcheol,
who lost his life
to an unfortunate accident,
and to the family of the deceased.
:cue
The thing is,
our investigation into the PH docs
has revealed quite a lot of issues.
Why are they blaming the PH docs
for a helicopter crash?
The way they tried to transfer
a patient without
a proper diagnosis, right?
They were in such a hurry to move him,
you know?
Such decisions led
to this tragic accident.
Maybe he should provide us
with better equipment then!
People always need someone to blame
when a major accident happens.
Is Dr. Do doing okay?
I noticed he even took a leave of absence.
I'm sorry.
He hasn't come out of his room
since the accident.
I'm so sorry.
Just turn it off.
Of course he's struggling.
The whole world just turned on him.
But he's not going to get through this
if he doesn't eat.
Dr. Do, it's me.
You should at least eat.
Dr. Do, it was just an accident.
It wasn't your fault.
But still…
If the pain gets unbearable,
come and lean on me.
I promised I'd stay
by your side, remember?
Okay?
Oh, my. Oh, my.
You have to try this right now.
"Ah, ah." Say "ah."
- I'm a little queasy.
- Why are you feeling queasy?
I think it's PMS.
I feel so bloated every time.
If it's giving you a hard time,
take some meds.
It won't get better
if you try to endure it.
Okay.
Why is everyone starving themselves, huh?
Eating some food makes everything better.
Dealing with sadness on an empty stomach
makes things worse.
I made this with local ingredients…
YOUR PERIOD IS 13 DAYS OVERDUE
-  Thirteen days overdue…
-  Why won't you have any?
An empty stomach
leads to sadness and illness.
Can't believe you're not having this.
:cue
- Granny, I'm here.
-  Oh, my.
Uh, what are you doing here
at this time? Huh?
Oh, we ran out of toilet paper
at the center.
Oh, really?
Uh, how's Dr. Do doing?
He seems to think it's all his fault.
He won't even come out of his room.
Goodness gracious me.
The whole world's
talking about him like that after all.
I feel so bad for him.
Even if he's shut his doors
and won't come outside,
you should linger outside his room often.
You have to keep pestering him so he knows
that he's got someone on his side.
It's the same with islands.
An island by itself is just
a deserted island where no one can live.
The islands need people
to keep hopping between them
and stay connected for them
to become habitable, eh.
Mmm.
Hmm?
Oh, why are you crying?
- Grandma.
- Why are you crying?
Oh, gosh, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
She tripped because of me,
and her doll got a little…
Don't cry.
I'll get you another one, okay?
I don't want another doll!
There's only one Tosun!
Then we just need to stitch her up.
Don't cry, okay? Stop crying.
Stop crying now.
If you're okay with it,
can I help you treat Tosun?
- Mmm.
-  Hmm?
I'm pretty sure I can do it.
Wow.
There, all done. Here.
Wow, she's as good as new.
Then you're going to
forgive me now, right?
Thanks.
LUCKY SUPERMARKET
Where could it be?
Are you a surgeon?
How could you tell?
I used to be an OR nurse.
Ah!
No wonder we clicked so well.
Wait.
Then are you a nurse
at the Pyeondong Health Center?
- I am.
-  That's great.
- Maybe you can help me.
- Mmm.
I'm here to meet Jiui
at the Pyeondong Health Center.
:cue
Dr. Do Jiui?
Mmm.
Who's that?
She said she's a friend of Dr. Do Jiui.
-  A friend.
- A friend.
A friend?
But do you think he'll come down for her?
He hasn't opened his door for days.
Oh. There he is.
Come outside with me.
Why are you here?
You look terrible.
I came running as soon as I saw the news.
I knew you would be like this.
Appendicitis is often tricky to diagnose.
The media has no idea
what they're talking about
pinning the blame on you.
Please just leave.
- Jiui--
- Why couldn't you console me back then?
After Seonu's death…
that's what I wanted
to hear from you most.
They don't seem to be on good terms,
so I wonder why she's here.
Especially at a time like this.
SUGWANG BAIT AND TACKLE SHOP
It's an emergency! Emergency!
- Let me check your temperature first.
- Okay.
Sir, you're just feeling
a little queasy, right?
Send the urgent patients to me first.
- Okay.
- Do you feel any pain,
or do you just feel nauseated?
- Let me take you to the exam room.
- I feel nauseated.
Goodness, I feel like I'm dying.
- What seems to be the problem?
- My insides are acting up like crazy.
Huh? Whoa. I think we need
to check this patient first.
- Use this to clean it up.
- Okay.
I'll take a look at him in my room.
Are you okay, sir?
- Come with me, sir.
- Okay.
Goodness, this is killing me.
- This way?
-  Yes.
What happened?
They came here on a group tour,
and they all shared some gimbap.
- Where is your discomfort?
- Right, well…
You're the doctor who was on TV.
I was kind of hoping to get examined
by a different doctor.
Uh, I've, uh, got an underlying condition,
so I'm just worried
that something terrible might happen
if I were to take the wrong meds.
- Sir, this doctor here is also--
- I-It's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
I'm an ER doctor.
:cue
If it's all right with you,
may I take a look?
Okay.
Sir, I'm going to take your pulse.
You're urinating less
or it's gotten darker, right?
Gosh…  …everything I drink
just passes right through me.
He's going to be dehydrated.
Prep an IV please.
- Okay.
- Let's get you on an IV first.
Okay.
Goodness gracious me, this is torture.
I'm Lee Hwayeong,
an ER doctor from Samjeong Hospital.
I'd like to offer my assistance
if you don't mind.
We should sort the patients
by their symptoms first.
Even if they got ill from the same food,
we can't give them the same prescription.
We'll be sorting the patients now.
People with uneasy stomachs,
people experiencing dehydration,
and those with stomach pain.
It hurts a bit there.
- But it's not a sharp pain, is it?
- No.
You said you had diarrhea.
Are you also running a fever?
Let me take a look at you, sir.
Could you lift up your shirt a little?
Please clench your fist for me.
Anyone here experiencing abdominal pain?
Anyone having diarrhea?
-  How does this feel?
- Do you have abdominal pain?
The nausea will go away soon,
but the diarrhea will last a few days.
- I'll prescribe you medicine for both.
- Okay.
Three times a day for five days.
Make sure you take all of them.
Your abdominal pain's mostly gone?
- Yes.
- Right.
So you're feeling nauseous,
and you have a migraine.
This should be fine.
But if your symptoms get worse,
be sure to visit a hospital.
- Drink lots of water, okay?
- Thank you.
Wow.
Oh, gosh, things could have really turned
ugly had it not been for you, doctor.
When those patients started flooding in,
I was in full-blown panic mode.
I don't know how to thank you.
Please don't mention it.
I'm just glad I could help.
I'm going to go upstairs now.
Can I get something to eat?
I haven't had anything to eat all day.
Let's eat. I'm starving.
I'm going to my room now.
Good work, everyone.
- Let's eat.
- Mmm.
Sounds good. Le-Let's eat.
Let's eat.
You haven't eaten all day.
Let's go outside.
Let's go eat at Cliffside.
Cliffside?
S-Sounds good.
:cue
Mmm!
The food here is delicious. Wow!
I'm glad you like it.
I was worried
it might not be to your liking,
since you're from the city and all.
By the way, how do you know Dr. Do…
Oh, I was just curious.
Since you came all this way,
you seem close,
but at the same time…
…you don't seem that close.
-  Stop it.
- Jiui and I…
used to date in university
for about five years.
- Huh?
-  Five years?
Oh, five years go by in a flash.
It's nothing, really.
I've never even dated someone
for five whole years.
Would you just…
She's right here.
Uh, oh, oh.
So you only dated for five years, huh?
I see.
That's when you're still young and naive.
Yeah, college kids are practically babies.
I felt like I had to come here
when I saw Jiui on the news.
I know Jiui better than anyone else.
-  Let's see now.
-  Au-Auntie, what is that?
Oh, I was going to ask you
to get these to Dr. Do Jiui.
You know what they say about how
an aching heart feeds off hunger.
In times like this,
we should just keep feeding him.
-  Give it to me.
- Uh-huh.
I'll get it to--
You should give it to him, Ms. Yuk.
What?
You're the one
Dr. Do needs most right now.
Right.
Oh, you're right.
Ms. Hari should go.
It's not like we'd be of any use to him
in this situation, right?
- You should hurry or it'll get cold.
-  Go make sure he eats it.
- I-I'll be going then.
-  Right.
Get it to him before it gets cold, okay?
- Thanks, Auntie.
- Here you go.
Thank you for your help today.
Yes, of course. Mmm.
Mmm. There she goes.
Ms. Yuk.
Huh?
If you really are
the person Jiui needs most right now,
please convince him to leave this island.
What?
I've looked into it,
and there's a way for PH docs
to be transferred.
- Jiui can get out of this--
- What do you mean by that?
Why should he have to leave?
He did nothing wrong.
I didn't mean that he did something wrong.
I'm sure you've seen it for yourself.
Jiui's really struggling.
Living here must have been hell for Jiui.
It must have reminded him of Seonu,
and he must have blamed himself.
Seonu?
Oh.
Then I guess you have no idea
why an island would be hell for Jiui.
- Jiui--
- I think…
I'd rather hear it directly from him.
I'll be going now.
Then I guess you have no idea
why an island would be hell for Jiui.
:cue
I guess Ms. Hari had to
just leave it here.
I get it, though.
I have no idea
how we should console him either,
since he's shut the door on us like this.
Dr. Do Jiui.
Dr. Do Jiui!
What is it?
You should eat.
I'll eat later.
Eat right now.
Everyone's worried about you.
DON'T SKIP YOUR MEALS, DR. DO
Hurry up and dig in.
It's seasoned perfectly today.
I'm sorry to put you all through this.
Please don't beat yourself up
too much over it, Dr. Do.
You were only trying to save a patient.
Anyone would have made the same call.
Do you really…
think so?
These days…
I'm so scared of being a doctor.
I'm so clueless about everything…
and I still have so much to learn,
so the fact that so many lives…
depend on the decisions I make…
really scares me.
Did you both dream of becoming doctors
right from the start?
To be honest, I only became a doctor
because everyone said I should.
Because they said studying hard
and becoming a doctor was the dream.
So I studied like my life depended on it,
and one day, before I knew it…
people called me "doctor."
I suddenly had to start treating patients.
Man, I was so nervous my hands
were shaking like crazy, you know?
I'm sure it's…
the same for everyone here.
You too, Dr. Hyeon?
It didn't seem like it.
I get scared every time.
Sometimes, I just want to hide.
:cue
WINTER FLU VACCINATION
- Can I have your name?
- It's Kim Malsun.
Ms. Kim Malsun,
are you feeling unwell today?
Not really.
I see.
- Let me check your temperature for you.
- Okay.
PYEONDONGDO FLU VACCINATION
-  Are you allergic to anything?
-  Oh, no.
Have you ever experienced side effects…
You're a real trooper.
My, that does sting.
Don't rub it.
Just keep applying pressure, please.
Goodness, you're all working so hard.
Have some of this while you work.
- Thank you, Mr. Park.
- Thank you.
We've had an amazing turnout
from the residents today.
It must be because you did
such a great job promoting this.
Well, actually, it's not because
I promoted it well or anything.
They're just scared they might die.
- What?
- Everyone's…
Anxious.
That falling ill on an island
could really mean certain death.
A helicopter crashed here,
and over yonder on Jangmokdo,
a granny passed away
from a heart attack
because she couldn't get to a hospital.
But they have a health center
and a helipad there.
Some good that helipad did.
The chopper couldn't even land
and had to leave.
They didn't even put
the finishing touches on those helipads
despite all that crap
they pulled to get them made.
It's been one accident after another.
Goodness gracious me.
Wait.
It's fine, I'll get it.
Using shoes as an excuse…
You've reached the Public Health Center.
Ms. Hwang.
Yes, Ms. Hari.
Would it be okay
if I went home from here today?
Is something going on?
I just need to look into something.
I see. Are you also going to Jangmokdo?
Huh?
How did you know that?
Well, Dr. Hyeon also said
he was going there to look into something.
- I guess you can tag along.
- Ah.
Okay, be safe.
Okay, Ms. Hwang.
Mmm. Right then.
Gosh, these are so dry.
Got to eat them faster.
SCHEDULE FOR THE SECOND
HALF-YEAR TRAINING SESSION
Dr. Yong, looks like you'll
have to attend this over the weekend.
You'll be transferred to
a different post soon after that,
so I guess this'll be
your last training session already.
Time sure flies.
This is a good thing, I guess.
You always felt so cooped up here.
Ms. Eom, do you want to
attend it together?
It's during the weekend anyway,
so a date on the mainland
might be a nice change of pace.
There's also this really fancy restaurant
I want to take you to.
Let's carve up some steaks and whatnot.
What do you say?
I guess I shouldn't look like a slob
since we're going to a fancy restaurant.
Since we're going out for steak,
I guess I might as well splurge a little.
How much… This is insane.
How can they charge so much
for a piece of cloth?
People must be swimming
in money or something.
Are they out of their…
What is it even made of?
Damn it.
DON'T SKIP YOUR MEALS, DR. DO
Jiui, can you spare me a moment?
I'll be waiting outside
until you come out.
:cue
JANGMOKDO DOCK
JANGMOKDO, PYEONDONGDO
- Hello.
-  Oh my, hello.
- You're from the Pyeondong Health Center?
- Yes.
I've been waiting for you.
I'm Lee Seongu from
the Jangmok Health Center.
- Hello.
- Thank you for your cooperation.
Not at all. The helipad's this way.
- Right this way.
- Right.
Mind your step.
I heard the chopper couldn't land.
Right.
They rushed the construction so much
that they didn't have a lighting setup,
and the helipad was so disorganized
that the chopper couldn't land.
Was the Pyeondongdo incident
also caused by lighting issues?
We're not sure yet.
They're still investigating.
We all know why.
My buddy's stationed at Gayeongdo,
and things are a mess
due to lighting issues there too.
I heard those bastards told them
to only transfer the patients by boat.
What the hell can we do on an island
when they block off the air routes?
Lighting…
Would you mind giving us
that doctor's contact information?
Sorry?
On the day of the accident…
I don't think I saw any lights
at the helipad either.
Yes, hello.
I'm Yuk Hari,
a nurse at the Pyeondong Health Center.
I'm looking into lighting issues
at helipads in Yeopoong-gun.
Hello. I'm Hyeon Chiyeon,
a PH doc at Pyeondong.
I heard they built
a new helipad there recently.
I heard the last time
you had an emergency patient,
you transferred them by boat
rather than a chopper.
Is everything working properly?
Was there a reason you did that?
Oh, yes. Uh-huh.
- Lighting issues at the helipads?
-  I understand.
Thank you.
So the Yujae Health Center
has stopped using medical helicopters?
If the lighting isn't finished yet,
that would impede landings and takeoffs.
- Have they wrapped up construction there?
- I see.
They suspended it?
So you're not using the helipad at all?
Uh. I understand. Okay.
Oh, my.
You two catch up.
I'm going to go to the supermarket.
Thanks for coming.
I knew you'd keep waiting
until I came out.
But I'm not here to hear you out.
I'm here to tell you about me.
I tried so hard to get past what you said
about how we didn't deserve to be happy.
Though it felt unfair to Seonu.
But…
I just couldn't do it.
I think you were right.
We don't deserve to be happy.
So I don't need your consolation now,
after all this time.
I won't leave you by yourself this time.
I looked into it.
PH docs can also get transferred
to a different station
if they have a valid reason.
If we were to get Gangseok to explain
your condition to the county office,
you can get transferred.
Come with me, Jiui.
Will leaving this place…
help me forget Seonu?
:cue
Why didn't we think of that
in the first place?
It was pitch black out there
because they hadn't set up the lighting,
and they let Dr. Do take the fall for it
to hide their shoddy construction work.
I'm going to bring this up
and make them take full responsibility.
- Don't do it.
- What?
I'll do it.
I'm a PH doc who's only here for a year.
But no good will come of you
making an enemy of Yeopoong-gun.
The chief told me that you might be
staying on this island for a long time.
Oh.
Please let me do it.
Since it's a PH doc matter,
let a PH doc handle it.
What are you waiting for?
Hurry up and go tell him.
Dr. Do!
Ms. Yuk.
The helicopter crash…
It was caused by Yeopoong-gun's
reckless helipad construction projects.
I looked into it all day today,
and apparently,
out of the 20 new helipads they built,
only three had functioning lights.
The lighting issue was also the reason
none of the CCTVs caught what happened.
So what I mean to say is…
The accident wasn't your fault, Dr. Do.
You need to know that.
That it wasn't your fault.
It wasn't your fault, Dr. Do.
Is that why you…
kept visiting all those islands?
You did it for me?
So please stop hiding.
I can't be by your side
if you keep hiding like that.
I'll stop hiding now.
:cue
Ta-da.
Ms. Eom.
Is it too much?
Yes, it is too much.
It's too much because you look so pretty!
Ah!
Here are some flowers I brought for you.
Thank you.
I don't know if I put on weight
or something,
but doesn't it look a bit tight on me?
Tight? Not at all.
You look so pretty.
You look like an angel.
Come on.
Our ferry will be leaving soon. Let's go.
- Come on.
- Let's go.
Dr. Do!
Hey, what are you doing here on a weekend?
I brought this so we can have it together.
I was really craving pasta
when I woke up this morning,
but I made too much
since I'm used to making two servings.
Dig in.
This used to be my grandma's favorite.
Thanks for this.
- Delicious, isn't it?
- Mm-hmm.
That's right, Dr. Chiyeon said
he filed a request at the county office
and demanded corrections from the outlets
that published those articles.
- Ah.
- They'll publish correction articles soon.
This isn't over yet.
I'll keep an eye on them
till the very end.
We have to make sure everyone
gives a proper apology.
This is good enough for me.
Eat up. The noodles will get mushy.
:cue
Excuse me.
How can they charge so much for one meal?
Would you mind if I ordered for us?
I've actually read up
on their best dishes in advance.
Sure.
We'd like the A course
with a medium tenderloin
and some caviar on the side, please.
Okay.
Would you like some wine?
How much is…
Do you have Château de Lune d'Or?
Yes, we do.
We'd like that,
and the jamón charcuterie board as well.
What grade is the jamón?
It's 100% Ibérico de Bellota.
Sounds great. That'll be all.
Yes, sir. Right away.
You're so pretty today.
I get it, so please stop saying that.
But you really do look super pretty today.
Thank you.
Enjoy your meal.
At these prices,
you'd expect a bigger portion.
Try this.
Didn't we order the same dish?
You're right.
But it tastes better
when we feed it to each other like this.
You're so cheesy.
Being cheesy's what dating's all about.
Here, say "ah."
Ah.
How do you like it?
Delicious, isn't it?
- You can order more if you'd like.
- Mmm.
Seriously?
What's wrong?
The others got to enjoy getting stranded
due to terrible weather.
It's so unfair that we should get
such clear skies during our visit.
Of all the things to complain about.
Dr. Yong, would you mind
waiting here for a short while?
What for?
Maybe it's because of the tight clothes,
but I've been feeling stuffy all day.
So I'm just going to grab
some antacids at a pharmacy.
Mmm. Let me bring you one.
I'm not a baby, okay?
Hold this for me. I'll be right back.
- Don't take too long.
- Okay.
I'd like some antacids, please.
Okay.
- That'll be 4,100 won.
- Okay.
Here you go.
The ship bound for
Pyeondongdo, Pyeondongdo is now departing.
What's taking her so long?
We'll miss the last ferry at this rate.
I guess that might be even better.
Uh.
I'm late.
Oh, man…
Dr. Yong!
Ms. Eom!
Why weren't you picking up?
I'm sorry. I had to go to the bathroom.
Okay. Let's hurry.
:cue
Are you all right?
I'm sorry.
I'm sure my sudden leave must have
put a lot of strain on everyone.
Come on, things like this
happen out of the blue all the time.
Don't let it get to you.
By the way, shouldn't those articles
have come out by now?
You're sure you told the county office,
the Ministry of Health and Welfare,
and the reporters, right?
Yes.
Then why haven't we heard
a peep from them?
I mean, they were all up in arms when
they were trying to ruin someone's life,
but they sure don't seem
very interested in the truth.
So frustrating.
When are they going to come out anyway?
PYEONDONGDO HELICOPTER PH DOC
- It's out!
-  Where?
"Health Center PH doc at Pyeondong
where helicopter crash occurred
revealed to have been
taking psychiatric medication"?
"It has recently come to light
that the PH doc stationed
at Pyeondong Health Center,
the recent site
of a fatal helicopter crash,
had a history of receiving
psychiatric treatment and medication."
"This has raised concerns
that the misdiagnosis
may have been caused
by a lapse in judgment
due to the medication he is taking."
"In response, Choi Hyangmi,
the director of public health,
has stated that she will be putting
the PH doc taking psychiatric medication
on standby and consider removing him
from his post."
What the hell?
So they've resorted to spreading fake news
just to shirk the blame now?
What the heck are they talking about?
What's this about a PH doc on medication?
It's all true.
Let me look into this.
No, Dr. Hyeon.
- But still, we should at least--
- Just don't!
I'm okay.
Oh, gosh…
How could something like this…
Those meds can cause
side effects like memory loss, dizziness,
and hallucinations…
It is a horrific incident caused
by a public health doctor's misdiagnosis.
:cue
Appendicitis is often tricky to diagnose.
If we explain your condition
to the county office…
How dare you come here!
How dare you!
Dr. Do.
Dr. Do, are you okay?
Don't worry about a thing.
I'm going to prove that those meds
had nothing to do with
your diagnosis, okay?
I can't take this anymore.
I'm so scared of being on an island.
I CAN'T BE BY YOUR SIDE
IF YOU KEEP HIDING LIKE THAT
PICK THE CUTIE PIE HERE
CUTIE PIE? WERE YOU LOOKING FOR ME?
IN ONE TAKE WITH NO BLOOPERS?
DOCTOR ON THE EDGE
Do you really think leaving the island
will help him recover?
Jiui. You might actually
have to step down as a doctor for good.
It just sounds a bit selfish.
The only way to treat unbearable pain
is to run away from it.
You must have struggled so much here,
surrounded on all sides by the ocean.
Surrounded or not, I wanted to
hang in there because I had you, Ms. Yuk.
Looks like we just keep having to
apologize to each other.
That's why Jiui wants to leave.
It's because he wants to live.
Translated by Yoon Hyuk Park