The person I like...
is the person standing
right in front of me.
Huh?
What's with that look on your face?
Isn't that a line from the
movie we just watched?
I'm not joking.
I'm asking you seriously.
I'm not.
I'm being completely serious, too.
The person right in front of me.
Huh?
But I'm the only one here.
No, I mean...
Isn't this exactly like
the movie we just saw?
I really do like you.
What?
What I mean is...
The person I like is you,
Wataru, standing right here.
Me?
I know the timing seems convenient,
but I've been planning to tell you anyway.
Then, what about before...
They got rejected because the other
person said he liked someone else.
Apparently, everyone who confessed
got rejected for that exact reason.
I know this must be a shock,
but there's someone...
I've had a crush on for a long time.
And that person is...
Wataru?
Hey, Wataru.
Oh, sorry.
I don't really know what to say...
Uh, do you like guys?
Oh, that's not what I meant...
How should I put this?
I can date girls normally,
but the one I fell for is you, Wataru.
Why me?
I wonder why.
Maybe it was just meant to be.
I see. So that's how it is.
Thank you.
Huh? For what?
Thank you for not being disgusted or
laughing, and for listening to me seriously.
The fact that I like you...
Hearing you say it to my face like that...
Anyway,
let's head back.
Huh?
Let's go home.
It might sound weird coming from me,
but are you sure you're okay with this?
It's fine.
You don't have to worry about it, Wataru.
I'm not asking you to like me back.
Just knowing how I feel
is enough for me.
What is that supposed to mean?
But in return, there's one favor
I'd like to ask. Would that be okay?
Sure.
Even though his confession was so casual,
his expression at that moment
was more sincere than ever.
I agreed before I even had time to think.
"My Summer Of You"
(Episode 2)
Morning.
What's with you?
I'm just so happy.
Come on, cut it out.
You're going to make me feel weird too.
Sorry, just ignore me.
No way.
By the way, about what I asked yesterday,
are you really okay with it?
Of course.
I keep my word.
That's so like you.
Man, I wish summer break
would hurry up and get here.
But we have exams before summer break.
Sekiguchi senpai, please help me out.
- Please!
- Let me think about it...
It'll cost you two
convenience store popsicles.
Thanks!
- Just as I thought.
- Thanks!
But Wataru, instead of asking me,
why don't you ask Saeki to tutor you?
Wouldn't that be better?
But he seems pretty busy lately.
And aren't you being a bit prickly?
He's definitely still sore about Saeki
beating him on the midterms.
Oh, Saeki is busy, huh?
But that guy barely even
studies for exams, right?
He said, "Just listening
in class is enough."
Wataru, stop rubbing it in.
Sigh.
Is there really absolutely nothing
I can beat him at?
That guy definitely
has a girlfriend, right?
For sure.
And she's definitely super cute.
A total babe.
If it weren't for me... with
his looks and everything,
he could easily date anyone he wanted.
Man, I'm so jealous.
Just give up.
That's the social hierarchy for you.
Is that really how the hierarchy works?
Yep.
Give it up.
I'm off to change the future of Japan.
How did we get onto that?
But falling in love
isn't really about that, is it?
Man, this is tough.
Hey, we haven't even started studying yet.
Guchi, you'll never
understand this in your lifetime.
Oh yeah?
Then let me teach you a lesson.
You want a piece of this?
Oh, they're finally going at it.
Go, go, go!
Alright, open your book.
No.
- Open it.
- No way.
We need to study.
I'm not studying.
A pilgrimage means visiting
the filming locations, right?
Yeah.
Summer break is coming up,
so I wanted to go then.
Is this what you wanted to ask me?
Yeah.
I really want to go with you.
What do you think?
Sounds great.
It'll make for a wonderful summer memory.
I'll leave it at that for now, Wataru.
- I'll text you later.
- Okay.
- Bye.
- See ya. Good luck with club practice.
Ah, I'm so excited for summer break.
Totally. I couldn't agree more.
Toda, are you going
anywhere for summer break?
Well, mostly working my part-time job.
Oh, how responsible.
Where are you working?
At my uncle's diner.
Oh...
You don't care at all, do you?
- Not really.
- Don't just say it out loud!
Wataru.
Oh, are you heading home?
Yeah.
Our plans for the day after
tomorrow are still good, right?
Yeah. What about you, Saeki?
I'm good to go.
Let's meet in front of
the ticket gate at 8:00 AM.
Okay.
- Don't oversleep.
- I won't.
- Actually, I might be too nervous to sleep.
- Huh?
See you then.
Yeah.
What's this? What's this?
What?
What on earth could possibly keep
the great Saeki-kun awake at night?
What's that supposed to mean?
We're just going on a film pilgrimage.
A pilgrimage?
Like for an anime or a movie?
Yeah, we both like the same movie.
I see. That makes sense.
Oh, make sure to take some pictures!
Huh?
Not of you, but of Saeki-kun!
Well, have fun on your pilgrimage!
Let's go home.
The greenery is getting so lush.
Oh, look, there are
mountains over there too.
Yeah.
Coming out here
really feels like a mini getaway.
Right?
I'm starting to get really excited.
This is great.
But the itinerary you
made is absolutely perfect.
And the movie "Sea of Light"
feels very much like your style.
- Really?
- Yeah.
It's Director Zaizen's masterpiece.
I figured you'd like it too.
Yeah, but it has a real indie vibe.
Though I doubt many people
go on pilgrimages for that movie anymore.
But to me,
it's a very important film.
Oh?
It really resonated with me.
I felt like a part of me was saved by it.
I see.
Wow, this is the place.
It looks exactly like it did in the movie.
Of course it does.
This is where they filmed it.
Even though it's an unstaffed station now,
I heard they still use it for
commercials sometimes.
I thought there'd be other tourists,
but we have the whole place to ourselves.
Yeah, it's like our own private station.
Oh, let me take a picture.
Oh, me too.
- Oh, nice.
- Looks great.
Wow, that looks beautiful.
Wataru.
Hmm?
Ah, hey!
Got a great shot.
Honestly...
Hey.
Want to try acting out that scene?
The scene where the protagonist gets out of prison
and someone talks to him for the first time.
Sure.
Where did you come from?
Wait a second.
That was spot on!
Don't just laugh.
Answer me.
I can't. Hold on.
My stomach hurts from laughing.
What's so funny anyway?
Hold on. It's just that you
sounded way too much like him.
That was hilarious.
His journey to find the parents who
abandoned him started right here, didn't it?
Let's go check out the
outside of the station too.
Okay.
The air is so fresh.
It really is.
This view really purifies the soul.
Is your soul really that dirty?
No, that's not it.
I'm just putting myself
in the protagonist's shoes.
I know.
Since we're here,
should we take some videos?
Oh, sure.
Then should I try
walking with some dramatic flair?
Yeah.
And... action!
What are you laughing at?
What's with that serious face?
I told you, I was trying to
walk with some dramatic flair.
Wait, try walking again.
And... action!
Nice expression.
Oh.
Did it turn out well?
Did you try to be funny at the very end?
Here you go.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Thank you.
Oh, thank you.
Let's eat!
Mmm, let's try the broth first.
Delicious.
What is this?
Mmm!
This is amazing!
These noodles are so chewy.
Saeki, don't just film.
Eat up.
It's really good.
Yeah.
So good.
This broth is incredible.
Mmm, delicious.
- It's good, right?
- Yeah.
This is seriously amazing.
- It was totally worth the trip.
- Definitely.
The seaweed is delicious too.
The bamboo shoots are great too.
Incredible.
These must all be local specialties.
I feel alive again.
Really.
Yours looks delicious too.
It is.
Let me have a bite.
Yum.
Do you want a bite of mine too?
- How is it?
- Delicious.
Good, right?
You've got to have
an icy treat in the summer.
Yeah.
Ow, brain freeze!
Are you okay?
No, this is a bit... I'm fine.
This is nice.
So relaxing.
Yeah.
Ah, this feels great.
Wow, what a view.
Wow, it's beautiful.
It really is.
Wow, the water is so clear.
Wow, amazing.
It's absolutely gorgeous.
Right?
Hey, want to go down there?
Huh?
Why not? Let's go play in the water.
- This feels great.
- How dare you splash me!
- Stop it!
- You're splashing pretty hard.
Stop!
Hey, you're dead meat!
Hey, I'm really going to fall!
You'll be fine.
Hey, okay!
I get it.
Okay, okay, let's take a break.
Alright, alright.
- Let's take a break.
The water is freezing.
Hey.
- Seriously...
- Let's skip stones.
Huh?
- Skipping stones.
- Skipping stones?
Have you never skipped stones before?
No.
This might actually be my first time
playing by a river.
Seriously?
Didn't you do this when you were a kid?
No, almost never.
I always stayed indoors during holidays.
I see. I was the exact opposite.
I was always playing outside.
Isn't there Higashimura Park?
I used to go there all the time.
Saeki?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I'm just really happy right now.
I'm glad.
But honestly, I'm the one who's
getting a bit too carried away.
- Woah!
- Watch out!
Sorry. Thanks for saving me.
Wataru, don't be so tense.
It's making me nervous too.
Don't ask for the impossible.
I can stand on my own now.
Thanks.
Saeki?
Um...
Can we stay like this
for just a little longer?
I didn't see anything
about there being rain.
- Hurry up, Saeki.
- Okay.
Damn, we got pretty soaked.
It probably wouldn't have been much different
if we had actually fallen into the river.
Don't say that.
And after you just saved me, too.
It's just a sudden afternoon shower.
I'm really looking forward to
the ocean view in the final scene.
Finally reaching the truth.
That's an iconic scene.
Yeah, it is.
I'm looking forward to it too.
It really feels like summer.
I really love summer.
Summer is special to me too.
Special?
Because it's the season I met you, Wataru.
You...
Don't say embarrassing things like that.
By the way, was it summer
when we met at the record store?
Yeah, it was summer then too.
I just wanted to say it.
You don't have to
take it seriously, Wataru.
How could I not take it seriously?
You might be used to
this kind of thing, Saeki,
but with zero dating experience,
I have no immunity.
Don't make me say it out loud.
It's depressing.
But Wataru, you're the first
person I've ever confessed to.
Seriously?
Yeah.
Because before, I was always
the one being confessed to.
Oh, bragging now, are we?
But you're amazing.
I wouldn't have the courage
to confess so casually.
For me, it wasn't so much courage
as it was determination.
I see.
I know it must be confusing
to suddenly have a friend confess to you.
If it makes things awkward for you,
there's nothing I can do.
I don't think that way at all.
Huh?
I don't think it's awkward.
Though it was definitely
one of the biggest shocks of my life.
But regardless of whether
you're a guy or a girl,
to be liked by someone like you, Saeki...
It makes me feel like
I'm not so bad after all.
Don't worry.
If I didn't like it,
I would've just said so.
It's been a while since I heard that.
Huh? Really?
Yeah.
The reason I don't mind it
must be because it's him.
Wataru.
Yeah?
I like you.
I know already.
At the time, I still pretended
not to notice that feeling.
(Next Episode)
Anyone would be annoyed seeing the person they
like getting all cozy with someone else, right?
I just thought you looked
cute when you were sulking.
I want you to follow your heart.
With someone expressing their
feelings so passionately, even I...