Hello.
Is that Mo Yungao?
All your men are dead.
Who are you?
Agent Zhang Haixia
of the Southern Archives.
You killed all my men?
A member of the Zhang family
really didn't disappoint me.
Thank you for telling me that.
I have a
very private question I want to ask you.
Go ahead.
Do you, like me,
have an intense desire
to revel in other people's suffering
at certain moments?
I have.
And if that desire never goes away,
what would you do?
Go along with it.
So from the beginning,
you also had a conscience.
When did that conscience
start to disappear?
Where will people like us
end up in the future?
You have too many questions.
I don't want to answer.
But I can tell you one thing—
your destination.
Your destination and mine
are definitely not the same.
If you want to know your destination,
you'd better come find me.
But my condition is
that you must become my friend.
The choice is yours.
Just like that,
Mo Yungao's Twilight Grass plan
was completely destroyed
with the assistance
of Zhang Haiqi, Zhang Hailou,
Zhang Haixia, and Zhang Qishan.
Tens of thousands of people in four cities
were saved from the fire.
Mo Yungao's warlord forces
were also quickly dismantled
in this incident.
His reputation disappeared
without a trace in a very short time.
[Archives: The Nanyang Mystery]
[Episode 22]
[Xiacheng]
Tell my fortune.
I remember you.
You still owe me a silver dollar.
I once asked you a question.
I had a thought in my mind—
should I kill it,
or will it kill me?
You told me to go with the flow
and act on what I truly wanted.
So later,
what did you choose?
I don't want this.
I'm not this kind of person.
[Fortune-teller] [Face reading]
I shouldn't have survived.
I should be dead.
You
are Mo Yungao.
What did you say?
Is it that hard to understand?
Zhang Haixia used Twilight Grass
to wipe out all Mo faction warlords.
[Investigation Report]
No one was left alive.
Thanks to the fact that Great Master Buddha's
men are all from the Zhang family
and have special physical constitutions,
they survived.
Otherwise,
they would all be dead this time.
Our goal this time
is to wipe out Mo's faction.
But Zhang Haixia
was almost out of control
during this operation.
I need to interrogate him.
But Zhang Haixia
is missing.
Great Master Buddha asked us for him.
You took him away
without telling us before.
Now he's missing,
and you ask us for him?
I should be asking you for him!
Zhang Hailou,
as for Zhang Haixia,
I'll give Great Master Buddha
an explanation.
But he's from the Archives, after all.
How he should be
dealt with is my business.
All right.
Then I will wait for your news.
However,
if my men find him first,
then don't blame me for showing no mercy.
[Changxiang Rice Noodles]
Take a look at the oil-paper umbrellas.
They are sturdy and durable.
Two bowls of noodles, extra spicy.
The Great Master Buddha
invited me this time.
Put this meal on his tab.
Here.
Here are your noodles.
Enjoy your meals.
What are you looking at? Get to work.
Mentor,
do you really believe
what Zhang Qishan said?
Shrimpie massacred the Mo faction warlords
and almost harmed the Zhang family.
You said you felt Zhang Haixia
had changed.
For all we know, this might
be his fault.
Is it because of that medicine?
Does that medicine
have such major side effects?
Let's find Zhang Haixia
and bring him back first.
But you also need to prepare
for the worst.
Prepare for the worst?
What do you mean?
You have a white hair strand.
Where?
I'm over a hundred years old, after all.
More than a hundred.
You can live for a thousand years.
Do you think I'm a monster?
Let's eat first.
Is it ready?
It's ready.
Extra spicy.
Please.
Mentor.
What's wrong with her?
Well...
I'm asking you, how is she?
Was she poisoned?
She was exposed to poison before.
Well...
It doesn't seem like she was poisoned.
Why are you hesitating?
I'm asking you, what's wrong with her?
Your sister's pulse is very strange.
She looks young,
but her pulse is like a 70-year-old's.
What else?
Nothing else.
But a pulse like that in a young person
is extremely strange.
Then why won't she wake up?
She's probably too tired.
She should be fine
after resting for a few days.
She's obviously unconscious now,
and you're telling me she's fine?
Are you kidding me?
Wait, I...
Get out!
Okay.
[Report]
Great Master Buddha,
[Zhang family
corpse-cultivated grass toxin]
[Concentration: three times
that of a normal sample]
Mo Yungao's bases
have all been breached.
All Twilight Grass
has also been destroyed.
Mo Yungao has already tried it in Nanyang?
Yes.
Mo Yungao released it in Nanyang,
and now he wants to release it nationwide.
I'm afraid
he wants to cause greater turmoil.
If he's really coming for that person,
he probably won't give up easily.
He will likely regroup
and cause even bigger trouble.
Keeping this Mo Yungao alive
is a disaster.
Unfortunately, my hands
are tied right now.
Zhang Haiqi and the others
are on their own.
Report!
Speak.
Great Master Buddha,
someone claiming to be your poor relative
is asking to see you
about a matter of life and death.
[Silence]
We found the cause.
[Report]
Here's the information
we found from Mo Yungao.
Zhang Haiqi was poisoned
by a special alkaloid.
While cultivating Twilight Grass,
he accidentally discovered
that its flowers were far more toxic.
So he ground them for use.
The yield of this flower is very low,
and it is extremely hard to cultivate.
But its potency is extremely strong.
It can be used against
high-level members of the Zhang family.
He only ground a small bottle of
poison powder,
and used it all on Zhang Haiqi.
Regarding the mechanism
that destroys the body,
well,
how bad will this situation
get?
Her whole body is aging rapidly now.
Within three months,
she will die of organ failure.
Aren't the Zhang family members
supposed to have special physiques?
Is there no special treatment?
The Zhang family's origins
have always been a mystery.
Even the Zhang family members
themselves don't know much about it.
If we want things to turn around now,
there's only one possibility.
We have to find their patriarch.
The patriarch of the Zhang family?
The head of the Zhang family.
Where is he?
The Zhang family patriarch
has been missing for a long time.
He was last seen in Bailejing.
Bailejing.
Bailejing covers a vast area
with hundreds of thousands of mountains.
The actions of the Zhang family patriarch
have always been mysterious
and unpredictable.
Even the Zhang family members
might not be able to find him.
Okay.
This is the report
on the Twilight Grass spread incident.
[Case File]
If she wakes up,
show it to her.
This matter
can be considered to have come to an end.
Mentor.
You're awake.
Yeah.
How long have I been out?
Three days.
How do you feel?
I'll go get a doctor.
Pour me some water.
I'm thirsty.
Okay.
Do you want to sit up first?
Zhang Qishan came
while you were unconscious.
He said
it was Mo Yungao
who poisoned you on the train.
He also left a document
for you to read when you wake up.
Drink some water first.
Careful, it's hot.
Mm.
I have a general idea.
I was still a bit conscious
during the coma,
hearing you talk intermittently.
This poison in me cannot be cured.
Who said that?
He said the only way to cure it
is to go to Bailejing
and find the Zhang family patriarch.
You're awake now.
-Let's go to Bailejing tomorrow.
-Is there any news about Zhang Haixia?
Zhang Haixia
probably planned his escape route
very early on,
and did anti-reconnaissance,
clearing all the traces he left behind.
Zhang Qishan couldn't find him either.
Now that he's gone,
what are you planning to do?
What am I planning to do?
I'll just bring him back
and talk to him.
If he has really lost his mind,
I'll fix him.
Although I know you won't listen,
I advise you not to look for him.
If something is really wrong
with Zhang Haixia,
or he even turns evil,
then you will have to face the situation
of whether to kill him
with your own hands.
I don't think you can do it.
So if you go after him,
it won't end well for you.
Is your brain fried from the fever?
Why don't you listen to
what you're saying?
I was just making an analogy.
You always lose your cool
when it comes to him.
I'm not like that now.
Shrimpie must have his reasons
for doing this.
If he really became like this
because of that drug,
then I have even more reason to cure him—
because I'm the one
who caused this to happen to him.
That's not guilt talking.
That's just your obsession.
Enough. That's not what's
important right now.
Right now, the most important thing is
to help you find the medicine.
Then we'll head to Bailejing
and bring Shrimpie back.
-Shrimpie...
-Then there's even less reason to.
I'm not going to Bailejing.
Why not?
This time,
I will die.
You...
Why are you like this?
Mentor,
can you not be like Zhang Haixia,
so immature and disobedient?
It makes me so tired.
I know what's happening to my body.
Endless youth isn't something
I can enjoy forever.
I've lived for over a hundred years—
my life has been long and full enough.
These days, death isn't
something I fear.
If anything, it feels peaceful,
and even welcome.
Yes,
you are quite open-minded.
You're basically an old lady
who has already lived a whole lifetime.
I'm different from you.
I'm still young.
Don't worry about it.
I'll go find the medicine for you.
Then I'll bring Zhang Haixia back.
That's your business.
We're bound to part sooner or later.
It's just happening
a little sooner than expected.
At least give it a try.
Just try it.
Do it for me.
Can't you live for me?
How dare you say that to me?
Then for Zhang Haixia.
Don't you care about him the most?
Do you want to just watch him
lose the will to go on?
Is growing taller the only thing
you've accomplished these years?
I'm tired. Get out.
Get out.
Remember to read the documents.
I'll go buy you some rice noodles.
Extra spicy.
Two bowls of rice noodles.
Pack one up. Extra spicy.
[Changxiang Rice Noodles]
Why is this troublemaker back again?
Hurry up and make him a bowl of noodles.
Let him eat and leave quickly.
This guy has been here twice.
Once he offended the officials
and completely smashed up my stall.
Another time,
someone almost died here.
This time,
who knows what trouble he'll cause.
Sir,
you really like eating rice noodles.
The girl who was with you last time—
I saw her pass out.
Is she okay now?
If she were dying, could you save her?
Noodles are ready.
Here you go, sir.
Extra spicy.
Water, water, water. Out of water.
Okay.
Too spicy?
Didn't you say we don't have
chili peppers in Changxiang?
Did I say your noodles are spicy?
No, no, no.
What's going on?
I'm gonna smash your sign to pieces!
I'll go get water.
What?
You want to smash our Changxiang sign?
Great Master Buddha is here.
Here's the water.
A bowl of noodles.
Okay.
The first time I came to Changxiang,
I ate the noodles made by this owner,
and decided to stay.
Enjoy your meal, Great Master Buddha.
Since I left the North,
I haven't had any contact
with the Zhang family.
You're the first distant relative
I've seen in all these years.
It does bring back memories.
Three relatives...
Soon, there'll only be one left.
My mentor is gravely ill
and dying.
She's given up
and is just waiting for the end.
That brother of mine went crazy.
I don't even know where he is now.
I still have to help you find someone,
and treat my mentor's illness.
But what if?
I mean, what if...
What if my brother
has truly lost his mind?
What am I supposed to do?
When dealing with someone who's gone mad,
the best way to calm them down
is not to treat them like they're mad.
Make him feel
that nothing has changed.
If they've done terrible things,
pretend you don't know about them.
Why?
Because right now,
if he thinks
he can still be with you like before,
the good in him
still has a reason to survive.
But if you've already started to hate him,
or if he comes to believe that
the good in him
has no hope left,
then that goodness
will disappear completely.
He will become an evil spirit from hell.
So,
you must act as if nothing
has happened.
You don't need to persuade me.
I won't go to Bailejing.
I am Qi Tiezui from the Nine Clans.
I'm talking about you.
Miss,
that little kid of yours
is at Great Master Buddha's residence.
He has been making a fuss for days.
Great Master Buddha specifically asked me
to come have a word with you.
No need.
Just a chat.
You have nothing to lose.
You are older.
You've learned to take things in stride.
But the young ones
might not think things through.
Besides,
I took six wen from you.
I can't just take it for nothing.
How about this?
Let's play
a little folk game today, shall we?
How old are you?
You're never too old for a game.
Besides,
those kids of yours
practically burned my place down.
Just consider it comforting me,
making me happy.
Please cooperate.
Alright.
South. Seven across, eight down.
All right.
An old blossom blooms anew.
Dead branches welcome spring once more.
Old grudges fade,
and old loves drift away with the tide.
A withered branch falls from the tree,
It falls under the tree, rolls three times,
lands at its roots, and rolls three times.
Gain and loss, both at their peak.
What it means is this:
the best and worst moments
in a person's life
reach their peaks at the same time.
You chose "South"
right off the bat.
You must have a wonderful encounter
in the south.
What if I don't want to go to the south?
Things change.
If one day you suddenly don't want to die,
it's best to be on the path of
saving yourself.
Do you people of the Nine Clans
always like to meddle in others' business?
I had a piece of fruit
at the Great Master Buddha's
residence once.
It was delicious.
I hear it comes from Xiacheng.
If you're still alive,
you might as well send me some.
Never mind saving myself.
Gain and loss, both at their peak?
Commander,
Beilian's base has also been occupied
by Zhang Qishan.
He is still sending troops
to search for us.
We
are defeated.
Defeated?
Yes
Are we really defeated?
We really are.
Excellent.
[Academy]
Old gentleman,
people say you're a man who knows all things—
the past and the present,
the hearts of men,
even the workings of fate.
And that you've never been wrong.
It took me quite a bit of effort
to track you down.
So I'd like to ask you something.
Right here,
and right now—
are you
going to
die or
live?
Die.
[Academy]
You figured it out.
I've decided not to kill you.
Your reputation as an immortal is ruined.
It's just an empty title.
Destined friend,
may I ask,
are you here for something else?
You've got something.
I do have
a big plan to execute,
but it's a bit complicated
and tricky.
So read my fortune.
When
and how can I achieve great success?
Wait until
three of your generals meet their end
and you suffer one crushing defeat;
then your grand design
will finally succeed.
Three generals lost and one defeat.
That means
I will lose three great generals
and suffer one defeat
before I achieve great success.
Is that what you mean?
He's really dead.
He really is an immortal.
Sir.
He's got something.
You are his students.
Why aren't you crying?
Cry out loud!
Sir!
This place is quite something.
Wait until three of your generals
meet their end
and you suffer one crushing defeat;
then your grand design will finally succeed.
I've already lost two lieutenants
and suffered this defeat.
If I lose one more lieutenant,
my grand scheme will be complete.
Commander.
Are you
willing to be my last lieutenant?
Me?
Am I qualified?
Yes, you are.
Thank you for the promotion,
Commander. I am willing.
You're quite agreeable.
Thank you, Commander.
You're thanking me?
Commander,
with the snake medicine,
it seems your wounds are almost healed.
This guy has some tricks.
[Snake Patriarch, Mo Yungao
Recruits Men of Talent]
He also used snakes to scout and report,
so we knew Zhang Qishan was coming.
We managed to evacuate
from the base in time.
He's just acting a bit weird.
Whatever I ask him,
he won't say a word.
Should I...
Why would he tell you?
Who do you think you are?
I spoke out of turn.
Is  Zhang Haiqi
dead?
No.
I have never seen this before.
Usually, after members of the Zhang family
are poisoned,
they immediately become paralyzed.
They would die within three days.
After Zhang Haiqi was poisoned,
not only did she not die,
but she also planned a long trip.
So she is just like that person,
a different member of the Zhang family.
But the Twilight Grass flower
must be effective.
Her condition is not good.
Ever since I knew you were Zhang Haiqi,
I opened it.
Under your sofa,
there is another bottle
with a stronger effect.
Alright.
However,
she won't live much longer anyway.
Poisoned by the Twilight Grass flower,
she will definitely die.
Report!
Commander,
Mr. Zhang has been brought here.
What about the other group?
Commander,
they have returned too.
I'm glad you're alright.
Our planting base
and seedlings
were all destroyed.
It was done by the Zhang family.
Commander,
although the Twilight Grass plan
failed this time
and re-cultivating the Twilight Grass
will take a lot of time and money,
I am confident.
These funds,
which I have already laundered,
can be used to continue
planting Twilight Grass.
The current situation is chaotic anyway,
so they won't find out.
Also,
do you remember?
We built another base back then,
though it has been abandoned for years.
It's right in Bailejing.
Do you know that
embezzling those public funds
could get me killed a hundred times over?
If this grass this time
still can't lure Zhang Qiling out,
don't you think
we should just die together?
Bailejing.
The first time I fought that guy
was at Bailejing.
Everything for me started there.
Now we are going back to Bailejing.
This is a very, very auspicious sign.
I will definitely find you this time.