The special train will pass through
the tunnel where we're lying in wait
at 12:30.
Stay focused—
we'll only have 20 seconds
to board the train.
Got it.
[Mo Yungao's Special Train
from Guangchuan to Nanling]
What are you looking at?
Nothing. Just rest.
After this trip,
let's go get a drink.
Sure.
[Archives: The Nanyang Mystery]
[Episode 21]
[Mo Yungao, Leader
of the Mo Faction Warlord of Beilian]
You do enjoy
bringing me useless people
to keep me entertained, don't you?
You need to be patient.
Are you telling me what to do now?
Do I look even a little impatient to you?
What was that about?
Commander, didn't you just
do this?
I really
was just trying to flick my hair.
I... I'm sorry, Commander!
Alright, alright.
Clean this up immediately.
Bai Yu.
Have you captured Zhang Haiqi yet?
Do you have any idea how much
manpower and resources I spent
trying to avenge you?
If you really want to repay my kindness,
bring me a few more useful members
of the Zhang family.
That would be worth far more
than anything else.
Understood.
Report!
Come in. Just come in.
Stop knocking already.
Commander, when we passed through
the tunnel just now,
someone tried to force her way
onto the train.
But she's highly skilled—
she actually managed to
evade a barrage of gunfire
and suffered only minor injuries.
Our men have captured her.
Who would have the nerve to barge onto
my special train?
We don't know her exact identity yet,
but while we were apprehending her,
we also received a telegram
from Zhang Qishan.
It only said one thing—
that she's the person
you've been longing for, Commander.
A
woman surnamed Zhang.
Here's the telegram.
[Telegram Draft]
This woman came to my residence
seeking a partnership.
She wanted evidence of your corruption
and abuse of power in Beilian.
Out of consideration
for our years as colleagues,
I had no wish to involve myself
in this matter.
Furthermore, this woman bears
a Qilin tattoo on her body
that only appears when her blood runs hot.
I've heard that you've long searched for
such a person without success,
so I deliberately revealed
your whereabouts to her
and leave her in your hands
to deal with as you see fit.
Commander,
what do you think?
Zhang Qishan?
He may act friendly towards me
on the surface,
but he's stabbed me in the back
so many times.
This is just his way of
clearing himself of suspicion—
worried I might think
he's one of the Zhang family.
Bring in that woman you caught.
I want to see her for myself.
Yes, Commander!
What kind of life
am I living all day long?
I was wondering
why you looked so familiar.
[File Name: Investigation Report on
the Southern Archives & the Zhang Family]
You're the Director of
the Southern Archives,
[Report]
Zhang Haiqi.
The supreme god,
there is none who can compare to you.
We are mired in filth and insignificance,
yet you still bestowed your favor upon me.
I've spent half my life
searching for your kind.
Do you know how many people
from the Archives I've captured?
I found they were very different
from ordinary people.
It was only after poring over countless
ancient texts
that I finally understood
that you belong to
an ancient clan bearing the surname Zhang.
Within your clan,
there's a legend:
every so often,
a prodigy of the age is born—
one whose existence
threatens the safety of your entire clan.
Having seen you today,
it seems the legend is true.
I'm deeply ashamed.
There is no prodigy of this age.
The fact that you pose a threat
to the Zhang family
is the Zhang family's own problem.
Let's move on to the next question:
why did Zhang Qishan bring you
onto my train?
What are you two up to?
As for what Zhang Qishan is up to,
you should ask him.
Scratching each other's backs—
I suppose there's some kind of deal
between you two.
Indeed.
As expected of you.
[Telegram Draft]
Send this
to Zhang Qishan.
Yes, Commander.
If your goal has always been
to capture members of the Zhang family,
then you've already caught
me, a member of the Zhang family.
So can you call off the release
of the Twilight Grass?
Actually, I'm not interested in
capturing all of you Zhangs.
There's only one specific person
from the Zhang family
that I'm after.
However,
since you're a member of the Zhang family,
you must know
where that person is.
And you must
have his file, too.
It might even be sitting in your hands
right now.
I've already destroyed the Archives.
If you want to find his file,
go dig for it yourself.
However,
I'm afraid you won't live until then.
That's impossible.
He'll definitely show himself eventually.
As
more and more of
you Zhangs disappear,
he'll realize
that he's the one I'm after.
And when he does, he'll come to me
of his own accord.
I have great respect for your people.
That's why I won't let
any part of you go to waste—
not a single one of you,
nor a single item
belonging to you.
Zhang Haiqi.
Do you think it's possible
that this bodyguard...
It's his first time serving as
my bodyguard.
You were responsible
for distracting me,
while he
put on another face
and infiltrated my train as a bodyguard.
As we speak, he's probably
looking for proof of my plans.
Once we're on the train,
I'll deal with Mo Yungao,
and you go find evidence of
his poisoning scheme.
If there's any Twilight Grass
on the train,
destroy it all.
We cannot allow even a single stalk
to enter Nanling.
Darn it.
Zhang Haitong?
Zhang Haiqing?
Zhang Haijiang?
Zhang Haimu.
Zhang Hairong.
Zhang Haiping.
Zhang Haicai.
They're all members of the Zhang family.
What are you doing?
This is not mine.
You remember that assassin
named Bai Zhu, right?
I...
I-I'm on my way to send a telegram.
I want you.
What?
Well, the Commander is still waiting.
How about we do it in a bit?
I want it now.
No, no, no,
this is inappropriate.
I-It hurts!
Ouch!
I want your hand first.
[Zhang Haiqing] [Zhang Haijiang]
Ouch! It hurts!
It really hurts!
What the hell did you grow up eating
to be so strong?
People like you.
Liquor?
You make medicinal liquor
with the Zhang family members?
It must be a great tonic, huh?
Trust
is the greatest trap.
Whatever you place your trust in
is exactly what will lead to
your downfall.
Miss,
look,
didn't we hook up before?
On the Nan'an?
I remember now.
You are...
Bai Zhu, right?
You... You...
What did you say?
One night together means something!
We may be enemies,
but I did let you leave that ship.
You can't just turn your back on me
like that, right?
Bullshit!
Zhang Haiqi killed my sister.
I'm going to kill you all.
W-What are you talking about,
Bai Zhu?
I'm not Bai Zhu!
Then who are you?
Bai Yu!
Is everything okay?
Yeah, everything's okay.
I just knocked some things over,
and I'm cleaning it up.
Lift your head.
Are you guys...
Okay?
How could we not be?
Go
and send this telegram to Zhang Qishan.
Where's my sister?
You said she got off the ship.
You're just locking the two of us up
in here like this?
You do realize I could kill you right now,
don't you?
You're so beautiful,
yet your heart is so vicious.
At least let me finish
this glass of wine first.
The master of these snakes
is right next door,
using his own way
to manipulate them and protect me.
This is all Chen Xifeng's doing.
Bailejing really is a remarkable place.
I've got quite a few talented
and extraordinary people
working under me now as well.
So you've known all along.
This kind of snake
is known as the Fidelity Snake.
It can tell friend from foe
and expose impostors.
So in front of me, disguises are useless.
Now then,
we'll wait for my men
to bring back that friend of yours—
the one posing as a bodyguard
with that fake face of his.
Then we'll talk about what happens next.
Of course, you could always
throw something at me right now
and punch a hole through my throat,
just as that Salty Zhang once did.
You should be faster than a snake.
But bear with me for a bit.
Beneath your sofa,
I've placed one of my latest creations.
It's a special powder ground from
the blossoms of the Twilight Grass.
I call it Yellow Jasmine.
Do you have any idea how difficult it was
to make the Twilight Grass bloom,
and how many human lives it took
to feed them?
This poison
is much stronger than
anything I've made before.
And you happen to be the perfect
test subject.
There's a neutralizing serum
mixed into my daily coffee.
You, on the other hand,
aren't so fortunate.
Well? You can't even lift
your arms right now, can you?
Sorry to disappoint,
but I'm of the Hai branch
of the Zhang family.
We have very subtle breath.
We can take one breath
and stay underwater for a long time.
That's our special ability.
And we don't need to gasp for air
the way ordinary people do.
Now talk.
What exactly is your scheme?
Where exactly are you planning to
release the Twilight Grass?
You are making it feel...
A bit too good.
Speak, or you will die.
You're the person
who looks the most like him
out of anyone I've ever seen!
And you're darn good-looking!
Makes me hate the thought of killing you!
Watch where you're shooting!
So...
You're the older sister, Bai Yu?
Don't you want to know
where your sister got off the ship?
What do you want?
I want to know
the locations of all your deployment
in every city.
If the Twilight Grass Poison
breaks out in the city,
I assure you
that your sister will definitely
die from poisoning in the city.
She misses you very much.
She also wants to reunite with you.
Don't you
want that too?
You want to stop the release of
the Twilight Grass?
Yes.
We've stationed suicide squads
in cities all across the region.
The Commander will notify them
by telegram.
Once they receive the order,
they'll start spreading
the Twilight Grass.
Then,
what if they don't receive the telegram?
Then the plan will be activated
at noon next Monday.
I lead the team in Nanling.
However,
it won't be next Monday at noon anymore.
Why?
Because you just
gave the telegram
for releasing the Twilight Grass
to the telegraph office.
What? I...
That telegram from earlier
was the coded order
to be sent to every deployment site.
If the Commander gave it to you,
then he intended for you to personally
send out the order
and set the Twilight Grass plan in motion.
Now, what about my sister?
Where is she?
Your sister
is on Kaiyuan Road,
Xiacheng, and...
[Nanling Station]
[Guangchuan to Nanling]
How's it going?
Mo Yungao has sent out a coded order
for all stations to start preparing
the Twilight Grass.
The train is arriving at
Nanling Station soon.
Our key task this time is
to deal with the Twilight Grass.
It seems
that coded telegram just now
wasn't meant for Zhang Qishan after all.
We must get the exact
poisoning locations
to Zhang Qishan immediately.
We must prevent the release at all costs.
I'll go send the telegram.
I'll go deal with the Twilight Grass.
Get off immediately after it's done.
Hold them off for 3 minutes.
Got it.
[Exit]
[Guangchuan to Nanling]
[Nanling Station]
[Report]
[Confidential Report on
the Twilight Grass Cultivation Experiment]
Once the Twilight Grass seeds
enter a human body,
[Report]
they reproduce and grow inside it,
eventually sprouting into new plants.
This kind of grass thrives in
dark, damp environments.
If exposed to intense heat and dryness,
it withers and dies easily.
That's why Mo Yungao has been
killing people all this time—
to use their corpses
to cultivate the Twilight Grass.
[Zhang Haisheng]
Scum.
[Zhang Haihan]
He even used the bodies
of Zhang family members
as fertilizer for the Twilight Grass.
[Zhang Haiju]
[Zhang Ming]
So much Twilight Grass.
There's no time left.
Fellow members of the Zhang family,
let me send you on your way.
I told you to take care of the grass,
not to blow up the train.
When are you ever going to
stop giving me heart attacks?
Don't worry.
This is the outskirts.
No innocent people will be hurt.
Take a look at this report.
This is the best way
to destroy the toxic weed.
Notice to all personnel in every city:
the deployment times and locations
transmitted in the previous telegram
are hereby null and void.
This new order
supersedes all prior instructions.
The revised deployment schedule,
locations, and methods
are as follows...
[Suburban River Channel, Changxiang]
Telegram from the Commander.
Orders from the Commander!
The deployment locations and schedule
have been revised.
Adjust the operation at once!
Yes!
Come on. Hurry up.
Get in! Get in!
Come on!
[Guangchuan]
Hurry up!
We are running out of time!
Hurry up! Hurry up!
[Suburban Highland Slope, Changxiang]
Get off!
How could this be?
We've changed the locations and schedule.
How did you know?
[One hour ago]
[All]
[All action]
[All action units]
Great Master Buddha.
These are revisions to
[Military Division]
the Twilight Grass operation
[The original deployment directive,
Order No. Hai-3, is hereby revoked immediately.]
and personnel movements
transmitted over
Mo Yungao's military channel.
Zhang Haiqi has taken action.
Compile this into a military report
and notify Nanling and all other locations
to hunt down Mo Yungao.
Put that down!
Stop there!
Freeze!
Left, right, left!
[Twilight Grass Cultivation Area,
Mo Yungao's Base, Xiaojiang]
Left, right, left!
[Zhang Haixia's Location]
Left, right, left, right!
Left, right, left!
There are enemies
lying in wait on the back hill!
Officer Li.
The Seed Division would like you
to come over
and review the progress of
seed germination.
Reporting, sir.
Enemy troops have been spotted
near the base.
This is the coded telegram
we just intercepted.
We're working on deciphering it.
Based on frequency analysis
and contextual inference,
we've essentially worked out
their encryption scheme.
These are the key terms
we've managed to decipher.
Officer Li,
please take a look.
Tell me,
why do some members of the Zhang family
[Li Pinrui, Researcher of
the Twilight Grass Project]
have antibodies against
the Twilight Grass?
Why do you think that is?
I think...
I think there's an emergency.
We just intercepted a coded telegram.
[Great Master Buddha Reinforcements]
Great Master Buddha.
Reinforcements.
Tell me.
If we use Zhang Qishan
to plant the Twilight Grass,
what would happen?
Report!
The enemy is jamming us.
All communication systems are down.
What did the coded telegram
we intercepted earlier say?
[Telegram]
This was the last one we picked up
before communications were lost.
We haven't had time to decipher it yet.
Sir,
they've switched to
a new encryption method.
It's a neighboring-letter cipher.
[Telegram]
Everyone, start testing
possible keys immediately!
The first group of words is the key.
The actual military report doesn't begin
until the second group.
Before encryption, this letter "S"
would have been either "R" or "T"—
which one it is
depends on the context.
But if that's the case,
wouldn't the 22 encrypted English segments
yield an enormous number
of possible combinations?
To be exact,
there are
4,194,304 possibilities.
Someone!
There are 3 battalions moving in on us.
Send a team to check.
Yes.
[No Trespassing]
Squad One.
Hurry!
Head to the east of the base immediately
and check if
there are 3 battalions approaching.
The rest of you,
defend the base fortress to the death.
There must not be
the slightest lapse in vigilance!
Hurry! Hurry!
Our outer defense system
has been dismantled by them.
There are also enemy footprints
and tire tracks.
Go back immediately
and report to Officer Li.
Reporting, sir.
Ten kilometers east of the base,
someone has dismantled
the explosives guarding the base.
We found enemy footprints
and tire tracks there as well.
Judging by the trail, they appear to
have moved toward the rear of the base.
Sir, what should we do next?
The base is under attack!
Zhang Qishan's troops are here.
Move my seeds out of here immediately!
Yes.
Everyone, assemble!
Prepare for battle!
Report!
We found an enemy.
Bring him here!
We can't bring him here.
You'll have to go there yourself.
Is Zhang Qishan here?
It doesn't matter.
Because you're all about to die.
It seems
Zhang Qishan didn't come.
Are you also from the Zhang family?
Tell all your men to come out
and surrender your weapons.
I'll ask the Commander
to spare your lives
and give you the honor of
becoming my test subjects!
Ready your weapons!