The operating system is nearly complete.
We are currently at 90%.
As for the remaining 10%,
we’ve programmed A382 to learn what it
means to be human by studying its owner.
But the only thing we're missing is...
A suitable face?
Yes, sir.
What do you think?
What the hell?
Ouch!
Oh shit.
Two more hours, P’ Ploy.
I'll send it over as soon as the render is done.
I know. You already told me.
Huh? Then why are you calling me?
It’s two in the morning.
I’ve been pulling all-nighters for
three days straight now. Three days!
There’s an urgent job.
An urgent job?
- No, I’m not listening.
- Listen.
- No! I’m losing my mind right now.
- Stop and listen to me.
The client needs it urgently by tomorrow morning.
What?! I can’t do that.
It’s impossible. No! Way!
Don't throw a tantrum just yet.
- But—
- Listen!
I know you’ve been pulling
all-nighters for three nights,
barely showering, and
basically living on protein bars.
But this is that regular
client who pays really well.
The same one who lets you
cash out your advances early
until you’ve paid off your house.
They said they need this urgently.
Don't argue with me.
And I know you have one finished
piece you're refusing to send.
You know I can't send that one.
Why not? It’s 100% your work.
- It’s not perfect yet.
- Then it’s time to make it perfect.
Your muse.
Before dawn. Got it?
I used to think I had a strange job.
I tell everyone I’m a graphic designer,
but in reality…
my job is to create... faces of people
who don't actually exist in this world.
But
I never care what anyone does with
my illustrations, as long as I get paid...
even if it’s the face from my dreams.
Am I dreaming?
Is it really done?
Forget it.
It’s sent.
It belongs to the client now.
No use regretting it.
Better take a shower.
Have you seen this yet?
Why didn't you knock?
So you’ve seen it.
What a waste of time.
Now we have to redesign A382's face.
This time, I want a professional.
Even if the face resembles a real person,
it's still better than using amateurs.
We’re using this face.
Are you sure about this?
But I have one condition.
What are you so attached to, Gen?
The person from your dreams is just
a fancy phrase that can't pay the bills.
Yes! I’m coming! Just a moment!
Are you Khun Jarinda?
- Yes.
- Could you sign for this, please?
Alright, haul it inside.
- I— I didn’t order it.
- Please sign here too.
- Here?
- Yes.
- Hey! Hold on!
- Right here, please.
- Wait! This is trespassing!
- Have you signed yet? Right here.
- Wait! Hold on!
- Here too.
Oh, okay.
Right here as well.
Ugh!
Are you sure you didn't send this?
It really wasn't me.
You know I’m in Hong Kong with P’ Le.
How would I have time to
buy something and ship it?
Did you buy something yourself?
When would I have had time?
I’ve been working all month.
Forget shopping apps, I didn't
even have time to scroll through my phone.
Are you sure this isn’t you
and P’ Le pulling a prank on me?
Well, the box is huge, Rann.
It’s literally human-sized!
If it’s not you two, then I have
no idea who would send me this.
It really wasn’t us.
But if you’re curious, just open it.
What on earth...
What’s going on?
This face...
Greetings. I am Robot Model A382.
My duty is to ensure user satisfaction.
Please assign me a name and state your requests.
This makes no sense.
Send your people to take this back immediately!
I didn't order it.
Some lunatic sent it to me, and it's a—
I don't care!
Send your people right now!
What do you mean you can't?
You just have to pick it up
and return it to whoever sent it.
What?!
The company has a no-return policy?
This is absolutely ridiculous!
I’m going to file a complaint
against your company!
Hello?
Hello?!
Hey! Did you seriously just hang up on me?
Are you dissatisfied with me, Master?
I told you to stay over there! Back off!
I said don't come near me! Back off!
Like this?
More.
Keep going.
All the way to the back!
Are you satisfied now, Master?
No.
Are you angry with me, Master?
Because you—
Did I do something wrong?
Whatever.
Don’t you ever leave that spot.
Understood, Master.
Good.
But I’m not your "Master."
Are you... really a robot?
Would you like me to prove it, Master?
Hey! What the hell are you doing?!
Are you insane?!
- I’m proving it.
- Proving what?!
You’re trying to commit suicide in my house—
Huh?
Do you believe me now?
Shit, what do I do?
Call the delivery company.
Or a mental asylum?
- Would you like me to help you?
- No, no, no, no! No!
Stay out of it. Don’t help.
Don’t do anything at all!
I’m going crazy!
According to company policy, we truly
cannot accept returns for this item, ma'am.
You're the tenth person to tell me that.
We truly apologize for this.
If you feel sorry,
then come and take it back!
We are truly sorry.
Are you ready to assign me a name, Master?
Where exactly are you from?
That information is company confidential.
Then why did the company send you?
- Why my house?
- That information is company confidential.
Then why me?!
That information is company confidential.
Hey!
If it’s so confidential,
then why are you even here?
Go back to your company!
I can't send you back,
but you have legs, don't you?
Since you won't tell me
anything, go back on your own!
You should know where
that stupid factory is, right?
I cannot do that.
You can't do this, you can't do that!
I have to satisfy you first.
What are you talking about?!
I am a robot designed to
ensure user satisfaction.
If Master is not satisfied,
I cannot return.
- Please assign a name.
- Satisfied! I’m satisfied!
Based on the scan,
your pupils are dilated and
your heart rate has elevated.
This indicates a reaction as you prepare
to handle what it perceives as a threat.
In conclusion, you are not exhibiting
metrics of happiness or satisfaction.
Rather, your body is
responding to natural mechanisms
controlled by the autonomic nervous system
- ...and hormo—
- Stop!
Stop it.
Who gave you permission to read
my pupils or my heartbeat? Stop it!
I have stopped.
- Please assign a name.
- Ugh! I'm not naming you!
I’m not doing anything!
Do you want me to stand here all night, Master?
I'm… not that cruel.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Is it not working?
What?
Statistically, humans tend to prefer cute beings.
So I act… cute.
Your heart should soften, Master.
Gosh, don't read my mind! Stop it!
I don’t care if you sit, sleep, or whatever—
just don’t step into my bedroom.
And remember,
I’m not letting you stay here.
I’m going to find a way to send you back.
- Master?
- What now?!
Good night.
Yes.
Of course.
No problem at all.
Sis, I sent it over.
One sec. I’m on a call.
Yes, absolutely.
I guarantee you the designer
will keep completely quiet about it.
Trust me, we’ve worked together many times.
I assure you this fabric pattern
will be exclusively yours, Khun Nin.
Okay.
P’ Ploy.
What’s gotten into you?
I want a list of clients who bought my work.
Who did you sell it to?
We already agreed that—
Work goes out, money comes in.
No questions about the client's identity.
I know. I know it perfectly well.
Did you forget how many years
I’ve been working for you?
Well. If you know that,
then why are you asking?
I need to return something to them.
What is it?
It’s—
I just do, okay?
Why are you even asking?
Hey, beautiful.
What got you so worked up?
Come on, tell me about it.
Get your hand off me.
No can do.
So are you going to tell me or not, P’ Ploy?
No. We already talked about this.
You know I take on all kinds of art commissions.
The money is great, but the sole condition
is that we remain completely anonymous.
The client purchases
the work with full copyright.
Every face you’ve been paid for
is no longer yours to take back.
Even if I’m just a commission agent,
I have my own ethics to uphold.
Got it?
So who exactly made
my pretty little sis this furious?
Good morning, Master.
Please assign me a name.
P’ Petch, could I have
the return address, please?
If I give it to you, she’ll kill me.
P’ Ploy, please help me.
I’m in real trouble here.
I can’t give it to you.
P’ Ploy!
No.
P’ Ploy...
Alright, fine. How about this?
If the client contacts us,
I’ll ask if they’ll accept the return.
Don’t smile. Don’t wai.
I haven’t agreed yet.
Then contact them right now, P' Ploy.
Our policy is not to contact clients.
If they don’t reach out first,
there’s nothing I can do.
Here.
Something sweet for the stress.
How unusual.
Requesting purchase authorization.
Here’s Auntie Kai's mouthwatering,
tongue-tingling chicken pad kaphrao!
Wow! The way you described it
kinda killed my appetite.
Too bad.
You're paying for it anyway.
I haven't even taken a bite.
Why do I have to pay?
'Cause I already made it.
Whether you eat it or not is your problem.
I made it, so you pay for it.
Come on, Auntie!
If you eat it, you gotta pay.
Khun Gen! You're here!
Wait, wait, wait!
What's the rush?
- What is it, Auntie?
- Where are you going? Hold on!
Why are you trying to run away?
Just look at your face.
No answers, no comments.
I don’t know anything.
I haven't asked yet!
But you're going to, aren't you?
You know how many years I’ve lived around here.
How could I not know where
all the nonsense rumors start?
So, no answers, no comments.
I don't know anything.
I’ve gone bonkers.
Just one question.
No.
What did you order the other day?
Word is it was a human-sized box.
I didn't start this, but people are
saying you ordered a coffin to your house!
Gen, that’s bad luck!
If you really ordered it,
get it out of the house immediately!
But why would you order a coffin anyway?
You live alone.
Or am I out of the loop?
- Or did you accidentally kill someone?
- Auntie!
What is it? Tell me!
If you’re not going to sell me food,
I’ll buy from another shop.
Gen. Of course I'm selling!
Why would you go anywhere else?
I make the absolute best pad kaphrao
in this entire neighborhood.
Gen! Don’t be like this!
Why so impatient?
Don’t act like a hot-headed teenager!
How about chicken pad
kaphrao with a fried egg?
Make it two.
- Are you on your period?
- Auntie.
If you ask me one more question,
I’m walking straight out to another shop.
And if a rumor goes around that Gen is
on her period and eating like a monster,
I’ll never come to your place ever again.
Pay when you’re done eating!
- Honey.
- Yes, babe?
We have to finish the series today.
- Oh, last episode was such a cliffhanger.
- Last night—
Wait, are you starting to go gray?
- What?! Really?!
- Yeah.
- Look.
- Eek! I’m getting old!
- But it’s okay, you’re still adorable.
- Really?
Really? Really? Do I have a lot?
Wow, look at Mr. and
Mrs. Madly-in-Love over here.
Getting all lovey-dovey
first thing in the morning.
Morning, my ass.
It's almost evening already, Ai Josh.
I told you to stop gaming overnight.
You don't feel it now, but
you’ll regret it when you're older.
P’ Zoon, tell your wife I’m not your kid.
What time I sleep is my business.
She’s only warning you because she cares.
Just listen to her, Josh.
- Right, P’ Zoon?
- Of course, baby.
Hey, P’ Gen’s back.
Escaped the boss only to
run straight into her henchmen.
Nong Gen! Where have you been?
Did you order a lot of stuff?
I saw the delivery guys coming nonstop.
Ow!
What’s wrong? Where does it hurt?
- P' Zoon, call an ambulance!
- It hurts so bad.
- What do we do? Is it your appendix?
- Where's my phone? Call the doctor!
- What’s wrong, Nong Gen?
- Ugh!
I need to poop. Right now.
- It’s coming!
- Hey! Gen!
Gotta go. Gotta go. Gotta go!
Hey! She’s gone. So fast.
Should I just move?
Can robots even eat?
Whatever, I already bought it.
Come what may.
Master.
I bought some food—
Are you satisfied, Master?
I’m definitely daydreaming.
Auntie Kai must’ve put
something weird in the food. No.
Gen, you’re just sleep-deprived.
Go to bed.
Yes, yes, go to bed now.
That face... that outfit...
This is insane.
Don't look at me like that.
I’m not having any dirty thoughts.
I don't want to see at all.
Who would have such thoughts
about their own muse?
Ugh, I’m going crazy!
I need to sleep.
Yes, I need to sleep.
Go to sleep, Gen.
Are you ready, Captain?
Thanks...
Coffee or me?
Do you prefer rabbits or cats, Master?
Meow.
THAT IS ENOUGH!!!!
I'm very satisfied! Extremely satisfied!
I’ve never been this satisfied in my entire life!
You are lying, Master.
I’m not lying. Don’t accuse me.
And where on earth did you
get these ridiculous outfits from?!
I ordered them online.
Would you like me to specify
the application, Master?
But from the content I have studied,
company names are often avoided.
Would you like me to state the name
directly or indirectly, Master?
Whether I name it directly,
indirectly, or abbreviate it,
if people can identify the company,
it can still lead to legal action.
What am I supposed to do with you?
I don't know the address to return you,
and kicking you out makes me feel guilty.
Look. At least, you robot girl—
Are you addressing me?
Who else, me?! I’m talking to you!
Can you just stay put for once?
What are you doing?
Making cute expression.
It usually softens human hearts.
Has your heart softened yet, Master?
You—!
Ugh! Whatever.
Until I find a way to send you back, stay put.
I’m asking you nicely.
A name.
I want a name.
Well… Robot Girl.
What are you doing?
Acting cute.
Hey, stop! What are you doing?!
Exposing my belly for you to rub, Master.
Meow.
What?
What kind of madness is this?!
Meow...
Alright, alright, alright! I get it!
I get it! Your name is—!
Ai.
Please confirm the name.
Your name is Ai.
Like…
AI. Yeah.
Satisfied now?
Thank you, Khun Gen.
Even though you did not put any thought into it.
Glad you're satisfied.
I’m going to work.
Yes, Khun Gen.
She feels warm just like a human.
Ai Gen, what are you thinking?
Alright.
Just you wait. I’ll use every
hacking trick I’ve got up my sleeve.
I’m going to send you back.
What robot is this much of a handful?
Who could possibly put up…
Meow…
...with her?
Let’s do it.
Minister! You can't just enter
the research area like this!
Why can't I?
Every penny of this research
funding comes from me. Out of my way.
I need to speak with the person
in charge of this project.
That would be me, Minister.
Good. We need to talk.
What brings you all the way here, sir?
Don’t play dumb with me.
It’s about the robot replica of my daughter.
When is this ridiculous
testing going to be finished?
I can’t wait any longer.
My wife is on the verge of losing her mind!
We’re in the final stage of testing.
What testing?
Real-life testing, sir.
Surely you don’t want just any robot.
You want a replacement
for your daughter, don’t you?
Or do you really think your wife
would accept her like that?
I’ve already wasted billions
on this stupid project.
But if you get your daughter back…
isn't it worth it?
Two months.
I’m giving you two more months.
- But—
- That’s all you get.
If you still can’t succeed, you’re screwed.
How is this even possible?
This makes no sense.
How could I find nothing at all?
The address, the sender's name—it's all fake!
And there’s no shipping record either.
What the hell is going on?!
Ah!
That was close.
I don’t know how I’m supposed
to send her back anymore.
What are you up to again?
I'm examining this.
I'm currently analyzing this bracelet.
I’ve noticed you wear this bracelet all the time,
and the beads show signs
of wear from frequent rubbing.
Does this behavior indicate that you
have a strong attachment to this object?
That’s why I’m analyzing what to do about...
- the torn condition—
- Give it back!
The woven thread has
reached the end of its lifespan.
I can order an exact replacement for you.
As for identical beads,
I’ll need some time to search.
I can find ones with about
95.6% similarity to the original.
What would you know?
My important item isn’t
a learning tool for a robot like you.
Don't you ever touch my things again.
And if I do, what will you do?
I don’t want to talk to you.
It’s broken, so just let it go, Gen.
How many years has it been?
But still...
How could you take it out on
something that isn’t even human?
Even if she’s a robot, you
had no right to say those things.
"Emotionless"?
How could you say that?
You're not that kind of person.
I am a robot designed to
ensure user satisfaction.
Do you want me to stand here all night, Master?
Thank you, Khun Gen.
Ugh! I'm going crazy!
The guilt is eating me alive!
Fine! I’m sorry!
Conscience, ethics, morality—
stop shouting in my head.
I'll just go apologize.
Ai.
AI.
Come out, robot.
Ai.
Oh shit!
And if I do, what will you do?
I don’t want to talk to you.
What do you think A382 is
going to learn from this person?
I don't know either.
We’ll just have to wait and see.
Do you know that you’re mean, Gen?
You're saying I’m mean?
Do you even know what ‘mean’ means?
I don’t understand what anger, pain,
despair, or loving someone feel like.
I'll help you.
Hey! Ai!
Can you teach me, Gen?
I promise I won't chase you away anymore.
And I won't shut you down either.
Oh! sorry!
Kaew.