♪Hey, you, you, you,
why is it you again?♪
♪Always stumbling upon
my little secrets♪
♪Falling on my brows, my lashes,
even the strands by my mouth♪
♪Like my favorite kitten
on a rainy spring afternoon♪
♪Hey, you, you, you,
why is it you again?♪
♪You effortlessly awaken
my protective instincts♪
♪Hitting all my little thoughts,
my doubts, and my temper♪
♪Like my favorite beer and fried chicken
in autumn, or spicy boiled fish in winter♪
♪Why is it you again?
That sweet way you speak♪
♪As if the whole world knows
my mind is full of you♪
♪Why is it still you?
That secret smile behind your cool facade♪
♪I might as well play along.
Let me protect you♪
♪Why is it always you?
The smile at the corner of your lips♪
♪Before I knew it, the words blurted out,
"I like you. I only like you."♪
=Love Has Fireworks=
(Based on "Investment Men and Women"
by Hong Er on Jinjiang Literature City)
=Episode 34=
So impulsive and reckless.
Now look. Shiyu is investigating you,
and Li Qiansheng has jumped in.
You...
Before anyone else acts,
you've already fallen
into the hole you dug yourself.
And you still want
to take over Fulaxida?
In your dreams!
So, Mr. Liao,
what should we do now?
I can only count on you now.
You're the only one who can save me,
right?
Well, as for the solution,
there is one.
But you must do as I say.
Come in.
Well, Ms. Qian, please get some rest.
I won't disturb you any longer.
Thank you.
Come home when you're done.
I know. Just go.
How did you know I was in the hospital?
As soon as I received the email,
I realized Sang Shiqi
would be after you.
I was worried,
so I called Yao Jingjing.
That's when I found out
what you've been up to.
You traveled 5,000 kilometers round-trip
in two days.
With your clumsy driving skills,
you rented a beat-up car
and drove to Taoyuan Creek by yourself.
Are you crazy?
Why would you do all this for me?
Why?
For no reason.
By the way, is your matter resolved?
It's resolved.
With all the help you gave me,
how could it not be?
But you got hurt because of it.
It breaks my heart.
It's nothing.
Look, I'm perfectly fine.
Nothing's wrong.
Are you really okay?
What about your choice?
The one you've always chosen
has been me,
right?
You just don't want to give me
another chance to hurt you,
neglect you, or bully you.
That's why that day,
you made up that lie
and asked me to move out.
If you really didn't have me
in your heart anymore,
how could you possibly,
for a data backup on a computer,
travel those 5,000 kilometers for me?
Do you know how worried I was?
I was scared to death
at the hospital today.
If you were the one being resuscitated,
I can't even bear to think about it.
If I could never see you again,
I would go crazy.
Qian Fei,
can you let me keep liking you?
Let me protect you.
Starting right now,
let me start to truly love you.
Okay?
Why aren't you saying anything?
If you don't say anything,
I'll take it as...
Yifei.
When did you get here?
I just arrived.
Did I wake you up?
No.
I was just dozing off.
I slept quite soundly, actually.
Would you like some tea?
Dad.
I came
to thank you.
Thank you for saving Qian Fei.
Don't mention it.
How did you know Qian Fei was in danger?
What do you think?
I've eaten more salt
than you've eaten rice.
Let me tell you, you know too little
about the dirty tricks
in the business world.
So, Dad, you had already
sent people
to protect Qian Fei all along.
I didn't want to make
the same mistake I made
with your mother
and watch helplessly
as you lose the person you love most.
Dad.
Yifei.
I think
this whole
loving father and filial son act
doesn't really suit the two of us.
You're right. That's true.
It doesn't suit us.
Even though I've been waiting
for this day for most of my life,
I'm still not quite used to it.
Yeah.
Alright.
I'll be honest with you.
Actually, when I saved Qian Fei,
I had my own ulterior motive.
I wanted you to owe me a favor.
Come back to Qiansheng already.
What... What are you laughing at?
I'm serious.
You have no idea what kind of situation
Qiansheng Group is in right now.
Those foreigners are about to strip us
of everything we have.
Hurry back.
Dad, have you ever considered
that there are other ways
to save the group?
I've thought of all that.
But...
the process is too complicated
and takes too long.
And in terms of finances and capital,
the risk is too great.
That's why we need a backdoor listing.
You mean...
Use my Fulaxida to help Qiansheng
with a backdoor listing.
I get it now.
No wonder you refused
to come back all these years
and even sold your house to invest.
You were
paving a way out for Qiansheng.
Is that right?
Dad, actually, from the very beginning,
I never looked down on Qiansheng.
On the contrary,
I love it very much.
You little rascal.
You've grown up.
Have some tea.
I'll tell you everything.
Rascal.
Liu, help me with these reports.
(Hejing Securities Co., Ltd.)
Hello.
Is this Mr. Sang's office?
(Marketing Director's Office)
You must be Fang Yun.
I am.
You're suspected
of stealing trade secrets.
Please cooperate with our investigation.
I think
there might be some misunderstanding.
We'll know if it's a misunderstanding
after the investigation.
Let me just grab my things.
Sure.
Okay.
Excuse me.
All the documents
you requested are right here.
From now on,
she is no longer an employee of Hejing.
Give the documents to the police.
Let's go.
(Police)
I was set up and used
by that man named Sang.
I lost all my money.
And I'm deep in debt.
I...
have elderly parents to support at home.
I was truly at a dead end,
which is why I was taken advantage of
by that Sang guy.
(Police)
I know
in this world, not everything
is completely right or wrong.
But I also know
that in everyone's heart,
they can distinguish
between right and wrong.
All this while,
I've looked up to you as my idol.
I aspired to become someone like you.
The flag that once guided me,
that lighthouse,
no longer exists.
But I won't be afraid
because I know I'm heading
in the right direction.
Later on, if there's anything you need
our help with for the investigation,
feel free to contact me anytime.
Okay, thank you.
We appreciate your hard work.
It's what we're supposed to do.
It's still at home. I haven't dared
to touch a single cent.
I haven't dared to spend it.
Where I've ended up today,
I truly regret it.
Alright. You two can go back first.
Okay.
Thank you.
You're still unwilling
to accept the truth,
right?
Let's go.
Ms. Fang?
Can I have a word with them?
Okay, but make it quick.
I'll wait for you outside.
Okay.
Yang, you can deliver
the documents first.
I've always felt
that the two of us are quite alike.
When I was little,
my grandma always used to tell me,
"A small cart that doesn't fall over
can keep moving slowly."
But back then,
I found her quite annoying.
Always nagging.
I didn't understand
what she was saying either.
It seems a bit late
to understand it now.
Sometimes, the righteous path
is indeed full of hardships.
But perhaps
it's also
a test you must pass to find happiness.
Before,
I always wanted you to live up to
my expectations
because I felt
you were like me.
But now I understand
that you're different from me.
Keep being yourself.
I really like you.
(Domestic Departures)
(China Customs)
(As you said, I didn't take...)
(I didn't take the flight I booked.
I can change it soon.)
(As you said, I didn't take the flight
I booked. I can change it soon.)
Idiot.
Sang Shiqi, you idiot!
Hello? Who is this?
Public Security Bureau?
Sang Shiqi,
where are you off to in such a hurry?
Don't move!
Take him away.
So what if you found out
I was in contact with him?
I have nothing to do with this.
Listen to me...
Cooperate with the investigation?
Okay. Alright.
Do you really think you can outsmart me?
Shiyu, you're still up?
It's getting late. Go to bed.
I've had a long day and am a bit tired.
Dad,
are you busy cutting ties
with Sang Shiqi?
I've found out everything.
The person who ordered Diansansan
to attack Shanlifang
was Sang Shiqi.
And you, long before I did,
already knew about this.
But why didn't you hold him accountable?
Why did you choose to forgive him?
Why?
The reason I did this
was naturally for Shanlifang's sake.
Don't you find that ridiculous?
What's ridiculous about it?
If I go after Sang Shiqi,
will Shanlifang's problems
be solved immediately?
Or
should I just stand by and watch you
lead Shanlifang
through endless restructuring,
waiting for an IPO that may never come?
But you can't just aid a villain.
Liao Shiyu!
Listen to me carefully.
I have nothing to do with Sang Shiqi's
crooked ways!
Shanlifang's problems
have always existed.
The damage caused
by Sang Shiqi's expose,
in a sense,
is far less than the damage would be
if it were exposed
after we went public ourselves.
It's true that Sang Shiqi
is a scoundrel.
But his desire for Shanlifang
to invest in Fulaxida
isn't purely a self-serving matter.
You have seen
Fulaxida's momentum yourself.
If we can go public
through a backdoor listing,
wouldn't that be much faster
than going public on our own?
Dad, I never thought you were so...
So what?
So devoid of a bottom line.
Bottom line?
What's the bottom line?
In the business world,
the bottom line is maximizing profits.
Liao Shiyu, you listen to me.
Starting today,
you're going to be the general manager
of a low-level department.
The vice president position
at Shanlifang
will be temporarily vacant.
Where are you going?
To resign.
You...
Ms. Liao.
Mr. Liao, how about I go talk to her?
Leave her be.
Go to the finance department.
Do what you're supposed to do.
What should we eat later?
Go home and sleep.
Why are you always so tired?
How about we go for a couple of drinks?
A couple of drinks?
Okay.
(Zhonggeng Global Creative Center)
Qian Fei.
Mr. Zhang.
Good morning.
Mr. Zhang, this way.
You're really something else.
Li Yifei is so popular.
It's not like you don't like him.
And yet you're here
pretending not to see him.
I just want to test his patience.
Girl, take it easy.
Be careful not to push him away.
Then you'll come running to me again,
(Xinzouqi Capital)
complaining about how lonely you are.
If he's that easily pushed away,
then he wasn't meant for me
in the first place.
Okay, fine.
(President's Office)
Mr. Zhang.
Qian Fei, have a seat.
You took two days of personal leave,
and somehow you dug up such a
captivating project.
It was just a coincidence.
I happened to cross paths with Fulaxida.
It's more than just a coincidence,
isn't it?
Look at this project.
Mr. Zhang, Mr. Li is here.
Mr. Li.
Please, come in.
Have a seat.
Please.
Sit.
I don't think introductions
are necessary.
No need.
We're old colleagues.
We know each other well.
Qian Fei, you shouldn't
have kept this from us.
A project this good, we should
have gotten involved much earlier.
That's not exactly it.
It's mainly because we at Fulaxida
have always had high standards
for our investors.
We've been turning them away.
Because it's not money we're lacking.
What we lack are good,
visionary investors.
You're an expert in this area too.
The fact that your company could quickly
respond to our investment proposal
and react to it,
doesn't that mean we're like-minded?
Of course.
Most importantly,
in this investment proposal,
I saw your sincerity and respect.
But not just for us.
Also for the rural areas in the west,
and for the farmers participating
in this project.
And I think what's most important
is that
moving forward,
we'll have even more farmers
participating in this.
Right. Typical capital firms
focus on money,
and on the return on investment.
But I think Xinzouqi is different.
Xinzouqi cares about
whether every penny invested
can be put into the eye
of the resource storm,
and whether it can bring about
a positive butterfly effect on society.
Well, I think the reason
All Things Grow, this application,
is so impressive
is not because it leverages trifles for
big impact and builds on a solid ground.
More importantly,
we see the value
of the connections it creates.
It can connect two
of the most distant points
in the world.
That's why I have great confidence
in this project,
and I've written all about it
in the proposal.
I agree with your assessment.
Then I now officially appoint you
as the person in charge of this project.
What do you two think?
Great. I couldn't ask for more.
Can I do it?
It's a pleasure working with you.
Thank you.
Drink up, you pest.
You were the one who ignored me first.
So I had to accept an investment
from a company like Xinzouqi.
Otherwise, I wouldn't
even be able to talk to you.
Don't flatter yourself.
Do you think I don't know
why you're here?
To you,
personal is personal,
business is business.
You keep them perfectly separate.
Aren't you the same?
It's not like you don't know me,
or Lu Ze,
or Ma Li.
You went to Taoyuan Creek
and saw All Things Grow.
Why didn't you come to me
for firsthand data?
You just slogged away
writing the plan yourself.
Independent research
is the best way to avoid pitfalls.
Get it?
So, you see?
It's because you like me too much.
You were afraid it would affect
your objective judgment.
Qian Fei.
I'm patient.
Whether it's for work
or for pursuing you,
I have patience for both.
I'm telling you,
we'll be seeing each other
often at work from now on.
There's no avoiding that.
So from now on,
we need to set some ground rules.
Go on.
First.
We can't let anyone know
that you and I are this close.
We have to make people think
we just have a normal
working relationship.
Second.
Things like giving me flowers
at the door last time,
that kind of behavior,
must never happen again.
Third.
If...
you have to go to places
of pleasure like bars,
you must tell me.
And if you absolutely have to flirt
with other girls,
you have to be completely discreet
and airtight about it.
If I find out, I will beat you to death.
Speak.
Why can't we let people know
about our relationship?
Why can't I come pick you up?
My whole life,
I've walked proudly in the open.
Why do I have to hide
in the shadows now?
Also,
why are bars considered
places of pleasure?
They have legitimate
business licenses, okay?
Most importantly,
if those girls think
I'm cool, handsome, and cute,
and they want to look at me
a little longer,
what can I do about it, right?
You can't just erase
natural-born good looks.
You know what?
It was from observing you and Gui Lili
and how you interacted
that I discovered
these bad habits of yours.
If it were someone else's boyfriend,
I could just laugh it off.
But for my boyfriend,
I can't tolerate it.
Then you can't call these
ground rules for work.
This is you claiming your territory
over your boyfriend.
Quiet.
So what if I'm claiming my territory?
What's wrong? Is there a problem?
Speak.
Of course there's no problem.
So if I agree to your terms,
does that mean you will have
to help me out more at work?
This work is what I'm supposed
to be doing anyway.
What does it have to do
with helping you?
Of course it does.
Fulaxida's business
is constantly expanding.
Although the threat from Sang Shiqi
has been eliminated,
Liao Jinshan is still eagerly
waiting for his chance.
I can't possibly keep an eye
on all the investors by myself.
Right?
What if problematic capital
like Shanlifang
takes advantage
of a vulnerability?
It would deal a heavy blow
to everything we've done.
If Shanlifang intends
to invest in Fulaxida,
it must first resolve its own issues,
which can't be fixed overnight.
But once those are resolved,
new problems will arise.
So what can I do about it?
Let's not worry
about Shanlifang's problems for now.
But what we need
to pay attention to right now
is another company.
Qiansheng Group.
Qiansheng?
Yes.
Because Fulaxida needs more
high-quality capital like Xinzouqi.
Qiansheng Group is very optimistic
about Fulaxida's
business model and future plans.
And we've previously reached
an investment intention.
However, this company
has just completed its privatization
and delisted in the US.
It hasn't finished
its capital transition yet.
So,
I want to leverage Xinzouqi's resources
to help Qiansheng.
I get it.
You want me to act
as a consultant for Xinzouqi
and secure a partnership with Qiansheng.
Exactly.
Does Mr. Zhang know?
Of course.
Now, it all depends on your answer.
Alright.
You agreed so quickly.
Come on. To a successful partnership.
Ding-dong.
Mr. Li,
I won't beat around the bush.
Okay.
I came here this time
to recommend myself.
I was wondering if I could
get a position at Zhizhong
or Fulaxida.
What do you mean?
You're leaving Shanlifang?
That's right.
I want to be like you
and create a world of my own.
I'm impressed.
But why does it have to be Zhizhong
or Fulaxida?
With your abilities, Ms. Liao,
you could go to any major company.
First,
I approve of Zhizhong's
business principles,
and I'm optimistic
about Fulaxida's project prospects.
Second, and more importantly,
I admire your work ethic
and your capabilities.
I also believe our shared philosophy
on studying abroad
will create more synergy.
So,
I hope to work at a reliable company
with reliable people.
Regardless of the position or salary,
I'm willing to accept it.
Ms. Liao,
I truly understand the troubles
your family background has caused you.
And I'm very grateful
for your confidence in Zhizhong,
in Fulaxida,
and in me personally.
However, Zhizhong
has very high requirements
for its employees'
professional backgrounds.
I recall you studied
management abroad, right?
Yes.
It might not be a good fit.
But Fulaxida might be an option.
You could invest
in your personal capacity
and become a shareholder.
What do you think?
Invest?
But I don't have much in savings.
Compared to what you need,
it would just be a drop in the bucket.
I see.
That makes things a bit difficult.
You see, we don't have
any open positions right now.
If I were to create a position
for you out of thin air,
wouldn't that have
a greater negative impact on you?
That's a very tactful way
of rejecting me, Mr. Li.
No, that's not what I meant.
What I was actually trying to say is...
Ms. Liao, with your personal abilities,
you could totally develop
a field of your own.
For example, resource allocation
or project management.
How about this?
I'll recommend someone to you.
Who?
Gui Lili.
Gui Lili?
Isn't she the assistant to Mr. Niu,
the supplier for Shanlifang?
She's not just Mr. Niu's assistant.
She's Mr. Niu's wife now.
She spends her days
sitting on a pile of money.
She's always wanted to build a career,
but she doesn't have any ideas.
So I think
with your abilities
and her financial resources,
you two could create some sparks.
Since she's so rich now,
why don't you get her
to invest in Fulaxida?
=Love Has Fireworks=
(Next Episode Preview)
What do you think?
Let's take a look around here first.
Do you know
why I brought you here today?
This apartment was
only lived in for a year.
It's basically a brand-new place.
And it's the most basic floor plan.
In the secondhand housing market now,
properties like yours
are the most sought-after.
- I'll leave it to you then.
- Stop!
It's okay.
You...
Qian Fei, have you lost your mind?
Wang Ruohai's mom
needs a kidney transplant.
Why are you
selling the apartment for him?
♪There's no need
to know the ending from the start♪
♪Let the melody play through the chords
with the wind♪
♪There's no need
to keep every promise from the past♪
♪Leave some surprises
for the unknown in life♪
♪There's no need
to force things between two people♪
♪Perhaps I'll feel alone,
yet still find you there for me♪
♪There's no need
to dwell on right or wrong, nor fear♪
♪A hug means more
than countless apologies♪
♪I'll send you into the wide world♪
♪To live with passion
and become who you truly are♪
♪A quiet shoulder♪
♪Like a harbor waiting
for your wandering soul♪
♪I'll wait for the day
you return to a simpler life♪
♪The lights of home warm the night♪
♪A companionship that lasts forever♪
♪Shining brightly
like the stars and the moon on high♪
♪I'll send you into the wide world♪
♪To live with passion
and become who you truly are♪
♪A quiet shoulder♪
♪Like a harbor waiting
for your wandering soul♪
♪I'll wait for the day
you return to a simpler life♪
♪The lights of home warm the night♪
♪A companionship that lasts forever♪
♪Shining brightly
like the stars and the moon on high♪