笙ｪHey, you, you, you,
why is it you again?笙ｪ
笙ｪAlways stumbling upon
my little secrets笙ｪ
笙ｪFalling on my brows, my lashes,
even the strands by my mouth笙ｪ
笙ｪLike my favorite kitten
on a rainy spring afternoon笙ｪ
笙ｪHey, you, you, you,
why is it you again?笙ｪ
笙ｪYou effortlessly awaken
my protective instincts笙ｪ
笙ｪHitting all my little thoughts,
my doubts, and my temper笙ｪ
笙ｪLike my favorite beer and fried chicken
in autumn, or spicy boiled fish in winter笙ｪ
笙ｪWhy is it you again?
That sweet way you speak笙ｪ
笙ｪAs if the whole world knows
my mind is full of you笙ｪ
笙ｪWhy is it still you?
That secret smile behind your cool facade笙ｪ
笙ｪI might as well play along.
Let me protect you笙ｪ
笙ｪWhy is it always you?
The smile at the corner of your lips笙ｪ
笙ｪBefore I knew it, the words blurted out,
"I like you. I only like you."笙ｪ
=Love Has Fireworks=
(Based on "Investment Men and Women"
by Hong Er on Jinjiang Literature City)
=Episode 33=
Thank you. You've worked hard.
You're welcome. Goodbye.
Hello, please sign here.
笙ｪWhat matters to me is what you need笙ｪ
笙ｪNo more, no less.
I only hope I can give it to you笙ｪ
笙ｪWhat I treasure is what I have笙ｪ
笙ｪBit by bit,
I only hope you're there with me笙ｪ
笙ｪThose sweet promises and words of love笙ｪ
笙ｪLike fireworks
lighting up the midnight sky笙ｪ
笙ｪTruths, lies,
and words said for appearances笙ｪ
笙ｪLeaving me
feeling like I'm walking on air笙ｪ
笙ｪHarsh words, lies,
and words I can't make sense of笙ｪ
笙ｪAll dressed up in hollow splendor笙ｪ
笙ｪDreams, nonsense,
and the words hidden in my heart笙ｪ
笙ｪBeneath this burning gaze笙ｪ
(Daisy's Meaning:
You're the love I hide inside.)
Wow, you actually bought it?
You know what? It looks pretty good.
You like it?
If you like it, it's yours.
Really?
笙ｪAnd words said for appearances笙ｪ
笙ｪLeaving me
feeling like I'm walking on air笙ｪ
笙ｪHarsh words, lies,
and words I can't make sense of笙ｪ
笙ｪAll dressed up in hollow splendor笙ｪ
笙ｪDreams, nonsense,
and the words hidden in my heart笙ｪ
笙ｪBeneath this burning gaze笙ｪ
Who would've thought
it would end like this?
He actually moved out.
She's your best friend.
How could you not know?
You two are very opinionated.
What if I just tell Fei
that Li Yifei's been missing her
after he got to Taoyuan Creek?
Maybe today
would've been a happy ending.
It's okay.
I'm telling you,
just leave this to time.
(Pretentious Li)
Hello, the number you've dialed
is powered off.
Is he on a plane,
or did he change his number?
Boss,
do you have a smaller portion of okra?
I might not finish it alone.
Yes. One moment, I'll find one for you.
Okay, thanks.
(Pretentious Li)
Hello?
I... I lost my phone.
It's been off all day.
I just bought a new one
and saw that you called me.
What's up?
I found a Kindle at home.
I wanted to ask if it's yours.
If it is, send me an address,
and I'll mail it to you.
I don't want it anymore.
Just throw it away.
Okay.
Do you
have anything else to say?
Hello.
This bag is smaller.
It should be enough for you alone.
Thank you.
Nothing else.
That's all then.
Hello, please take a look.
(Real Estate)
Hello.
Miss.
It's me. You don't remember?
A year ago, you listed
a shared rental with us.
Do you have a place now?
Yes...
If I do, I'll contact you again.
Alright. My number's on there.
Call me anytime if you need anything.
Okay, thank you.
Goodbye.
(Sitting in the living room
and drinking beer with Li Yifei)
(feels like it happened
in the last century.)
(It's been a very, very long time.)
What brings you here today?
You're pretty lucky.
I'm usually out and about.
I finally made it back
to the office today.
I'm here for a project progress meeting.
Fei.
They say women in love
have the best skin.
You're glowing lately.
Tell me, are you dating someone?
Do you have nothing to talk about
if you're not gossiping about me?
You came alone today?
Yeah.
You're not with Li Yifei anymore?
Of course I am. He's my boss.
Then why didn't he come today?
Don't ask.
My boss has been swamped
with troubles lately.
What happened to him?
Before working
on the Shanlifang Hotel Group project,
he was handling a convertible bond
issuance for another company.
Everything had been prepared.
We're only waiting
for the client's confirmation,
but they found out the bonds
had already been issued.
They said Zhizhong
wanted too much money,
so they took the complete materials
my boss had prepared
and secretly hired another brokerage.
What jerks.
But that's a matter
between the companies.
What does it have to do with Li Yifei?
I know you want to hear it.
Same old rules.
(Top Up to Red Packet)
(WeChat Pay)
(Wishing You Prosperity)
(Loading)
(Qian Fei's Red Packet, Open)
Thanks.
Since they couldn't reach an agreement,
they'll go to court.
But the lawyer the company hired
keeps saying
a guaranteed contract is missing.
He insists
it was previously given to Yifei.
But for some reason,
Yifei was completely
out of sorts during that time.
Even he wasn't sure
whether he'd properly stored
that guarantee contract.
Then,
that lawyer printed out
all the related communications
and had them notarized.
At the critical moment,
the boss's phone went missing.
Doesn't he have his email?
Don't even mention it.
It was probably hacked.
All the files inside were deleted,
and he didn't make a backup.
That lawyer
is trying to pin the blame on Yifei.
He insists Yifei took bribes
from that company
and deliberately lost the case.
Li Yifei would never do that.
Exactly.
Not a single one of our coworkers
believed Yifei would do that.
But during that period,
Yifei really was acting strange.
His documents were lost,
and his phone was lost.
Even something as important
as his email was logged into
on another computer.
Maybe he forgot to log out
and got hacked.
But I remember
there seemed to be
a lot of first-hand materials.
Didn't they all go through you?
At that time,
the company sent me away
for training for a week.
When I came back,
the boss was already in trouble.
I told you he can't do without me.
Compared to Li Yifei,
I think that new lawyer you hired
looks more like the mole.
My guess is
that lawyer
is settling a personal score.
Wasn't Yifei in a bad mood?
He was pretty irritable, too.
And that lawyer
is always so full of himself,
making everyone cooperate with him.
Yifei talked back to him
a couple of times,
which made the lawyer look bad.
Now that he's got leverage,
how could he not use it?
Then what happened next?
Normally, it's not a big deal.
But the problem is
that lawyer has connections
with the board.
We can ignore his nonsense,
but if the higher-ups listen,
Boss probably won't be able to stay.
Then we still need to find
that guarantee contract.
How do we find it?
The phone and email data are all gone.
(Xinzouqi Capital Co., Ltd.)
Shanshan.
Can you send me the original file?
Give me a few minutes.
I'm backing up my phone
to my computer right now.
As soon as it's done,
I'll send it to you.
Okay.
Thanks.
Idiot.
What are you doing?
I'm transferring my phone data
to my computer.
I want to do that, too. Can you help me?
You're hopeless. You can't even do this?
Give me your phone.
Wait till I'm done.
(The phone's gone, but the data isn't.)
(Xinzouqi Capital Co., Ltd.)
Hello, Xin You. This is Qian Fei.
Here's the thing.
Among the things I donated last time,
there was an old computer. Remember it?
Yes, I need it urgently.
That's great. As long as it's not lost.
How about this? I'll take leave
and come see you today.
(Shuangliu International Airport)
No, I have to come.
It'll save time this way.
Okay, let's stay in touch.
(Book)
Didn't you say
you were no longer a hopeless romantic
and could think maturely
about relationships now?
You're worrying about Li Yifei
and running around for him.
Does that look rational to you?
Not being together
was my choice
after considering many factors.
But standing by and doing nothing
isn't who I am.
I can't worry about that now.
Let's get through this first.
You're totally doomed.
You've fallen for Li Yifei.
Judging from the way you're acting,
I will never believe you if you say
you don't want to be with him.
And you keep saying
you don't see a future.
I think your future is tied to his.
I don't know about that,
but I do know
that my future with you
is definitely intertwined.
I've got to go. Time to check in.
笙ｪWhat matters to me is what you need笙ｪ
笙ｪNo more, no less.
I only hope I can give it to you笙ｪ
笙ｪWhat I treasure is what I have笙ｪ
笙ｪBit by bit,
I only hope you're there with me笙ｪ
笙ｪThose sweet promises and words of love笙ｪ
笙ｪLike fireworks
lighting up the midnight sky笙ｪ
笙ｪTruths, lies,
and words said for appearances笙ｪ
笙ｪLeaving me
feeling like I'm walking on air笙ｪ
(You're totally doomed.)
(You've fallen for Li Yifei.)
(Judging from the way you're acting,)
(I will never believe you)
(if you say
you don't want to be with him.)
(And you keep saying
you don't see a future.)
(I think your future is tied to his.)
(Taoyuan Creek)
Qian Fei is here.
- Qian Fei.
Qian Fei.
Welcome, Qian Fei.
Xin You.
- Long time no see.
- You've had a long trip.
Xin Ba.
Qian Fei.
I missed you so much.
I missed you all too.
The kids really like you.
You've gotten prettier.
Such a sweet talker.
Was the trip smooth?
Very smooth.
The kids talk about you every day.
They really miss you.
- So adorable.
- I'm so grateful.
You and Yifei
came here to see me a year ago.
Not only did it free me
from my emotional burden,
but Xin Ba also got treatment.
And all the county's
farmers and ranchers
got to partner with Fulaxida.
Ever since the app launched,
customers' orders
have been booked until next year.
That's wonderful.
I heard the customers
have even named the fields,
the calves, and lambs.
That's right.
Especially the livestock.
Some customers actually ask
the farmers to keep feeding them
and never slaughter them.
Without making a fuss,
Li Yifei did something amazing.
Xin Ba, take Fei home.
I'll get your computer.
- Okay, let's go.
Qian Fei, here.
Will it come over?
You have more food. It'll eat yours.
Qian Fei.
Your phone.
(All Things Grow)
I can already see them all so soon.
Qian Fei.
I got the computer back.
That's great.
Kids, go play outside.
Let's go play outside!
Go on.
(Deputy Director's Office)
Look.
(Chairman Hong Yiyun)
This timestamp and owner info.
I'm absolutely sure
I handed this company's
guarantee contract to you back then.
Impossible, Boss.
I've checked many times.
I don't have it.
Think carefully. Did you miss somewhere?
Didn't we keep everything
in the archives room?
You checked several times just now, too.
How lucky.
The teachers have been using
this computer all along.
The system was never reinstalled.
What you're looking for
should still be in there.
But I remember
I saved it on the desktop.
Why can't I find it now?
Are you sure it was on the desktop?
I'm sure.
Here, let me take a look.
Okay.
What's the file name?
Li Phone Backup.
(Li Phone Backup)
Take a look. Is this it?
That's it.
How did you find it so quickly?
(Li Phone Backup)
You've done Li Yifei a huge favor.
Haven't you, too?
That's what friends do.
(Fang)
What's wrong?
I have something urgent to deal with.
Go ahead.
(Li Yifei)
(Email Sending...)
(Li Phone Backup)
How did Qian Fei know I needed these?
She mentioned you when we met earlier.
I casually said a few things.
Forget it for now.
Let's find the contract
and contact Legal.
(Li Phone Backup)
Look at this.
No.
(Pretentious Li)
(Last Modified Date)
(Qian Fei: The modification time
of the folder below)
(matches the time when Liao Shiyu)
(went on stage
at the Shanlifang Charity Gala.)
(Part II: Guarantee Arrangements)
Boss, this data
hasn't been sorted out yet.
How about this?
Contact Legal and have them prepare
the materials immediately
and get in touch with the lawyer.
As for this data,
I'll send it to your email in a bit.
Let's split up.
Good idea. I'll go now.
Go.
Well... Xin You.
I have something urgent.
I need to leave.
Leaving so soon?
At least stay for a meal.
No.
I should get going.
I think I need to take
this computer back.
After I return to Shanghai,
I'll send over a new one.
The teacher's files and documents
will be copied to the new computer.
Okay.
Alright, I'm heading out.
Thanks, Xin You.
No problem.
(Li Yifei)
(Qian Fei: The modification time
of the folder below)
(matches the time when Liao Shiyu
went on stage at the Shanlifang Charity Gala.)
(And I contacted Weibo customer service.
My password was changed at that exact time.)
Well done.
I'm professional.
(I have a plan. I'll contact you later.)
What are you doing?
Sir.
Someone complained
that you're disturbing our members.
Please leave immediately.
Complained about me?
Who am I disturbing?
Please leave immediately.
I'm looking for someone.
Excuse me.
Do you know which room
the guest you're looking for is in?
Ms. Liao.
Mr. Li.
Found her.
Thanks.
You can go out now.
Diansansan's IP address
appeared here several times.
You mean
he's a member here?
I've already obtained
Lis's membership list,
but I don't know many of them.
My father probably knows
most of them though.
Could I see it?
Well...
Ms. Liao,
you don't suspect
I'm involved in this, do you?
Not at all.
Mr. Li.
After your advice at the group,
I knew this had nothing to do with you.
It's just...
Alright.
I hope you'll keep this secret.
Don't worry.
(Lis Premium Club Membership List)
(Sang Shiqi)
This guy is close to your father, right?
Then this list
shouldn't be shown to your father yet.
(Sang Shiqi)
(Part II: Guarantee Arrangements)
Boss, this data
hasn't been sorted out yet.
(Recent Calls)
(Qian Fei)
(Li Yifei)
Hello?
Is Qian Fei with you?
No.
She went to Chengdu.
Why did she go to Chengdu?
To help you find your lost phone data.
Chengdu?
Fei's old computer
was donated to Xin You and the others.
She thought
there might still be your data on it.
I see.
(Xin You)
Xin You, is Qian Fei still with you?
She left in a hurry.
She said she was catching
the earliest flight back.
Okay.
Thanks.
(Flight Information)
(Exit)
Miss,
do you know that car behind us?
That black car?
No.
(Qian Fei)
Qian Fei, answer the phone.
What's this car doing?
Is this guy crazy?
(Recent Calls)
(Qian Fei)
Sir, stop the car.
Just stop the car. Don't provoke him.
Are you out of your mind?
Hello, is this 110?
Yes, there's a car
following us.
(Qian Fei, Calling)
(Qian Fei)
Hello? Where are you?
Are you Qian Fei's friend?
I'm from the police station.
She was taken to the hospital
after a car accident.
She left her phone here.
Which hospital?
(Emergency)
This is the emergency center.
A traffic accident victim has arrived.
Prepare 1,000 ml
of type O blood immediately.
Okay.
(Nurses' Station)
Nurse, there was...
Nurse, there was a young woman
brought in this morning.
How is she now? Where is she?
Name and age?
Qian Fei, aged 29. 29.
Where is she? How is she?
Who are you?
You can't go in.
If you're not family,
wait over there.
I... I'm her boyfriend.
Qian Fei!
This is a hospital.
Li Yifei?
笙ｪThere's no need
to force things between two people笙ｪ
笙ｪPerhaps I'll feel alone,
yet still find you there for me笙ｪ
笙ｪThere's no need to dwell
on right or wrong, nor fear笙ｪ
笙ｪA hug means more than
countless apologies笙ｪ
You scared me to death.
笙ｪI'll send you into the wide world笙ｪ
笙ｪTo live with passion
and become who you truly are笙ｪ
笙ｪA quiet shoulder笙ｪ
What are you doing here?
I...
I wasn't talking to you.
What are you doing here?
笙ｪA companionship that lasts forever笙ｪ
Well...
笙ｪShining brightly like the stars
and the moon on high笙ｪ
It doesn't hurt, right?
Are you hurt anywhere else?
I'm fine.
笙ｪA quiet shoulder笙ｪ
笙ｪLike a harbor
waiting for your wandering soul笙ｪ
I'm glad you're okay.
笙ｪA companionship that lasts forever笙ｪ
笙ｪShining brightly like the stars
and the moon on high笙ｪ
Let me see your injury.
Does it hurt?
By the way,
how did you two end up together?
Don't forget.
You're not fighting alone.
So this is why
you didn't answer my calls.
Couldn't you have waited?
Mr. Liao, that computer
contains Shanlifang's original data
and evidence that I framed Qian Fei.
Once it's exposed,
it'll definitely affect
Shanlifang's next plans.
Now you remember Shanlifang?
Back in the car,
what did you tell me?
Mr. Liao, the reason I did this
was to help you face the problem sooner.
Otherwise,
the penalties Shanlifang faces
will be far greater
than the current losses.
Don't you agree?
What a silver tongue.
If you really cared about me,
you should've told me directly.
The reason you stirred up
such a huge public uproar
was to destroy Shanlifang.
No.
It's true I stirred things up,
but I never intended
to destroy Shanlifang.
Quite the opposite.
My future and my life
are now tightly bound to Shanlifang.
What a load of nonsense.
Mr. Liao.
You'll definitely thank me
in the future.
I guess I'm taking the indirect route
to get the job done.
Think about it carefully.
With your precious daughter's
stubborn personality,
if I hadn't suddenly pulled
something like this,
Shanlifang would've missed
its best chance to go public.
You mean Fulaxida?
You're shrewd.
Before this,
you were already interested in Fulaxida.
You even made
some small-scale investments through me.
I'll be honest with you.
I've already started taking action
against Fulaxida and Li Yifei.
If we're getting into details,
then this matter...
Mr. Liao,
even you can't stay uninvolved.
Sounds like you're threatening me.
No, Mr. Liao.
How could this be a threat?
It's a reminder.
I think
you need to be a little braver.
Think about it. Shanlifang's failed IPO
is already a settled fact.
Why not focus
all your energy
on a brand-new opportunity
like Fulaxida?
So impulsive and reckless.
Now, look. Shiyu is investigating you,
and Li Qiansheng has jumped in.
You...
Before anyone else acts,
you've already fallen
into the hole you dug yourself.
=Love Has Fireworks=
(Next Episode Preview)
The one you've always chosen
has been me,
right?
Qian Fei.
Can you let me keep liking you?
Let me protect you,
okay?
I'm telling you,
we'll be seeing each other
often at work from now on.
There's no avoiding that.
So from now on,
we need to set some ground rules.
笙ｪThere's no need
to know the ending from the start笙ｪ
笙ｪLet the melody play through the chords
with the wind笙ｪ
笙ｪThere's no need
to keep every promise from the past笙ｪ
笙ｪLeave some surprises
for the unknown in life笙ｪ
笙ｪThere's no need
to force things between two people笙ｪ
笙ｪPerhaps I'll feel alone,
yet still find you there for me笙ｪ
笙ｪThere's no need
to dwell on right or wrong, nor fear笙ｪ
笙ｪA hug means more
than countless apologies笙ｪ
笙ｪI'll send you into the wide world笙ｪ
笙ｪTo live with passion
and become who you truly are笙ｪ
笙ｪA quiet shoulder笙ｪ
笙ｪLike a harbor waiting
for your wandering soul笙ｪ
笙ｪI'll wait for the day
you return to a simpler life笙ｪ
笙ｪThe lights of home warm the night笙ｪ
笙ｪA companionship that lasts forever笙ｪ
笙ｪShining brightly
like the stars and the moon on high笙ｪ
笙ｪI'll send you into the wide world笙ｪ
笙ｪTo live with passion
and become who you truly are笙ｪ
笙ｪA quiet shoulder笙ｪ
笙ｪLike a harbor waiting
for your wandering soul笙ｪ
笙ｪI'll wait for the day
you return to a simpler life笙ｪ
笙ｪThe lights of home warm the night笙ｪ
笙ｪA companionship that lasts forever笙ｪ
笙ｪShining brightly
like the stars and the moon on high笙ｪ