♪Hey, you, you, you,
why is it you again?♪
♪Always stumbling upon
my little secrets♪
♪Falling on my brows, my lashes,
even the strands by my mouth♪
♪Like my favorite kitten
on a rainy spring afternoon♪
♪Hey, you, you, you,
why is it you again?♪
♪You effortlessly awaken
my protective instincts♪
♪Hitting all my little thoughts,
my doubts, and my temper♪
♪Like my favorite beer and fried chicken
in autumn, or spicy boiled fish in winter♪
♪Why is it you again?
That sweet way you speak♪
♪As if the whole world knows
my mind is full of you♪
♪Why is it still you?
That secret smile behind your cool facade♪
♪I might as well play along.
Let me protect you♪
♪Why is it always you?
The smile at the corner of your lips♪
♪Before I knew it, the words blurted out,
"I like you. I only like you."♪
=Love Has Fireworks=
(Based on "Investment Men and Women"
by Hong Er on Jinjiang Literature City)
=Episode 36=
What's wrong?
What is this?
You skipped work to come to see me?
How did you know?
I already booked your ticket.
Go change.
The driver's on the way.
Are you serious?
I worked half the night
just so I could see you today.
I just got
out of the shower
and was about to lie down.
And now you're kicking me out?
Just to see me,
you'd abandon work?
Shouldn't I come see you?
I told you on the phone last night
that I missed you.
If I miss you, I should see you.
Isn't that more important than work?
Well...
If you don't work properly,
how are you going to renew
the lease on that mansion?
Mansion?
You've known me this long.
Do you think I'm someone
who cares about money?
Leave.
I'm not leaving.
I'm telling you,
this is
irresponsible to your work.
I only want to be responsible for you.
The driver will be here soon.
I'll pay him
to turn back and leave.
Any other questions?
The flight ticket will go to waste.
♪What matters to me is what you need♪
♪No more, no less.
I only hope I can give it to you♪
♪What I treasure is what I have♪
♪Bit by bit,
I only hope you're there with me♪
♪Those sweet promises and words of love♪
♪Like fireworks
lighting up the midnight sky♪
♪Truths, lies,
and words said for appearances♪
♪Leaving me
feeling like I'm walking on air♪
♪Harsh words, lies,
and words I can't make sense of♪
(Kissy)
(Early flight. I'll leave first.)
(I won't neglect my work.)
(I'll pick you up
when you're back in Shanghai.)
♪Beneath this burning gaze♪
♪Those sweet promises and words of love♪
♪Like fireworks
lighting up the midnight sky♪
♪Truths, lies,
and words said for appearances♪
♪Leaving me
feeling like I'm walking on air♪
♪Harsh words, lies,
and words I can't make sense of♪
♪All dressed up in hollow splendor♪
♪Dreams, nonsense,
and the words hidden in my heart♪
♪Beneath this burning gaze♪
(Devices)
(One-Click Cloud Upload,
Smart Recommendations)
(Fulaxida Co., Ltd.)
Excellent.
I've found that Fulaxida
is a company rooted in the earth
while reaching for the sky,
looking ahead.
It's such an energetic
and ambitious company.
Why wouldn't Qiansheng
Manufacturing invest?
So our letter of intent
is already prepared.
Mr. Li.
We can sign anytime.
Chairman Li.
(Qiansheng Manufacturing Group Co., Ltd.
2018 Semiannual Report, Part V)
I'm back.
We finally get to be together,
yet you're not excited at all.
No kisses, hugs,
or lifting me up.
You don't love me anymore.
I do.
It's just
that now isn't the time
for kisses, hugs, and lifting you up.
So when is it?
(Qiansheng Manufacturing Group Co., Ltd.
2018 Semiannual Report, Part V)
You went to Qiansheng?
Mr. Zhang went with me.
We got several GB of data.
I've just printed it all out.
Qiansheng's data is indeed complex.
You worked hard.
So what's the plan?
Mr. Zhang assigned me some staff.
Once everything's
sorted and categorized,
we can work on the transition plan.
How long will it take?
With my expertise,
what do you think?
True.
Your data skills are second to none.
And why is that?
Why?
Because you recognize talent.
I praise you a little, and you are showing off.
I'm hungry.
If you're not busy,
go cook me some noodles.
Noodles.
After spending so much time
with my clever cook,
I've become a good cook as well.
Just wait.
I'll make you a bowl
of house special fat noodles.
Noodles.
(Look at the person
I found for you. How diligent.)
(Old man: You're just a bridge.)
(Don't get involved
in matters between clients.)
(And stop showing off in front of me.)
I'll show off all I want.
Please.
Chairman Li.
Ms. Qian.
Hello.
Hello. I'm Qian Fei,
manager of Xinzouqi's
Project Investment Department
and consultant for this project.
You're truly young and accomplished.
No, you're too kind.
Okay, please have a seat.
Okay.
(Qiansheng Group Capital Transition Plan)
Let's begin.
Okay.
First,
I'll be analyzing some issues
that arose during Qiansheng Group's
American delisting process.
I'll present my personal views.
Then,
we'll look at the final plan
after a thorough discussion.
First, I'd like to discuss
privatization failure
mainly involves two stages.
The first is during the transaction.
The second
is after the transaction is completed.
In fact, privatization
is a double-edged sword
for companies...
Here, Ms. Qian.
A toast to you.
No, I should toast you.
Young people don't need to be so modest.
And you've truly
done our group a huge favor.
If you ever need help,
just let me know.
This is all part of our job.
Xinzouqi also looks forward
to more exchanges and cooperation
with Qiansheng in the future.
Good. Come on.
- Cheers. Let's all drink.
- Cheers.
- Come on.
- Together.
Thank you for your hospitality today,
Chairman Li.
Not at all.
You really don't need me
to arrange a car?
No need.
My colleagues and I
are all heading the same way.
Okay.
Qian Fei.
Mr. Li.
Shiyu, what are you doing here?
We were discussing a project.
Hello.
Come in and have a seat.
No need.
I'm heading back.
You go ahead and chat.
See you next time, Chairman Li.
Okay. Goodbye, Ms. Qian.
Bye.
Don't wait for me. Head back now.
I still have something to do.
Sure.
Bye.
- Goodbye.
- Bye.
Have a seat.
I've given you plenty of time.
And you still can't fix
these data loopholes?
Chairman.
Doing it this way
will really cause problems
during the capital verification process.
Everyone's competing for Fulaxida now.
Competitors keep popping up.
Even that recently emerged
Xiantai Capital has joined in.
And you're still being overly cautious.
I'm giving you two days.
No matter the issue,
get it fixed quickly.
Chairman, a friend wants to see you.
No.
What's going on?
Jinshan.
Such a big temper.
Qiansheng.
Qiansheng,
you came
without even giving me a heads-up.
Just some trivial matters.
- Sit.
- Here.
What tea would you like? Cinnamon?
No tea.
That won't do.
I didn't come here for tea.
I know.
It's about Fulaxida.
The Art of War says,
Ten to one, surround them.
Five to one, attack them. Two to one, divide them.
Qiansheng holds all the advantages.
Shanlifang
can't even find any room to maneuver.
I'm not here to show off to you.
Look.
You and I know
Shanlifang's problems.
As for Qiansheng's predicament,
it can't escape on its own either.
So
since that's the case,
what are we still fighting over?
What's the point of two old men
arguing like this?
We'll just become a joke
to the younger generation.
What exactly are you trying to say?
I'm saying, do what we're supposed to do
and leave the future
to the younger generation.
Easy for you to say.
You're saying the future
should be left to your son, aren't you?
Obviously.
If not him, then who?
Besides, you're the same.
Don't you also have to
leave the future to your daughter?
My daughter is no longer here.
Who says so?
I do.
Shiyu.
Dad.
Didn't you resign?
Why are you back?
I'm now an investment manager
at Xiantai Capital.
You...
Yes. Xiantai Capital is a company
I founded with friends after I resigned.
We're preparing to invest in Fulaxida.
Isn't it risky
for a startup like Xiantai Capital
to invest
in Fulaxida?
Or rather,
would they be willing
to accept investments
from an investment company like ours
that has no investment experience?
Of course they would.
Xiantai Capital
can be considered a venture capital firm
in a certain sense.
It's different from the mindset
that only allows winning
and never allows losing.
With government policy support
over the past few years,
Fulaxida's prospects
are quite promising.
If you're willing to invest,
I believe the chances of being accepted
are very high.
Really?
Then, could we hire you
as our consultant?
Of course.
As long as you reach an agreement
with Xinzouqi.
Here, Qian Fei.
A toast to you.
Okay.
Sorry, I didn't order any alcohol.
It's on the house.
I can't accept that.
How much is it?
Any friend of Mr. Li Jr.
is on the house.
Mr. Li Jr.?
Yeah.
Li Yifei from Qiansheng Group.
Enjoy.
Look at the state you're in now.
You still want to defeat your father?
You'll never beat him.
How am I not a rich heir?
(So he really is a rich heir.)
(Then all the support I gave him)
(must seem ridiculous to him.)
Operation failed.
(Verification Failed)
(Qian Fei)
(Qian Fei, Calling)
Sorry.
The user you dialed
is currently unavailable.
Please try again later.
Landlady.
Landlady, are you home?
I heard something.
Qian Fei, are you okay?
Are you home?
Qian Fei.
Qian Fei, open the door. Qian Fei.
Are you okay?
Qian...
(Qian Fei: Heir of Qiansheng Group,
you'd better move back to your mansion!)
Heir of Qiansheng Group?
I...
How did she know?
(Qi)
(Qi, Calling)
Hello, Fei?
Hello, Qi?
Let me ask you.
Did Qian Fei contact you later?
She said she'd thank me this afternoon.
I told her to meet me
at the bar tonight.
The thing is, I only got her gift,
but not her.
(Open the door and let me explain.)
(Message sent
but rejected by the recipient.)
Sorry.
The user you dialed
is currently unavailable.
She blocked me?
Qian Fei, what are you doing? Qian Fei!
Qian Fei, let me explain! Qian Fei!
You... You open the door
and let me explain, okay?
I'll explain.
Qian Fei, open the door first!
Stop knocking.
I'll call the police if you keep it up.
You're serious?
What are you doing? No...
Weren't we fine?
Let me explain to you properly.
Let me explain.
(Zhonggeng Global Creative Center)
(Xinzouqi Capital Co., Ltd.)
Ms. Qian.
Are you still swamped with work today?
Mr. Zhang.
It's basically all done.
Here's the thing.
Our company's project
with Qiansheng Group
has basically been finalized.
Originally,
I was going to visit them myself today,
but something came up.
Why don't you go in my place?
No problem, sure.
Then I'll get ready
and head to their company.
No need.
Chairman Li is at home today.
Just visit him at his house.
Sure.
Alright, thanks.
Alright, it's fine.
Hello, Ms. Qian.
Please come in.
Okay.
Let me take that.
This way, please.
Chairman.
Ms. Qian is here.
Ms. Qian.
Chairman Li.
Please sit.
What would you like to drink?
Tea, thank you.
Okay.
Ms. Qian.
Thank you.
Ms. Qian,
let's be honest with each other.
To tell you the truth,
if my son weren't so stubborn,
I would never have agreed
to him dating someone
from a family like yours.
So you're meeting me today
as Li Yifei's father?
That's right.
If you weren't such an important client,
I'd definitely fire back
with a few sharp remarks.
Such as?
For example, your family's wealth
looks good on paper,
but it's hard to turn into cash.
Not only do you have to worry about
delisting in the America and relisting in China,
but you also have to keep wondering
whether someone
will go after your assets.
So you're under much more pressure
than I am.
You've got quite a personality.
Let me ask you something.
If I wrote you a check,
one you could cash anytime,
what would you do?
Write me?
Do you even need to ask?
I'd take the money and leave.
Is that all?
Aren't you supposed
to throw the check in my face?
Why is he making things worse?
No.
Have you been watching too many dramas?
- Who'd turn down money?
- Trust your dad.
Besides,
my name even contains "Qian."
Wrong question.
Here, let me ask another one.
Money or my son,
which do you love?
Why don't you phrase it differently?
If money and your son
both fell into a river,
what should I save first?
That works.
Right, who would you save?
I'd save the money.
Then what about my son?
No need to worry about your son.
He's an excellent swimmer.
He said his dad taught him personally
when he was little.
You even know that?
He's laughing.
My dad laughed.
That means he's happy.
He's happy.
Normally, I'd be sure,
but this time, after all...
What do you mean?
Ms. Qian.
Yes?
I know you're upset with Yifei.
I completely understand that.
Let me put it this way.
I actually approved of Yifei hiding
the fact that he's my son.
That's why
you didn't mention
a word about it either
when I was handling Qiansheng Group.
That's right.
My thinking was simple.
I was worried.
I worried that if people knew
he was my son,
their interactions
and intentions
wouldn't be so genuine.
Secondly, I'm still worried.
I'm worried that he'd use my name
to get ahead in society.
He wouldn't see the world as it is.
He wouldn't get real tempering.
What worried me most was
that he wouldn't find
someone who truly loves him.
This is also the best protection
I can give him right now.
You're a good father.
I do my best.
Have some tea.
Why'd it go quiet?
It really went quiet.
No, I need to check.
Dad.
Where did they go?
Qian Fei.
Qian Fei, wait.
Well, I...
I...
Don't listen to my dad.
Why are you standing here?
You're not going back?
Of course.
Let's go.
During the time we lived together,
I often felt
like I was an uninvited guest
who suddenly barged into your world.
I was afraid you'd kick me out.
I just didn't want to ruin
this steady happiness.
Do you know, Qian Fei?
From the day
I was born,
I've carried a label.
Li Qiansheng's son.
To others, that label
is dazzling
and full of prestige.
But to me,
it's always felt like shackles.
That's why ever since I was little,
I've kept working hard.
I wanted to prove to everyone
that even without my dad,
I could do just as well,
or even better than him.
But after I met you,
I suddenly realized
there are things
more meaningful than proving yourself.
Even if it's just
being with the person you love
and simply sharing
a plate of stir-fried eggplant,
you can be very happy.
Thank you, Qian Fei.
What's wrong?
You...
After all that buildup
and acting pitiful,
it turns out
you just wanted stir-fried eggplant.
That's why I say you get me.
I'm telling you,
you'd better behave.
I'm not forgetting this.
Listen up.
One day I might do something big,
something I'll keep from you,
without telling you at all.
Watch out.
I'll make you taste how it feels, too.
Yes, ma'am.
But I...
I still have one thing
I haven't told you.
What is it?
What other bombshell is waiting for me?
I...
I really...
What is it?
I really missed you so much.
I missed you so much.
So everyone in the neighborhood
must pay attention.
Try not to pile up clutter
outside your homes.
When the weather is dry,
it's very easy to cause a fire.
And children at home
must be careful when using electricity.
Don't play with outlets.
Don't do things
like sticking chopsticks into sockets.
That's dangerous behavior.
How much stock is left for Link 1?
Link 1? Let me check.
Only 3 orders left on Link 1, Madam.
Here's the deal today.
If you buy one box,
it's 69 yuan.
Buy five boxes and get one free.
I'll make that decision.
No.
Alright, three.
Three.
- Three, two, one.
Start grabbing.
Sold out.
(Obstetrics and Gynecology
Education Guide)
(Congratulations to Fulaxida Co., Ltd.
on its successful IPO.)
I've already canceled
my sponsor representative license.
I'm ready to embark on a new journey.
Countdown.
10, 9, 8, 7,
6, 5, 4, 3,
2, 1.
Qian Fei.
(Congratulations to Fulaxida Co., Ltd.
on its successful IPO.)
(Fulaxida SSE Listing
Celebration Banquet)
(Registration)
Here, let me toast you.
A toast to you.
No.
I'm toasting you.
Because I want to thank you.
Ever since Yifei
started living with you...
What do you mean living with me?
We're roommates.
Same thing to me.
Alright.
Ever since Yifei became your roommate,
I've noticed he's changed a lot.
Like what?
I...
watched him grow up.
I know him very well.
Selfish.
Spoiled.
Lazy.
Never considerate of others.
Always had his head in the clouds,
not knowing what he wanted.
Right?
But look at him now.
He's learned to see things
from others' perspectives
and think of others.
He's learned
to keep his feet on the ground.
And his vision has grown broader.
Why do you think that is?
Why?
It must be because of you.
Only you could've shaped him like this.
Seeing Yifei become who he is today,
I'm truly happy.
I think
I can finally trust him
to a girl who can make him better.
What's more, this girl is so smart
and knows how to run a household.
She even managed to sell a house
to my son.
After hearing what you said earlier,
I thought you were
a stern but warm-hearted gentleman.
But that last line
sounded like I took advantage of him.
Let me tell you this.
Even if you forced your son on me,
I might not even want him.
Now that's a problem?
♪There's no need to know
the ending from the start♪
♪Let the melody
play through the chords with the wind♪
♪There's no need
to keep every promise from the past♪
♪Leave some surprises
for the unknown in life♪
♪There's no need to judge the present
by fragments of the past♪
♪After all, a little disappointment
is what gives birth to poetry♪
♪There's no need to lose heart
over what once was♪
♪It takes a little courage
to be worthy of praise♪
♪I'll send you into the wide world♪
♪To live with passion
and become who you truly are♪
♪A quiet shoulder♪
♪Like a harbor
waiting for your wandering soul♪
♪I'll wait for the day
you return to a simpler life♪
♪The lights of home warm the night♪
♪A companionship that lasts forever♪
♪Shining brightly
like the stars and the moon on high♪
♪There's no need
to force things between two people♪
(Li Yifei, will you marry me?)
♪Yet still find you there for me♪
♪There's no need
to dwell on right or wrong, nor fear♪
♪A hug
means more than countless apologies♪
♪I'll send you into the wide world♪
♪To live with passion
and become who you truly are♪
♪A quiet shoulder♪
♪Like a harbor
waiting for your wandering soul♪
♪I'll wait for the day
you return to a simpler life♪
♪The lights of home warm the night♪
♪A companionship that lasts forever♪
♪Shining brightly
like the stars and the moon on high♪
♪I'll send you into the wide world♪
♪To live with passion
and become who you truly are♪
♪A quiet shoulder♪
♪Like a harbor
waiting for your wandering soul♪
♪I'll wait for the day
you return to a simpler life♪
♪The lights of home warm the night♪
♪A companionship that lasts forever♪
Landlady.
I'm hungry.
♪Whenever I look up♪
♪I meet your gaze, those eyes♪
♪I wish to hold on to that light of joy♪
♪And embrace that fleeting happiness♪
♪Sometimes we cry, sometimes we laugh♪
♪Sometimes
we're swept away by sweetness♪
♪Sometimes we run. Sometimes we fall♪
♪Sometimes I feel
having you is the best♪
♪I've never loved anyone
like I love you♪
I'm telling you,
this place you rented...
- Why is it you again?
♪I've never been cherished
the way you cherish me♪
- You again?
♪I've never met
a sea as brilliant as you♪
♪Every minute is so colorful♪
♪I've never known
a love as warm as yours♪
♪Nothing more needs to be said,
I won't let go of you♪
♪Sometimes we cry♪
Here, take it.
Didn't you say you'd help me?
Stop drinking.
Rock, paper, scissors.
♪Sometimes we run. Sometimes we fall♪
♪Sometimes I feel
having you is the best♪
♪I've never met
a sea as brilliant as you♪
♪Every minute is so colorful♪
♪I've never known
a love as warm as yours♪
♪Nothing more needs to be said,
I won't let go of you♪
Qian Fei.
I'm hungry.
All you think about is food.
♪There's no need
to know the ending from the start♪
♪Let the melody play through the chords
with the wind♪
♪There's no need
to keep every promise from the past♪
♪Leave some surprises
for the unknown in life♪
♪There's no need
to force things between two people♪
♪Perhaps I'll feel alone,
yet still find you there for me♪
♪There's no need
to dwell on right or wrong, nor fear♪
♪A hug means more
than countless apologies♪
♪I'll send you into the wide world♪
♪To live with passion
and become who you truly are♪
♪A quiet shoulder♪
♪Like a harbor waiting
for your wandering soul♪
♪I'll wait for the day
you return to a simpler life♪
♪The lights of home warm the night♪
♪A companionship that lasts forever♪
♪Shining brightly
like the stars and the moon on high♪
♪I'll send you into the wide world♪
♪To live with passion
and become who you truly are♪
♪A quiet shoulder♪
♪Like a harbor waiting
for your wandering soul♪
♪I'll wait for the day
you return to a simpler life♪
♪The lights of home warm the night♪
♪A companionship that lasts forever♪
♪Shining brightly
like the stars and the moon on high♪