♪Hey, you, you, you,
why is it you again?♪
♪Always stumbling upon
my little secrets♪
♪Falling on my brows, my lashes,
even the strands by my mouth♪
♪Like my favorite kitten
on a rainy spring afternoon♪
♪Hey, you, you, you,
why is it you again?♪
♪You effortlessly awaken
my protective instincts♪
♪Hitting all my little thoughts,
my doubts, and my temper♪
♪Like my favorite beer and fried chicken
in autumn, or spicy boiled fish in winter♪
♪Why is it you again?
That sweet way you speak♪
♪As if the whole world knows
my mind is full of you♪
♪Why is it still you?
That secret smile behind your cool facade♪
♪I might as well play along.
Let me protect you♪
♪Why is it always you?
The smile at the corner of your lips♪
♪Before I knew it, the words blurted out,
"I like you. I only like you."♪
=Love Has Fireworks=
(Based on "Investment Men and Women"
by Hong Er on Jinjiang Literature City)
=Episode 35=
Isn't she the assistant to Mr. Niu,
the supplier for Shanlifang?
She's not just Mr. Niu's assistant.
She's Mr. Niu's wife now.
She spends her days
sitting on a pile of money.
She's always wanted to build a career,
but she doesn't have any ideas.
So I think
with your abilities
and her financial resources,
you two could create some sparks.
Since she's so rich now,
why don't you get her
to invest in Fulaxida?
To be honest, she's my ex.
And I'm not single anymore.
I don't think
it's appropriate
to stay in touch with her.
My girlfriend might not like it.
Your girlfriend
is Qian Fei, right?
Yes, she's my girlfriend.
You're a good man.
I don't think
she said that to compliment you.
Are you jealous?
If it were someone else,
I'd have no reason to be jealous.
Alright. I understand.
Got it.
But honestly,
Liao Shiyu isn't interested in me.
She only said that because
seeing how I treated you
reminded her
of what she had with Wang Ruohai.
When they were together,
I had nothing to do with him.
I only visited his mom
because I cared about her,
not because of him.
I didn't say anything.
Why are you explaining yourself?
I'm just stating the facts.
Alright. Let's drop it.
I'm taking you somewhere.
You live here now?
Are you renting it, or did you buy it?
I'm renting it.
You make a bit of money,
and you start wasting it.
Have you forgotten our three rules?
I'm kidding. I haven't.
I don't go to social events
and private parties anymore.
I've sworn them all off.
Please come in.
What do you think?
Let's take a look around here first.
Jeez.
Why won't you save your money
instead of renting a place this big?
If you save for another year or so,
you'd be able to buy a place.
You're right.
So, how about letting me
move back in with you?
You see, if I rent your place,
I can help with your mortgage
and save money myself.
Isn't that good?
It's not a bad idea.
I'll think about it.
Do you know
why I brought you here today?
What?
What are you thinking?
It's exactly what you're thinking.
♪I really miss you so much,
miss you so much♪
♪My heart is pounding loud♪
♪Matching my breathing♪
♪Tuning into the frequency
of missing you♪
♪Love you so much♪
♪You are the only one in the world♪
♪Living in my heart♪
♪Even the stars see through
the tenderness of the night♪
♪Sprinkled across the city streets♪
♪The evening breeze blows through
every window again♪
♪Sneaking a peek
at the little universe they share♪
♪A chance encounter stirs
the heart that has been lazily waiting♪
♪My heart ignites the fireworks of love♪
♪Falling in love with you
without permission♪
♪I began to doodle
in this romantic sketchbook♪
♪I really miss you so much,
miss you so much♪
♪My heart is pounding loud♪
♪Matching my breathing♪
♪Tuning into the frequency
of missing you♪
♪Love you so much♪
♪You are the only one in the world♪
♪Living in my heart♪
Not used to dressing like this?
Is it obvious?
You look beautiful.
There's something I want to ask you.
What is it?
Never mind.
Let's go.
If Jun gets married this year
and they have a baby,
I'll be a grandma
in no time.
I'm so happy.
Mrs. Jun.
Welcome!
Come. Let me introduce everyone.
Come.
This is Eldest Aunt.
You're so pretty.
Isn't she?
This red packet is for you.
Take it.
You have to take it.
Let me introduce.
Uncle.
Here's another one.
It's a small gesture.
You have to take it.
Thank you, Uncle.
This is Youngest Aunt.
Hello, Youngest Aunt.
Yu, you're so pretty.
This is Second Aunt.
Hello, Second Aunt.
Red packet.
Thank you, Second Aunt.
Honey, what are you waiting for?
Where's the red packet?
Come.
Look.
This is from us.
Take it.
Thank you, Mrs. Jun.
It's a small gesture from Dad and Mom.
Take it.
Thank you, Mr. and Mrs. Jun.
What's wrong with you?
Don't they look good?
They do, right?
They make a great couple.
Hurry up.
Sit down.
Have a seat.
Come and sit.
Where's your car?
Just bought it.
No one's sat in the queen's seat.
Please.
From now on,
I won't buy things on a whim anymore.
I'll leave my money
with you.
Okay?
No!
I'm starting to wonder
if you have any money left.
I'm broke.
I don't know
how I'm paying next month's rent.
How about you support me?
You're so hopeless.
Do you have a hole in your pocket?
You can't hold on to money.
You'll spend yourself broke.
In that case,
to save money,
I suggest
that I move back in with you sooner.
Then I'll have my dad check the calendar
and pick
an auspicious day.
Great. I like that idea.
We have to pick a good day.
I'll just relax at the villa
and wait for your dad to set the date.
Then I'll march
right back in.
Should we get a fortune teller
to check our natal charts?
Keep your eyes on the road.
March right back in?
You really think it's your home?
Mr. Li,
this is the final investment agreement.
Please take a look.
Alright.
Mr. Zhang.
Why are you being so sneaky?
You made me wait here
when we could've come up together
from the parking garage.
Have you forgotten our three rules?
There you go again.
Things are different now. Sit tight.
Let me ask you.
We're close enough now, aren't we?
Why can't people know about us?
What am I to you,
really?
Office romances are a bad idea,
don't you know that?
We may not work at the same company,
but we're on the same project.
I don't want it to affect our work.
Besides, I heard
you had two ladies from your company
sitting on either side of you
during the company dinner last week.
Don't think I don't know.
What's that got to do with me?
They insisted on sitting there.
I couldn't stop them.
I practically hid outside the room.
Nothing happened. Seriously. Trust me.
If you don't, ask Lu Ze.
Trust me.
My standards
are pretty unique now.
Other than a tough landlady like you,
I don't have eyes for anyone else.
Those delicate
and clingy girls at my office
are not my type.
I don't like them.
Fine. I'll verify that myself.
Then, once I become even better,
I'll finally make it official.
How much better do you plan to get?
I want to be as good as you.
You're capable and handsome.
Too eye-catching.
Hold on.
What did you just say?
Repeat that again.
I said
you're too handsome
and too capable.
That's eye-catching.
That's why you won't make us official?
You may not be intelligent,
but you've got
a good judgment of people.
Seriously, though,
after everything
I've been through this past year,
I've realized something.
Looks may attract
a man at first,
but sooner or later,
they'll get used to them.
Only if you become strong enough
to stand on your own,
if one day we go our separate ways,
I won't have anything to fear.
A truly capable woman
will never lack admirers.
So you're already
leaving yourself a way out, huh?
I don't care.
I just want to become better.
As good as you.
Alright. Keep improving.
I won't stop you.
But let me make one thing clear.
If one day you become
too good for me,
or you still won't make us official,
just wait.
I'll tell the whole world.
I'll expose you online.
Haven't you already announced
enough things to the world?
Have I?
Who's texting you?
(Wang Ruohai: Fei, my mom's illness got
worse. She needs a kidney transplant.)
(I need a lot of money.
Can you help me?)
Uh, a colleague needs me
to review some documents.
Really?
Alright. I'll drive faster.
This apartment was
only lived in for a year.
It's basically a brand-new place.
And it's the most basic floor plan.
In the secondhand housing market now,
properties like yours
are the most sought-after.
I'm sure it will sell
within a week.
- I'll leave it to you then.
- Stop!
It's okay.
You...
Qian Fei, have you lost your mind?
Wang Ruohai's mom
needs a kidney transplant.
Why are you
selling the apartment for him?
Answer me. I'm really upset right now.
Li Yifei,
this is my house.
Whether I rent it or sell it
is my decision.
But...
I'm your boyfriend.
Don't I get a say?
You...
We haven't made it official yet.
What do you mean by that, Qian Fei?
I've given you my whole heart.
You said you didn't want people
to know our relationship. Fine.
But this place holds our memories.
Are you ready to let it go?
Did you ever think about how I'd feel?
When I was out of work,
Wang Ruohai helped me.
Now it's my turn to help him.
Alright.
Then don't sell the apartment.
I'll lend him money.
Seriously?
Why don't you understand?
You're so stubborn.
You're the one being stubborn.
You're being unreasonable.
No.
We're not selling it.
Stop putting it back.
Who would've thought the one who'd
end up helping Wang Ruohai the most
would be you, his ex-girlfriend?
Don't bring it up.
So, how did Li Yifei take it?
Don't even ask.
We had a huge fight over it.
He was really mad.
See?
He was jealous.
You'd just started dating,
and then you sold your apartment
to help your ex.
To everyone else,
it looked like a noble thing to do.
But from Li Yifei's perspective,
of course, he'd be upset.
But the way I saw it,
I just wanted to repay
what I owed Wang Ruohai.
After that, we'd be done
with each other.
You'd better be careful.
You might end up repaying one ex
and turning your current boyfriend
into another.
Don't jinx it.
You have way too many clothes.
I know.
You're using your own money
to help your girlfriend's ex?
You two really are made for each other.
Of course.
The woman I chose
is a perfect match.
Li Yifei, did you come here to complain
or to show off?
If that's all, I'm heading out.
Dang Yu's waiting for me.
Hey.
Help me figure this out.
Do you think she helped Wang Ruohai
because she still has feelings for him?
I think
you should change your surname to Lin.
Next time you two fight, bury some flowers.
[*Referencing Lin Daiyu, the sentimental]
[heroine from Dream of the Red Chamber]
This isn't the time for jokes.
Young Master Li.
Qian Fei has no feelings at all
for her ex.
She just wanted to repay
when she owed him,
so she could draw a clean line
once and for all.
How do you know?
How do I know?
Dang Yu told me.
She really said that?
Right. Selling the apartment
to repay what she owed him.
Why didn't I think of that?
I was so angry
I couldn't think straight.
Stop drinking.
Please keep it for me.
I'm going.
Alright.
Hello, Qi?
Can you do me a favor?
Come.
Since Li Yifei is guaranteeing the loan,
we can take our time
with the paperwork.
I know you need the money urgently,
so I'll transfer the funds first.
Thank you so much.
You did me a huge favor.
Now that everything's signed,
we'll just follow the normal process.
I'm not going anywhere.
I trust you.
Actually, I have one more favor to ask.
Go ahead.
Could I stay a few more days?
I really need the money,
and I haven't found
a suitable place yet.
That's not up to me.
You'll have to ask the new landlord.
I rented the apartment out.
How do I get in touch
with the new landlord?
Funny how things change.
Now I'm the landlord.
There are so many boxes.
What do I do?
Let's see.
If I move this here,
it doesn't seem right.
If I put it in that room,
it doesn't seem right either.
If I open it
and pile everything on the floor,
it's worse.
What now?
This is hard.
Moving is the worst.
Meanwhile, someone over there
hasn't lifted a finger.
I'll move them
into the master bedroom?
What's wrong with you?
All you've done is sit here eating.
You didn't ask if I was hungry.
Are you hungry?
Yes.
Too bad. It's all gone.
Fine.
Let me ask you something.
Look,
there are so many boxes here.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
So many of them.
How are we supposed
to sort all this out?
How did you do it
when you moved into the villa?
Do it the same way.
I hired movers.
Hire them again.
I've got you now.
Why would I need to hire movers?
In your dreams!
Tenant.
What kind of tenant
just sits there
while the landlord does all the moving?
Does that seem right?
Absolutely not.
I'm the landlord now.
You're the tenant.
Shouldn't you behave like
you're living in someone else's place?
Aren't you worried
I'll kick you out?
When I was the landlady,
that's how you acted as my tenant.
I'm following your example.
I should've seen that coming.
So this is how
you're getting back at me.
Fine.
When you were the landlady,
you slept in that room.
Now that I'm the landlord,
I'm taking it.
Clear your stuff out
and move it in here.
I'm sleeping in that room.
Hurry up.
Come on. Get moving.
Get in there and start packing.
Once you're done,
I can move my stuff in.
Come on. Get moving.
I promised I'd help.
Come on. Move this box over there.
Clear some space here.
♪Hey, you, you, you,
why is it you again?♪
Once you're done,
don't throw away the boxes.
Flatten them and stack them over there.
We can use them next time.
Take the clothes out. Hang up
the ones you don't usually wear.
Put the dirty ones aside.
Hey, has this blanket been washed
or not?
No idea.
Right. Hang those hangers up, too.
Sort your winter and summer clothes.
These are dirty.
Throw them in the washer.
Pile them on the bed.
Put them on the bed.
I'll wash them later.
♪My doubts, and my temper♪
What's next?
Put the books
on the shelf.
♪Or spicy boiled fish in winter♪
I just moved it over here.
Hurry up.
♪That sweet way you speak♪
♪As if the whole world knows
my mind is full of you♪
♪Why is it still you? That secret
smile behind your cool facade♪
♪I might as well play along.
Let me protect you♪
♪Why is it always you?
The smile at the corner of your lips♪
♪Before I knew it,
the words blurted out♪
♪I like you. I only like you♪
Finally got everything
sorted out for you.
Not bad.
Hang on.
Something doesn't look right.
It's fine.
The place looks great.
Don't set the bar so high for yourself.
You call this helping me?
I did everything myself.
Ever since you became the landlord,
you've grown up so fast.
You're almost a functioning adult now.
Good for you.
If my dad saw me
working this hard,
he'd probably
wake up crying.
Give me a break.
I need to put my feet up.
I just realized something.
Since I met you,
my taste
in clothes
has gotten
a lot more down-to-earth.
Were you sleeping in silk pajamas?
Exactly.
But look at me now.
I'm wearing
a bargain white T-shirt
and these shorts.
I've never felt so free,
so happy, and so comfortable.
I'm finally back!
My bathroom.
My kitchen.
My dining table.
My TV.
My couch.
And...
my beauty.
I missed you terribly.
Get off.
Do your job as a landlord properly.
Stop all that nonsense.
Look. You're smiling now.
You have no idea.
I've been trying to cheer you up.
Alright. I know.
You helped
Wang Ruohai
because you wanted
to make a clean break.
I understand.
I was being petty.
You were just being silly.
Qi transferred
all the money over.
I asked her to.
I told her you needed the money.
See?
I got it done.
If you want to thank me,
does that mean
you should become my girl?
Are you my girl?
Well,
you're really something else.
Things everyone else
thinks are impossible,
you always find a way.
You've done so much for me.
I know that.
You've spent so much time helping me,
but you never said a word.
Then you casually go,
"It's taken care of.
Can you be my girl now?"
Thank you.
Without you,
I don't know what I'd have done.
Silly.
So, have you decided?
Are you going to be mine
or be mine,
or be mine, or be mine, or be mine?
You're annoying.
(Light up every star.
We're all the light chaser.)
(Qian Fei)
(Pretentious Li)
Fei!
Let me see. Have you lost weight?
No.
Come on. Sit down.
The three of us all live in Shanghai,
yet somehow we're
meeting up out of town.
You're to blame.
You've been spending all your
free time following Mr. Lu around.
I haven't settled
the score with you yet.
You stole my girl.
The moment I found out
you were coming to Xining
and our trips overlapped,
I booked this place.
The best barbecue in Xining.
To show my sincerity,
you get to decide
our food tonight.
Good. Leave your wallet.
You can go.
Off you go.
Hey, honey.
Why are you siding with her?
Oh my.
You two are the only people
I let treat me like this.
Have you ordered?
Not yet. We were waiting for you.
We were waiting for you.
- Excuse me.
We're ready to order.
(Posting...)
(Qian Fei)
(Had a great dinner tonight
with my bestie. Happy)
(Post)
(A huge thanks to Mr. Lu
for generously treating us.)
(Pretentious Li)
Hello? Can you hear me?
Yes.
What's that?
How come everyone else gets to see you,
but your boyfriend doesn't?
Where are you headed next?
Flying to Guiyang tomorrow morning.
I'll get there around noon.
I've only got one meeting
in the afternoon.
Then I'm flying
to Yinchuan the next day.
I heard Guiyang's sour fish soup
is amazing.
I really want to try it.
Is food
all you ever think about?
No.
For example?
You.
What?
Me?
So you miss me?
Well, well.
My patience finally paid off.
Come on. I just said it
in the heat of the moment.
Don't read too much into it.
Keep that up,
even a psych ward
won't be able to help you.
Oh, come on.
You missed me.
You're just too stubborn to admit it.
Take a page out of my book.
I'm not shy about saying it.
So here it is.
Qian Fei, I miss you.
I miss you, too.
What are you doing tomorrow?
I have meetings
tomorrow.
Miss, we've landed.
Thank you.
Let me help you.
You're welcome.
(International/Hong Kong, China;
Macau, China; Taiwan, China)
Small world. We met again.
Yeah.
What do you do?
You must be working really hard.
I'm a venture capitalist.
Not many women go into venture capital.
Are you based in Guiyang?
No. I'm here on business.
I work in Shanghai.
What a coincidence.
My company's based in Shanghai too.
Here's my card.
Yingxing Outdoor?
You listed on the STAR Market last year.
You really are in the finance industry.
You know your stuff.
What a small world, Mr. Meng.
Li.
Is she your girlfriend?
Pretty obvious.
Isn't it?
She's young, successful,
and beautiful.
You're a lucky man.
I'm here on business.
My driver's waiting outside,
so I won't keep you.
Alright.
Once we're back in Shanghai,
let me take you two out for dinner.
Sounds good.
Bye.
What are you doing here?
Didn't you say you were tied up
with a project in Shanghai?
Well done, you.
You've cast a wide net indeed.
Do you know how old he is?
He's almost sixty.
What are you talking about? What net?
He was the one who came up to me.
Good thing I came over.
Or how much trouble that bad luck
with men would've gotten you into.
It's a small world.
How do you know him?
I handled his company's IPO.
Of course I know him.
I'm telling you,
don't let that gentlemanly look
fool you.
He's a flirt.
Once he sets his sights on a woman,
she doesn't stand a chance.
Good thing I showed up today.
Otherwise, he would've
made a move on you.
You used to be so sensible.
How did you become such a handful?
I'm wondering, too.
Why do I keep attracting
middle-aged men?
Where have all the young guys gone?
Maybe the older ones have bad eyesight.
What about you?
Why are you stuck on me?
Me?
Guess my eyesight gave out early.
Hey, you!
So why are you here?
I'm here for work.
When you're done,
come to Da'ai Sour Fish Soup
on East Street.
Got it?
Stop paying attention
to those middle-aged guys.
You did a great job.
You have a good prospect.
Not at all. You flatter me.
It's because you prepared
everything so well.
So today's meeting went so smoothly.
Your team is excellent.
I've got a lot to learn.
We look forward to working
with Xinzouqi Capital.
I hope we'll have more opportunities
to work together.
Absolutely. See you next time.
(Vacant, Available)
I've been waiting for you for ages.
Everything's here.
They're all local specialties.
And your favorite sour fish soup.
Do you like it?
Look. I ordered everything for you.
Come. Sit.
It smells so great.
Do you like them?
Try a little of everything.
I'll get you some soup.
Okay.
Drink it while it's hot.
This is the famous local chicken soup.
Here you go.
How is it?
It smells so good.
Have you eaten? Try this.
Delicious.
And the crispy pork shred.
You have to try it. Here.
What else do you want?
Is it good?
So spicy. So good.
I love watching you eat.
Try everything.
You eat, too.
I am.
So good.
Sour, spicy, and sweet.
Try this.
I said try everything,
not finish everything.
You're going to eat yourself sick.
Aren't you worried
I'll go find another girl?
Life is precious.
Good food is even more precious.
When there's good food,
you and your girls don't stand a chance.
What do you mean?
How can you abandon me
just like that?
Fine.
If I'm not important to you,
spit out everything
you just ate.
I can't.
How about this?
Why don't you
compliment yourself a little?
Maybe then
I'll throw up everything I ate.
What?
Can't handle a little honesty?
Go ahead. Eat up.
Forget the girls. You'll do.
I'll settle for you.
Good. Not a single bite went to waste.
I'm impressed.
Are you done with everything
you came to Guiyang for?
Yes.
When are you heading back to Shanghai?
I'm going to Yinchuan with you.
Why? Have you got nothing better to do?
Tomorrow's Friday.
After you're done
visiting the companies,
we'll stay there for a couple of days.
What about your work in Shanghai?
What about Zhizhong
and Fulaxida?
I'm ignoring all of it.
As if.
The company is very happy
with your performance so far.
After you visit the remaining clients
in Yinchuan and Taiyuan,
head straight back to Shanghai.
We'll have the rest of the team
cover the clients in the southeast.
Come back and get some rest.
You've done enough
going to over twenty cities.
Thank you, boss. I really appreciate it.
See you in Shanghai.
Li Yifei!
I'm going back to Shanghai!
What? I can't hear you.
I finally get to go home!
Ma Li?
Hello, Ma Li?
Qian Fei?
Why are you answering Yifei's phone?
He's taking a shower.
Tell him to get back here.
The company's waiting for him
to chair a meeting.
He only took two days off.
He has to be there
for tomorrow afternoon's meeting.
Alright.
Li Yifei!
What's wrong?
What is this?
You skipped work to come to see me?
How did you know?
I already booked your ticket.
Go change.
The driver's on the way.
Are you serious?
I worked half the night
just so I could see you today.
I just got
out of the shower
and was about to lie down.
=Love Has Fireworks=
(Next Episode Preview)
I can't let you pay for me.
How much is it?
Any friend of Mr. Li Jr.
is on the house.
Mr. Li Jr.?
Yeah.
Li Yifei from Qiansheng Group.
Ms. Qian,
let's be honest with each other.
To tell you the truth,
if my son weren't so stubborn,
I would never have agreed
to him dating someone
from a family like yours.
♪There's no need
to know the ending from the start♪
♪Let the melody play through the chords
with the wind♪
♪There's no need
to keep every promise from the past♪
♪Leave some surprises
for the unknown in life♪
♪There's no need
to force things between two people♪
♪Perhaps I'll feel alone,
yet still find you there for me♪
♪There's no need
to dwell on right or wrong, nor fear♪
♪A hug means more
than countless apologies♪
♪I'll send you into the wide world♪
♪To live with passion
and become who you truly are♪
♪A quiet shoulder♪
♪Like a harbor waiting
for your wandering soul♪
♪I'll wait for the day
you return to a simpler life♪
♪The lights of home warm the night♪
♪A companionship that lasts forever♪
♪Shining brightly
like the stars and the moon on high♪
♪I'll send you into the wide world♪
♪To live with passion
and become who you truly are♪
♪A quiet shoulder♪
♪Like a harbor waiting
for your wandering soul♪
♪I'll wait for the day
you return to a simpler life♪
♪The lights of home warm the night♪
♪A companionship that lasts forever♪
♪Shining brightly
like the stars and the moon on high♪