[ominous music]
[grunts]
May this charm protect,
guard, and keep an eye on my family.
[ominous music fades]
[pensive music playing]
[chuckles]
You look so serious.
You're always studying laws.
No wonder you're single.
[exclaims] That's not funny!
Your brother has never been funny.
His jokes are outdated.
Really?
Hey, it's a sin…
- [chuckles]
- …to badmouth your husband.
Joking without being funny
is an even bigger sin.
- Really? [giggles]
- [whines] It hurts!
Cut it out!
You and Rani remind me
of how Mom and Dad used to be.
Jealous?
You should get a boyfriend.
[groans]
[exhales]
Instead of interning at a law office,
why don't you come with me
and help run Dad's business
at the sugarcane field?
Forget internship, you'll get a paycheck.
Isn't all that law school wasted
if I'm just managing sugarcane?
Your brother just doesn't want
to be away from you.
Right?
You always act like you don't care.
[hums] Don't get carried away.
[door slams]
[door thuds]
Andi.
[chair scraping]
[ominous music]
[whispers] Five. Odd.
What's with odd numbers?
She believes an even number of spots
on the cloth
means danger is coming.
[chair scraping]
Dina, let's have breakfast.
Take a break from work.
Here.
It's been eight years.
Why are you still doing this?
Yeah. We're fine so far.
It's okay. Just in case.
[water pouring]
Mom.
Mom…
Mom, you've got me.
Now, I'll take Dad's place
to look after our family.
Let's eat. You don't want to be late.
Have some before it gets cold, Mom.
You…
Lately, you look like
you've gained weight.
Are you pregnant?
She's been snacking a lot.
Yesterday, she had an entire martabak.
That's why she gained weight.
- [Andi chuckles]
- [Rani chuckles awkwardly]
Don't hurry to have a baby.
Is it a problem, Mom?
[poignant music]
[hisses sharply]
Mom, I'm off.
- Take care.
- Bye.
- Mom, I'm off to work.
- Okay.
- Don't forget your lunch.
- Yes, Mom. Bye.
- Bye.
- Peace be upon you.
[both] And upon you peace.
[Dina] Bye.
Drive safe.
[car doors open, shut]
[car starts]
Um…
I'll be inside.
[worker] We've managed to deal with
the wild grass that was harming
the sugarcane.
Glad to hear that, Seno.
Indeed.
Our previous harvest had
a five percent decline in quality.
Really?
[Ki Rojo] What's the problem, Sri?
Nothing strange has happened, right?
As long as you keep the charm safe,
nothing can enter your home.
There haven't been any problems, Ki.
Then why are you here?
I'm not sure.
But I feel uneasy, Ki.
It feels like something
is keeping me on edge.
Usually, the things that make us anxious
don't come from without.
What… do you mean, Ki?
Think about it.
Are you sure it's really over?
[foreboding music]
[ominous whispers]
[fire crackling]
[distant screams]
Sir! What's going on here?
I don't know. Our fields caught fire.
Go get some water! Hurry!
[men] Water!
Water!
Hurry!
- [intense music]
- [workers shouting]
[coughing]
[music crescendos then stops]
[glass shatters]
What's the matter?
[hesitates]
I was cleaning the table
when the photo frame fell by itself.
[ominous music]
I'll take care of it.
[phone whirring]
[whirring]
Mom.
Grandma and Grandpa's landline
might be down.
It'll take some time to fix.
The food's ready. Let's eat.
No. I have a bad feeling about this.
Mom, can't you stop?
A fallen photo isn't always a bad sign.
We're tired of watching you act like this.
[Andi] Mom.
We all want to live in peace.
Without fear or worry…
[loud thud]
[sighs]
Mom.
[door opens]
[door slams]
[sighs]
[pensive music]
Mom.
I made you ginger tea.
God willing,
Grandma and Grandpa will be okay.
Make sure to drink it, Mom.
[door shuts]
[sighs]
[gate rattles]
[knocking]
Dad?
Mom?
Dad, Mom?
[foreboding music]
[loud thud]
[door creaking]
Mom?
Dad?
[Grandpa, shakily] Sri.
Mom.
[music crescendos]
[creaking]
[eerie whispers]
[gasps]
Sri.
[whines]
Dad.
[yelps]
[panting]
HOSPITAL
[doctor] Your pregnancy is two months in.
Thank God,
the baby's heart rate is healthy.
Praise be to God.
Is it a boy or a girl?
We don't know the gender yet,
but the baby is healthy.
[tender music]
This is the perfect time to tell Mom.
She'll be so happy.
- Oh my.
- [chuckles]
[music turns ominous]
Dear?
What's wrong?
Peace be upon you.
Peace be upon you, Mom.
- And upon you peace.
- We have good news…
What's wrong?
Save it for later, okay?
Grandpa called earlier.
He said Grandma is sick.
They need us there.
I've notified my office
about a family emergency.
So Mom's intuition was right?
[somber music]
Mom, I'm sorry for my words last night.
It's all right.
I understand.
Sorry for making you all uncomfortable.
I'll try my best not to worry you.
Hey, dear.
We've got a long way to go.
You can sleep if you're tired.
[eerie whispers]
[foreboding music]
Thanks.
Hey.
Grandpa!
- Grandpa!
- Come in.
[Grandpa grunts]
- Hi, Grandpa.
- Grandma.
- Put the bags in the room.
- Okay.
- Hi, Grandpa.
- Hi.
Let's have a meal after this.
- Grandma has prepared everything.
- Grandma.
Sri.
Come in.
I'm sure you've missed Grandma's cooking.
We're going to our rooms.
- Okay.
- Come on.
[Andi] Come on.
Mom.
Are you sick?
You look so pale.
I'm okay, Sri.
That's how your mom is.
She doesn't want you to worry.
It's just your dad overreacting.
Okay, but…
if you're sick, don't try to hide it.
Talk to me.
I just miss you,
the grandkids,
and Rani.
I'm sorry.
For not visiting more.
Don't be sad.
[poignant music]
I'll heat up the food.
Yes, Mom.
Sri.
I'm going to the shed.
Okay, Dad.
You should try Grandma's food.
[exclaims] They're the best.
Mom.
She forgot to turn on the stove.
I should have come here sooner.
You've missed Grandma's cooking, right?
Mom. Why don't you rest?
We'll make dinner.
Andi, take her to her room.
Yes, Mom.
Come on, Grandma.
Let's clean it up.
Throw it away and start from scratch.
You still do embroidery?
Embroidery?
Yeah.
Here you go.
You should rest, Grandma.
Who are you?
I'm Andi, your grandson.
[gagging]
[retches]
[retching]
Is she okay?
She got queasy.
Hurry, clean the fridge
and throw it all in the trash.
Why do they need this much meat anyway?
[sighs]
Let it all out.
[retches]
Go ahead.
[nearby cat meowing]
[meows] Kitty!
[cat continues meowing]
Kitty.
Come here.
[meows] Come here, kitty.
What's your name?
[cat growls]
[loud thud]
[strained meows]
[rattling sound]
Grandpa?
What are you doing? Can I come in?
[creaks]
No.
It's messy in here.
Okay.
[foreboding music]
Let's go inside. Get you something to eat.
You must be hungry.
Grandma, Grandpa, do you remember?
I used to play
hide-and-seek in this house.
[giggles]
Listen. It's a funny story.
One time…
Have some.
I hid in Grandma's wardrobe.
Everyone panicked looking for me
because I fell asleep inside.
[laughing]
He's always been a troublemaker.
That's naughty, dear.
- [laughing]
- Do you guys remember?
[foreboding music]
Grandma, Grandpa.
It's okay if you don't remember.
It's not important.
Finish your meals.
[music crescendos]
[music subsides]
[laughing]
[maniacal laugh]
[meows]
You know, I…
I want to bring Grandpa
and Grandma to live with us.
They need someone to look after them.
Yeah, Mom.
It'd be easier for us to care for them.
[cat yowling]
[ominous music]
[door creaks]
[crickets chirping]
[ominous music]
Grandma?
Grandma.
Where are you going?
Grandma!
[ominous music]
She's always sleepwalking like that.
It's okay. I'll take care of her.
[ominous music continues]
Kitty.
Looking for something?
My cat from yesterday.
Oh.
Kitty.
[suspenseful sting]
You're finally awake.
[gasps]
Yes. Sorry, Grandma. I overslept.
If you're tired, it's okay to sleep in.
[ominous music]
Mom. Have you seen my cat?
I can't find it anywhere. I'm sad.
It's only a cat, Dina.
It'll come back before you know it.
Oh, by the way,
can you get some rice from the store?
Dina, are you on your period?
No. Why?
It's nothing.
It must be Rani.
I'll get going.
Take care.
[solemn music]
What's on your mind?
Hm?
Let's go.
If you're ready, let's get going.
Where are you going with that axe, Dad?
I'm getting wood from the forest.
To fix the shed.
Some are rotting…
Andi will go with you.
No need.
I'll manage on my own.
You're not wearing shoes?
Dad!
Grandma.
We're heading out.
I want to show Rani around.
Be back for lunch, okay?
I want to cook for you.
Okay.
We'll be right back.
[foreboding music]
Grandpa!
Where are you going?
[foreboding music crescendos]
[groans]
[winces]
Grandpa?
[gentle music]
[Andi] When I was a kid,
every time I visited my grandparents…
[both chuckling]
Every time I visited them,
Dina and I often came here to play.
[soothing music]
Sit here.
Careful.
[exhales]
Andi.
[Andi] Mm?
You once told me
your father died because he was cursed
with black magic.
But you've never told me why.
Now that you're my wife,
you deserve to know what happened
in my family's and my past.
But promise me
that it won't change how you see
my family or me.
Hm?
Before she was married,
my mom had two friends,
Laila and Herman.
Herman later became my dad.
Both my mom and Laila secretly liked him.
Eventually, my dad chose Laila.
My mom loved my dad so much
that she used a shortcut to win him over.
With black magic.
[Andi] Turns out, Laila was pregnant.
She asked my mom to let Herman go,
but my mom refused.
My mom was already planning to marry him.
[faint eerie laughter]
Andi?
Twenty years later,
Laila returned with black magic
to get revenge on my family.
Dear? Dear!
[Andi] She killed my dad
with black magic.
My mom and sister almost died.
Luckily, I managed to save them.
And…
[faint eerie laughter]
What happened to Laila afterwards?
Laila and Hanum…
Who's Hanum?
Hanum…
[ominous music]
[Andi] She tricked my family
by pretending to love me.
But she was Laila's daughter
from my dad.
While trying to save my mom and sister,
I managed to stop Laila and Hanum,
and they burned to death.
[faint eerie laughter]
Let's go home.
Andi.
What is it?
[intense music]
[strikes flesh]
[ominous music]
[gasps]
[Grandma] Under the full moon,
the dead shall rise.
Under the full moon, the dead shall rise.
- Under the full moon, the dead shall rise.
- Mom?
What are you talking about?
Mom!
Mom…
What are you doing, Mom?
[ominous music]
[gasps]
I'm making lunch for everyone.
[Sri] What's wrong with your back?
Why didn't you say anything?
Does it hurt?
Forgive me, Mom.
I promise
I'll take good care of you and Dad.
I'll bring you to the doctor.
[somber music]
[clinking]
What are you doing here, Dina?
Why are you alone?
Let's go back.
[Dina] Mom.
Yes?
I feel like Grandma and Grandpa
are acting weird.
Don't you feel that too?
Do you know
the disease that affects
seniors' memories?
It can cause severe memory loss
and, in extreme cases,
it can make them
behave oddly.
Do things that don't make sense.
[sighs]
I think your grandparents have dementia.
Are you sure?
I don't think it's dementia.
Mom.
If this is just like what happened before,
what do we do?
Don't bring that up again.
I've had enough.
Andi.
Whatever happened in your past
won't change the way I see you.
[eerie chuckles]
Andi.
It's me.
Hanum.
What's wrong?
I'm okay.
[deep breaths]
[sighs]
[ominous music]
[Grandpa] Under…
Under the full moon, the dead shall rise.
[ominous music crescendos]
[Grandpa chanting] Under the full moon,
the dead shall rise.
[Grandpa chanting] Under
[Grandpa chanting] Under…
[thuds]
Under the full moon, the dead shall rise.
[Grandpa chanting] Under the full moon,
the dead shall rise.
Under the full moon,
Under the full moon, the dead shall rise.
[creaks]
[gasps]
Grandpa.
It's me, Dina.
[panting]
[knocking rapidly]
[knocking stops]
[gasps]
What's the matter?
Why are you up this late?
What are you looking for?
I was
getting some water.
[door slams shut]
[Grandma softly singing lullaby
in Javanese]
[gasping]
Listen to me, Mom.
It can't be dementia. Something's off.
The one I saw last night wasn't Grandpa.
Stop talking nonsense.
You're always the most sensitive and alert
about these things!
Why don't you trust me now?
What do you want?
You're the ones who said I overthink,
worry too much,
and tie everything to the supernatural,
making your lives uncomfortable.
Now I'm following your advice,
and you want me to go back the way I was.
I don't understand.
[heavy breathing]
I want to go home now. I'm scared.
I can't stay here.
Something's off with your grandma.
We will leave, just not now.
It wouldn't be nice
if we left just like that.
Rani, just…
Stop assuming the worst.
She's my grandma.
She wouldn't hurt you.
What's up?
I need to tell you something.
[foreboding music]
Who are you looking for?
I'm from the neighborhood.
Sorry to intrude.
Has the house owner come back?
[hesitates] Come back?
I was asked to deliver a letter
for the mosque donation.
I came by a few days ago,
but no one was home.
But there's no way my parents
would leave the house,
not for several days.
I tried knocking on the door
and all the windows,
but no one answered.
All right then.
Please let your parents know.
Excuse me.
[mysterious music]
Dad.
Mom.
Have you seen Grandpa and Grandma?
No.
- Andi.
- Hm?
Have you seen your grandparents?
Aren't they in the house?
I can't find them.
I was going to take Grandma to the doctor.
Maybe they went
to the forest I saw Grandpa in?
The forest?
Grandpa!
Grandma!
Mom! Dad!
- Grandpa!
- Dad!
Grandpa!
- Grandpa!
- Dad!
Grandma!
- Mom!
- Rani.
- Grandma!
- You should've stayed home.
- Dad!
- I don't want to be there alone.
Rani.
Dad!
[foreboding music]
Mom!
[panting]
[coughs]
This is where I saw Grandpa.
- [gasps] Oh my God.
- [flies buzzing]
There's more.
[gags]
[flies buzzing]
Something's off with these goats.
Their heads are gone.
You're sure Grandpa did this?
Dina, are you sure?
You're acting like Mom,
not believing me.
Mom!
Grandpa!
[heavy breathing]
[foreboding music]
Rani?
Are you okay?
We have to call the police.
I'm worried they got lost in the forest
and couldn't find their way back.
Yes, Mom.
I'll take you to the police station.
["Mawar Berduri" playing on record player]
[relieved sigh]
[Sri] Where have you been, Mom?
Let us know next time.
We were so worried.
Don't do that again, Mom.
Where have you two been?
You went to the forest?
Dina, make some warm tea for Grandma.
Yes, Mom.
Rani.
Why do you look so pale?
Are you not feeling well?
You shouldn't push yourself.
It's not good for the baby inside you.
How would you even know she's pregnant?
A mother's instinct is never wrong.
Are you pregnant, Rani?
I was going to tell you
as a surprise.
But the moment wasn't right.
The right moment?
You should've told me right away!
What?
You should be happy to have a grandkid.
There's no way Mom wouldn't be happy
about your pregnancy.
[sobs]
It's her first grandchild.
She must be excited.
[somber music]
It's okay.
Don't be sad, dear.
How could you?
That's how you reacted to her pregnancy?
Shouldn't you be happy?
[sighs]
[Hanum] How does it feel?
Your own mother doesn't like her grandkid.
Is it painful?
But this pain is nothing, dear.
[laughs]
[heavy breathing]
[creaking]
[ominous music]
[rattles]
EAST JAVA
[Grandpa and Grandma chanting faintly]
Under the full moon, the dead shall rise.
[ominous music]
[music crescendos]
[clatters]
[door slowly creaks]
[ominous music]
Sri.
[gasps]
Herman.
This is all your fault, Sri.
You have to face the consequences.
[chuckles]
Dina.
Dina!
[gasps]
How are you, Sri?
[Laila laughs]
Oh, dear.
[Sri wailing, screams]
[chopping]
[Grandpa humming]
[chopping gets faster]
DINA, I NEED TO DO SOMETHING IMPORTANT.
TELL ANDI I'M BORROWING HIS CAR.
Dina, where's Mom?
My car's missing.
I planned to take us all home today.
Do you know where Mom went?
[foreboding music]
I forgot to mention something.
Yesterday in the forest,
I saw a figure dressed in a robe
for a moment.
Jarwo.
[Andi] Jarwo.
Who's Jarwo?
The shaman our mom hired.
He was supposed to be dead,
but Laila resurrected him
and turned him against us.
I've been seeing Hanum's ghost too.
Hanum?
Jarwo.
Hanum.
What's going on?
[door creaks]
[ominous music]
You're all awake?
Why are you still in here?
Come on out.
We've prepared a special dish for you.
[ominous music]
[Sri] My daughter-in-law is pregnant.
What should I do to ward it off?
It's not that easy.
The devils resent those
who turn their backs on them.
Yes, I know. But…
Please.
Just let me take the consequences myself.
So you left your house?
I had to.
We went to my parents' house.
They're sick.
Demons have tricked you.
[water trickling]
What do we do now?
Stay here. Don't go anywhere.
- Andi!
- Brother!
I'll go check Grandpa's room.
Dina.
Wait here.
If anything happens, scream.
Okay?
[ominous music]
[grunts]
[Grandma] Rani.
[Grandma] Come keep me company.
[heavy breathing]
[Grandma] Come here.
[Grandma] Stay with me.
[groans]
[Grandma] Rani.
[Grandma] Come here.
[ominous music]
[music slowly fades]
[shaky breathing]
[chuckles]
[Grandpa chuckles]
[panting]
[panicked breath]
They know your house has
too strong protection
for them to infiltrate.
To get to you and your family,
they had to make you leave.
[chanting]
[ominous music]
[gags]
[chanting]
[chanting continues]
[retches, coughs]
You can never run from your destiny, Sri.
[chuckles]
[Jarwo] Wherever you go,
the devils will find you.
[maniacal laughter]
[glass shatters]
[shrieking]
Ki Rojo!
[Sri screaming] Ki Rojo!
Ki…
[ominous music]
[music turns somber]
[chanting]
[somber music]
- Ki!
- [groans]
[groans] Come here.
Sri.
[shrieks]
[somber music stops]
[flies buzzing]
[ominous music]
[gasping]
SPIRIT GATE
Today?
[thuds]
[panting]
[suspenseful music]
What's wrong?
Are you afraid?
[screaming]
Where are you going?
[Grandpa] Rani?
[thuds]
[eerie laughter]
Hanum?
What's wrong?
Surprised?
You really thought I was dead?
Hm?
[chuckling]
I'm alive, dear.
Salim helped me.
He was my mother's loyal servant.
[somber music]
[Hanum] He looked after me patiently,
even though I wished I'd died
with my mother.
I did my best,
trying to accept my situation.
But…
the scars on my body…
keep pulling me back to the past.
I'll never forget what you did.
Mom!
[kid wailing] Mom!
[whistle]
[Hanum] My hatred never faded.
Until fate stepped in.
When the pregnancy hits two months,
we'll do an ultrasound
and let my mom know.
Yeah.
Careful.
[Hanum] I swear,
as long as I live,
you'll never live in peace.
[Salim] No, Hanum.
Let this be over.
No!
They must pay for my mother's death.
And I want them all dead!
[Salim] If you still insist,
I won't hesitate to call the police.
- [knife piercing flesh]
- [grunts]
No one can stop me now.
You hear me, Salim?
- No one can stop me!
- [blood splatters]
[grunts]
[panting]
[humming]
[chanting]
Why did you summon me?
Jarwo.
I want you to help me
take revenge for my mother's death
on Sri's whole family.
[laughs]
That troublesome woman?
Sri.
[Jarwo hums]
You've protected your house well,
so my power
can't enter.
You're smarter than I thought, Sri.
Can you see
the baby inside Andi's wife's womb?
A baby?
A baby!
[Jarwo] Under the full moon,
the spirit gate will open,
and the dead shall rise.
["Sang Penikam" playing on record player]
[music grows loud]
[Grandpa] Looking for someone?
What do you want?
- [shrieks]
- [splatters]
[laughs]
I'm looking for my family, old man.
Who are you?
Laila and Herman's daughter.
[gasps]
- [splatters]
- [Grandma screams]
[chuckles]
["Sang Penikam" continues]
[Grandma's screams fall silent]
[giggles]
[Andi] How could you, Hanum?
You killed my innocent grandparents
to satisfy your revenge?
What else do you want?
Tell me!
What do I want?
I can't wait
for the whole family to reunite, dear.
[laughing]
[Jarwo] Andi.
Andi! Dina!
Rani!
[gasps]
Dad! Mom!
[ominous music]
SPIRIT GATE
[Hanum] Under the full moon,
the spirit gate will open,
and the dead shall rise.
[cow mooing]
[singing in ancient Javanese]
[gasping]
[singing stops]
Hanum! What do you want?
Why Rani? She's innocent!
[Jarwo laughs]
It's time for your mom to pay the price.
Because she didn't want
to sacrifice you kids!
[Jarwo] She used the devil's power
to win over your dad.
But to make it last forever,
the devil demanded a sacrifice.
Your mother made a pact.
Her first grandchild
would be offered as the sacrifice.
No way.
No way!
Impossible!
[Jarwo chuckles]
[Hanum] That sacrifice is mine now,
after I offered your family's lives
to the devil!
[laughing]
[shouts] Why, Hanum!
Why are you doing this?
What else do you want to do?
Take my life, Hanum!
Take my life instead!
Leave my child alone!
Take me!
I would love to, Andi.
But sadly,
I need a pure soul
to bring my mother back from the dead!
[Jarwo chanting]
The spirit gate has opened.
Hanum, please don't do it.
Hanum, please! Stop!
[groaning in pain]
Don't hurt the baby!
The baby is innocent!
Hanum!
[Rani groaning in pain]
[Rani screaming]
[grunts]
No!
[Rani screams]
[Jarwo laughs]
[Rani screaming from afar]
Damn you, Hanum!
Damn you!
[laughing]
[splatters]
[cow mooing]
[gasps]
Don't look here.
Why, Mom?
Do you see what you've done?
Do you see what you've done to my child?
I'm sorry, Andi.
Under the full moon,
the spirit gate will open,
and the dead shall rise.
[gasps]
Mom.
Why does this keep happening
to our family?
It's okay now.
Don't move.
Stay here.
[sobbing]
[ominous music]
[ominous music fades]
Hanum.
Mom.
I've missed you so much.
[sobbing] Mom.
Finally, we meet again.
I've wronged you too much.
- [Andi] Mom.
- Mom.
What are you doing?
Mom?
Mom.
Mom!
- Mom!
You've paid the price now, Sri.
- [laughs]
- Shut up, Jarwo!
You can't stop me!
- [yelps]
- [Dina] Mom!
Mom!
[Sri wincing]
[grunts]
Damn you!
[chanting]
[chanting continues]
[yelps]
[Jarwo straining]
Dear.
[Hanum sobbing]
No! Mom, stop!
Don't do it, Mom!
Don't do it!
I love you guys.
I'm sorry.
Mom!
[Dina sobbing] No!
Don't do it, Mom.
[screaming]
Mom!
Laila!
See you in hell, Laila!
[screaming]
Mom!
[wailing]
Damn you, Sri!
Mom!
[Dina] Don't do it!
[Hanum] You must die!
[screams]
[Andi grunting]
[panting]
[somber music]
["Mawar Berduri" playing]
It's time we leave this place
and start a new life.