[On a busy Saturday night]
[How will Kumusta's night go?]
- Oh, hello!
- Hello.
- Our workers!
- Are you a server here?
[Kim Myung Soo - Singer and Actor]
Our workers!
[Kim Min Seok - Actor]
- How are you? - Nice to meet you.
Is that his friend?
Oh, the friends are here!
Oh, the chingu is here!
- Hello!
- Oh, hello!
- Nice to meet you.
- Same here.
And then, here's our captain!
- Chef JP!
- Hi.
- Hello.
- They are my friends.
Ah, hi, hi. Nice to meet you.
What's your name?
My name is Myung Soo.
- L!
- L?
- Yeah.
- L.
- My name is Min Seok.
- Min Seok.
- Min, Min!
- Min!
- M...
- His name...
- Simply M, L.
- Okay.
[M - Worker 1][L - Worker 2]
- M, L. - Yeah.
- Hello!
- Chef, Chef!
- Janella!
- Oh, Janella.
- Nice to meet you!
- Janella.
Hello.
Workers, come this way.
- Workers?
- What do you mean, "worker"?
Workers!
We just got here...
Oh, this! This first.
- Oh, thank you!
- Kamsahamnida!
Alright, our fellow workers.
Start getting dressed now.
- Start getting dressed now?
- What is it?
- It's official.
- Okay.
Really?
- Go and get changed.
- Okay.
Move it!
- Yes, yes, sir...
- Keep it moving!
Hurry... go change.
- Did he just say "workers"?
- Okay.
- Where do we change?
- Go upstairs and change.
- Okay.
- What's going on here now?
- Pali-pali!
Faster-faster!
- "Pali-pali," Philippines?
- Faster.
- Faster. "Dali-dali."
- Dali-dali?
- Hurry!
"Bagal mo!"
Say, "Ang bagal mo!"
It means, "You're so slow!"
- "Ang bagal..."
- "Bagal..."
- "Mo!"
- Yeah, "Bagal mo!"
- "Bagal mo!"
You, "Bagal mo!"
- "Chef, bagal mo!"
- Yeah!
- You say it to Chef.
- Chef!
- Chef, he has something to say.
Bagal mo!
Excuse!
Excuse me!
[Kumusta]
[All Stars]
[Workers Ready For Duty]
- What? - Wow!
- Wow!
- Hello, look at them.
- We wear them for now.
Thank you.
- This is all so sudden.
- That's what I mean.
One friend will help in the hall,
and then can your other friend...
Help with the dishes?
Wash the dishes?
- Everything is okay.
- Okay.
- Thank you!
- Okay, thank you.
So you'll be in charge
of dishwashing for today.
[Dishwasher M]
Okay.
Dishwashing?
Yes!
Thank you.
Since you're the handsome one,
you stay out front.
I'll just go inside
- and do the dishes or something...
- Oh, come on.
- Make sure the customers...
- Oh, yeah.
don't leave any leftovers.
Washing dishes is no joke,
so make sure they finish it.
[Server L]
- Ask them to finish all. - Okay.
I am going to take a look at the sink.
- So, what's going to happen...
- Okay, wash...
Wash...
No, you don't need that.
Like this.
Example like that. You can just put it here.
- Like this. And then...
- Okay.
- So it has soap...
- Finish?
Yes. You want to try?
Can I give it a go?
- Test?
- Test!
If ever you get their orders,
- this is their table number.
- Table number.
We have 1...
- 2, 3...
- 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8 and 9.
Yes, and then the name of the dish.
This is...
That's the one, two, three, four?
- Yes.
- Yeah.
[Stations Assigned]
We're finally open.
We're open.
- Hello! Come on in!
- Hello!
- Hello.
- Let's roll!
You can sit anywhere you'd like.
Where would you prefer?
- Where would be good?
- First off...
Since there are three of you,
how about this spot?
- Oh, sure.
- That seems alright.
Thank you.
- And here's your menu.
- Thank you.
Take your time, whenever you're ready.
Your friends, "pali-pali."
- Pali-pali.
- Yes.
Very good.
- Good.
- Yes.
I think it is going to be a smooth evening.
That's true.
Do you have any recommendations?
Ah, recommendations?
It's actually my first day today, so...
- But mostly...
- Okay...
I heard they mostly recommend the inasal.
So mostly the sinigang and inasal...
Then can we get one inasal,
- one sea bream.
- One sea bream and...
one kare-kare. Can you do that for us?
- Yes, of course.
- Thank you.
Menu...
Sinigang, one.
Inasal, one.
Salt-crusted sea bream, one.
And San Miguel, three.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
[Straight to the Kitchen]
Did you drop the pork?
- Already did.
- Okay.
Tomatoes.
Vegetables.
Sinigang is ready.
It's Table 1.
- Table 1.
- Yeah, sinigang.
Where would you like this?
- You can place it right here.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
This is sinigang.
- Ah, this is sinigang?
- Yes.
What should we do?
We didn't order sinigang, right?
- How can I help you?
- We didn't order this.
We ordered this, this, and this...
Ah!
- Oh, it was kare-kare.
- Ah, yes, yes.
- Then can we get one inasal,
- Yes, inasal.
- one sea bream.
- One sea bream
- and one kare-kare. Can you do that for us?
- Sure.
Menu...
Sinigang, one.
[Wrong Dish Served]
Ah!
- We can eat it anyway.
- We don't really mind.
I'll bring it right away.
- Sorry about that.
- No worries.
Wait, wait, wait, wait... Sorry, sorry...
Table 1...
- Kare-kare.
- Kare-kare, one.
Additional?
Table 1, additional kare-kare?
- New order?
[...Yes (No)]
- Table 1. - Table 1.
- Additional kare-kare.
- Kare-kare. Yes.
- Okay, thank you.
- You're welcome.
Additional kare-kare!
Kare-kare!
[Sorry...]
Hello, come on in.
Table for how many?
- For six.
- Okay.
- Six? Feel free to take that table.
Hello, table for how many?
Ah, three...
For three...
Either that table or this one works.
- Want another chair here?
- Sure.
Okay, we're filling up guys.
This is going to be rushed.
- A long night.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Got this.
Okay, one palabok, one fish,
one kare-kare, one garlic rice.
Yes.
Okay.
One palabok, one inasal,
one fish, one kare-kare.
- New?
- Yeah, new.
Three sisig.
Whoa!
Oh, my gosh!
- Sorry for the wait, I'll bring it right away.
- It's okay.
- No worries, take your time.
- The food is so tasty.
I'm so sorry.
Kare-kare!
Table 1.
Hi, this is your kare-kare.
Thank you.
Please don't touch this. It's very hot.
Oh, it's finally out.
Enjoy your meal!
- Thank you!
That looks delicious.
Is this tripe? Is this some kind of tripe?
This is interesting.
- Yeah.
- I'll try it out.
Is it curry? Is it similar to Korean curry?
- It's completely different.
- Different?
- It has a strong taste of peanuts.
- Strong?
- It's savory.
- Very unique.
- Why? Is it good?
- Yeah.
You don't like peanut sauce.
- But I think you'll like this.
- Oh, exciting.
Just try with that.
- It's good, right?
- It's really good.
It's really good, isn't it?
My number one pick.
Oh, we got customers.
Welcome!
Hello!
I gotta run away.
- May I take a seat?
- Yes!
- Okay, thank you.
- Sure.
Check out the menu
and let me know when you're ready.
Hello, table for how many?
- Is this table okay?
- Yes.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Let me know when you're ready.
- Okay.
Hello!
Our seating right now is...
- Just the two of you?
- Yes.
This is the only spot left. Is that okay?
- Ah, yes.
- You can take a seat here. Follow me, please.
I'll get you another chair, hold on.
- Do you mind if I take this chair?
- No problem.
Because the table is full,
I need an extra chair. Thank you.
She's a huge fan.
- Oh, hello!
- I even went to your concert!
I've been a huge fan since elementary school.
Great to meet you.
Let me know when you're ready.
I'll get your water right away.
[Dinner Service Full House]
- We have a full house now.
- Really?
Wow, this is perfectly cooked.
As in, full.
Here.
- Table 9?
- Yes.
Yeah, okay.
Apologies for the wait, here's your Sprite.
Oh, we didn't order Sprite.
We ordered beer, though.
- Should we just drink it?
- Nope.
Beer is coming right up!
Two San Miguel, right?
- Is it not?
- No.
San Miguel, two.
- San Miguel?
- Yeah.
They said Sprite!
- Two San Miguel, please.
- Okay.
Two Sprite, please.
[2 Sprite / 2 Beer]
From Table 9.
- I'm sorry.
- That's okay?
- San Miguel, two, Table 9?
- Yes, yes.
Sorry about that,
here are your two San Miguels.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Why?
We're so out of it today.
I know.
Me too, me too.
I also... crazy.
Man, it's busy!
Very busy.
Does it always turn once or twice over?
Or even thrice? The customer's visit?
I'm not sure.
I've been so out of it.
Palabok, one for Table 3.
Table 4.
[Serving Support]
Table 3 and Table 4.
Tables 3 and 4?
Table 3, Table 4.
Table 4.
- Table 4, okay.
- Thank you, M.
- Table 4.
Okay, thank you.
- Table 5.
- Table 5, okay.
Table 5.
Excuse me, here's your food.
Enjoy your meal, thank you.
Enjoy your meal!
So, you have to take this to Table 5.
- Table 5?
- The fish.
- Okay.
- Okay?
Sauce, please.
Here you go, Chef.
Thank you.
Still owe one sea bream to Table 5.
There that table is Table 5.
- Take it over there.
- Okay. Put a check on it.
- Here's your sea bream!
- Okay.
Thank you.
I'd appreciate it
if you could make a little room.
That sea bream is huge.
- Why is it so ugly?
- Thank you.
Enjoy your "massive" fish.
Wow, look at the meat.
- It's such a massive fish, right?
- Right.
I want to eat some fish...
Mommy will give you some. It has skin, too.
Is it hot?
- I'll touch it.
- It's not hot.
- It's not hot, right?
- Oh, this is shrimp.
Look at you eating fish!
It's really good, right?
When I see the fish meal, I am not surprised
why everyone was impressed.
Right.
They would say, "Wow, it's huge."
It made me realize
how big of a fish sea bream...
- really is.
- Right.
But it's so good that I keep reaching for it.
It's really tender.
It's a perfect match.
- Right?
- Should I just pour it over?
No, we should dip it.
I feel like we could finish the whole thing.
- So nice.
- Yes.
- Palabok is ready for Table 6.
- Table 6.
- Table 6, and the name is?
- Yes.
- Palabok.
Yes, like noodles with veg and meat.
- Ah, noodle with veg and meat, okay.
- Yes.
- Philippine noodle with veg and meat.
- Table 5.
- Palabok.
Thank you, M.
Table 5...
I'll serve the palabok for Table 5.
Oh wait, M.
Palabok for Table 5... is that right?
She told me it's Table 5.
Is it Table 5?
- Table 6!
- Six.
Six...
- Six?
- Ah, five?
But it's done. It's done already.
Is there anything that hasn't been served yet?
- We got everything.
- Oh, alright.
It's this table, isn't it?
[Her number was wrong...]
- She told me a wrong number. - Table 6.
- Palabok is for that table, right?
- Yes. Thank you.
- Excuse me.
- Hello.
This is your order, right?
[Double Check]
Is there any food that hasn't come out yet?
I think we're missing one of this.
- One of these...
- So one more...
That should be served? Okay, understood.
Yes, Ji?
Table 6.
Inasal, one more.
- Yes, actually, two?
- One more?
- One...
- Ah, additional?
- So they have two?
- Ah, no.
Only one has been served, so we need one more.
- One inasal.
- Yes.
Okay.
Inasal coming.
It's working, it's working.
Okay.
- Are you missing one inasal?
- Ah, right, yes.
- I'll clear this out for you.
- Thank you.
Inasal!
Wow.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Palabok!
For Table 9.
- Table 9.
- Okay.
Here's your inasal.
- Thank you.
- Okay, enjoy your meal.
Here's your palabok.
- Thank you.
- Okay, enjoy your meal.
Whoa, I got dizzy from moving so fast.
- I'm dizzy.
- Dizzy?
We're out of the woods or not yet?
We almost.
They're about to leave.
One sea bream, one inasal,
one sinigang, and one gising-gising,
two garlic rice, three halo-halo,
and three Cokes. Is that correct?
Gosh, I'm kinda scared to do the dishes.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
Dishwashing, dishwashing.
- Wash, wash?
- Yes.
- Yes, please.
- Okay.
[It's M Time]
M. Hi, M!
- Are you okay?
- Okay.
Whoa.
Oh?
- I'm sorry.
- Out, out.
Sorry, sorry.
Only wash.
- Okay.
- I know...
- Okay. Thank you.
- Thank you, thank you.
I'm in dishwashing hell.
I'm sorry.
Wow!
- Yes, I know. It's never-ending. I'm sorry.
- Wow!
Welcome to our world.
Welcome to the kitchen!
Wow!
[Trapped in Dishwashing Hell]
- Hello!
- Hello.
Wow, hello.
Hello!
Oh, hello.
Oh, my God!
Hello.
- Infinite?
- Oh, yeah.
- Hello!
- Nice to meet you.
- Hello.
Oh, table for how many?
- For six.
- Oh, six.
Please wait a moment.
We'll get a table ready for you shortly.
- Table 6, please.
- Thank you.
Table 6. Please.
Here's your menu.
Thank you.
- Infinite.
- It's water.
Please send us your video.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
♪ When a man is in love ♪
[Man In Love (2013) - Infinite]
♪ There are so many things ♪
♪ I want to do for you while staying with you ♪
♪ When I fall in love ♪
Thank you.
- I really can't...
- It's a dream come true for him.
Gosh, we're staring way too hard.
- It's... it was too...
- That's too intense.
Wow, you were glued to his face.
I was surprised, too.
- My hand... What?
- Help me clean up.
My fingers got all pruney.
The customers...
- Clear this and...
- That place is inescapable.
Can you clear that table?
For real, I...
We're really here to work, huh?
- Really...
- Ah!
You okay?
Are you okay?
I'm fine! Don't worry about me.
- It's just a show. Thank you.
- Performance, performance.
- Service, service.
- I'm good, I'm good.
Yeah.
I slipped on the stairs.
- I heard that. Are you okay?
- Oh, my gosh!
I'm good. I'm good.
Oh, my gosh.
You've got a lot going on.
Did you roll down?
- Oh, no!
- Did you land on your butt?
Oh, no!
But are you okay?
No, I'm good. Don't worry about me.
- Okay, palabok is for Table 1.
- Table 1.
- Table 1 and?
- Table 5.
Tables 1 and 5.
And Table 3!
- And Table 3.
- Okay.
I'll make two sisig.
One, five, three.
- One, five, three.
You bring it to Table 1.
Just tell me where Table 1 is.
Where's Table 1?
Table 1 is at the front.
- Okay.
- The one with three customers.
Excuse me.
- Thank you.
- Enjoy your meal.
- Here's your...
Palabok...
Palabok!
I'm stuck on dishes
so I have no idea what's on the menu.
- I'm soaked.
- Thank you.
Did you order palabok?
- Yes.
- Here you go. Enjoy!
- Thank you!
Wow!
- Here's your palabok!
- Wow!
Oh, palabok!
- Oh my, palabok. Oh, my!
- It looks so good.
Enjoy your meal!
This is what table?
- Careful. Just hold it here, not here.
- Yeah.
Okay, Table 5.
- Table 5, okay.
- That is correct.
- Thank you. Please be careful, it's hot.
- You're welcome.
Oh, wow.
- Wow! Sinigang!
- Sinigang!
Looks yummy.
Tables 1 and 5, okay!
Thank you for waiting.
Thank you.
- Oh, my God!
- Wow, sisig!
You okay, L?
Fighting, aja!
- Let's do this!
- It's okay!
It's okay!
Chef okay? You okay?
- Yeah, okay, let's go!
- Very busy.
- If I were you guys...
- Yes.
I couldn't do this.
So, props to you guys.
Thank you.
You okay, L? You want water?
- You want... What do you want?
- Just water.
- Okay, I'll get you water. Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Inasal!
- Inasal?
- Two.
I don't know...
- Table number?
- I don't know.
Inasal, inasal... Table 3!
Three...
Tables 1 and 3, inasal?
Inasal, Tables 1 and 3?
Ah, okay.
- Drink water first.
- Oh, thank you.
Inasal is Tables 1 and 5.
- Tables 1 and 5, okay.
- Okay.
- Tables 1 and 5.
Their sisig is like...
Something's in there, right?
- I don't think I've seen this before.
- What do you call this?
- Onion?
- No.
This one, the... It's like chicken something...
- It's like pastil.
- Pastil!
- Yeah, pastil.
- Pastil.
I miss that too.
- Chicharon.
- Just the soup.
- It's so delicious.
- There you go.
Pastil sisig.
It's complete!
- The ingredients, right?
- The ingredients, the seasoning.
Have some sinigang.
Me too, please.
It's so sinigang.
So sour, right? It's delicious!
It's good.
- I miss...
- I like it more compared to...
- Exactly!
- I miss the Philippines.
- Nothing beats this one.
- The sour taste is really...
You really feel it.
Overwhelming, like...
The pasta is so soft, and then...
the sauce is mixed just right.
Not too soupy, not too dry.
Well, palabok doesn't really mix well.
But this is really...
I'm not really a fan of palabok,
but this is the best. It's so good.
Their inasal is the best too.
Everything, actually everything.
It's so hard to rank them.
Very Pinoy even if it's in Korea.
Can you give me sisig?
It's delicious.
The sauce is so delicious.
You can't find this taste
and aroma anywhere else.
- Like a real local favor.
- Yes.
Even in the local area...
It feels like food from a trendy restaurant.
Oh, the texture of this is amazing.
I really like it.
- Everything is good.
- Yes.
The chili is tasty, right?
Sisig?
It's so Filipino.
Looks like you're not getting full, huh?
There's Sir JP!
Good thing there's calamansi, right?
Palabok would lose its flavor
without calamansi.
How are you, sir?
Feels like home.
- Yeah, feels like home.
- Thank you.
We also mentioned that.
Because there are Filipino restaurants around,
but there's something missing.
But this is the one, end of discussion.
Pack it up, pack it up.
Thank you.
- Excuse me, oppa.
- Okay.
Sinigang, inasal, sisig, rice.
Kare-kare?
- Do you have your kare-kare?
- No.
Not yet? Okay.
Are there any dishes
that haven't been served yet?
- Garlic rice.
- The rice isn't out yet, right?
- Is that all?
- Yeah.
Are there any dishes that haven't been...
- Thank you for waiting.
- Oh...
- Garlic rice and the dessert.
- Dessert.
Do you want your dessert now or...
- No, no. Later.
- Later, okay.
Garlic rice...
We haven't served yet the...
Your garlic rice and inasal
haven't been served yet, right?
- Oh, here's your inasal!
- Here you are.
Three garlic rice.
Enjoy your meal.
Three garlic rice!
Three garlic rice?
On its way.
Coming, making now!
By now, his friends are probably...
regretting that they helped.
Cause they're struggling.
Oh, Lord, thank you.
This is the last, people of the Republic.
- Yes.
- Just one rice.
Oh, sorry, just two.
- Oh, three.
- It's okay. This is worth it.
Three rice and then...
- That's it.
- Okay.
And then we're still open.
It's worth it, it's worth it...
- Garlic rice!
- Coming!
What is this?
Give this to them. Nah, I'm just joking.
- Staff meal?
- No, we have to serve them.
Wow, but it looks tasty.
Tables 1, 3, 4.
Okay.
- Thank you!
- Tables 1, 3, 4.
One, three, four.
Thank you.
That's it, pancit.
- Here's your garlic rice.
- Thank you!
Okay, enjoy!
- Here's your rice. Enjoy!
- Thank you!
- Here's your garlic rice. Enjoy!
- Thank you.
Be grateful.
You're tired, but you're grateful.
You're tired...
What's on your mind?
No, I'm just telling myself:
"Yes, I am tired, but I have to be grateful."
Wow, I'm impressed.
This one, too.
So you accept you're tired, but...
Yeah, you're grateful for work.
- Right?
- Yeah.
Because if you just stop
on the thought that you're tired,
then everything will just go down the drain.
Yeah!
And you'd be like, you'd start to complain.
"Why am I here? Why am I doing this?"
This and that, right?
- Whining.
- Yeah, and you start to whine.
Yes, you are tired,
but you're grateful for work!
- People are enjoying our food, right?
- Our food.
- But you know...
- So...
That's what separates the boys from the men.
Ji, what can we help you with?
Ji, Ji, Ji!
Do we have garlic rice?
Yes, garlic rice.
Do we still have garlic rice?
- Yes.
- Yes, we do have garlic rice.
- Here.
- Okay.
Can I have some garlic rice?
How many?
- One.
- Here it comes.
Okay, thank you.
Ji, thank you.
- Thank you.
- Thank you very much.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you so much, really.
Really, thank you so much.
Wild.
- Good?
- Good.
Poor Ji.
You want...
What do you want? Chicken?
- It's okay. It's okay.
- Chicken skin?
What?
You want? Ah, Ji.
Sisig?
Ah, thank you.
Okay, thank you.
Why are you stealing my food?
I'll give you one. I'll give you one.
Chef, they said we should probably
just utilize the leftovers...
and the sinigang.
Thank you. Thank you.
L, do you want some?
Oh, you too?
Yeah, one for you?
- Oh, yeah.
- Okay, no problem.
You eat first.
- No, it's okay.
- Okay.
I'll stand outside. You eat.
M!
Do the dishes!
Stop it. I couldn't do anything here
for an hour and a half.
Okay friends, move it!
Leave me alone...
Wow, that's evil.
- Pretty evil, huh?
- Ji, until the very end...
Since today's my last chance
to make the most out of them,
I'll squeeze out everything I can
and use them until the very end.
That's how it should be.
[08:30 PM Workers Heading Home]
Oppa.
- Thanks.
- Thanks for all your help!
No, thank you guys as well.
Thank you for being here.
We appreciate your presence.
Very busy.
- You've been very helpful. Thank you so much.
- It's okay.
You're welcome.
- Chef!
- Yo.
Chef...
My friends who helped today
want to say goodbye.
Okay, hug?
Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
- Thank you for all your help!
- He is so funny.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
- Bye.
- Thank you.
- Bye-bye.
- See you again.
- Thank you so much.
See you tomorrow?
- Maybe.
- Okay.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye.
- Good job today.
- Okay.
- Take care, M. Good job.
- Sure.
Bye.
Oh, my gosh.
I can feel my age.
Every time you come in, I'm afraid.
New order! Palabok!
Right.
Really, Chef?
You're sneaky, huh?
Finding a way.
It's just bromance.
I just miss having a guy around.
Like your brother.
- A bro.
- Your younger brother.
Girls, like five days...
I miss...
What?
- What?
- You miss what?
Why did I say: "I miss man"?
I miss bro... Brother!
- Brother.
- Brotherhood.
- Bro, bro.
- Bro, like a baby brother.
- Brother.
- Bro.
Great job again today, everyone.
Everyone...
No, thank you!
- Thank you!
- Yeah, thank you.
- No, no, yeah. Thank you!
- Everyone...
Everyone's exhausted.
Hang!
I keep hanging.
We're all spacing out.
Thank you for your energy.
And thank you for your friends.
Also, very...
Like I was very... We were very surprised that
they are like...
- They were really into it too.
- Their game.
They're good sport.
And they are very fast.
- Fast.
- Yeah.
- And not complaining.
- Yes.
Like, they are very happy to do it.
- Yeah.
- Yes.
I would just want to say...
Yeah, I'm... really proud of this team.
Yeah, we've done the impossible.
Good night.
Okay, good night, good night.
I'm so tired. I have nothing to say.
Good night, ladies and gentlemen.
Thank you for a good job!
- Good service. Thank you.
- Good job, everyone.
Thank you so much for all your hard work.
Bye, good night!
Good night!
[A Summary of the Grind]
[Day 1]
Too cute.
- Hello!
[Day 2]
Upon returning.
- Five?
- Five.
[Day 3]
Hello!
Be ready for your customers.
[Day 4]
♪ When a man is in love ♪
Enjoy your meal.
[The Last Push]
[Day 5]
This is our last lunch service.
[11:30 AM]
- Ah, good morning! - Good morning.
How are you?
Ah, good. How are you?
- Fine.
- Fine?
Good morning!
- Morning.
How are you feeling today?
- Good.
- Good? Okay.
- That's good.
- How are you?
[Yup Okay Let's Go!]
- Yes, okay, let's go! - Okay!
- Okay!
- Let's go!
[Meanwhile]
Hello!
Hi, Arci!
[The Queen Returns]
Yeah, hello.
Good morning!
[The Reliable Backup for the Final Shift]
We have a new staff.
Arci!
- Welcome back!
- Arci!
Sweetheart!
Arci!
You're here!
Yes!
I'm here to help!
- Thank you!
- Sure.
You're here!
This is it, our energy is here.
Thank you!
Hello!
Wow!
How can I help?
Chef.
So, should I get changed?
- Yes, please. Yes, please.
- Okay.
Got it.
Hi!
How can I help?
Maybe this.
Here, do you wanna make appetizer plates?
Yeah, sure.
Jodi, we're ready!
- Ready?
- Yes.
Okay, we can open.
It's starting to drizzle.
[Rainy Kumusta]
[Today's Menu]
We're open!
We're open.
We are officially open.
[Ready to Serve]
[Fueling Up for the Rush!]
Hello, welcome!
Hello.
- Wow, it's cool!
- Table for how many?
- Five.
Five? This way, please.
Wow, so pretty!
- Please have a seat here.
- Thank you.
Pretty ladies.
Five customers. We have five.
They're here? Oh my.
Okay...
[Appetizers]
[Menu]
[Water]
- Call us when you're ready to order.
- Okay.
- Order everything.
- How about one in the picture?
- One of everything, please.
- Yes, all menu.
- Ah...
- We'd like to taste all of them.
- Would you like one of everything?
- Yes.
For now... all of them.
- Can we order all of them?
- Yes, of course.
- Then everything, please.
- Sure, got it.
- We can have an ice cream later.
- Okay.
Yes.
Wow!
- Oh.
- That's a lot!
- Okay.
- Sinigang.
One sinigang, one palabok, one inasal,
[Full Course]
one fish, one kare-kare, one garlic rice
one sisig, one gising-gising.
Inasal.
Palabok...
Hello, welcome!
Hello.
[Customers Flooding In!]
[Tables Filling Up Fast]
Hello, this is our calamansi juice.
- Thank you.
One sinigang, one inasal, one sisig, please.
- We'll have one of these, and a Coke, please.
- Okay.
- Would you like a regular Coke?
- Yes.
- Okay, got it.
- Thank you.
Palabok.
Fish.
- Sprite. Zero Sprite.
- Zero Sprite.
Okay.
Thank you.
- Good morning, everybody!
- Morning.
Orders up! We have...
One sinigang, one inasal, one sisig.
One palabok, one fish.
Another kare-kare.
So make that two kare-kare.
There are three sisig now.
That's a new order?
That's a new order.
- That's a lot of orders.
- I know.
You need help, Coach?
Ay, Coach... Chef?
You need help with anything?
- You want me to...
- Plate me the... Plate me the inasal.
- Plate me the inasal, plate me the fish.
- Okay.
Okay.
I owe you one sinigang, right?
Yes.
Okay, did you drop the vegetables?
Oh! Sorry, I only dropped
one set of vegetables.
No worries.
[Smooth-Saling!]
The "Coach" cracked me up.
I don't even know where that came from.
I've been thinking about calling him "Coach."
And then you called him "Coach."
I don't know where that came from.
Okay, sinigang is up!
Palabok also for Table 5.
- The food is here!
- Here it is.
Here's your palabok.
- Okay.
- One more is coming.
- Here it is.
- Here's your sinigang.
- Move this.
I'll bring you plates and a ladle.
- Thank you.
- Here's your inasal.
- Inasal.
- Calamansi...
- Drizzle.
Again...
- Okay.
- Okay, thank you.
- Enjoy your meal.
- Yes, we will!
Garlic rice for Table 5.
Table 5.
Yes.
Yeah, Table 5 first.
- Yes!
- Because we don't have...
So just Table 5.
- Okay.
- But just one, just one.
- Only one? Okay.
- Yes, I just prepared two extra.
There's no more rice.
So I just prepared. Just one.
It's easier with a staff around.
Jodi!
- Jodi, Table 1?
- Ah, Table 5.
Okay 5, got it.
[Queen makes it easier]
One garlic rice.
- Here you go.
- It's good.
It's good? Alright.
- Thank you.
Oh, sisig.
- Sisig.
- I'll do the sisig.
Faster, faster.
Faster!
- Faster!
- Wait! Wait!
- Okay, okay.
This must be today's menu?
Sinigang is like Filipino...
- Like kimchi stew in Korea.
- Oh, really?
- I've never seen that before.
Let's check it out.
The sea bream looks good, too.
These seem like dishes we don't usually see.
They said it's Filipino food.
- Oh, let's go there.
- It's very pretty.
- Hello!
- Hello.
- Okay, you can sit...
Oh, it's so pretty.
- Hello.
- Oh, hello!
Hello.
- Hello.
- Hello. Oh, my God.
[Who..?]
- Hello. Oh, my God. - Hello.
- Oh, nice to meet you.
- Please take a seat.
- So pretty!
- Make yourself comfortable.
Ah, thank you!
Here's your menu.
And I'll just get your water.
Thank you.
- The staff is really pretty.
- She is.
Oh, that shocked me!
That Table 4...
The people sitting there
are really famous in Korea...
[Huge Food Influencers]
at eating shows.
Yes. Yes.
The pros.
I understand.
[Korea's All-Star Mukbangers]
[Kim Min Kyung - Comedian]
[Park Ki Ryang - Cheerleader]
You could say they work for Michelin.
[Epilogue]
This is our welcome drink.
It's calamansi juice.
- Is this calamansi?
- I like it.
- It's really good.
- Thank you.