Saifah, help me!
- There's a fire! Come on,come here!
- Help! Please help my brother!
No! Let go of me!
- No, Mr. Thee!
- Do you have any idea
how much we had to suffer?
How could you leave your own kids?!
- Mr. Thee!
- How could you?!
How about Tawan, honey? Did he come too?
Is your brother here too? Is he?
Where is he?
That's unrelated, though.
Even though I've met my mom,
I never thought of leaving you.
No!
You have no choice
but to be someone I've created,
and I'm the only mother you can have.
Mr. Thee,
how's Ms. Narin doing?
She's still in the OR.
Doctor, how is my mother?
The surgery went smoothly.
I'm transferring her to the ICU,
so we can closely monitor her condition
for a day or two.
If everything looks good,
she can be transferred to a room,
so please don't worry.
Okay. Thank you, Doctor.
- Thank you.
I know my mother ended our contract.
Let's not discuss it yet, Mr. Thee.
Don't worry, Mr. Thee.
Mr. Pat and I will handle it.
Actually, I was going to tell you
that my mother had no right to do it.
Why not?
Why wouldn't I be able to end it?
We're the employer here.
You can end it,
but if you do it without cause,
The One must pay
50% of the contract's value
as severance pay to A Round Trip Travel.
Mr. Thee added this condition
to the contract.
Our legal team just checked the details
and notified me about it.
Don't tell me,
Thee's planned this from the start.
So, how much do you know
about Thee's mother?
I never knew
he was looking for his mother.
He never told me before.
So Narin is actually his real mother.
So this is why he bought her business.
Yes.
Which means that
The One holds shares
in Narin Beach Resort.
What are you planning to do, Mrs. Anna?
Since Thee's refusing to do
what I want him to,
I'll have to handle it my way.
I heard that Mrs. Anna
removed you as the CEO at TJ Group.
I'm sorry for causing you trouble.
It's got nothing to do with you.
It's just because Mom…
I mean, Mrs. Anna…
Just call her what you used to.
Okay.
Mom's probably mad at me
for not marrying Bell.
You mean Ms. Bella,
the girl who came with Mrs. Anna
when we had that party at the hotel?
Yes.
Bell and I have known each other
since we were little,
but I don't love her.
You love Ms. Mook, right?
Yes.
I'm glad you've found
a nice woman like her.
But Mrs. Anna really loves you,
and she's raised you well.
I understand, Mom.
But she's forcing me to marry,
and I don't agree with it.
I really can't allow it.
It's Mook.
- Here, let me help you.
- Thank you.
- Go ahead.
- Okay.
Good morning.
How are you doing, Ms. Narin?
I'm doing a lot better now.
The doctor's discharging me in a few days.
I really appreciate your help, Ms. Mook.
If you hadn't, I'd be doing way worse.
And thank you
for helping me see my son again.
Thank you for helping Saifah
all this time.
I haven't really done much for Mr. Thee.
Hey, I told my mom that I love you.
Hold each other's hands tightly, honey.
Deal with your problems one by one.
I'm rooting for you.
My mom likes you.
Yeah?
So, what should we do now,
about Mrs. Anna?
I'll probably have to give her some time.
For now, I want to take care of my mom
until she recovers.
Good idea.
That way, you'll get to spend
lots of time with her.
Mook,
I really appreciate you
for telling me to calm down.
Otherwise,
I would've misunderstood my mom
for the rest of my life.
Mook, do you remember?
I asked you to have faith in my love.
I've proven it to you, see?
Thank you.
I thought what happened to us was crazy,
but what happened to Mr. Thee
was somehow crazier!
It's a good thing, though,
that he got to see his mother again.
He called off the wedding.
That means he chooses you, Mook!
But I don't know
how it'll go for us either.
Of course, it's going to be
a happy ending.
Everything's sorted out now.
You're the one who told me
to deal with my problems, Mook.
I got through the worst thing
that ever happened to me
because of you.
Mr. Thee's proven himself.
Now it's your turn to help him in return.
I know that.
I'm just scared.
I'm scared that it won't work out
like I'm hoping it would.
I'm scared that
I'll make my mom sad again.
I think she'll understand, though,
because she can tell
that you really like Mr. Thee.
You've got to fight.
Come on, fight!
- Get up!
- Careful!
Us three, the three nasty girls…
No, pretty girls.
No matter how much drama comes our way,
we won't be afraid of anything, right?
- Yeah.
Come on, let's recharge.
- Thanks.
- We've got this!
Mr. Pun,
please shower and do your homework,
or your mother will scold you
when she gets home.
Mr. Pun, your mother's home.
Why hasn't he showered yet?
Can't you see what time it is?
I've told him many times,
but he wouldn't stop playing video games.
Pun,
stop playing video games,
go shower, and do your homework, okay?
Pun.
I told you to stop playing. Now.
Can't you hear me?
I told you to stop right now!
I don't want to shower yet.
I want to play video games.
Give it back!
I said I want to play video games!
Why'd you take my video game?
So you're going against my orders?
You order everyone around!
Not just me, but Dad too.
And when we don't do what you say,
you fight with us.
Who taught you to say that?
But it's true!
You and Dad always fight
whenever you meet.
You're so heartless!
I hate you, Mom!
Mr. Pun.
A kid's behavior can change
when they've been exposed to violence,
such as raising your voice,
arguing, or fighting,
all of which can lead
to behavioral changes in kids.
Are you accusing us
of making our son a troubled kid?
It helps to stop behaving violently
in front of your kid.
I'm counting on you both.
We'll have to help each other,
both at school and at home.
I want to marry Pat.
I love him, Dad.
Just think it through.
I'm a politician.
I've worked in politics all my life,
so I want a son-in-law
who can carry on my work.
But I'll marry no one but him.
Then, can you convince him
to work with me?
He seems to only care
about running his travel agency,
and he doesn't have a lot of money either.
Don't worry, Dad.
I'll make sure he works with you.
Pat's a pushover.
He'll do anything I say.
But as for his money, I don't care.
Well, we have enough
to last a lifetime anyway.
Please, Dad.
Please let me marry Pat.
Please?
Please, Dad?
I warned you, Prao.
Just don't regret it later.
Thank you!
Thank you.
It's our home, Prao.
I worked hard to afford this house
for our family.
I actually like it here,
but if my dad saw it,
he wouldn't let me live here.
You know how much he worries about me.
Are you all set?
Let's go, then. My dad's waiting.
But we have to go
to our son's school event today.
That's today?
But my dad's party
is having an important meeting.
We have to be there.
Dad wants to introduce you
to his party members.
What about our son's school event, Prao?
If we don't go see his show, he'll be sad.
Don't overthink it, Pat.
Once he's with his friends,
he'll have fun and forget us.
Then you can go to your dad's meeting.
I'll go to our son's event.
Pat!
RUAM JAI PARTY
Good afternoon.
- Good afternoon.
Where's your husband?
Let me try calling him.
Oh, hello, Mr. Pansak.
- Hello, Mr. Siri.
- Hello.
- Hello, Ms. Yupa.
I heard you're announcing
the new MP candidate today. Where is he?
Bring him over and introduce us.
Something urgent came up,
so Pat couldn't come.
What a shame. If you'll excuse us.
Sure, Mr. Siri. Go ahead, ma'am.
I'm sorry, Dad.
You should just accept reality
and let Pat go.
You can never change him.
Come on, let's head inside,
Mr. Siri. Let's go.
Let's talk inside. We're ready.
I had to cancel my event
at the association just to wait for you.
Mommy, I want to eat pizza.
I can't let you eat junk food.
My son has to become successful,
like his grandpa.
No one wants to be your puppet, Prao.
I'll get to play
in the water now, right, Mommy?
Where have you been?
You know you upset my dad, right?
- Because you're--
- Let's talk later.
We're here to take our son
on a trip, remember?
Then you can take him.
I'm not in the mood.
You two are yelling at each other again.
The problem is that you never trust me.
You never listened to me
or agreed with anything I said.
You just want me to be
what you want me to be.
You should ask yourself
if you still even want me, Prao.
I won.
Congratulations.
Just how many awards have you won
since the day we met?
Thank you
for always supporting me
and rooting for me.
I wish my dad was as supportive as you.
Have you spoken to your dad at all?
He rarely cares about me anyway.
And after that thing with Thee,
it looks like I'll have to stay
in Thailand permanently
because he won't let me return.
Are you okay?
Let's celebrate somewhere.
PRAO
Go right ahead.
Yes, Prao?
What?
You want me to pick up our son?
You should go.
We can celebrate some other day.
I've got work to do anyway.
I love eating pizza here the most, Mommy.
If you like it, then don't hold back.
Can I really eat pizza, Mommy?
Of course you can. You have my permission.
Okay?
- Is it good?
- Yes.
Are you happy today?
See, I'm not fighting
with your dad at all.
Then,
if…
your dad and I were to become friends
and not fight again,
would you like that?
If you were friends, you wouldn't fight,
just like how
Kongkwan and I don't fight, right?
Yes.
- Eat up, okay?
- Okay.
Want anything else? I'll get it for you.
Which topping do you want? This one?
Eat up, okay?
Let's go.
Go upstairs, take a shower,
and do your homework, Pun.
Okay.
See you later, Daddy.
See you later.
Come on.
Come on in.
We need to talk.
When are you going to see my dad?
Prao, you already know
that I'll never enter politics.
I've always told you that, haven't I?
Actually, I always knew the answer.
I just chose to lie to myself.
Ever since the day we got married,
I thought
I could change your mind one day.
If there were just the two of us,
I'd keep on fighting.
But we have a child now,
and I don't want him
to witness our problems anymore.
Now I understand
just how badly our problems affected him.
I've been keeping tabs on you
because I didn't want anyone
to take what's mine.
But now, I don't need to try
and keep you anymore.
It's better to break up
when we can still talk
than to end up hating each other.
But what about our son, Prao?
What are you going to do?
Today, I saw him being happy.
It means that
if we stopped being husband and wife,
stopped fighting, and stopped arguing,
we'd become parents with a united front.
Maybe then, our son might
be happier than how he is now.
I don't want to hurt him anymore.
I agree with you.
And I must apologize to you too.
I can't be who you hoped I'd be.
It's not your fault.
I was the one
who chose this in the first place.
Thank you, Teacher,
for saving my son's life.
Saifah was a very good kid.
Although he wasn't here for long,
I could sense that he's a good person.
Congratulations.
Thank you, Teacher.
Even after he moved out of here,
he's always helped the kids
at Piamsuk Orphanage.
Many kids here got to go to school
thanks to his donations.
I'm glad I could help out.
So, does Mrs. Anna know about this yet?
Please give her some time.
She adopted you
when you were little, after all.
Maybe now that you've found
your real mother,
Mrs. Anna doesn't quite know how to act.
Sure.
I'll try to help her understand.
I hope she'll listen to me.
You were lucky
to have found this place
in your toughest times.
Let's not mention it ever again, Mom.
I'm glad to meet you again.
I'm glad to meet you too, Thee.
I want to offer a scholarship
for the children here too.
How about we name it Saengtawan?
I found out about Tawan.
PIAMSUK ORPHANAGE
Saifah sure is lucky
to meet his real mother.
You know, I felt really sorry
for him back then.
His home was on fire,
and his brother
was burned to death in front of him.
I'm sorry?
I heard some locals saved Saifah,
but his brother passed away in the fire.
Mom.
Mom, I'm sorry…
that I wasn't upfront with you.
I was afraid that if I told you,
your condition would get worse.
It's okay, honey.
You don't have to apologize. I understand.
At least in all this misfortune,
there's something good too.
Just to see you today
is such a great gift for me, honey.
I want to offer a scholarship
for all the disadvantaged children.
I'm sure your brother would be happy.
Sure, Mom.
If Tawan were still alive,
he'd be happy to hear.
Thee,
there's one more person I want to meet.
Who, Mom?
Go to sleep, honey.
Mommy, when will you
invite Thee over again?
I miss him.
You like him a lot, don't you, Kongkwan?
I do. He's fun to talk to.
He likes to play with me,
and he's kind too.
I'll remember to tell him
that you miss him.
Okay.
Go to sleep, okay?
It's been a long time since I had
such a good banana in coconut milk.
Please, dig in, Ms. Narin.
Thank you.
Aren't you going to try some, Mr. Thee?
Sure.
Mook already told me
about you and Mr. Thee.
I'm really happy for you.
I really appreciate that.
It might just be the best thing
that's ever happened to me.
And I must thank Mook, too,
for helping me and my son
understand each other better.
Take off your shoes, okay? Good job, honey
Thee!
- Hello.
- I'm back.
- Hello, Auntie.
- Hello.
Are you here to see me?
I really miss you, Thee.
Yes, I am.
I have a new toy to show you.
Come and see.
Right now?
- Then, I'll be right back.
- Okay.
Kongkwan.
Then, I'd better go look after her.
Go right ahead.
Kongkwan always gets that way
when she meets Mr. Thee.
I see.
I wanted to apologize on my son's behalf
for all the things he's done
to make Mook sad.
I was never mad at him.
I just felt bad for my daughter.
Mook's been let down
by this kind of problem before.
I don't want my daughter
to get hurt by the same problems again.
I understand.
To mothers like us,
our child's happiness matters the most.
But Thee's proven
just how serious he is about Mook.
You may have heard
that he refused to get married.
I understand
that you're worried about Mook.
But I think those two
really love each other.
I believe
that they'll be ready to fight
through any obstacles that may come.
I hope you'll give Thee a chance.
I should dig in.
- This one.
- A seat for Mommy.
It should be back there.
- Oh yeah?
- Because this one…
Won't you come help us build?
Sure.
Let's see.
What are you building here?
We're building a house, Mommy.
Thee said
if we want to build a strong house,
we have to work together.
You have to help too,
so our house will be perfect.
I'll build our house
and our family.
But I can't do it alone.
You have to help me.
Sure.
We'll build a house together.
Okay.
Here, right?
Yes.
Now we've got all three.
Who's this?
You.
- What about this?
- Mommy.
- And who's this?
- Me.
Why'd you make me mow the lawn?
Because that's your job.
So I need to mow the lawn
in order to live here?
I've given them the envelope.
Usa, what if we get caught
rigging the bid with Mr. Somkiat?
And what if our company actually wins?
Where will we get the funding?
Don't be afraid of such nonsense, Kuk.
I told you, Mrs. Anna
will fully support us.
As for the funding,
she'll take care of it too.
All we need to do is win the bid.
I'll help you any way I can.
I won't leave you like Mook did.
I'm treating you
to many fancy Chinese dishes today
to celebrate the good news
our family is getting.
What good news, Ma?
The good news about your company's
big project, of course.
Once the official result
has been announced,
Kuk and I will treat you to a meal
at the most expensive restaurant.
You're such a great girlfriend, Usa.
I'm just glad there's no black shadow
to bring bad luck into our house.
Ever since Mook left,
our house has been filled
with good energy and good news.
Well, she's now a dark shadow
at A Round Trip instead, Ma.
Mrs. Anna got so upset
that she wanted to end their contract.
Soon, we'll get to replace them for sure.
Do you believe me now?
A dragon will always be a dragon.
There's no way you will lose
to a girl like Mook.
I'm sure of that.
Sure, Ma.
Right, eat up. Don't hold back.
Some chicken for your health.
- Thank you.
- There.
- Give some to Usa too.
- Eat up, okay?
Good.
Eat up.
So the troublemaker's asleep?
Yes, Mom.
She must be tired after playing all day.
Today, Ms. Narin apologized to me
on Mr. Thee's behalf.
How is he doing, by the way?
Mrs. Anna is really angry.
She removed him from his CEO position,
so now Mr. Thee has more time
to look after Ms. Narin.
Maybe it's better this way.
I'm not sure about that.
It's up to you now.
Are you ready to go back to him?
Do you think
I'll be let down again?
No one knows the future, Mook.
You just need to be prepared.
And you have to ask yourself
if you're ready to start over.
You're not mad at him anymore, right?
I wasn't.
I just didn't want to see you get hurt.
But Mr. Thee's proven to me
that he'd give up anything for you.
All there's left to do is to ask yourself
what your decision will be.
Why'd you come back?
Did you forget something?
I forgot…
What is it?
Tell me, so I can get it for you.
I forgot whether I've told you
that I love you.
You already did.
You did that day. Don't you remember?
I meant today.
I want to tell you every day.
I love you, Mook.
Mook?
I love you too.
That's all I needed.
CALLING…
Where is he?
I'm friends with Ms. Bell.
And I'm also friends with Mr. Thee.
I heard from Mr. Thee
that you have business here,
so I wanted to see you.
What is it?
This is an award Ms. Bell won
in a contest for designers.
I think the person
she wants to show it off to the most
is you.
Ms. Bell's worked hard to prove herself
so that you'd see her worth.
That's more important to her
than the award itself.
If you're here to talk about this,
you shouldn't bother.
You should leave.
Our bookings have dropped significantly,
perhaps because we don't have
a campaign to boost our sales.
Then why don't we launch one?
The campaign Mr. Thee worked on
was about to be launched,
but I see we still haven't promoted it.
So, are we promoting the couple campaign,
or are we changing it?
As for the reservation system
and the deals we offer,
Mr. Thee came up with a plan
to adjust the deals,
yet right now,
we're still using the old plan.
So, are we changing or not?
If you have any concerns,
leave it with Pitak.
Then we'll find a conclusion.
That's all for today.
What's with all this mess?
So no one can handle anything
at this hotel
just because Thee's gone?
Yes.
Normally, Mr. Thee handles
and decides everything.
How can I work
if you're sitting there staring at me?
It's not like I'm bothering you.
I'm just staring at my girlfriend.
What about Ms. Narin?
Don't you have to be with her?
You can call her Mom.
Is Mom doing better now?
Yes. She's gone back to work today.
She must be worried about her staff there.
She loves all of her employees
like they're family.
Everyone must be happy she's back to work.
Anyway, give me a second.
I'll be done with work in a bit.
Take your time. No rush.
I have to meet someone today anyway.
Okay.
Mr. Thee, someone's here to see you.
Are you sure you won't return to The One?
It's a mess there right now.
I wasn't the one who wanted to quit.
You know that, Mr. Pitak.
I just can't help but worry.
You know, sometimes I think
you and Mrs. Anna are exactly the same.
How so?
You just don't know how to lose.
Can I see?
What are the problems? I'll take a look.
Are you doing alright now, Ms. Narin?
When we heard that you got sick,
we were so worried.
I'm doing better now. Thank you so much.
You can go back to work.
Okay.
Ms. Narin, I was just looking for you.
What's wrong, Mr. Chadchai?
The One has called
an urgent shareholders' meeting.
Are you sure you don't want
to join us at lunch?
It's okay, Ms. Mook.
I have to rush off to The One,
because ever since Mr. Thee left,
it's so chaotic over there.
Let's go.
K. ANNA
I'm sorry, what?!
Mrs. Anna is at Narin Beach Resort.
She called an urgent meeting
with all executives and teams.
Excuse me for being late.
I didn't know there was an urgent meeting.
I had to call this urgent meeting
because I have something important
to notify you about.
First, please allow me
to introduce myself.
My name is Anna Teerasu.
I am the CEO at TJ Group.
CEO?
Oh dear.
I'm in the wrong seat, aren't I?
No worries. Please have a seat.
I'd like to buy back
all of Narin Beach Resort's shares
from The One.
Prao and I
have got divorced.
Please take good care of Saifah
for me, Mook.
I will.
Come here.
Subtitle translation by:
Ramil Natnitiwitaya