Mom, I'm sorry…
…that I wasn't upfront with you.
I was afraid that if I told you,
your condition would get worse.
Who taught you to say that?
But it's true!
You and Dad always fight
whenever you meet.
You're so heartless!
I hate you, Mom!
Mook,
do you remember?
I asked you to have faith in my love.
I've proven it to you, see?
My name is Anna Teerasu.
I am the CEO at TJ Group.
Oh dear.
I'm in the wrong seat, aren't I?
No worries. Please have a seat.
Then, let's get started.
I will be clear and concise.
This won't take long.
First, I'd like to inform you all
that going forward,
Mr. Theechuda Teerasu
will no longer have any involvement
whatsoever with TJ Group,
and he will lose all co-management rights
at Narin Beach Resort.
Second,
I am taking over management here
in his place.
I will have decision-making power
proportional to the number of my shares.
And lastly, there will be adjustments
to our corporate structure
and our management approach.
This is to ensure that Narin Beach Resort
meets our objectives.
What does all this mean?
It means that we're shuffling the cards
of our management planning
as well as our employee evaluations
where applicable.
Maybe it's nothing serious,
like we're afraid of.
I know my mom well.
She'd do anything to win against me.
She did it to you too, remember?
Can I ask you something?
Up until now,
how is your relationship with her?
Since she adopted me
from Piamsuk Orphanage…
she has changed my name,
shaped me into this person
she wanted me to be,
sent me to good schools,
and taken good care of me.
But every time she gives me something,
she sets a condition.
And I have to do something
in return for it.
Something that's twice as great.
That's how I've always lived.
And another thing I remember is that…
I've never felt any love coming from her.
But Mr. Thee promised us
when we signed the contract
that there wouldn't be
any personnel changes.
Then, let me go back
and clarify the first point
that I mentioned earlier once again.
Going forward,
Mr. Thee will no longer have
any decision-making power whatsoever.
But Mr. Thee--
Does anyone else
have any questions or concerns?
If not, I'd like to end this meeting.
Since you're all silent,
I'll take it that you have no objections.
In that case, that concludes our meeting.
I must ask you all to leave
because I have a personal matter
to discuss with Ms. Narin.
I've heard about you and Thee.
What a small world we live in.
I'll be frank with you.
If you're going to pull
the "I'm his birth mother" card
to win Thee back from me,
I think you're making the wrong decision.
So you did all this because you're afraid
you'd lose Thee, didn't you?
I never planned to take him away from you.
In fact, I appreciate you
for raising him well,
and I think Thee is very lucky
to have a mother like you.
But he can only have one mother,
and everything should go back
to the way it was.
As for the changes to this place,
it depends on your decision now,
Ms. Narin.
I'm really sorry, Ms. Narin.
I never expected
that The One buying our shares
would cause all this trouble.
Mom!
Good afternoon.
"Mom"?
I'll tell you about it later,
Mr. Chadchai,
but now, I must ask you to leave.
Of course.
Have a seat, honey.
Mom, are you okay?
I'm okay.
What did my mother say?
Mrs. Anna said she's stripping you
of all your management rights
and replacing you as management here.
She'll also change
the hotel's entire system.
The One holds more shares than us,
which gives them
total decision-making power.
I'm sorry, Mom,
for causing all this trouble.
Don't apologize, honey.
I know that Mrs. Anna's only doing this
because she doesn't want to lose you.
But I'm not an object
for her to use me as leverage like this.
If I need to lose something
in order to see my son again,
I'll gladly oblige.
I assume you've told Thee
about the shareholder meeting
- that I called today.
- Yes.
Good,
because I want him to know
what will happen to his loved ones
if he dares to cross me.
Don't you feel sorry
for him at all, Mrs. Anna?
Well, he never cared about my feelings.
I'll wait and see how he'll handle this.
But he's still your son, no matter what.
I hope you don't forget that.
Why can't I have a baby?
Why does it have to be me?
Please calm down.
I won't let John try for a baby
with another woman!
I need a baby,
so I can secure everything that's mine.
Pitak, you have to help me!
Why don't you want to eat?
I want to go home.
You mean the orphanage?
You want to go back
to being an orphan again?
I have a mother.
I'm going back there to find her.
I am your mother.
You're not!
Remember, from now on, I'm your mother.
And Mr. John is your father.
You have to do everything I tell you,
or I'll stop donating to Piamsuk Orphanage
and your friends will be in trouble.
Understood?
So, if I do everything you say,
I'll get to go back to my mom, right?
You'll get everything you want.
Now, call me "mother".
Mother.
MUSCLE CAR THAILAND
BANGKOK FASHION CONTEST 2022 - BELLA BELL
THE BEST OF YOUNG DESIGNERS
This is an award Ms. Bell won
from a contest for designers.
I think the person
she wants to show it off to the most
is you.
Ms. Bell's worked hard to prove herself
so that you'd see her worth.
That's more important to Ms. Bell
than the award itself.
Lately, you never have time
for your employees, Boss.
I need to tell you something important.
Prao and I have decided to get a divorce.
And she's okay with it?
She was the one who decided.
I think we've come to a point
where she's accepted the truth
that we both can't be
what we want each other to be,
and we can no longer force ourselves.
Talking things out and accepting the truth
are the best idea.
You might view it as a failure,
but to me, it might be a new beginning
that's better than the last.
Prao and I agreed that
it'll be better for Poonpun this way.
But we'll still be good parents to him.
Well, does Bella know about this yet?
My mom lets me eat pizza now, Kongkwan.
- Really?
- Yeah.
And she stopped fighting with my dad too.
My mom and dad said they'd become friends.
And since they're friends,
they won't fight.
Just like my mom and dad used to say.
So that means
they'll stop being my parents?
No, they still are.
It's just that they'll be friends instead.
It's actually great. This way,
they won't fight like they used to.
And it means I'll get to eat pizza again
and mom won't scold me, right?
Let's go.
Can you send them this bid proposal?
Sure, Ms. Usa.
Did you tell accounting about my orders?
Yes, I did.
Do I really have to handle all this?
This isn't even half
of what Mr. Thee used to handle.
Come on in.
Someone's here to see you, Mrs. Anna.
Who? Can't you see I'm busy?
It's Mr. Joe, ma'am.
I wanted to see you today
because I need to tell you
something important.
So you've changed your mind and decided
to sign our project's contract?
I must apologize on Thee's behalf.
I haven't been ignoring this issue either.
Recently, I've stripped him
of all his management rights
over TJ Group.
I've decided
to invest with you
like I planned to at first.
I knew I wasn't wrong about you.
You're a visionary.
You can separate work
and personal life very well.
But I have one condition.
What's the condition?
I'll only sign the project's contract
if Mr. Thee is in charge of this project.
Excuse me?
Aren't you mad at Thee?
You said it yourself.
I can separate work and personal life.
And I don't see anyone
who's capable enough
that I can trust as much as Thee.
I'll leave it to you to decide.
- If you'll excuse me.
- Yes.
See you later.
What's going on? You sure went all out.
Well, it's a special day, after all.
What's the occasion?
It's what I wanted to do for you.
It just wasn't the right time back then.
So you…
Prao and I
got a divorce.
I HEREBY CERTIFY THAT THE INFORMATION
PROVIDED IS TRUE AND CORRECT
HUSBAND'S SIGNATURE - WIFE'S SIGNATURE
Thank you.
You're all set.
- Thank you.
We can still be good friends, right, Prao?
Of course.
If your to-be-girlfriend
won't get jealous, then sure.
I promise that I'll do my best
as a father like always.
Of course you will.
Once you become a parent,
you're always a parent.
I won't mind it
if you want to start over with someone.
You can go ahead and move on.
We talked,
and we settled things on good terms.
It didn't happen because of you at all.
Actually, I'd been considering it
for a while.
If I didn't know you and Mr. Thee,
I wouldn't be where I am today.
Me and Thee?
Yes.
Mr. Thee gave me the courage
to accept the truth.
And you gave me the courage
to walk out of my comfort zone.
I used to tell myself
I wouldn't be able to love anyone again.
But you let me experience it once again.
Can you give me a chance?
How's that for your answer?
Sure.
Can you read that?
It's pronounced "confused".
- With a "C"?
- Want to talk about anything else?
‪Mom, let me help.
Looks like he'll be stuck here now.
Kongkwan asks about Mr. Thee every day.
What are you and Mr. Thee going to do now?
Or do you want me to ask him myself?
Mom! Stop teasing me.
I think it's nice
to take things slow like this.
After all, he's got a lot
to think about and to deal with,
like the situation with Mrs. Anna.
When he didn't have a mother,
it was a problem.
Yet, now that he has two mothers,
there's still a problem.
But I think both his mothers
love him just the same.
It's just that their ways
of showing love are different.
Is Kongkwan asleep?
Yes.
Thank you for staying
and keeping her company.
Actually, she's the one
who kept me company.
I had lots of fun.
Did you hear about my boss and Mrs. Prao?
They got a divorce.
They ended things on good terms,
and they agreed to remain good friends.
As far as I know,
Mr. Pat's a pretty good guy.
I'm sure he knows by now
what he really wants,
so he wanted to make things clear.
So…
what about us?
Aren't you stressed enough
about the current situation?
Not to mention Mrs. Anna.
Hello, Mr. Pitak.
Sure. I'll go tomorrow.
Looks like we really have to choose
an auspicious date for our wedding now.
Have a seat.
If I hadn't called you,
you never would've come, would you?
Well, I thought you didn't want to see me.
Even when you had a shareholder meeting
at Narin Beach Resort,
you didn't tell me anything.
So, why did you want to see me today?
Mr. Joe agreed to sign
the project's contract with us…
with TJ Group.
Congratulations.
But Mr. Joe has a condition, Mr. Thee.
What's the condition?
You need to be in charge of the project.
About how I'm calling off the wedding too.
My daughter wasn't sad
that you refused to marry her at all.
I actually invited you here today
to ask you something.
Do you happen to know the man named Anapat
who's friends with my daughter?
Who is he? What's his background?
Mr. Anapat is the CEO
of A Round Trip Travel.
They're The One's partner.
He's polite, and he's always been
very responsible in his work.
How are things between you and Mrs. Anna?
I heard she stripped you
of your role at TJ Group?
She's very mad at me,
but I do understand
and accept all of her decisions.
Mr. Joe, as for the project
you wanted to invest with us--
Right,
I wanted to talk to you about it too.
I've made my decision.
I'd like to invest with you,
but on the condition
that you must be in charge of the project.
But I don't think my mom will allow it.
I know Mrs. Anna well.
She always chooses the best option.
I'm no different.
Investing in something
with unpredictable risks
is something I'd never do.
So you want me to go back
to being in charge of the project?
You were the one who taught me
that no matter what I plan to do,
I need to get something in return.
Tell me what you need.
I'd like to buy
all of Narin Beach Resort's shares back
from The One.
Hi. You're here already?
Let me finish my work really quick.
Dad!
Congratulations.
But next time,
you have to come show off
your awards to me, okay?
- Thee.
- Let me help you, Mom.
Sure. Thanks, honey.
The other day, I really enjoyed
Mrs. Aree's banana in coconut milk,
so I asked for her recipe.
You two try it and tell me if it's good.
Sure.
Before we eat our desserts,
I have good news to share with you today.
You got all your shares back.
Now, you're the only rightful owner
of Narin Beach Resort.
What do you mean?
I bought back
all of TJ Group's shares for you.
Really, honey?
Yes, Mom.
In return, I'll be in charge
of the project my mother is about to do.
That's good, honey.
You have to help Mrs. Anna
in every way you can.
I have something to tell you too.
Mook, come sit next to me.
Okay.
I'm handing Narin Beach Resort over
to you, Saifah.
Why, Mom?
I've been working hard for this day,
the day I get to meet my son
and hand everything over to him.
Plus, I want to rest now.
What about you two?
What are your plans for the future?
See?
We really have to set a date
for our wedding now.
I hope you'll stay by each other's side
and take care of each other
as best you can.
Please take care of Saifah, Mook.
Of course.
So the bid results aren't out yet?
Ms. Usa is the coordinator for that,
so any updates should go through her.
USA - CALLING…
Come on in.
Mr. Apichart, the company we bid for
contacted us, asking us to clarify
the document forgery claims
made by one of our competitors.
Call Ms. Usa.
She hasn't come into work yet.
I last saw her yesterday.
She came into work for a bit,
then she left and went somewhere.
Oh no!
Why is it such a mess in here?
Doesn't his girlfriend
take care of anything?
What a mess.
Yes, Kuk?
FAMILY TOUR AND TRAVEL
What happened, Kuk?
Tell me! What happened?
Ma. Ma, you have to help me.
The company we bid for
wants to investigate us
over claims that we forged our documents.
What do we do now, Ma?
But Usa said we had it in the bag!
She also said Anna
would be able to help us.
So, where is she?
Why isn't she helping you deal with this?
I don't know, Ma.
I don't know where she went.
I can't get a hold of Ms. Usa.
And the people in accounting
told me that, earlier,
she ordered that 5,000,000 baht
be sent to her from our account,
claiming she'd use it for the bid.
What? What'd you say? Five million?!
Why am I just hearing about this now?
So that means she…
Ma, Ma, Ma. Sit.
Sit down.
Get me an inhaler.
Got it.
Ma. You have to help me, Ma.
You have to help me.
No wonder why, in your room,
all of her clothes
and belongings are gone.
She must've run away already.
Ma, you have to help me.
I don't want to go to jail, Ma.
What should I do, Ma?
Ma! You have to help me, Ma.
Ma, you have to help me.
- Ma!
- Mrs. Anna.
Mrs. Anna should be able to help us.
Are you sure, Ma?
I don't want to go to jail, Ma.
I don't want to.
I don't want to go to jail.
We did everything as you suggested.
You've got to help my son, Mrs. Anna.
What? I never suggested you
to forge your documents.
Why didn't you come to me
before doing those things?
Over at the company
I recommended you, they're furious.
They told me someone reported
that your company rigged the bid
and that you don't match
their qualifications.
But Usa told me
you'd help our company win the bid.
That's irrelevant.
I said I could put in a good word
for your company,
and you'd have to submit
your bid normally.
I never told you to forge documents
or play dirty like that.
Can you please find a way
to help my son, Mrs. Anna?
I can't promise that I'll be able to help,
because what you did really was wrong.
Ma. You have to help me, Ma.
Please, Ma.
It's okay, honey. You're okay. Relax.
Ma.
Ma, will they tell the police
to arrest me?
Or should we tell them
I had no idea about it
and Usa was the one who did everything?
I've got nothing to do with it, Ma. Ma!
I know, I know, I know!
Of course I'd have to find
a way to help you.
But right now, my head
feels like it's about to burst.
Let's think of a new plan tomorrow, Kuk.
What do I do?
I've given them the envelope.
What if we get caught
rigging the bid with Mr. Somkiat?
Don't be afraid of such nonsense, Kuk.
I told you, Mrs. Anna
will fully support us.
All we need to do is win the bid.
I'll help you any way I can.
I won't leave you like Mook did.
- Oh no!
- Ma! Ma!
Kuk!
- Help!
- Ma, what happened?
I'm screwed! Help!
It's all gone.
My stuff…
She took it all.
I went easy on you, you old hag.
That's what you get for being stingy.
Serves you right.
You lost the bid,
and your company lost its reputation.
As for all this stuff
and the 5,000,000 baht,
just think of them as my bonus,
you mama's boy.
CASHIER'S CHEQUE
USA PATTARASIN - ONE MILLION BAHT
Thank you, Mr. Somkiat,
for trusting me with this partnership.
I'm the one who should thank you, Ms. Usa.
Our company can't lose this bid.
And Family Tour is a tough competitor.
I just want to ensure
my company won't lose the bid.
Don't worry, Mr. Somkiat.
I'm in charge of all the paperwork
for the bid.
I assure you,
the numbers we propose for the bid
will be exactly what you want for sure.
You're quite smart, Ms. Usa.
Let me know if you ever want
to find a new place to work.
I'll accept every offer you give me.
Really?
I just so happened
to be seeking new experiences.
In that case,
I'll give you another important
piece of information.
The truth is,
Family Tour doesn't meet
all the qualifications
like we claimed in the bid proposal.
So that means
there have been forgeries in the proposal?
‪Let me see?
I think it's a great idea, Whan.
- Okay.
- Organizing a trip with an itinerary,
- document preparation,
- Look.
and travel advisory for each country
can help reassure our clients.
Okay.
Don't forget to post
all this information on our page,
so that when people share it,
it'll also promote our company.
Sure.
I'll create an artwork
and send it over for you to check.
Okay. Go ahead.
‪Let's zoom in.
Well, when are you two getting married?
- What?
I asked you when you two
are getting married.
You just won't stop being lovey-dovey.
What?
We're still in the talking stage.
Don't say that.
Oh, yeah? I just want to throw
my notebook at you.
- You can't go in there!
- Won't you keep watching the video?
- No!
- Ma!
Mr. Suetrong, call the police.
- Call them. Do it now.
- Got it.
Now, please.
- Hey, hey!
- Ma, what are you doing? Get up.
Please don't do this.
Please help Kuk.
I beg of you.
Please help him, Mook.
Ma?
Ma.
Congratulations on being back to work.
I'm just back
to oversee Mr. Joe's project.
As for the other operations,
I doubt my mom would let me manage them.
If I find no issues with the details here,
we can prepare for the signing right away.
Got it.
Congratulations for meeting
your mother, Mr. Thee.
Thank you.
I'm sorry I never told you
about it before, Mr. Pitak.
Now, it's all up to Mrs. Anna.
It may be hard to make her understand.
Come on in.
Mook.
I've heard my mother
talk about the bid before.
Mr. Amnat, who's a friend of hers,
is hosting the bid.
Yes.
Mrs. Anna recommended
the project to Ms. Usa.
No one can contact Usa.
She's probably gotten away.
I think she's onto them.
Is there any way you can help Kuk?
I'll try talking to my mom.
I'm sorry for bothering you
with Kuk's problem.
It's no bother, Mook.
Mr. Apichart
is Kongkwan's father, after all.
You don't need to be a dragon.
You being my son is good enough.
One thing I've never given Thee
is the love and warmth that a mother
is supposed to give her child.
So,
why don't we both compensate him
with what we never gave to him before?
What do you think?
If I want to marry Thee,
will you be okay with that?
If it's Thee, then sure.
Thank you, honey.
Subtitle translation by:
Ramil Natnitiwitaya