Please mind the gap between train and platform
How old are you?
-If you ask me back, it means…
-You’re rude!
Who asks about age these days?
Hey, a boy is staring at me.
Am I so pretty?
-I sure am.
-Maybe you’re not Gen Z like me.
Being a Gen Z is like riding the MRT.
Fast and rushed.
We love competition.
We dare to be different.
But we all...
have our own goals.
Just like me, who wants to chase my dream.
I want to quickly make it happen.
Because I know that
Gen Alpha will catch up to me soon!
So I have to run.
Run.
Be hurry and fight for it,
or else my dream is—
Sorry, I wasn’t looking.
I’m really sorry.
It’s okay.
I wasn’t paying attention.
Well,
are you auditioning for Ultimate Wolf too?
Mhm.
Good luck.
I’ve auditioned for many agencies,
but I still haven’t passed.
Nice to meet you.
I hope we get to meet again at the agency.
Then I’ll go audition first.
This is the part
that…
I believe many people will be shocked.
Who are you?
Ahh.
P’Gun, you don’t know me?
Who?
What’s your name?
I’m Jeng.
Do you know me?
Oh.
Just like that.
You know, actually,
I picked you because you’re
the worst, useless and hopeless one.
Your singing is terrible.
Do you know my songs?
What songs?
“Born to be cool.”
“Watch your mouth, kiddo.”
“Burp and break up.”
“My fresh farts.”
Seriously?
Those are your songs?
Yes.
And my last song is…
“Biggg egooo.”
999!
Hey.
Why is the website spinning like this?
My fingers are locking up.
Already?
Look at Pier.
Don’t be baffled.
It’s already been 72 hours,
and we haven’t reached 1,000 views.
How could we be idols?
I think…
I’m going to report this to YouTube.
Because no matter what,
T-Pop stage,
Whoa.
Thai Music Countdown,
CAT Festival,
Ooh.
Pa Ted.
Big Mountain Festival
are waiting for me!
That’s more like it.
Let’s keep going!
(Praying)
Please go up.
With all the good deeds I’ve done,
please don’t let me fail.
I’ve made my decision.
-I’m disbanding—
-Wait!
Please don’t!
I haven’t bought a house for my mom yet.
I don’t even have a car.
How would you?
The views are only in the thousands.
But Boss,
all of our songs’ views
have exceeded the target.
Because I’ve been streaming with you
in the room next door.
Can you see my thumbs?
It might be locked for the rest of my life.
Boss, you have such a visionary mindset.
True.
You’re kind and dress so elegantly.
Elegant my ass.
Even my Gucci pants,
I have to pawn them!
Boss.
Well…
We have a song to present.
It’s the song you said
it would make us
as famous as other T-Pop groups
Show me.
Three, two, one.
You said I’m like your little brother
Can we be lovers already?
I don’t know how to eat properly
I’m obsessed with body hair
Can we grow body hair together?
Because I don't want to shave it off
Want some body hair, Boss?
That’s kinda gross.
Who said I was going to disband?
I knew it!
He was just joking.
But!
I…
will give you a new image.
Let’s change
the target group!
Oh.
You mean…
Changing from university students to high school students?
Kindergarten, actually.
Huh?
We’re going to make kids’ songs like Teletubbies,
wear mascot costumes, do some Thai dance,
and say…
Juek juek.
But Boss,
that’s unlike idol.
Juek juek.
We’re screwed.
Amen.
I hope we get lucky in our new path.
Where are you guys going?
Oh.
I’ve made up my mind.
I’m quitting and starting a new life.
I’m not doing that.
Singing for kindergarten kids?
That’s not being an idol,
more like a kindergarten teacher.
You’re right.
I’m done with this too.
I think
someone with my look
can walk in front of the GMM building
and get noticed by some big shot.
Or should I just call P’Option?
Maybe I’ll become someone like Keng Namping or Zee NuNew.
So…
When are you guys leaving?
Right now.
No need to wait or check for an auspicious time.
Nothing is tying us down.
Wait.
Did you already tell Boss?
Of course.
While you were sleeping.
But…
Boss was so calm.
Just like when we only had a few hundred views.
We’re not an idol group anymore,
but a real life documentary.
Mhm.
I…
miss my mom’s cooking more than the views.
Hey.
Can I join you?
Since we’re quitting,
I don't wanna be starve.
Then,
I’ll have two fried eggs.
Not fully cooked, just like our group’s future.
Bro.
That's not helping.
Yeah.
For me,
we’re too old to sing for kindergarten kids.
We can’t keep failing the higher ups anymore.
Boss doesn’t see anything in us.
What about me?
Jeng.
A leader like you is a rare find.
Most people run away when they face problems.
But I believe one day,
you’ll become a great leader.
Keep fighting.
Alright then.
I’ll go tell Boss.
If you guys finish packing,
you can go home first.
Catch up with us.
Yeah.
See you.
Good luck. Come after us soon.
Let’s go around the GMM building.
Tell your mom I’m starving.
-Let me walk first.
-I’m hungry.
What should I do?
Boss.
I…
Say no more.
You want to quit too, don't you?
Boss.
-I mean…
-Don’t call me Boss anymore.
Just call me brother.
From now on,
I’m no longer your boss.
I’m not managing you anymore,
so it’s not right to call me Boss.
But…
Can I be your older brother?
I’ll still look after you.
And if you miss me,
we can meet up for a meal.
I’ll treat you,
but we’ll split the bill.
Boss, I…
Jeng.
You…
You’re a good leader.
You’re much better than you think,
my dear little brother.
Don’t blame yourself.
Don’t think you’re not good.
You’re always good enough for me.
I hope you succeed at your new agency.
What new agency, Boss?
Who said I’m leaving?
I’m staying with you.
I’ll fight alongside you.
Jeng!
I thought you were going to leave me too.
Boss.
I’m completely soaked.
But…
I have a proposal.
What is it?
If you don’t quit,
I’ll listen to anything.
Well…
Please let me choose the new members.
If it doesn’t work out,
I’ll do anything you say.
Anything?
Except
singing in a mascot costume.
Okay.
So…
Where are you going to find new members?
Your friends all left the group.
I'l try to invite my friends.
Alright.
If you trust me, then I trust you.
And…
I have one more request.
What is it?
Don’t tell me…
you want a paycheck now.
No.
I just want to call you
Boss, like before.
Because you’re like my father,
my older brother,
and my benefactor.
Without you,
I wouldn’t be who I am today.
I love you
and respect you so much.
Jeng.
Boss, I can’t breathe.
I’m not leaving you, okay?
Huh?
You’re a monk?
You…
I mean, sir.
How many years have it been?
Ten years.
Ten years?
May you be blessed.
I hope
you still remember when we danced to Sorry Sorry
by Super Junior
at the Children’s Day event.
I’m sorry, sorry, sorry.
What should I do?
My first friend already has two kids.
The second one is at the border.
The third one became a monk.
And I was so confident talking to Boss.
What now?
How about...
Please.
If I still have good karma left,
I pray to gods.
Please help me find new members miraculously.
Amen.
Six, seven, eight.
Raise your right arm.
Six, seven, eight, again.
Go, go.
Next, switch sides.
Very good.
Right, left, right.
So handsome.
Right.
Oh my, he’s too good.
This isn’t just a regular aerobics class.
He’s the idol of these grandmas!
Before we finish, I have a gift for you.
So handsome.
Really handsome.
Help me, I’m about to faint.
This is it.
My savior.
Thank God.
I’ll be going now. Bye.
Is something wrong?
I felt an energy from your dance.
And the world needs it.
What kind of energy?
Idol energy.
I guess the gods haven’t worked yet.
What’s your name?
I’m Fong.
Do you need something? I have to go.
Hey, wait.
What I wanted to say is…
Fong,
please become an idol with me.
Damn.
The gods still haven’t helped.
Fine.
Please forget it.
I’m interested.
The gods have helped me!
Why are you changing the members?
Well,
everyone in my group quit.
Because our Boss
made us sing kindergarten songs
and wear mascot costumes on Children’s Day.
But our dream
is to perform a countdown show at Siam.
Actually,
I was going to quit too.
But Boss saw my potential.
I think…
having someone see your worth
is really amazing.
That’s why I chose to stay
and try again.
I’ve also lost my dream before.
I was chosen.
But…
But what?
Damn!
Were you a cover dance champion?
Yes.
But my boss liked P’Add Carabao.
He wanted me to make
Thai folk rock songs.
That's not it!
Why should we let others choose our paths?
What era are we living in?
There shouldn’t be any limits
or restrictions.
Your life
can’t be replaced by anyone else.
Being true to yourself
is the best.
I guess no one understands me
as much as you do.
As for me,
I have to wear a mascot costume
and sing for kindergarten kids.
It seems we’re both hurt.
Then let’s start a group together.
Deal!
Woohoo!
Excuse me.
Would you like to join our group?
There are two of us.
We could be a band.
-One with male and female members.
-No, thanks.
Hey.
It’s fine.
We need to find more members.
Oh!
I know someone.
Who?
My old friend.
I’ll call him.
Before you call,
check on him first.
Check what?
Check if he’s become a monk.
He isn’t religious.
Oh.
I’ve seen him going to temples though.
Is he a temple attendant?
Back then,
he was a rapper.
His stage name was "CCT Cutter J."
His words were sharp,
sharper than a paper cutter,
and stronger than a poisoned knife.
I know CCT means cutter.
But what does J stand for?
Jaew.
His mom’s name.
He might want to remember his mom while rapping.
So what does he do now?
He changed careers.
To the left, our hero for the day.
Row faster!
The right boat is a bad boy, but it’s okay.
Catch up quickly.
Come on, faster. It'll be too late!
Left side, row harder. Right side, row harder.
What a very close match. They’re about to win.
Oh yeah!
-That was amazing!
-Whoa.
He’s not a normal boat race commentator.
He’s clearly a legendary rapper.
Should we invite him?
Sure.
Give me the map.
Where is he?
Suphan Buri province.
Suphan Buri?
We came all this way. We have to meet him.
Of course.
My back hurts.
Ouch.
We’re here.
Hey.
We came all this way.
We better get an amazing rapper.
Of course, I’ve already talked to Cutter.
Anyway, why did that guy come with us?
I told Boss we're going to find a rapper in another province,
so he sent him with us.
Boss said
he’ll be taking care of superstars like us.
Then where are our fans?
Come on.
It’s good to be prepared.
We’ll be famous soon anyway.
Then, where is the boat race event?
Good question.
Let’s ask that lady.
Two Thai teas, please.
Aunt, what time does the long tail boat race start?
Oh, it ended an hour ago.
Where have you been?
Look over there.
Don’t tell me…
we came here for nothing.
Today, we have something special.
Everything looks so delicious.
Come take a look.
Cutter!
That’s his voice! I remember it.
When I say wave, you say call.
-Wave.
-Call!
When I say call, you say stop.
-Call.
-Stop!
Okay.
Hey, Mommy.
Please stop. We’ve got customers.
Yo.
Okay.
Hey.
Long time no see.
You’ve gotten handsome.
As I should.
Hey yo, what’s up, bro.
Hey, hey, hey!
Who’s he?
Well, do you want to form a group with us?
You said you wanted to become an idol.
Now, Ultimate Wolf is reaching out to us.
This guy is a member of the agency.
This guy?
This is Jeng?
A member?
Alright, listen.
We’ll become the next wolf.
I mean, the next superstar.
Ah.
You scared me with that wolf part.
Actually,
what you proposed
is pretty interesting.
But…
the job I’m doing now
is at its peak.
The highest point,
you know what I mean?
Hah.
Don’t you want to be a rapper anymore?
You have so much potential.
Whoa.
What a sweet tongue.
Actually,
for me…
I’m really interested.
But…
my mom
doesn’t support it. She said no.
What?
Who said I don’t support you?
Mom.
Yeah!
This is…
such a cool mom.
Let’s go, Mom.
I just don’t support his old agency.
They suddenly changed music style,
and made my son lost his direction.
But from now on…
Yes, Mom?
Listen.
Yeah?
If you have a dream, you need passion.
Passion.
And when you have passion, you have to go for it.
Okay, let’s go.
-With friends helping you like this…
-My friends.
-You have to do it.
-Just do it!
-Got it?
-Got it, Mom.
I believe in you, baby.
Yeah, my mom believes in me.
-Yeah, you can do it.
-I can do it!
My mom say yes.
Okay, say yes?
-Yes!
-Yes.
My mom said yes, okay, we can go.
Yes, let’s go.
Yay!
Yes, yes, yes!
I really admire you guys.
You successfully chased me and convinced me to join you.
Mom said she wants me to shine.
That’s the spirit.
Yeah.
If you don’t come with us,
you’ll regret it.
What’s that flashing light?
Is someone illegally gambling?
There aren’t any clubs around here.
Huh?
What are they looking at?
I wonder.
Ah!
Someone is jumping off a building!
I want to die.
Huh? Jumping off a building?
Hurry, let’s go see it.
Don’t do it. Calm down.
Don’t jump.
Whoa.
This is my first time seeing it.
I should record this.
Love
I love you with all my heart
Who is that?
The feelings I’ve kept inside
Can you hear it, my love?
I want to ask…
What are you doing?
You sang this song five times already.
But it usually works.
Can you sing a song about
parental love?
Sure.
As you wish.
My mother is the greatest—
My mom left me when I was three!
I only had my grandma!
Sob sob.
I can’t take it anymore!
Ah!
Don’t jump!
Change the song.
Give me a song about grandma.
But I don’t know any songs like that.
Then just make a new one.
Okay.
Grandma
Grandma gobbles longans, grandma’s drool goes down
Please walk carefully and be careful not to fall
My grandma loves eating longans.
I always peel them for her.
I miss you, Grandma.
Where are you?
Noi.
Come down.
Come peel longans for me again.
Grandma.
I miss you.
Come down.
I’ll jump right down to you.
Don’t!
Just come down the stairs.
The stairs?
Okay, wait for me.
Amazing!
How did you know they like longans?
Good heavens. That’s him.
My main vocal!
Can I cover his face
and post it on TikTok ?
Can I?
Hello.
Whoa, just now…
Your voice gave me goosebumps!
So,
what’s your name, Mr. Golden Voice?
I’m Yu.
Your voice and your song
are so moving
that even the Grim Reaper let the man go.
Just because of longans?
Well…
It’s art.
It’s symbolism.
Because art isn’t a direct thing.
It’s about...
seeing beauty from different perspectives.
Exactly.
It’s like how we can’t see a soul with bare eyes,
but we have to use...
our heart to guide our body.
Yes, that’s what I’m looking for.
A poem can’t become great because of a paintbrush.
It becomes great because of
the meaning.
Would you like to join my group?
When Liu Bei met Zhuge Liang,
the land united.
You’re the one I’m looking for.
Even more than Liu Bei and Zhuge Liang.
Please be my main vocal.
Sure.
An aerobics dancer,
a boat race commentator,
a rescue volunteer,
and…
the last remaining member of the group.
Why does our profile
seem like a bunch of weirdos?
Hahaha.
Uh.
Oh.
I’m going to find Sommai.
He must be hungry.
Bye.
Go practice.
If you do well,
we can sign the contract right away.
What if we don’t, Boss?
Do you want to know?
We won’t disappoint you.
We won’t.
The girl group trainee from our rival agency
is about to debut.
Try researching them.
Kamikeme Entertainment!
Yes, Kamikeme.
Every song they released became a hit.
Their views always skyrocket.
Their concert tickets always sold out.
People lined up to buy tickets the moment the mall opened.
People buy tickets online these days, Boss.
That’s it.
How could a music label like that…
be more popular than us?
But they already are!
What did you say, Boss?
Never mind.
Guys,
practice hard.
We have to beat them
and shake up the T-Pop industry.
Alright, you may leave.
Somjai.
Take them to the practice room.
Sommai at your service.
Yes, that's what I mean.
Go, do your best.
Yes, sir.
Follow me this way.
Come on, right this way.
This way, rookies.
Come here.
Sean.
Yes, sir.
How is the investigation about Bai Liu going?
What are they doing?
So this is what happened…
I’m so excited.
We can’t fail this mission.
-Don’t say that.
-Or else we’ll be fired.
What if we run into P'Waii?
Our agency is in crisis.
And what’s with that outfit?
P’Waii.
P’Waii!
It’s P’Waii in the flesh.
I can’t stop falling in love
You’re the love I lost
Let’s stay apart, so you can love someone else
Oh my god.
No freaking way. I'm so delighted.
Someone still remembers my song.
I’m so happy too.
I’ve been your fan
since you were singing in front of the market.
I even twerked in front of you, remember?
Huh? You don’t?
Yes, sir.
I’m in front of Bai Liu’s company.
Somjai followed some celebrities.
I’ve tried to call him back, but he won’t listen.
Very unprofessional.
Sir, I’ll call you back.
There are so many people here.
Jarassi.
Follow up on Lisa’s concert deal at the end of this year.
I’ll make it grand,
bigger than anything we’ve ever done.
Good. Make it so good that
our rival collapses completely.
Don’t worry.
I’m good at collapsing.
Because I collapse all the time.
Great.
How dare you mock me like that?
Bai Liu!
By the way,
do you have a problem with Bai Liu?
You keep mentioning her.
It’s nothing.
Go back to work.
Yes, sir.
I’ll take care of my business.
Are you free tonight?
I want to negotiate.
I'm so ready, woohoo!
This place is amazing.
This is
our practice room.
Isn't it a warehouse?
Come on.
BTS started in an apartment.
Steve Jobs also started in a garage.
And we’re starting here.
At a warehouse?
Yeah.
It’s not that bad.
But can we really practice here?
Of course.
Our voice sounds good even without mixing.
But I feel some kind of presence here.
I just feel hot.
Why don’t we practice in the room the Boss gave us?
No.
If we go there,
Sean the spy will report us.
Sir. Sir.
We can’t let him see us before we’re ready.
Good point.
Then should we start now?
Okay.
Come.
Come on.
Let’s go.
Go.
What should I do?
How am I supposed to apologize?
How about this?
Bai Liu!
I’m really sorry.
Please forgive me.
I was wrong.
No.
It looks so dumb.
Not cool at all.
Maybe this.
Hey, hello, Bai Liu.
Can you forgive me, please?
I’m sorry, sorry, sorry about this.
Apologies. Apologies. Apologies.
No, not this one.
My English is terrible.
Forget it.
Or maybe.
I should just act cool.
Bai Liu.
I…
want to apologize
for what I did.
I was really wrong.
Please,
forgive me, Bai Liu.
Long time no see, Crayons.
Just call me Si Tian.
We’re Thai.
Why can’t I call you the way I used to?
Or should I call you...
candle stick?
Whatever you want.
What did you call me here for?
Well…
Need advice because your agency’s shutting down?
Don’t play around.
I came to ask for advice
as an old friend.
Friend?
What kind of friend?
Are you talking about…
the friend you kissed in the bathroom?
That was a long time ago.
Why bring it up again?
Let’s…
talk about our business.
Our?
You really said “our.”
I think
you have no right to say that.
For the past ten years,
what have you done to me?
Do you even remember?
Hah.
You said you loved me
and wanted to date me,
but you didn’t dare go public.
Pathetic!
Back then,
we were still young.
Same-sex marriage wasn’t legal yet.
Same-sex marriage?
That’s just an excuse.
Hey.
Let me tell you something.
Do you know how everyone
made fun of me?
They thought I was the only one desperate.
Back then, I thought
you had hives,
so I bought Calamine for you.
Hives?
I’m losing my mind?
What the heck are you talking about?
Hey.
Listen.
Everyone was gossiping.
They said I was
the only one imagining things.
I was so embarrassed
I wanted to disappear.
If you had any sense in the first place,
you wouldn’t have flirted with me.
Anyway,
about things
from the past…
I…
I’m sorry.
And today,
I want to
ask for advice about the music label.
There it is!
Why didn’t I win the lottery?
You haven’t changed at all.
When you talk to me,
you only care about what you can gain.
Because your agency is successful,
so I just wanted some advice.
Can’t you help me?
As another human being.
Your agency.
Ka or Gay or something like that.
Stop!
Don’t talk about gay people like that!
Why?
Do you have a problem with being gay?
Someone like you wouldn’t understand.
And you said “another human being”?
How dare you?
You shouldn't said it.
I only use “human”
for honest people.
Not someone like you!
And about what you came here for…
Dream on. I’m not helping you.
Oh.
And stop sending spies in disguise.
I’m so tired of it.
Somjai and Somruethai
wore an obvious fake mustache.
Bruh, claiming to be a fan?
I could spot them from a mile away.
Jarassi.
Start the car.
What a shame.
The fun is over.
Bye.
Oh.
I said that wrong.
What I meant to say is…
Let the fun begin.
Game on, bitch!
Hey! Can I get a strong drink?
-Guys.
-Yeah?
Don’t be nervous.
Don’t pressure yourselves.
We got this.
Here.
I have something for you.
Whoa!
A friendship bracelet!
Thank you, bro.
For everyone?
I got a power.
Yeah.
Here.
We’re a team.
Right?
Yes, my friend.
Are you ready?
Boss is waiting.
Ready.
Let’s go.
Let’s do this.
'Miss you, miss you'
Sigh, it's even more boring to listen to
'Love me, love me'
You know that it's tiring (hey!)
Please note, please note
That there's no need to take care of each other constantly
Well, I'm not quite like anybody else
You'll take care of everything (you're saying)
Paying for every single thing (it's too much)
You must have done these things with others before
And they all fеll for you, right?
But just act cute for me
And then I'll fall in lovе with you
Making a move like this is old school
Don't have to do
No flowers
Cus I'll be flower-picking
Pick, pick, pick
Ya ya ya ya ya ya a a
Ya ya ya ya a a
Cus I'm fatal chic-ing
Chic, chic, chic
Ya ya ya ya ya ya a a
Ya ya ya ya a a
Ah!
Balls!
How was it, Boss?
Aren’t we amazing?
We’re awesome, right?
P’ Sean, are you speechless?
Sean.
Go get the thing.
What thing?
Is it…
our contract?
Guys.
We’re going to be on the same team.
That’s amazing.
Debut, debut.
Not really.
I had Sean prepare mascot costumes.
Four of them.
You’ll perform on Children’s Day
at Wat Yai Nong Khai School.
Mascots?
No, Boss.
We just started.
Maybe we haven’t found the right path yet.
But I think…
this is the right path.
I’ll make a practice schedule for tomorrow.
Huh?
Did you misunderstand something?
Talented people like us still need practice?
Yes. Practice wearing mascots.
Huh?
No mascots.
No way.
We’re this handsome.
We can’t do that.
You keep pushing the mascots to us.
You don’t trust me.
I’m going to boycott you.
Come on, Boss.
Your vision is terrible.
Can we change from mascots to aerobics?
It’s easier.
Aerobics.
Wait for me.
Hey.
Are you going to debut as a mascot yourself?
Want me to name it for you?
Sweet Potato Cat.
Ohh, Play.
What’s wrong?
I don’t know what to do.
Yesterday,
I went to ask another agency for advice,
but he scolded me.
And today,
after watching their performance,
I tried to suggest an option,
but they got upset with me.
What should I do?
Can I stop listening?
Just kidding.
Let it out.
I’ll lend you an ear.
I want to be an idol.
Sit down, Cutter.
You’re drunk.
Hey.
What do you think… Boss thinks of us?
I think it’s positive.
When we danced,
I added Tai Chi moves.
Boss might be impressed with the difficult flips.
At least,
we performed until the end.
We did our best.
Thank you, everyone.
It’s okay, Jeng.
If we don’t pass the audition,
I’ll take you guys
to work in rescue with me.
Give me an idea.
How can we make a boy band
with such a stupid boss
become famous?
-Are you insulting me?/N-Yes.
Sure.
The key to creating a successful T-Pop group…
doesn’t start with good singing.
First,
it’s about making the audience feel connected.
Second,
the song needs to be memorable within ten seconds.
Not like "Little Brother", right?
What little brother?
Third, present the group’s back story.
Where are they from? What are they fighting for?
Fighting for their life.
Fourth,
the agency has to help with the promotion.
I promoted until it went negative.
Fifth,
you need a main that kills.
Someone has to die?
You can be the first.
It means someone that attracts people.
A group needs good visuals, good characters.
Someone who can sing, play instruments.
Someone handsome, cool, and attractive…
If you can’t do that, it’s over.
Wait.
I know someone.
And most importantly, you need K—
What the heck?
Hello, what’s up?
I need your help.
Huh?
Yu, why are you so cute?
Cutter, you're drunk.
I'm not.
Thank you.
Please sing for a short while.
My stomach hurts.
-Good luck.
-Hey, I can’t.
Hey, you.
Uh.
The singer has a stomachache.
So I’ll take a short break here.
Huh? Why?
Can’t you sing?
I want to hear it.
-Don’t leave the stage silent.
-Right.
But I’m not really good at singing.
-Just sing.
-Just do your best.
Take off your mask too.
Sing.
Take off your mask.
Alright.
Then I’ll sing a song that comes to mind.
It’s a song I wrote for someone.
Someone I used to have a crush on.
I believe many of you have felt this way too.
Just like me.
Ever since you walked into my life, my world changed overnight
Never knew I could fall so hard someday
When you smile, I can’t help but smile your way
When I look into your eyes, I see the whole world inside
Could I spend all the day I have left living for you?
A lifetime still wouldn’t be enough to spend by your side
No matter how many lifetimes,
I’d like to find you again
Let this loop go on and on,
Wake up to you with every dawn
Now until eternity, I pray it’s always you
If wishes could truly come true,
I’d like to repeat this life with you
Can it please be you?
No matter how far the road may be, it’s you I’ll always see
Let this loop go on and on,
Wake up to you with every dawn
Now until eternity, I pray it’s always you
If wishes could truly come true,
I’d like to repeat this life with you
Can it please be you?
No matter how far the road may be, it’s you I’ll always...
see
I hope you can express how you feel,
without hiding your true feelings,
like I did.
(If wishes could truly come true,)
(I’d like to repeat this life with you)
(Can it please be you?)
(No matter how far the road may be, it’s you I’ll always see)
Tomorrow, I’ll ask for leave.
Yu, can you call a ride?
They’re way too drunk.
Hey.
Who said I’m drunk?
I’m just not the same.
Pull yourself together.
The car is almost here.
It’s nearby.
Hey.
Huh?
I see grandma.
Where?
There.
Damn.
It’s not grandma.
It’s Mama noodles!
Yeah.
Whose car is this?
What should we do? This is a BMW.
Cutter, where are you going?
Well.
We need to find some water.
Before the owner comes after us.
Okay.
Here’s some water.
Thank you.
Cutter, come wash your face.
It’s not for him,
but the car.
Take some responsibility for throwing up at it.
He's old enough. Why doesn’t he know his limits?
Don't be a burden to others.
Sorry, my friend—
And you want to be an idol?
He can’t even set a good example for the younger generation.
Idol?
I want to be an idol.
He keeps shouting that loudly.
If you really want to be an idol,
use your mouth to practice singing
and dancing.
Calm down, please.
We’re Thai people. We’ve kind hearts.
Let’s be harmonious.
Let’s gather around and bring our hearts together.
No more harmony.
If I clean it, this ends here.
Fong.
Go check on Cutter.
Clean it properly.
Cutter, seriously.
Once you’re sober,
you’ll be punished.
Here, drink this.
You shouted a lot to help your friend.
Have some. It’ll soothe your throat.
You wanted to be an idol, right?
Take care of your voice.
You’re busy looking out for others.
Try looking after yourself too.
Keep wiping.
It’s clean now.
Are you satisfied?
Not bad.
Why do I feel like I’ve seen you before?
Have we met before?
I don’t think so.
Maybe we just passed by each other.
Passed by?
You look familiar.
You should go home.
Be good.
I’m sure we’ll meet again.
Can you move?
Oh!
I’m going home.
Okay.
Guys, move aside.
Hello, bro.
Alright, I’ll help you.
(Watch the uncut version only on iQIYI and IQ.com.)