Thank you very much, Mr. Pedron.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Ant, uh...
Ant?
We just want to say...
we're sorry for what happened.
Everyone will forget that
eventually.
Just carry on.
Do you need help with anything?
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ANT] Guys.
Bro? Wait up!
I filed for a Leave of Absence.
Dad's idea.
He said my situation
is like being in a fishbowl.
I have to get out
of the fishbowl for now.
But it's nothing.
I mean,
we're still friends, right?
[CHUCKLES]
You sicko.
I should've known that
you're a pervert.
It was you, right?
Huh?
You filmed us
for your own pleasure.
No!
Dude, I would never do that!
Don't accuse me of such a thing.
Believe me!
If you're innocent, then why?
Why didn't you tell us
you're gay?
I'm ashamed.
I couldn't face myself.
I was afraid that if you
found out the truth about me,
you wouldn't accept who I am.
And that's exactly
what's happening now, but...
Dude, come on.
I'm still the same person.
I'm still your friend.
If you're really their friend,
you shouldn't have
kept it from them.
Shut up and keep
out of this, Earl!
He is with us...
because unlike you,
Mr. Voyeurism,
he is a real man.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Come on, let him be.
Ant is on LOA anyway.
Let's just move on.
Never show yourself
to us again, huh?
Hey. Cole!
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Back off!
[SCOFFS]
I don't get it, Nyx.
Why'd you do it?
You promised to keep
my sexuality a secret.
[SOBS, SNIFFLES]
None of you girls had
the right to out me.
[SNIFFLES] Nyx.
You promised, right?
I believed all your
empty promises.
How many times
do I have to tell you
that I had nothing to do
with your leaked nudes!
I could never betray you
like that.
Besides, I would've quit SOSH.
You know that.
I was willing to quit
despite you knowing
how much this matters to me.
God knows how important
this is to me!
I'm sorry... I'm sorry.
- [ANT EXHALES SHARPLY]
- Sorry.
What good are your apologies?
Sorry? Sorry?
Really, Nyx?
I feel sorry for you.
I'm sorry for what happened
to you,
but it's just your bodies
that were exposed,
not your whole selves!
At least you can still have
a life while you ruined mine!
Nyx...
[SOBBING]
Nyx, Dad doesn't talk
to me anymore.
He couldn't even look at me.
I've lost my family.
I've lost everything, Nyx!
You're the only one
who understands me.
- You get me.
- Sorry...
Sorry, Ant. Sorry...
Sorry...
What's your problem?
You deserve it.
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
I deserve it?
I'll say what you want
to hear, Isobel.
We're even now.
You've won.
So please...
Just leave me alone.
Let me be.
Especially you, Nyx.
No...
I believed you.
Ant...
Ant, I'm sorry.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
If you tell Cole
or any of those jerks,
I'll make sure this
won't be the last.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Got that?
[NYX] Enough!
What?
Enough, Isobel.
It's Pride Day!
You forgot?
Enough.
[ISOBEL] I've warned you.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[ISOBEL] We finally got Ant.
One down, four to go.
[NYX]
You're going insane, Isobel.
I promised Ant.
You made me look
like a liar, you witch!
I didn't promise him anything.
We agreed on revenge.
That's it.
We go all in, or nothing at all.
Isobel, please understand Nyx.
Of course she's upset.
Didn't we all agree not to
make impulsive decisions?
Every agreement is sacrosanct!
Sacrosanct!
Don't bombard me
with gibberish, Marla.
I'm not some nincompoop
trying to stand here
and watch someone waste
all of our efforts and our plans
just because someone got
their conscience magnified!
Imagine...
if I didn't threaten Ant,
he would've ratted us out.
All our efforts and plans.
All our plans would've
been jeopardized.
And besides,
I'm the only one making
an effort here.
I'm the only one pitching in.
What's that, Isobel?
What?
What are you even pitching in?
What's this, drinking gin?
We're all pitching in, too.
Really? What did you pitch in?
Calculating success over failure
with your itchy little crotch?
- And...
- [HUFFS]
Face it, Dessalyn,
your probabilities are boring.
Hey! Bitch!
I'm always warning you.
But we always end up failing
because of all your
unpredictable decisions!
Your thinking is so destructive!
You never think about how your
bitching could backfire on us!
Your selfishness makes you more
like a gutter girl than I am!
Okay, okay, girls.
Enough.
Come on!
There's no need to hurt
each other, okay?
Let's not forget,
we're not enemies here.
We're a team.
We're all in this together.
Wow! Wait, so we're a team now?
You make me want to puke!
What about you, Marla?
What did you pitch in?
You're the "leader"
of this group,
yet you're the one making
the safest choices,
setting us up for failure.
You claim to be number one,
but you're just a coward.
I'm not a coward!
Being cautious is different.
You're ineffective.
Just admit it.
Coward.
Ditto.
I hate to admit it, girls,
but...
Isobel is the only one
making sense right now.
She just had to make sure
Ant was gone.
Whether we took his word
that he'd quit,
Isobel just had to make sure.
But really, Isobel.
You're too impulsive, girl.
What you did could really
backfire on us.
But I get you.
We need the upper hand
in every situation,
and Isobel made that
possible for us.
Actually...
You went overboard.
Kind of dramatic,
in my opinion.
But aren't we all going
overboard anyway?
I'm willing to do anything,
just so Migo gets kicked out
of this school.
Look at you girls!
Cheers to all of you!
You win. Just leave me
out of whatever crazy
mess you're desperately trying
to pull off because I'm out!
I'm backing out! I quit!
- [NYX EXHALES SHARPLY]
- Get over yourself!
[PANTS]
You can't leave this group, Nyx.
And why?!
Because you are the only one
who got what you wanted.
Don't you think it's time
to return the favor?
Always the main character, huh?!
You're freaking shameless!
It's not just your personality
that's rotten to the core,
it's also your breath,
it stinks!
Freaking reeks!
Like the disgusting trash
that you are!
Isobel, just brush your teeth!
If you still stink,
keep pigging down!
Chow down as hard
as you can chow,
you emaciated witch!
You know what SPH means?
Super Pathetic Hungry!
That's what you are!
Brush your damn teeth!
You're all petty!
I joined this girl group
because I believed
I found a support system
that I yearned for.
We have a shared
traumatic experience
here in SOSH, you know?!
But no!
I give up on
this pathetic revenge!
I'm done with all of you!
I quit!
I'm out! [INHALES SHARPLY]
You'd never know how
I really feel, especially you!
I'm just holding back,
you stinky mouth-breather.
If I were you,
I'd use mouthwash!
I'd gargle so hard!
[FAKES GARGLING]
Then swallow it all up!
You crazy witch!
Goodbye!
[NYX WHIMPERING]
[DOOR OPENS]
- Oh my god!
- [MARLA GROANS]
Good job, Isobel.
- [APPLAUSE]
- [GROANS]
Does it hurt
to be talked down to?
[SNICKERS]
[SIGHS]
Why would I be hurt?
I didn't even understand
anything.
[GLUM MUSIC PLAYING]
Shut up.
[CLAPS]
Let's eat then.
Then brush our teeth after.
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PHONE TYPING]
[CONTINUES TYPING]
Babe.
I'll drive you home.
No, thanks.
I'm waiting for my driver.
He isn't here yet.
Please, let me do this for you.
So you'll be safe with me.
Babe, please?
Can you stop calling me "babe?"
- But--
- Just leave me alone.
But you are my babe.
What do you want?
Only you, babe.
Really?
I find that hard to believe.
Marla...
I'm sorry.
Sorry, I was wrong.
I shouldn't have...
...left you alone.
I shouldn't have broke up
with you.
Sorry, Marla...
if I left you when you
needed me the most.
Maybe I was really afraid.
You know,
no matter how many times
Dad beats me up
if he found out
we're still together,
I'd take it all for you.
It doesn't really matter
what I do,
the beatings will never stop.
Remember when I told you
that I'd always
be there for you?
Take my word again.
Please?
Did you send my nudes
in your group chat?
What?!
Why would I do that?
You're not answering
my question.
N-No.
N-no... I would never do that.
Believe me, Marla.
You know,
for the past few months,
I was pressured to be good,
I get short-tempered
because of pretending...
but...
did you see our group chat?
No...
No.
There you go.
I think you're just
caught up in...
an unrealistic narrative.
That I leaked your nudes.
How did you make that up?
When I asked if you were
behind Ant getting outed,
I believed you when
you said it wasn't you.
But when it comes to me...
when I needed you
to believe me...
...you find it very hard to do.
Is it that hard to trust me?
We've known each other
for so long, Marla.
I want to be there
for you, Marla.
Please?
I have to go.
Oh, wait, Marla.
Promise...
I'll find out who leaked
your nudes.
And when I do, I'll make him
suffer for everything.
This is how much
I love you, Marla.
[COLE] Trust me,
I'll do everything
to get you back, Marla, please?
Please?
Is there a problem here?
Marla, are you okay?
Such a show-off!
You always appear
out of nowhere.
I can see through you.
You're crazy
for my girlfriend, right?
Girlfriend? [SNICKERS]
- Aren't you the ex?
- What utter nonsense?
I am not your girlfriend
anymore, Cole.
- This isn't your business.
- Like I care?
She's my girlfriend.
You're just an ex-boyfriend.
Can't you understand?
- To hell with you!
- [MARLA] Hey! Stop!
- [CHUCKLES WRYLY]
- What now? Huh?!
[MARLA] Stop it!
- You think you're the King?
- What do you mean?
Stop hiding behind your dad.
- [MARLA] Okay, stop!
- Oh, really?
Watch out who
you're messing with.
I already know
who I'm dealing with.
- [MARLA] Guys, stop!
- I'm not afraid of you.
[MARLA] Shh! Stop!
My god!
Are you guys really going
to fight over me?
Really?
We're not going to fight, Marla.
Oh, no?
Okay.
[MARLA SNORTS SOFTLY]
But if you want,
I can make it happen.
[SNICKERS]
Whatever!
I can't deal with this anymore.
I'm so out of here.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Baby!
Babe! Wait, wait a minute.
Can we just talk, please?
- Babe--
- Oh, come on!
[SNICKERS]
This cat and dog chase
is getting old.
Daph.
Can we please stop this?
Talk to me.
Daph!
I'm getting so fired up.
[CLAPS] Talk to me!
No!
[DAPHNE LAUGHS]
- [LAUGHING]
- What?!
- What's so funny?
- [LAUGHS SARCASTICALLY]
- Huh?
- Nothing.
You're already losing
your control.
Like an orangutan.
Ah...
You're only being aggressive
to dominate me.
It turns you on, regardless.
Hmm?
[THUD]
You like that...
right?
[BANGS]
You want aggression?
- [SNICKERS]
- Hmm?!
You get turned on, right?
The same way I get turned on
whenever you show your--
What's that word again?
Ah!
- Gutter girl personality.
- [SNICKERS]
Gutter girl?!
Gutter girl, huh?!
Get out of here!
Get out!
- Really?
- Really!
- Are you deaf?
Dang it, I don't want
to be with you.
- I'm done with you.
- Getting riled up?
- I don't love you!
- Go on!
- [SLAPS]
- I don't love you anymore!
- [BANGS]
- Dang it!
[BANGS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[LESTER LAUGHS]
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- Let's get married.
- Huh?
Are you nuts?!
I'm serious.
Okay. I talked to mom.
I told her,
I am choosing you.
And there's nothing
she can do about it.
Well...
Obviously, she went crazy.
So...
I thought...
[SNICKERS]
Why not...
...let's run away.
Get married.
Live a happy life, you know?
[SCOFFS]
Really?
I mean...
What the heck are you
talking about?!
Uh...
Babe...
I can give you the life
that you want.
All your dreams
will be our reality,
and even all the dreams
your parents have for you.
So...
I am not going to leave
until you say yes.
Why would I say yes?!
[LESTER SCOFFS]
You're on your own!
You think I don't know
all the things you say
to your pals about me...
and my friends, too.
Okay, here we go again.
What?
You find Marla sexy?
Isobel turns you on?
[LESTER LAUGHS]
Baby!
Baby, baby, baby...
I don't even know where
you're getting that from.
Yes!
Your friends
are conventionally attractive.
If I want them,
I can have them.
And yet, here I am,
head over heels for you.
Does that mean anything to you?
[SCOFFS]
Why?
What do I have that they don't?
Well,
for starters,
you're not like the other girls.
I like how...
feisty you are.
And
I love that you are
not intimidated by my...
alpha strong personality.
- [SCOFFS]
- [CHUCKLES]
I fell hard for you.
I am head over heels for you.
For real?
What if Cole tells you to
let him have his way with me?
Would you?
And why would I do that?
Isn't it obvious?
You're just Cole's dog.
All of SOSH knows
you're just Cole's sidekick.
- Shut up.
- Or else what?
You're not even Robin.
You're Alfred.
The butler of Bruce Wayne
AKA Batman!
You're just his slave!
You're not only a mama's boy,
you're also Cole's slave!
- I said shut up!
- Ow!
- [WHIMPERS]
- Mm.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[CHUCKLES]
That's all you can do,
hurt me.
You really know
how to push my buttons, huh?
Yes, I know.
I'm a piece of work.
But when I'm with you,
I always try to be good.
I know that we're good together.
And you know that.
So please,
stop making me chase you...
because you know for a
fact that I am going to.
And I'm not going to stop
because I love you.
[WHIMPERS]
No.
No, you don't.
You just love the chase, period.
When you chase me
you get a sense of purpose
but when you actually
get what you want
you get bored.
I know you...
Daphne Baldemor.
People may call you
different names,
but to me,
you are Daphne.
My Daphne.
And...
we both know
that you are never boring.
[CHUCKLES]
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
Next time...
please just say yes.
Damn you!
Bye!
Answer my calls okay?
Love you!
[THUDS]
For the love of--
What is this, girl?!
You keep creeping out
like some ghoul.
Well,
I'd be the prettiest ghoul then.
Tsk.
What is it?
Look.
I don’t do these one-on-ones.
I don't do heart-to-heart talks.
I never say sorry.
But you are missing the point.
Are you for real?
Is that how you're supposed
to apologize?
Is that how you ask
for forgiveness?
Aren't we just ruining
other people's lives?
Are you satisfied
to play the villain?
Do you have canker sores?
What are... Why are you
talking like that?
Insecure frog!
You're just jealous
'cause I'm multi-lingual.
It's tiring to be always
prim and proper at school.
No one knows this.
But I loved Cole.
Oh!
Oh, gosh.
What a segue, girl.
I didn’t care
about being the mistress.
I just go for what I want.
I look out for no one
but myself.
It’s human nature.
Just like in the animal kingdom.
The weak is abandoned,
the runt is killed.
Thank you so much for that
wonderful zoology lesson,
Mr. Kim.
But I got...
lost in paradise.
What?!
You can't rely on anyone.
Not your loved ones.
Not your parents.
Not a boy.
Just yourself.
Hey, I'm straight!
In all fairness,
those are some abs.
[SIGHS]
What was that?
I got that when I was 12.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
During that time,
Dad already had
a new family.
So did Mom.
Dad migrated to America
and my mom to Canada.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
Grandma was sick.
I was alone.
I got the appendectomy surgery
alone.
I was all alone the whole time.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
I learned an important lesson.
No one will be there for you,
but yourself.
So you got to
put yourself first.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
I get you.
I really do.
I get where you're coming from.
But that's not who I am.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
That's not me.
Girl, you know,
I was raised by two gay parents.
Two selfless gays.
Growing up,
I saw how...
they put others
before themselves.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
They keep giving everything...
to their families.
Their siblings,
their siblings' kids...
who they've sent to school.
I wasn't even blood-related,
yet they adopted me...
and gave me a home.
They cared for me
like their own.
Gosh.
It's overwhelming...
how much they sacrifice...
for others.
But despite their generosity,
despite giving everything,
they keep proving themselves
deserving of acceptance.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
Imagine,
they need to
be successful first,
and not just be
their gay selves.
They had to be successful gays,
of all things!
Isn't that unfair?
There.
That's why I salute
both my dads...
so much!
So...
I'm sorry...
if I offended you...
on the part...
that I felt really sorry
for Ant.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
That's your problem.
You keep thinking about
other people too much.
You lack selfishness.
Hey, that hurts!
It's true, but...
isn't getting back at Ant
an act of selfishness?
The whole revenge thing
against Ant!
Yeah, but you didn’t do it.
I was the one
who did it for you.
[SIGHS HEAVILY]
You wanna know why I
fought for vengeance so bad?
Because you are
the devil's spawn?
Oops.
[SIGHS]
I take on revenge...
so that someday,
I can remember that what
they did to me was wrong.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
The day might come
when I blame myself.
That I might feel that I deserve
everything that happened to me.
So all these...
revenge, chemistry...
rage...
I do all of these...
so that I can remember
and remind myself...
that I deserve...
that I deserve to love,
that I deserve to be loved.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
Even if I’m the only one
who loves me.
Do you still love Cole?
- So gorgeous...
- No...
He took my photos...
This is just for me.
without my consent.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SOBBING]
There is a fine line...
between love and hate.
[MUSIC TURNS MOROSE]
But right now,
all I feel is anger.
[BREATH QUIVERS]
So...
[SNIFFLES]
We need you, Nyx.
[EXHALES]
Our girl group can't disband
before it even launches.
Shut up.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SOBS SOFTLY]
You can't leave us now.
[SCOFFS]
This is embarrassing.
Don't be silly.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Don't worry.
Everything you said...
stays with us.
You're safe with me.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
But...
you said something...
that shook me.
You've accepted that
we're a girl group?
Ha!
You acknowledged it.
[BOOKS CLATTER]
[CURIOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[WARREN GRUNTS LOUDLY]
[CURIOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
So you heard
the whole conversation?
How much did you hear?
N-No, I heard nothing.
Uh...
Well, I heard something but...
it was all gibberish.
Besides, I won't tell a soul.
Don't worry.
Swear on your life!
I swear.
How can I be sure
that I can trust you?
Well...
Uh...
Um
B-Because you kissed me?
[CURIOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
So
I should trust you
because I kissed you?
So you do remember?
O-Of course.
[CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
You can't even
look me in the eye.
Uh...
Sorry. Sorry.
You’re sorry about the kiss?
No, no, not that.
Did you like our kiss?
- Yes...
- Why didn’t you say anything?
- N-No...
- Was it that forgettable?
N-No, Isobel,
it just caught me off guard.
Do you regret it?
No.
I... I liked the kiss.
I mean, the kiss was nice...
Mm-hmm.
Thanks.
[MUSIC TURNS STIRRING]
I-I'm here if you need anything.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Hmm...
Can you please help me...
move on?
Just kidding!
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
"I KNOW YOUR SECRET"
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Good morning, class!
[CHAIR CLATTERS]
Um...
Alright, listen up!
As you know,
our annual Hackathon
is coming up soon.
But this year, we are
doing something different.
Whoever wins the competition,
will be exempted from
the quarterly exams.
But not only that.
Should the winner come from
a regular section like this one,
that person will also be
promoted to the S-class.
So... if I were you,
I would make
the most of this situation,
especially those whose
grades are in danger.
Opportunities like this
happen only once.
Okay?
[SCOFFS]
Mr. Oliver?
Yes, Ms. Javier?
Can I join?
I was the champion last year.
[SCOFFS]
No, Ms. Javier.
With your current suspension,
you're not eligible to
join the Hackathon this year.
Maybe if your...
case is lifted before then,
but that's a big maybe.
[CHUCKLES]
Really, sir?
Yes, Ms. Javier.
[MIGO LAUGHS]
[MOCKINGLY] Really, sir?
Mr. Alcera, do you have
anything to add?
Uh, nothing, sir,
but I'm sorry for--
[OLIVER]
Okay, so be quiet, then.
Okay.
[OLIVER] Alright, let's start.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[SCOFFS]
[MOUTHING] You're ugly!
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
[DOOR SLIDES OPEN]
Nyx!
I'm so glad you're back.
- Can't you walk any faster?
- I missed your beautiful face.
I know, right?
According to my calculations,
there was a 60% chance
that you'd return.
And I was right.
Silly you. There you go again!
But I did miss our girl group.
You know?
We are not a girl group.
- Oh.
- Woah!
- Come on.
- Party pooper.
- Bugger! You too!
- Such a party pooper!
That's not what I heard earlier.
Oh!
I might as well
leave again.
Fine. We’re a girl group.
See? We're clicking. I love it!
Now, we really, really need
a name for our girl group.
Like this very moment.
Yes, we do.
We'll decide on that next time.
But for now,
back to the game plan.
So...
who's our next target?
[INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING]
[APRIL] Migo.
- What an entrance.
- You're here?
- She came out of nowhere.
- Oh, hey!
- Now that's an entrance.
- Like a mushroom.
You really hate
your ex that much, huh?
I can feel your anger,
your rage.
It's seeping through.
I'm just being strategic.
Migo protects the boys online.
Taking him down
will weaken their group.
And yes, you're correct.
I hate Migo.
With all my heart.
Well...
if you think about
the Bifurcation Theory
as a metaphor,
getting rid of Migo
will cause a change
in the system’s conditions
which will lead
to a tipping point.
And I know exactly
how to take Migo down.
[ISOBEL] Mm...
You really hate him.
Love it.
There will be a SOSH Hackathon.
It's a coding competition where
the winner gets an advantage,
such as getting exempted
from the next quarterly exams.
Migo needs to win
the Hackathon
because he's failing.
[SCOFFS]
How could he not?
He's always sleeping in class.
I'll join the competition.
Once I'm in,
I'll crush that stupid Migo.
He's so easy to distract,
especially when he gets cranky.
I did it before,
I can do it again.
His grade average
won't be enough,
he'll get kicked out of school,
and I will get my revenge.
[LIGHT CLAPPING]
Okay, okay.
Cold.
Calculating.
Ruthless.
I'm impressed.
Thank you.
But we have a tiny problem.
We're all banned
from competitions
because of our suspension.
Ugh!
After all that yapping?
I mean, was that
entire speech for nothing?
Yapping?
What's that? Is that like a
native word from Tondo?
Bitch, I already told you,
I'm from Cubao.
[INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING]
Girls...
I have an idea.
Oh!
I think I can find a way to
get you into that Hackathon.
But...
I need you guys
to trust me.
[INTRIGUING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Did you mean it?
W-What?
When you said you would
do anything to win me back.
Oh, of course! Why?
Well, there are upcoming events,
and the girls and I
want to join and compete
Maybe you can convince
Principal Mckenna
to let April join the Hackathon.
And if she wins,
we get to compete
for honors again.
April?
Wait,
why would you
want to help my sister?
She's your sister. Don't you?
You know, Marla,
I know you're kind,
I've always liked that
about you.
but you're not that selfless.
I just don't believe it.
[SCOFFS]
Okay, you caught me.
After all, we're on
the same boat.
I feel bad for her.
But I'm doing this for myself.
I'm just giving April
some leverage,
but I know that I have
the right to graduate
and to choose what college
and internship I want abroad.
Not because I'm smart,
and not because I'm pretty,
but because I know,
and you know that I deserve it.
Then you'll be eligible
to be the top one
and earn awards, is that it?
Would that be a problem?
[CHUCKLES]
Um...
Wait.
Why would you think
Principal Mckenna
would listen to me?
You know, Marla,
I already talked to
her regarding that.
You did?
Of course.
Even if you didn't ask me to,
I still did it, Marla.
Actually,
I've already asked her
many times over
to clear your records.
So your suspensions
won't be reflected.
And even when our video
scandal leaked, Marla,
we never filed a complaint
to the school...
because I know...
you'd never do that.
But what else can I do, right?
I mean,
you've already pinned me
as the bad guy,
as if...
I've never been kind to you.
To your eyes.
Aren't you curious?
Don't you ever wonder,
even once,
who leaked your video?
Actually,
the perpetrator got away clean.
The cameras were gone.
Not a trace online,
according to Migo.
It's like everything vanished,
Marla.
There's nothing I can do
but to move on from it.
Perhaps, you should...
move on as well.
I would gladly move on,
if you help me.
Your dad has donated
so much to the school,
and there's also
Lester's connection.
And also,
you’re so charming,
I really believe that
you can sweet talk your way
to Principal Mckenna’s heart.
Or
Or what?
You demand it.
You're Cole Javier.
And if I do this,
you'll get back with me?
Hmm...
I'll consider it.
You're only gonna consider?
Come on.
That's a big ask, Marla.
You're asking me to
expend my social capital
on you and the girls.
That can't be all I'm getting.
You can't be that lucky.
Why?
Am I not worth it?
Okay. Okay, okay.
I'll... I'll do it.
Okay, thank you!
[EXHALES DEEPLY] Shit!
[SOFT TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
[KEYPAD BEEPING]
[LINE RINGS]
Hey, Lester.
I need you
to do something for me.
Just be quick,
okay?
[SCHOOL BELL RINGING]
Have you seen Lester?
Not yet.
Look for him later, okay?
Cole! Cole, Cole!
- Hey! Not a step closer.
- Cole, what the hell?
That's fine, Charmaine.
Cole, why would you do that?
Why'd you let April
join the Hackathon?
Why?
I'm just helping my sister.
I thought you didn't care
about her?
You know better than I do? Huh?
Oh, my God.
Are you trying to get back
with Marla, bro?
[LAUGHS]
Bro!
That's spaghetti code, bro!
- Come on! It's so obvious!
- Can you just stop already?!
She’s just using you
to get to you, man, she's...
She's just...
using you, can't you see that?
I know what I'm doing.
Oh, my god, bro...
Can't you see?
We can all see it.
She's just using you,
just to get to you...
- to get to us!
- No... no.
Just relax.
Bro!
Why, bro? Please!
What'd you say, huh?
What did you say again?
- Don't call me "bro".
- Hey? Whoa!
Hey! Hey, hey!
Is there a problem here?
Huh?
[CHUCKLES]
[COLE] What?
If April beats me
at the Hackathon,
I'll get kicked out!
If I'm gone, who's gonna
protect all of you then?!
If...
if I'm gone
you're all going down next!
Is that a threat?
Hey.
Your job...
is to protect us online.
You can do that shit
anywhere, even in hell.
What if they take me out,
if I'm done for,
you guys are next.
Then don't lose.
Beat my sister!
You're such a wimp.
if you'd ever lose to a girl.
What, are you gay?
Of course not!
Then it's settled.
Beat April and stop
being a fucking wussy!
Okay, okay.
I'll just find another way
if I'd ever lose.
Hackathon hasn't started yet,
but, you're thinking as if
you've lost already?
Thinking like a loser.
Good thing I'm ten steps ahead.
Am I right, Lester?
Correct.
Catch.
[LAUGHING MOCKINGLY]
- There.
- What's this?
The coverage of the Hackathon.
[SCOFFS]
Now,
if you still manage to lose,
then you’re fucking hopeless.
Okay?
That's why my sister left you.
Come on, this is just
a waste of time.
Here, hide it.
What's my name again?
Earl.
Good.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SNIFFLES]
[SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING]
[SINISTER MUSIC CONTINUES]
Hackathon starts in 10 minutes,
and you have
your assigned computers,
and your names are placed
on your respective tables.
Later,
you will enter stage left,
and if you get eliminated,
exit stage right.
And...
here are your complimentary
snacks and refreshments.
If you have any questions,
just tell me.
I’m Warren, by the way,
I'm your stage manager.
- Good luck later.
- [STUDENT] Thank you.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Are you okay?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
April...
April!
April, my loves.
Are you ready to lose?
Are you ready to lose face?
[BOTH LAUGHING SARCASTICALLY]
Good luck.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
You're cute today, huh.
I know.
Cheers!
For sportsmanship.
Okay... if you say so.
[MIGO GULPING]
[HOST] Welcome to State
Omni-Standard High Hackathon!
Today, our coders will
fight for the title of
Best Programmer
at State Omni-Science High!
From our eight finalists,
only one of them will win.
Our contestants
will battle it out
in a series of bouts.
This will be
a single elimination round
as they climb up the ranks
to be crowned
the Best Programmer.
With our first match,
please welcome,
Migo versus Marco!
[CHEERING, APPLAUSE]
Yes!
[CHANTING] Migo! Migo!
- Kings of SOSH!
- Whoo!
Migo! Migo! Migo!
Kings of SOSH!
Thank you. You may
now take your seats.
Players ready?
In 3, 2, 1 andcode!
- [LESTER] Let's go, Migo!
- [EARL] Whoo!
- [SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
- [KEYBOARD CLACKING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[HOST] Time's up!
Migo has won! Congratulations!
[CHEERING, APPLAUSE]
- [HOST] Alright!
- Come on!
[HOST] And let's move on
to our second match.
Please welcome
April versus Sofia!
[CHEERING, APPLAUSE]
[HOST] Get ready.
In 3, 2, 1
Code!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
Time's up!
Winner...
April!
Congratulations! Excellent job!
[CHEERING, APPLAUSE]
Alright!
From our eight contestants,
we have finally narrowed it down
to our two finalists.
They have one more challenge
ahead of them,
and whoever wins this will
take home the Coders' Award.
And for our final round,
we have April Javier!
- Boo!
- [CHEERING, APPLAUSE]
[HOST] Migo Alcera!
- Boo!
- Yeah!
[CHEERING, APPLAUSE]
Go, Migo!
You know what, just give up.
You'll just embarrass yourself
in front of your friends.
- [HOST] Once again...
- Why? Are you scared?
[LAUGHS]
Why would I be scared?
I'm way better than you.
You know that.
- You know, April...
- Title of Best Programmer...
your hoo-bris will be
your demise.
[APRIL LAUGHS MOCKINGLY]
You mean "hubris?" [LAUGHS]
But, seriously, Migo,
you still have a chance
to back out.
This will be a single
elimination round
as they climb up the ranks
- to be crowned
- [BOTH YAWNING]
the Best Programmer.
- You know...
- These coders will race
I can help you pass
all your exams.
You don't need this competition
just to pass.
[SNICKERS] I don't need
your help.
Daphne, what's our probability
of success?
Both coders will get the
same question to answer
in this allotted time.
It's high! April's success rate
is at 87%.
- [BOTH CHUCKLE]
- Perfect!
Perfect! Perfect!
[HOST] Good luck to all
our contestants!
[YAWNING]
- Sleepy?
- Let's get this
- competition rolling!
- [GROANS]
You're a boring rival.
Your face is boring!
[MAN SCREAMS]
Make some noise! Wooh!
[YAWNS]
[GROANS]
Uh, April?
- April?
- Present!
- I'm present!
- Present.
Oh, shoot!
[HOST] Good! Okay.
Uh, please take your positions.
[QUIRKY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MIGO YAWNS LOUDLY]
Marla: "What did you do?"
[PHONE CHIMES]
Isobel: "I just wanted to give
April the upper hand.
I created a powerful
sleeping pill
and put it in Migo's
bottled water
but I don't know
why April is sleepy too."
[APRIL] There's your seat.
[HOST] Looks like
our contestants are...
- ...feeling a bit sleepy.
- Go away!
Nyx: "Bonkers!
April can't lose here!"
[HOST] Maybe it's too easy
for you both, huh?
Daphne: "That's what I'm saying!
Impulsive choices!"
- [MIGO] Snap out of it!
- "We're cooked!"
Isobel: "At least I did
something to help.
- [HOST] Alright, Migo.
- How about you?"
- [HOST] lease take your seat.
- Marla: "Enough.
Arguing will not help
the situation.
We need to keep April awake."
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
[EXHALES]
[HOST] Let's begin
the final round.
Coders, ready...
In 3...
2...
1...
- Go!
- Alright! Yes!
I think our host needs
a co-host today!
Yeah! Right? Wooh!
[CHEERING, APPLAUDING]
Thank you for this
wonderful night of welcoming!
We all have a surprise
for April,
do you all know that?
It's her birthday, guys,
so let's greet her!
Happy Birthday, April!
[CROWD] Happy birthday, April!
Very good!
Happy birthday, April!
I think she can't feel it yet.
I don't think she does.
She's got birthday blues.
So I think we need to sing her
a happy birthday!
Yes!
[HAPPY BIRTHDAY SONG CUE]
[SINGING]
Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday,
happy birthday...
Happy birthday to you!
Yes, she got woken up
because it is her birthday!
- It's your birthday, isn't it?
- [GRUNTING]
It's still not enough,
I suppose...
I think we need
more music, right?
Right? Right!
We wish for a song, DJ!
Beat drop drop
that beat down low!
DJ?
Yes?
DJ, the music!
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
[NYX] Okay, yes!
Okay! Hey, yo!
Hey, yo!
When I say, "boom!"
you say, "burn!"
- Boom!
- [CROWD] Burn!
Boom, boom!
[CROWD] Burn! Burn!
Very good!
Your turn, your time to shine.
When I say, "boom!"
You say, "burn!"
Please wake up and
finish this, good grief.
- Boom?
- Burn!
Hold up, she's still got
something up her sleeve.
Of course,
she won't just back down!
Show us what you got, come on!
Show it! There! Yeah!
Okay, go! Twerk!
Lower!
- [CROWD] Lower! Lower!
- [APRIL GROANS]
- Lower!
- [CROWD] Lower!
Lower! There!
Ms. Rodriguez?
Yes?
Yes, I think that's enough.
Okay!
Okay, you may now take
your seat, please?
- It's down to 83%!
- Thank you for your wonderful
- Okay, I got this. Okay? Wait.
- intermission, Ms. Rodriguez!
83%.
[HOST] Our participants
need to concentrate.
Alright, contestants, proceed!
It's over for you, April!
[MIGO GROWLING]
[YAWNS]
[GROWLING]
[MIGO GROANING]
Guys, what happened?
We're no longer following
the program.
And can we keep the music down?
We're like a
community festival here.
This is a Hackathon!
Keep the music down!
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
[MARLA] Warren? Warren!
- Huh?
- Can you do me a favor, please?
Can you give this to April
and make her drink it.
Why? W-what's this?
Just let her drink it.
Right now!
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Uh... O-Okay, got it.
Right now, please?
Go, go, go!
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MIGO SHOUTING]
[YAWNS]
April?
Drink this.
- [MIGO GROANS]
- No.
- I have to work on this.
- Just drink this.
[MIGO GROANING]
Okay, I get it already.
[APRIL YAWNS]
[MIGO GROANS]
[MIGO GROANING]
We're here.
Fix yourself.
Thanks a lot, Carl!
[MIGO] Woo-hoo!
- April! April!
- [MIGO SHOUTING]
[MIGO] You think
you've won, April?
Stop!
[MIGO] I'll win this! [LAUGHS]
Wooh!
I can't...
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[YAWNS] I really can't anymore.
[THUDS]
Oh, shoot!
[GASPS]
April?
She's sleeping.
Timer pause.
Wooh!
- She fell asleep, Sir.
- Wake her up!
- April?
- April!
Wake her up already!
- April? Wake up.
- April?
She's not waking up!
Probably exhausted
from all the studying.
Panel of judges,
what should I do?
One of the contestants
fell asleep.
This contest is going
to drive me crazy.
Judge?
Psst! Hey?
- Huh?
- [WARREN] April?
Uh...
[WARREN] April...
Okay, since Ms. April Javier
is sleeping, dreaming,
and can no longer continue...
Mr. Migo Alcera, you are
still not the winner, okay?
However...
you can choose any opponent
from the previous contestants,
or...
maybe someone out here
wants to challenge Mr. Alcera?
Anyone from the audience?
[WHISPERING]
[CLAPS]
I go for Marco Dela Rosa!
The loser that I beat earlier!
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
I volunteer Marla Briones!
I second the motion!
I third the emotion?
[HOST] Wow, volunteers?
What's this, the Hunger Games?
Uh...
Migo...
do you accept Marla
as your challenger?
T-That'll do!
I can beat her
with my eyes closed.
Uh, Marla,
do you accept the challenge?
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Yes.
Okay!
Uh, can we have
a 15-minute break?
Okay?
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CHUCKLES] We're back at 88%!
[CURIOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
- Marla?
- Hmm?
Can I talk to you?
Why?
It's important.
[CURIOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
Come on.
What is it that you wanted
to talk to me about?
I have to get back
to the competition.
Are you sure?
Why? You don't think I can win?
No, it's not that.
Earl, show Marla.
Uh...
M-Migo and I developed...
- a program--
- And Lester!
M-Migo, Lester, and I
developed a program
where we could
create a powerful virus.
Mm-hmm.
D-Do you remember
that anonymous user
who uploaded all your nudes
to the school's online bulletin?
We've been trying to trace them,
but...
they're well protected online.
To top that,
every device that
manages to hack them
automatically gets a virus.
Can we cut to the chase, please?
T-The only thing
that can kill a virus
isn't strong protection...
but a more power--
Bu-- [SIGHS]
But a more powerful virus...
Bingo!
...that can defeat it.
Yes.
And we did it.
[MOUTH CLICKS] Yes!
We accessed the profile
and we traced it back to...
Cole's IP address.
Cole?
[EARL] Let me finish.
We tapped into
all the CCTV cameras
in Cole's house,
and...
[CLACKS]
Look very closely.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Marla...
Are you sure you want
to help the person
who leaked all your nude photos?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]