♪Hey, you, you, you,
why is it you again?♪
♪Always stumbling upon
my little secrets♪
♪Falling on my brows, my lashes,
even the strands by my mouth♪
♪Like my favorite kitten
on a rainy spring afternoon♪
♪Hey, you, you, you,
why is it you again?♪
♪You effortlessly awaken
my protective instincts♪
♪Hitting all my little thoughts,
my doubts, and my temper♪
♪Like my favorite beer and fried chicken
in autumn, or spicy boiled fish in winter♪
♪Why is it you again?
That sweet way you speak♪
♪As if the whole world knows
my mind is full of you♪
♪Why is it still you?
That secret smile behind your cool facade♪
♪I might as well play along.
Let me protect you♪
♪Why is it always you?
The smile at the corner of your lips♪
♪Before I knew it, the words blurted out,
"I like you. I only like you."♪
=Love Has Fireworks=
(Based on "Investment Men and Women"
by Hong Er on Jinjiang Literature City)
=Episode 12=
Hello, are you here
for the fire inspection?
This way, please.
Dang...
I saw the inspection records.
You failed the last inspection.
Don't be nervous.
You've prepared very thoroughly
this time.
Look, from the fire extinguishers
over here
to the fire hoses and the inspection
and maintenance records here,
it's all very well done.
If you do this every time,
it makes our job much easier, right?
But there's one thing. Come take a look.
This...
The alarm shouldn't be obstructed.
Otherwise,
it'll affect its sensitivity, okay?
They don't really have
any major issues here.
It's just that the fire equipment
is expired.
That's something to focus on
in future inspections.
Nothing else, really.
Team leader.
My...
My stomach feels a bit upset.
Can I...
Go on, hurry.
I'll wait for you up ahead.
Okay.
Ms. Fang.
My mom asked you to spy on me,
didn't she?
From the moment I entered the building,
I noticed
you were secretly following me.
From when we started
the fire inspection until now,
about two hours have passed.
During that time, you haven't done any
actual cleaning work.
You've just been secretly following me.
It's too late to start now.
I led you here just to remind you
that the security cameras are on.
I'm afraid
if the building management sees you,
they'll think you're
slacking off and fine you.
Why would they fine me?
Mom.
You called Ms. Fang,
and she let you cover her shift?
Well, she knows that I...
Aren't I doing this for your own good?
For my good?
Or to spy on me?
However,
your disguise just now
was actually quite successful.
I really didn't recognize you.
Well, that's your fault.
You wouldn't tell me who she is.
So I had no choice
but to find out for myself.
So, did you find anything?
Well, today,
so far,
I haven't found anything.
Mom.
Nothing has even started yet.
You don't need to worry about it.
I know what I'm doing with my love life.
Besides,
regarding Ms. Fang,
I think you should go
to the management office
and explain the situation.
If there's really a fine,
I'll pay for it.
Son.
What I did today
won't affect your job, will it?
No, not at all.
Don't worry.
I got a call.
What?
Hello?
Team leader, okay.
I'll be right down.
I have to go, Mom.
Okay, you should go.
I'll... I'll leave right away, too.
Come home early.
I know.
So, for today's inspection,
it's all finished.
Overall, we're satisfied.
However...
Mom.
Jun.
I've been home for a while.
Why aren't you back yet?
I just finished
the fire inspection here.
I just left the building.
Mom, I have to go now.
Jun,
is your stomach bothering you again?
The meeting isn't over yet.
Why did he hang up?
Did you hear what I just said?
Yes, I heard you.
You're writing our group's report.
Write clearly which departments
have what problems and when
the corrections will be completed.
(Where has she gone?)
Any other questions?
(She's gone in the blink of an eye.)
Okay.
Let's start with a slow jog.
Watch your breathing.
Keep your body upright.
That's it.
Good, that's it.
Psycho.
I wasn't talking about you.
Slow down your pace.
Keep your body up.
Watch your breathing.
Let's pick up the pace.
Sis, what's wrong?
What is this thing?
Are you done following me?
I'm not following you.
I just happened to be jogging here, too.
What a coincidence.
Goodbye.
Let's go. We'll run this way.
Keep up.
Within three days,
I'll finalize the entire plan
and give it to Chairman Liao.
Then, all you have to do is recheck
the calculations
I've already done each day.
No problem, Boss.
Boss,
I really can't imagine
who else could sort out this mess
for Shanlifang Hotel
in such a short time.
Boss, let's go.
- Let's go.
- I feel...
I feel like I've forgotten something.
I just feel uneasy.
- It's okay.
- Wait for me.
Thanks.
Qian Fei. That question
you asked me this afternoon,
did you figure it out?
I did.
Thanks to you.
Thank you.
It's nothing.
We've all been where you are now.
Don't generalize.
That wasn't me.
Actually, I'm quite curious.
Like, I've been at Hejing Securities
for three years,
and now I'm working
with you who are from Zhizhong.
People in investment banking
are actually always pretty tense.
They talk fast.
How do you manage
to seem so relaxed?
I'm older than everyone else.
If I don't learn to let go,
I'd be trading my life for money.
This line of work is all
about physical endurance, you know?
I'm planning to work
for a few more years
and then change careers.
To do what?
I haven't decided it yet.
Maybe I'll go back to my hometown.
I'll find a wife first,
and then we'll open
a private kitchen restaurant
or a bar, something like that.
(Pretentious Li: Want a ride home?)
Our field is where the youth shine.
Look at me, I'm almost 40.
It's time to step back
and live a simple, happy life.
That sounds nice.
(Want a ride home?)
That way,
you're your own boss on your own turf.
You should definitely do it.
(Qian Fei: No.)
I can do it.
You can do it.
(Aren't you cooking in?)
We're here.
Goodbye, Mr. Li.
Goodbye, Boss.
Qian Fei.
(Notification: Po Ming is now live.)
(Click to enter the live stream)
Top lane, get ready to group up.
Wait. Wait for me to get there
before you engage.
Stun them. I've got my ultimate ready.
(Po Ming)
(Food delivery)
(Failed)
(Grand Chancellor: Open the door.
Have dinner first.)
What the heck?
Grand Chancellor.
No more gifts in the livestream.
If you send anything else,
I'm blocking you.
(Po Ming)
(Grand Chancellor: Oh.)
Hello, Po Ming.
Stay right there.
How long do you plan
on stalking me, you creep?
Please, let me explain.
I'm really not stalking you.
I just happen to be
in the same public places
that you're in.
And I just happen
to observe your daily life.
You've really redefined
my understanding of the word "stalking."
You were the one waiting
for me at my company, right?
Yes.
And now, you're having food delivered
to my doorstep.
With this kind of behavior, someone more
timid would have
either called the police
or been scared to death by you.
Did I scare you?
I'm sorry.
I'll be more careful next time.
I'll try not to let you find out.
You want there to be a next time?
What I mean is,
next time, I want to be able
to look at you openly
and then do these things for you.
Fine. I'm calling the police right now.
Besides, I already took a picture
of you following me.
No.
Now, you're putting your hands on me?
Let me tell you something.
There's a limit to being a fan.
Do you know why I don't show my face
when I stream?
It's to avoid obsessive fans like you.
I'm not an obsessive fan.
I'm definitely a true fan. True love.
You're definitely truly sick.
Actually,
I just want to get to know you
a little better.
Fine.
For today,
since you're a friend
of Qian Fei's tenant,
I'll let it go.
But if there's a next time,
I'm definitely calling the police.
Do you understand?
How can I make it so you don't see me,
but you can't forget me?
This place's food
is getting worse and worse.
Really?
Tell me,
how can such a wonderful girl exist?
She's good-looking, has a nice voice,
and she's good at games.
She has personality, a bit of a temper,
and she's independent.
The key is, she can do anything.
She's just so full of life.
I think you've just fallen
for her hands.
Of course not.
I like her as a person.
I like everything about her.
If you like her, then go for it.
Telling me
won't get you a "yes" from her.
But she said
if she sees me again,
she'll call the police.
Call the police?
Look at how dense you are.
She says she doesn't want to see you,
and you just give up?
Use your brain, will you?
But she doesn't like me
being so aggressive.
Shouldn't I respect that?
The Art of War is about strategy.
The Thirty-Six Stratagems
is about tactics.
Tactics serve strategy,
and strategy guides tactics.
Strategically, you respect her.
Be cautious, and de-escalate.
Tactically, you get close to her
and look for a chance.
Applaud if you understand.
I don't get it.
To put it simply,
if you want to pursue her,
if you want to pursue a girl,
you have to be thick-skinned.
Got it now?
Got it.
So, have you won Qian Fei over?
Why so worked up?
I was just asking you
about your progress with your landlady.
Don't be like that.
When did I ever say I was going
to pursue my landlady?
You asking me so suddenly
made me spit out my drink.
You like her,
but you are not pursuing her.
You just want
to be the world's best tenant.
It's not that I don't want to.
It's that I don't want
to think about it for now.
Don't want to think about it?
Or are you afraid
you won't succeed if you try?
From the looks of it,
you've already died
before the battle has even begun.
I mean,
I haven't even said anything yet,
and she's already sworn an oath
to the heavens.
She said she could never
like me in this lifetime.
And if she ever does,
she'll be struck by lightning,
lose her job, and go bankrupt.
Tell me, how could I dare to pursue her?
Even if I dared...
Could she handle it?
She definitely couldn't handle that.
That would be like tempting
the heavens to commit a crime.
Exactly.
Looking at you now,
suddenly, I feel pretty lucky.
At least if I want to pursue someone,
I can.
Failing won't cause
some cosmic disaster.
Let's have a drink, buddy.
Here's to you and your landlady.
May you last one day at a time.
What do you mean?
Are you jinxing me?
Eat.
(What's she up to now?)
(Do Not Disturb)
(Make the City More Civilized,
Make Life Better)
Why are you still up?
Be honest with me.
You and that young lady,
have you made any progress?
You've been coming home
so late every day.
What are you talking about?
I just had dinner with Fei.
The past few days,
I was working overtime.
What kind of overtime?
The kind that doubles your salary?
You're never this happy
when you work overtime.
Tell us the truth.
Son, let me tell you.
On my way back
from the financial center today,
I was thinking.
I think you're hiding something from me.
You kept pushing me away,
telling me to hurry home.
You're hiding something from me.
Yes, you're up to something.
No.
My colleague called me
for a fire inspection.
I... I was working.
Okay, let's not talk about that.
Jun, let me ask you.
How are things progressing
with that girl?
What are her circumstances like?
What's her family background?
What's her character like?
Your mother and I are very concerned.
If this relationship
is going to continue,
your mother and I have a responsibility.
Dad,
you're thinking way too far ahead.
I've just been a bit busy
with work lately.
So busy that I've almost forgotten
what the girl even looks like.
You're busy, huh?
Okay, fine.
I'll set you up
with my troupe leader's daughter.
Mom.
My director just told me today
that my work performance
has been excellent.
By the end of the year, it's very likely
that I'll get a promotion.
No more blind dates for me for now.
It's affecting my work.
A promotion?
You're getting a promotion?
Really?
Then, that would make you
a deputy section chief.
Son...
Why didn't you say so earlier?
You had me guessing
and worrying all day.
You're exhausting me.
This attitude you came home with today
certainly fits with your promotion.
Son.
You... You go get some rest.
- Go to sleep.
- Yes.
Well, you should get some rest.
From now on,
when it comes to daily life,
don't you worry about a single thing.
Yes. We'll take care of everything.
Don't you worry.
You have nothing to worry about.
That's right.
- Go to sleep.
Get some rest.
Our son is getting a promotion.
That's right.
If he gets another promotion after this,
then in this whole neighborhood,
he'll be a role model
for the young people.
An exemplar.
I'll be so proud.
I'm going
to the department store tomorrow
to buy you some nice clothes.
You'll look so respectable
when you go out.
What would you buy me that for?
Isn't that a waste of money?
Why are you being so stubborn?
What time is it now?
Let's go to bed, too.
You go ahead.
I can't sleep at all.
It's like I drank
a strong cup of coffee.
Qian Fei.
(Investment Due Diligence)
Aren't you going to work?
I'm screwed.
I'm late.
Wait for me.
What were you doing
hiding in your room last night?
Studying.
Who was it that said in this world,
only work will not
let down your efforts?
Work won't let you down,
but you have to take it easy.
Don't wear out the work itself.
Just drive.
(Oh, Li Yifei, Li Yifei.)
(The so-called relationship expert.)
(How could I fall for such a weirdo?)
Annual amortization amount...
equals the original price divided
by the effective service life.
Question.
According to our country's
national tax law,
when investing in real estate
as a shareholder,
participating in the investee's
profit distribution,
and jointly bearing the investment risk,
is business tax levied?
No business tax is levied...
Don't get so obsessed.
Where are we?
We're here.
We're at Shanlifang?
What do you think?
Why didn't you wake me up?
I saw you were sleeping so soundly,
I didn't have the heart to...
Your master has a heart of gold.
Aren't you afraid
our colleagues will see?
There aren't many colleagues around now.
Alright, you should get out of the car.
Thanks.
Mr. Wang.
Are you looking for Ms. Fang?
This has been signed
and needs to be given to Ms. Fang.
Give it to me.
If there's anything
you need me to pass along,
just let me know.
After all, it's my responsibility.
You don't have to come over yourself.
Okay.
Thanks, then.
No problem.
Not bad.
He's blushing.
I don't think so.
It's probably just the heat.
Alright, that's progress.
I'll give you a thumbs-up for that.
(Come to the riverside.
The place we met last time.)
Ms. Fang is looking for me.
I'm heading over now.
Zhao.
Ms. Fang.
How have you been lately?
I'm okay.
I imagine you haven't been okay.
I've been giving you the cold shoulder.
Actually,
it's because you made a mistake.
But it's not to punish you.
It's to wait for you
to clean up your mess.
Haven't you always liked
to act on your own?
Writing research reports,
going to Chengdu for due diligence,
and then, without any warning,
blowing up in the meeting.
So why can't you, this time,
act on your own
and give me a pleasant surprise?
I did all that before
to survive in Shanghai
and maintain a bottom line.
But what I need now
is to integrate into the team
and solve problems together
with everyone.
That's progress.
And it's true
that you are different from others.
Thank you for the compliment, Ms. Fang.
What did I compliment you on?
Did I compliment you
for having financial ideals?
For having professional integrity?
Don't you know that you're
both impulsive and foolish?
In the workplace,
we need reckless, uninhibited idiots
like you to be human shields.
Do you know that?
That's why you're still standing here.
Understand?
You're so adorably stupid.
As for Zhizhong,
they've always wanted
to get rid of the potential risk
of financial fraud
from Shanlifang Hotel Group.
So Li Yifei used you as a mouthpiece
to expose everything.
Of course,
Hejing also wants to distance itself.
But our two companies,
whether in terms of background
or our relationship with Shanlifang,
are not entirely the same.
So there are many things Li Yifei can do
that I can't.
Before this,
I told you not to tell anyone else
about Shanlifang Hotel Group's
financial problems.
The original plan was
to mediate as much as possible
and resolve this matter
privately.
Then, we'd pass the review meeting.
But you went and exposed it all.
You've stirred up
the hornet's nest
of Shanlifang Group's vested interests.
A lot of trouble will follow.
Now, you tell me how to solve it.
Have you figured out a solution?
Those messy accounts...
Where do we start calculating, and how?
I hope you can give me an answer.
I...
Ms. Fang, I...
I what?
You've caused such a huge mess,
and I still kept you.
Do you know why?
Because you have an ability
that others don't.
So, like I said,
don't waste your potential.
Don't let one Wang Ruohai
throw you off your game.
Calm down and believe in yourself.
Ms. Fang.
Can... Can I ask you for something?
What is it?
Well,
can I
stop being Mr. Li's special assistant?
Why?
Because...
Because I want to learn from you.
You can learn from both of us
at the same time.
I think Mr. Li treats you quite well.
But I have to remind you,
even though
you're Li Yifei's special assistant,
you're still an employee of Hejing.
All's fair in war.
Killing with a borrowed knife.
Li Yifei is probably an expert at that.
What's with that look?
Is it that bad?
Seriously?
Can you let me focus on my analysis?
No, you can just tell me.
Be quiet.
Let me analyze this properly.
What kind of friend
helps you out like this?
You have to give such
an important document to her in person.
Don't tell me you don't even
have the guts for that.
Your research report
will be a bombshell for Liao Jinshan.
A nuclear-level one, you know?
(Could it be)
(that he's been using me all this time?)
(Shanlifang Hotel Group)
Very good.
You're improving.
We'll finish when the time's up.
Okay.
Hello. Hi.
Hello.
Excuse me, are you Ms. Dang Yu?
Yes.
Great. Just a moment.
Did you order this?
No.
Here, these flowers are for you.
Thanks.
Wait a second.
The customer also asked me
to read the card out loud.
That's not necessary.
No way.
Sis,
let's hear it.
Yes.
This is part of my job.
Please understand.
Okay.
Ms. Dang Yu,
you are the sky,
you are the earth,
and you are
the only superstar in my heart.
That's it?
There's one more thing. Here.
The customer
also asked me
to do this gesture for you.
Alright, I wish you a happy life.
If you're satisfied with my service,
please remember to leave a good review.
Satisfied. Good review.
Thank you.
Bye-bye.
That's funny, huh?
It's fine. Laugh if you want to.
You dare to laugh, huh?
Weighted run, and add another half hour.
Hello.
Excuse me, are you Po Ming?
Yes.
But how did you know it was me?
(Po Ming. Note:
The recipient is a cool bartender.)
Thanks.
Mr. Li.
Are you looking for Qian Fei?
I...
She's already left for the day.
I'm just grabbing something.
See you tomorrow.
Okay.
So eager to leave work.
(Shanlifang Hotel Group)
(Signed for by: Brother Po Ming)
Brother?
Let me see.
I'm a little dizzy.
My blood pressure...
Honey.
What are you doing with my phone?
Go hang out with your brother.
Honey, come on.
What's wrong with my mom?
My blood pressure is high.
You've misunderstood.
Dad, Mom.
Landlady, I'm back.
Landlady.
Do you have that many social events?
Didn't we agree
that you'd focus on learning
from your master?
Your master is already home.
Where are you?
It's so boring being home alone.
(Conference Room)
All's fair in war.
Killing with a borrowed knife.
Li Yifei must be very good at this.
(Qian Fei,)
(you were even able
to let go of Wang Ruohai.)
(Why can't you let this go?)
(He's right.)
(Only work will never let you down.)
(There are no saviors in this world.)
(The only one who can save you
is yourself.)
(Li Yifei: Landlady,
why aren't you back yet?)
(I'm worried about my personal safety.)
(Where are you?)
(Landlady, say something
so I know you're alive.)
(You haven't been kidnapped,
have you?)
(Voice Call)
(Qian Fei)
(Asset Management Plan Appears)
(Li Yifei: Where are you?)
(Landlady, say something
so I know you're alive.)
(Conference Room)
(Qian Fei: Ms. Fang, here's a plan to
resolve Shanlifang's asset management.)
(It can boost efficiency by two-thirds.
I hope to discuss it in the meeting.)
(Asset Management Plan Appears)
=Love Has Fireworks=
(Next Episode Preview)
So, tell me.
You have such a 180-degree change
in attitude.
Why?
The workplace is a battlefield.
Being too outspoken can often lead
to you being used by others.
What do you mean?
Ms. Fang.
I'd like to talk to you
about my work responsibilities.
Come on.
Long time no see.
♪There's no need
to know the ending from the start♪
♪Let the melody play through the chords
with the wind♪
♪There's no need
to keep every promise from the past♪
♪Leave some surprises
for the unknown in life♪
♪There's no need
to force things between two people♪
♪Perhaps I'll feel alone,
yet still find you there for me♪
♪There's no need
to dwell on right or wrong, nor fear♪
♪A hug means more
than countless apologies♪
♪I'll send you into the wide world♪
♪To live with passion
and become who you truly are♪
♪A quiet shoulder♪
♪Like a harbor waiting
for your wandering soul♪
♪I'll wait for the day
you return to a simpler life♪
♪The lights of home warm the night♪
♪A companionship that lasts forever♪
♪Shining brightly
like the stars and the moon on high♪
♪I'll send you into the wide world♪
♪To live with passion
and become who you truly are♪
♪A quiet shoulder♪
♪Like a harbor waiting
for your wandering soul♪
♪I'll wait for the day
you return to a simpler life♪
♪The lights of home warm the night♪
♪A companionship that lasts forever♪
♪Shining brightly
like the stars and the moon on high♪