♪Hey, you, you, you,
why is it you again?♪
♪Always stumbling upon
my little secrets♪
♪Falling on my brows, my lashes,
even the strands by my mouth♪
♪Like my favorite kitten
on a rainy spring afternoon♪
♪Hey, you, you, you,
why is it you again?♪
♪You effortlessly awaken
my protective instincts♪
♪Hitting all my little thoughts,
my doubts, and my temper♪
♪Like my favorite beer and fried chicken
in autumn, or spicy boiled fish in winter♪
♪Why is it you again?
That sweet way you speak♪
♪As if the whole world knows
my mind is full of you♪
♪Why is it still you?
That secret smile behind your cool facade♪
♪I might as well play along.
Let me protect you♪
♪Why is it always you?
The smile at the corner of your lips♪
♪Before I knew it, the words blurted out,
"I like you. I only like you."♪
=Love Has Fireworks=
(Based on "Investment Men and Women"
by Hong Er on Jinjiang Literature City)
=Episode 8=
Look.
Isn't that someone wearing white?
I don't know about outside,
but there's definitely
someone wearing white in this car.
When you feel like
something's behind you,
never turn around.
Haven't you heard?
Everyone has three flames behind them.
Every time you turn your head,
one goes out.
One turn, one flame goes out.
And once all three are gone,
you're done for.
Don't turn around.
He's right behind us.
♪What matters to me is what you need♪
♪No more, no less.
I only hope I can give it to you♪
♪What I treasure is what I have♪
♪Bit by bit, I only hope
you're there with me♪
♪Those sweet promises and words of love♪
♪Like fireworks
lighting up the midnight sky♪
What are you doing?
I just wanted you to lie down
so you'd sleep more comfortably.
Let me drive.
You?
Can you really drive?
Don't sell me short. I got
my driver's license when I was 18.
Stop fooling around.
Come on.
Hurry up.
No, no, no.
How did I sleep for two hours?
Didn't I tell you to wake me up
in fifteen minutes?
I tried.
You slept like a dog.
Brake! Brake! Brake!
What happened?
What happened? What do you think?
Get out of the car.
Dangerous.
Do you realize what you're doing?
If you hadn't grabbed
the steering wheel,
we wouldn't have ended up
stuck in the mud.
If I hadn't grabbed it, you would've
driven straight into the lake.
You still blame me
for touching the wheel?
What do we do now?
I'll try backing it out first.
Wait outside.
Be careful.
I don't think it's working.
What do we do?
It's stuck.
All four wheels are buried.
What now?
Goodness. No signal at all.
I've got nothing either.
This is a low-lying mountain area.
It'd be strange if there was a signal.
Wait here.
I'll go check over there.
Come back. I'm scared.
Quick.
There's no one around.
That won't do. No one's here at all.
Are you cold?
Hey.
I did the math.
Before the navigation said
there was no road ahead,
we passed through a village.
After that, we drove for 19 minutes.
Then, the speed limit
was 25 kilometers per hour
because of the gravel road.
Which means
we're only a little over ten kilometers
from town.
If we can't
get the car out tonight,
then first thing tomorrow morning,
we'll go look for help.
What do you think?
I thought you were scared.
Turns out you were calculating all this.
I am scared.
But it doesn't help.
We've got to stay calm
and think things through
to figure out a solution.
Right. It's a good plan.
But there isn't anyone around.
We have no choice.
We can't just stand here
and do nothing.
We can't just keep waiting.
Let's move around a bit.
Don't freeze out here.
Come on. Get moving.
You're doing it wrong.
Show me the right way.
I'll do one. Follow me.
Go ahead.
Watch carefully.
One, two, three, four.
Old man, are you doing physical therapy?
Have you been watching
too many romance dramas?
Yeah.
That's enough.
I'm tired. I'm going to sleep.
Listen.
Do you hear that?
Stop being annoying.
This trick doesn't work anymore.
There's a sound.
Sounds like an engine.
It's a tractor! Quick!
Over here!
Our luck isn't that bad at all.
Someone came to help us
first thing in the morning.
Not only did they pull our car out,
but they even pointed us
in the right direction.
That just proves I'm a nice person.
You know?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Focus on driving.
(Xin You: I've uploaded everything
you wanted to this link.)
(You were right. Not everyone
is driven purely by profit.)
(In the right hands, it can reveal the truth.)
Hey.
Xin You messaged me.
What did he say?
Pull over. Quick.
What's wrong?
- Pull over first.
- Wait.
Look.
Look at this.
What?
Xin You sent me the link
to Shanlifang's original Chengdu data.
Look.
Oh my goodness!
That's amazing.
I told you.
We misunderstood him.
He's a nice person.
Come on. We've got a huge job
ahead of us.
Hurry.
Our hard work paid off.
Hungry?
What did you buy?
We came all the way to Chengdu,
so I bought some souvenirs.
This is for you.
Fermented chili bean paste?
You bought this for me?
Why would I buy it for you?
The store gave it away for free.
It seemed like a waste to throw it out.
I figured you always put this
in your stir-fried eggplant.
It's really good.
Make it more often. I like it.
What did you buy?
Why did they give you so many freebies?
You didn't buy all this for yourself, did you?
Fine. Don't take it then.
You said I could order
whatever I wanted.
Throw them all away.
Who said I didn't want them?
It'd be such a waste.
Does that mean you'll prepare
a pair of chopsticks for me tonight?
You promised
you'd make extra dishes for me.
You haven't made them yet.
What dishes?
Ms. Fang hasn't agreed to reinstate me.
What's there to celebrate?
There'll be something
to celebrate tonight.
Forget it.
I don't want to get my hopes up.
The bigger the hope,
the bigger the disappointment.
As long as I've done my best,
that's enough.
No!
No what?
Listen.
I'm eating those dishes
no matter what.
We've been to Chengdu and Taoyuan.
What else is there to be afraid of?
We risked our lives
to get this information.
And a director at Hejing
is enough to scare you?
Just wait and see.
The whole Shanlifang
is going to feel the shock.
Why are you so worked up?
Are you making the food or not?
I promise. Whether I get the job or not,
I'll prepare a pair of chopsticks for you.
So embarrassing.
What exactly did you buy?
They gave you so many freebies.
Take me there. Come on.
None of your business.
Buy one, and get nine free.
What a narcissist.
Hello, Mr. Jiang?
What?
I'll be right back in Shanghai.
I'll send you my flight number.
Okay.
What's wrong?
My dad got hurt.
Is it serious?
I don't know.
Try not to worry too much.
Your dad will be fine.
I haven't said you can eat yet.
No eating until I say so,
okay?
Come. Eat.
Good dog.
Come.
Come on, Maomao.
Maomao.
Come here.
Go.
Old Man Li.
What's your problem?
You used a trick to lure me home?
How childish can you get?
I'm not playing along anymore.
No, no.
Yifei, I wasn't lying.
I'm injured.
Where are you hurt?
I twisted my ankle.
I was walking the dog,
and I twisted my ankle.
So this is the "serious injury"
Mr. Jiang said
left you bedridden?
Well,
Jiang always exaggerates.
It's not that serious.
But I really was hurt.
Are you okay now?
I'm fine.
Good. I'm leaving then.
I'm not done talking.
Don't go yet.
I'm busy.
If there's nothing else, I'm going.
Who said I had nothing to say?
Did you even give me a chance?
Fine, go on.
Yifei,
you haven't been home in a long time.
Stay for lunch this time.
Maomao.
Come here.
Go on. Go find your big brother.
Don't call me Old Man Li next time.
Am I that old?
Eating with you is no different
from eating alone.
You're quiet.
You made that rule when I was little.
No talking at the dinner table, right?
Not exactly.
Only you're allowed to talk.
Well, you can talk.
It's okay. I'm used to it.
How have you been?
Busy.
Busy with everything.
Just busy.
You're just keeping yourself busy
for no good reason.
Wasting your time.
Yeah.
Compared to your big business deals,
everything I do
is a waste of time.
Let's talk business.
Since you're so concerned
about me,
I've decided
to invest a little in your company.
How does that sound?
No.
If you want to invest,
it's either that you believe in
the project
or that you expect a return.
You're making it sound like charity.
Bet there are strings attached.
Forget it.
I don't have any strings attached.
Really?
Don't you just want me
to come back and work for you?
Is that a condition?
Shouldn't that be
what you're supposed to do?
Besides,
it won't affect you running your...
What's called again?
What Laxi...
Laxi?
It's Fulaxida.
Fulaxida.
It won't affect it.
Look,
you help me run Qiansheng,
and I'll support Fulaxida.
We can tackle both together.
There's no need, Mr. Li.
I mean it.
Why are you so stubborn?
Listen.
I can't stand by
and watch my son's company
get crushed by someone else.
Crushed?
What are you talking about?
Don't tell me you don't know.
I heard someone's trying to poach
your executive with high salaries.
And your senior management
is tempted.
Who did it?
Who else could it be?
That Liao.
Aren't you helping him go public?
Why is he working against you?
How do you know about this?
What kind of question is that?
If it's a career my son cares about,
how could I not keep an eye on it?
Yeah.
I can tell.
You really do care about me.
Anyway, I'm the only one
who can give my son a hard time.
Nobody else gets to.
Mr. Li,
I appreciate that.
Well,
I can handle Chairman Liao
myself.
And Fulaxida doesn't lack money.
So stop worrying about it.
Take care of Maomao,
and manage your
Qiansheng Manufacturing well.
Also,
stop trying to trick me.
I'm busy. You've got
your life all figured out. I don't.
I haven't settled down
and built a career yet.
Hold on.
Speaking of which,
when are you getting married?
Is it with that Gui Lili?
Enough.
Stop pretending you don't know.
Didn't your paparazzi tell you
that Gui Lili and I broke up?
You didn't know?
Tell me what happened.
Stop.
Don't start with the sarcasm.
I know what you're going to say.
Look at you.
Old man, let's make a deal.
Stop getting overly involved
in my personal life.
Can I ask you for one thing, too?
Can you stop calling me "old man"?
Have you seen such a young old man?
Alright.
You're young.
I am young.
I'm full, young old man.
I'll get going.
You know what?
Breaking up with Gui Lili
was the right choice.
Bring home someone
you can actually build a family with.
This is yours?
It's a big box. You won't finish it all.
I'll help you.
Premium Da Hong Pao tea.
The water temperature is 100 degrees.
Got it.
I thought you didn't drink tea.
Mr. Jiang.
Yifei,
you didn't drive here?
I pawned the car.
Isn't that inconvenient?
Pick one from the garage.
No need.
I'm a young guy who sold the house
to start a business.
Driving a luxury car wouldn't suit me.
I'm off.
Right, Mr. Jiang.
Mr. Jiang, don't you have
a Polo?
Lend it to me.
I'll have my dad get you a bigger car.
Alright.
You really came up
with strange ideas.
Alright. Take it.
(Chairman Liao Jinshan's
60th Birthday Banquet)
Here's today's menu.
Please review it.
(Reception Desk)
Why are there so many similar dishes?
What's going on?
Ms. Liao.
Shiyu.
Dad.
Why are you here so early?
There's plenty of time before it starts.
I just came to take a look.
I'm handling everything here.
Don't you trust me?
I'm a workaholic.
Can't help it.
Go ahead and get busy.
You picked
all of these?
I carefully chose every single dish.
What do you think?
Do you like them?
My daughter
has always been thoughtful
and meticulous.
Of course, I trust you.
It's good you came early.
You can spend more time with Ruohai.
Ruohai?
You're calling him so affectionately.
Dad.
Ruohai.
Chairman Liao.
Yes?
Ruohai,
didn't you prepare a gift for my dad?
Just a small gift.
Happy birthday, Chairman Liao.
Dad,
Ruohai specially had this
custom-made for you in Italy.
Open it.
He put a lot of thought into it.
Come on.
Let me see.
Why is there only one?
It's a golf glove.
You only need one.
Do you like it?
Try it on.
It fits perfectly.
Perfect.
Ms. Liao, the cake has arrived.
Okay.
I'll go check it out.
I'm indifferent to worldly things.
At my age,
I don't care about
money or status anymore.
The only thing I care about
is sincerity.
If you didn't have the sincerity
to pick out a birthday gift yourself,
why bother giving one at all?
I'm sorry, Chairman Liao.
It won't happen again.
Remember this.
You can lie to me.
But if one day
I find out
that you've deceived my daughter...
I'm saying if.
I'm back.
How's your dad? Is he doing any better?
(Da Hong Pao Tea)
Well, try not to worry too much.
When people get older,
they'll have some health issues.
It's normal.
I made you some white fungus soup.
Have some.
If you stress yourself out, you won't
be able to look after your dad.
Sit.
Drink it while it's hot.
Thank you.
It's nothing.
Well,
go ahead and drink.
Rest up early.
Thanks.
No problem.
Comforting.
So comforting.
Someone made white fungus soup for me.
Right, my dad said
he has an important task for you.
What kind of task?
It's probably related to the IPO.
Easy. I'll help you.
My dad is entrusting you
with something important.
It means he trusts you.
He's starting to rely on you more.
You should be happy about that.
Almost done.
Landlady.
Landlady?
Where is she?
I'm hungry.
Yangzhou fried rice.
(In-Depth Report on Shanlifang Hotel)
Not bad.
She finished it this quickly.
He ate the fried rice.
Looks like it's nothing too serious.
How dare he mess with my document!
(I'm not freeloading. I polished
your report. Consider us even.)
(Expansion Through Acquisitions)
This guy
may have a bad temper,
but he really knows his stuff
when it comes to professional expertise.
Done. I'm going to send it.
♪Like my favorite kitten♪
(Research Report on
Chengdu Shanlifang Hotel)
(Sending email...)
(Sent successfully)
We're done!
♪You effortlessly awaken
my protective instincts♪
♪Hitting all my little thoughts♪
♪My doubts, and my temper♪
♪Like my favorite beer
and fried chicken in autumn♪
(The revisions are not bad.)
(Thanks.)
(Qian Fei)
(Is a verbal thank-you all I get?)
♪You effortlessly awaken
my protective instincts♪
♪Hitting all my little thoughts♪
(Wasn't the fried rice
my thank-you gift?)
♪Like my favorite beer
and fried chicken in autumn♪
♪Or spicy boiled fish in winter♪
(I want tea eggs.)
(The kind you left
in the fridge last time.)
(I see.)
(I was wondering why they disappeared
after only two meals.)
(You ate them.)
(We're out of tea.)
(I brought back a box.
It's by the door.)
(We don't have any eggs.)
(A carton just got delivered.
It's in the fridge.)
(You win.)
♪Before I knew it,
the words blurted out♪
♪I like you. I only like you♪
Li Yifei has a thing
for flashy nonsense.
Da Hong Pao, my foot.
As if there's that much
authentic Da Hong Pao to go around.
They're just selling the packaging.
It smells nice.
This tea smells amazing.
Hey.
Is that real Da Hong Pao?
It is.
Stop knocking. I'm sleeping.
What a waste.
If I'd known, I would've sold it
and bought you
some loose tea leaves instead.
They would've worked just fine
for tea eggs.
In that case,
I should take a photo
with my tea eggs.
Her cooking skills
are pretty impressive.
Nice.
(Zhizhong Construction Investment)
Ms. Fang.
Do you have a minute?
Would you like to come to my office
for a drink?
Sure.
Please.
Wait here.
This way, please.
Here's your coffee.
Alright.
Close the door for me.
Ms. Fang, working with you
these past few days
has shown me
what true professionalism looks like.
I lost to you in the competition
for Shanlifang's lead underwriting deal.
I'm completely convinced.
If you have something to say,
just say it.
Let's skip the flattery, shall we?
I doubt you invited me for coffee
just for small talk.
You're right.
Since we're being direct,
I won't beat around the bush.
At today's meeting,
I noticed you kept holding back.
I assume you're keeping something
to yourself.
So, I was hoping we could sit down
and have an honest conversation.
What do you think?
I think you've been
holding back more, Mr. Li.
You went to Chengdu recently?
You were on vacation, weren't you?
You sure know a lot
about my whereabouts.
You disappeared
in the middle of the meeting.
It was unusual.
Of course, I paid attention.
How was it?
The Chengdu trip.
Haven't you received
the investigation report?
I see.
I was wondering
how a girl like Qian Fei
managed to dig up so much information.
Turns out she had someone
backing her up.
You've got that wrong.
We happened
to run into each other
during the investigation.
Neither of us was backing the other up.
We got the results
through our joint efforts.
Did you know each other before?
Sort of.
That girl nearly made me miss
the bid submission once.
I have to say,
the people you train
really are something else.
She's no longer one of Hejing's people.
Is that so?
But she told me
that you really wanted her
on the project team.
And that it was you who inspired her
to go to Chengdu
to look for the original materials.
I think
she may have misunderstood.
Misunderstanding or not,
I think this girl
has a lot of potential.
Really?
Take the Chengdu trip, for example.
Rather than saying I helped her,
I'd say
she helped me.
Why don't you recruit
such an outstanding talent to your firm?
I'd love to.
But she isn't interested.
She has no interest
in Zhizhong.
That girl
is set on following you, Ms. Fang.
So you invited me for coffee
to put in a good word for Qian Fei.
Not exactly.
You were the one
who brought up Qian Fei just now.
What I actually wanted to discuss
was Shanlifang's accounts.
Since we've both discovered problems,
we can't pretend we know nothing,
can we?
True.
What do you think, Mr. Li?
We have to bring this issue out
into the open.
Otherwise, we'd both
be breaking the law.
That's true.
But if we do that,
I'd feel awful about Qian Fei.
How so?
You know what Mr. Liao is like.
If we bring this up,
he might not terminate
Hejing's contract right away,
but he'll definitely take it out
on Qian Fei.
If that happens...
Qian Fei has worked so hard
to get her job back.
I understand that.
But what if things don't work out
the way she hopes? Is it fair?
Even so,
I can't go up against the Chairman.
I can't just force the issue.
I won't be able to protect her.
I see.
How about this?
I'll be the one
to bring it into the open.
As for Hejing,
you can pretend
you know nothing about any of this.
What do you think?
No.
We can't let Zhizhong
shoulder this alone.
That wouldn't sit right with me.
I'd feel terrible about it.
I understand.
I just think that
as long as we can pressure Shanlifang
into cooperating with a new audit,
that's our goal.
As for who takes the fall,
it doesn't matter.
Alright then.
Thank you, Mr. Li.
(Zhizhong Construction Investment)
Cui.
Call HR.
Okay.
It was just a dream.
I knew it.
Good things only happen in dreams.
So many missed calls.
Hello?
Hello, Yu? You called me?
I just woke up.
Gosh, you were sleeping?
=Love Has Fireworks=
(Next Episode Preview)
Qian Fei.
You must be thrilled.
I got transferred,
and you filled in my place.
What are you on about?
Stop pretending.
Isn't this all thanks to you?
Have you actually fallen
for your landlady?
With my standards?
You think I'd fall for her?
I have something to ask you.
One question for one meal.
I can cook for you.
Do you dare eat it?
What do you mean?
♪There's no need
to know the ending from the start♪
♪Let the melody play through the chords
with the wind♪
♪There's no need
to keep every promise from the past♪
♪Leave some surprises
for the unknown in life♪
♪There's no need
to force things between two people♪
♪Perhaps I'll feel alone,
yet still find you there for me♪
♪There's no need
to dwell on right or wrong, nor fear♪
♪A hug means more
than countless apologies♪
♪I'll send you into the wide world♪
♪To live with passion
and become who you truly are♪
♪A quiet shoulder♪
♪Like a harbor waiting
for your wandering soul♪
♪I'll wait for the day
you return to a simpler life♪
♪The lights of home warm the night♪
♪A companionship that lasts forever♪
♪Shining brightly
like the stars and the moon on high♪
♪I'll send you into the wide world♪
♪To live with passion
and become who you truly are♪
♪A quiet shoulder♪
♪Like a harbor waiting
for your wandering soul♪
♪I'll wait for the day
you return to a simpler life♪
♪The lights of home warm the night♪
♪A companionship that lasts forever♪
♪Shining brightly
like the stars and the moon on high♪