♪Hey, you, you, you,
why is it you again?♪
♪Always stumbling upon
my little secrets♪
♪Falling on my brows, my lashes,
even the strands by my mouth♪
♪Like my favorite kitten
on a rainy spring afternoon♪
♪Hey, you, you, you,
why is it you again?♪
♪You effortlessly awaken
my protective instincts♪
♪Hitting all my little thoughts,
my doubts, and my temper♪
♪Like my favorite beer and fried chicken
in autumn, or spicy boiled fish in winter♪
♪Why is it you again?
That sweet way you speak♪
♪As if the whole world knows
my mind is full of you♪
♪Why is it still you?
That secret smile behind your cool facade♪
♪I might as well play along.
Let me protect you♪
♪Why is it always you?
The smile at the corner of your lips♪
♪Before I knew it, the words blurted out,
"I like you. I only like you."♪
=Love Has Fireworks=
(Based on "Investment Men and Women"
by Hong Er on Jinjiang Literature City)
=Episode 15=
Of course,
we don't want to see Xinxin Vision
come to an end either.
Our Financial Director
prepared a proposal for you.
If you can find an investor
before the spin-off is completed,
we can assist with the transition.
I will find someone to take over.
I won't give up.
That's the capital market.
It's that ruthless.
Hard work alone
doesn't guarantee results.
Just like you,
the sponsor handling the group's IPO
taught me a lesson this time.
Hejing Securities?
That's right.
I have a friend who was also involved in
Shanlifang Hotel Group's
IPO sponsorship this time.
Who is it?
Maybe we know each other.
Qian Fei from Hejing.
So it's her.
Since Qian Fei is your friend,
then you should have known long ago
that the asset revaluation plan
for the whole group this time
was orchestrated entirely by her.
You could also say
that the spin-off of Xinxin Vision
was prompted under her recommendation.
Hey, pretty, all by yourself?
Hey.
What set you off this time?
Didn't you burn your books
and swear at graduation
that you'd never study again?
You're being so serious,
even taking notes.
An original English edition?
Not bad.
You didn't even tell me you were coming.
There's no comparison, right?
You know what?
That tenant at my place
is a living embodiment of a picky guy.
All he does
is look pretty and does no work.
He refuses to lift
a single finger for chores.
For someone like him,
I didn't take him seriously at all.
I always thought he was just
the ultimate superficial pretty boy.
Until one day, I suddenly realized
he's not only a pretty face
but also like a wizard.
He can casually show off a skill
and blow your mind.
Living with someone like that every day,
how could I not study?
I get it.
You were motivated
by the pretentious tenant of yours,
right?
Back then, Wang Ruohai
used all kinds of harsh words
just to get you to go to self-study,
yet he couldn't even
make you budge an inch from your bed.
Look at you now.
Thanks.
How does a mere tenant
give you so much motivation?
Well,
wasn't that because
Wang Ruohai was one of us?
You don't need to save face
in front of your own people.
If he called me lazy, I'd just agree.
If he said I was shameless,
I'd just accept it.
But Li Yifei is different.
He's an outsider.
In front of an outsider,
don't you
have to prove yourself?
Wait,
why did you suddenly
bring up Wang Ruohai?
Hold on,
you were the one
who brought him up first.
You called me first and said
he was giving you trouble again.
I came here to help you sort things out,
so don't turn it around on me.
It really is trouble.
Think about it,
it's bad enough that I'm in the same
workplace as my ex-boyfriend,
but now I also have to work with
my ex-boyfriend's current girlfriend.
How annoying is that?
I'm the one who got dumped,
but I've moved on, and I'm fine.
On the other hand,
he spends every day
being awkward and whiny,
trying so hard to avoid me.
If he keeps avoiding me like this,
he might as well just
kick me out of the sponsor team.
It's getting in the way of work.
What if he actually kicks you out?
I'll just fight my way back.
It's not like I haven't done it before.
That's all?
And here I thought you were so tough.
You should have at least
dragged him down with you.
You're all talk.
So you're the capable one?
If you're so capable,
why are you still waiting around
for Lu Ze to finish work?
How is that the same?
How is it any different?
Why did he come here today anyway?
I have no idea. I went
to his office to look for him,
but he wasn't there.
They said he was here,
so I just came over.
I had nothing else to do anyway.
To pick him up.
Pick him up?
Aren't you sweet?
By the way,
here.
Is...
Isn't this the little bear
from the other day?
Didn't we fall short
of the 2,000-yuan minimum that day?
They wouldn't give it to us.
So I went back over the weekend,
spent enough,
and brought it over for you.
So cute!
So chubby!
Do you like it?
No, I don't.
But
don't you think
it looks just like my tenant?
Look. The little gold buttons,
and the little suit.
Especially that innocent, pitiful act.
So annoyingly pathetic.
I'll smack you.
Something's off with you.
How can looking
at a bear remind you of him?
Lately, you keep mentioning Li Yifei.
Is there something going on?
I knew you were going to say that.
There's nothing going on.
Don't overthink it.
Forget it, take it back.
It just annoys me looking at it.
No. If you put it that way,
I can't take it back.
What would it look like
if I carried your tenant away?
I know.
Next time he pushes your buttons
and makes you upset,
you can poke pins into this little bear.
Just poke it.
Poke it.
- To vent your anger.
- Poke you.
Poke...
If he found out,
that'd be hilarious.
Poke it...
Beat it up.
If he found out, he'd be furious.
That's so wicked.
Honey.
You're here.
Finally.
Hurry up and take your wife away.
You two chat for a bit.
I need to take a call.
Hello, go ahead.
Why did you suddenly show up
at the office today?
Don't you know why I'm here?
I came to negotiate with Liao Shiyu.
Negotiate?
Why are you negotiating?
Qian Fei, do you know
how much you mean to Jingjing?
What do you mean by that?
You're not just best friends.
You're sisters, and family.
You're even more
important to her than I am.
Even if she has stayed up all night,
the moment she hears you're in trouble,
she'll rush over right away
to accompany you,
drink with you, and stand up for you,
without a single word of complaint.
She and I are about to get married now.
She's so happy seeing my career thrive,
filled with joy.
She thought we could
go public along with Shanlifang,
cash out on the equity,
and live a peaceful life.
Even last night,
she was still telling me
that we must take you with us
when we go on trips.
But what did you do?
Qian Fei,
Shanlifang needs
to spin off Xinxin Vision
before going public,
and you planned this entire proposal,
so why didn't you tell me?
Even if you just told Jingjing,
it would have been fine.
I'm at a loss now.
No,
I really don't understand why.
about Shanlifang
spinning off Xinxin Vision,
I didn't know anything about it.
There's no need for this.
We are all adults here.
I really didn't know.
There's no need to play dumb, Qian Fei.
Liao Shiyu told me.
The entire proposal was planned by you.
No, Lu Ze...
I will find a solution.
Xinxin Vision won't
just go under like this.
Seriously, you... Listen...
This is so annoying.
A problem came up with my next project.
Drive me to the office.
Okay.
We'll take off first.
Bye-bye.
Hurry up. I'm in a rush.
- Look, he insists I go.
- Don't be angry.
I just looked
through Xinxin Vision's files.
Has it really been confirmed
that it has to be spun off?
Gently.
Are you okay?
I'm perfectly fine.
But in the plan I made,
it didn't even involve Xinxin Vision.
The plan you made was just a framework.
When it comes to actual implementation,
it's not as simple as it looks on paper.
You understand, right?
As for the part about Xinxin Vision,
I checked it myself.
You said it yourself,
you've seen their files.
So you must understand
what the problem actually is, right?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Is there no other way?
Many products developed by their company
have great social significance.
If it weren't for those products,
when I stay in hotels now,
I'd still have to bring
my own bath towels and sleeping bags.
Otherwise, it just feels unsafe.
Just how cheap
are the hotels you stay at?
I'm being serious with you.
Yes.
Come, let's go over there.
Then...
Then why do you care so much
about Xinxin Vision?
Shanlifang Hotel Group committed fraud.
They overvalued
Xinxin Vision's appraised price
and its proportion
in their intangible assets.
But...
This isn't Xinxin Vision's fault.
Should they be the ones to bear
the consequences of a re-audit?
I remember during
the Venture Capital Forum,
you were there too, right?
Didn't you watch Lu Ze's roadshow?
It was brilliant, no?
Yes, I watched it.
A formulaic roadshow.
A textbook example of being superficial.
Watch your tone.
As for Xinxin Vision,
not only are their
financial statements terrible,
but for the past three years,
they haven't developed
a single new product
that can be launched either.
Shanlifang's investment in them
used to be
out of sentimentality.
But later on,
it became a tool
for Chairman Liao to raise money.
The valuation of intangible assets
is the easiest place
to exploit loopholes.
In the capital market, Xinxin Vision
no longer has any value.
Otherwise, why hasn't
any buyer taken over?
Capital is not stupid.
Well,
it's going to be spun off,
and no other company
is going to take over.
Doesn't that mean
all the efforts they made before
will be wasted?
Yes.
The world of capital
is just that brutal.
Hurry up and think of something.
Give me a suggestion.
Alright.
I thought about every possibility
to save it long before you did.
But look at it
from Shanlifang's perspective.
Right now,
any factor that could get in the way
of a successful IPO
must be eliminated.
Xinxin Vision has too much debt,
you know?
Getting rid of it
is the only way.
Understand?
Be professional.
Your technique is actually professional.
Let me help you.
You know,
I can still practice a bit more.
Does it really hurt that bad?
Honestly,
it feels much better
after you massaged it just now.
Well, ride back in my car in a bit.
That's so kind of you?
Are you cooking up
a scheme in your head again?
I know.
You want to order food
and have me cook it, right?
Come on, why are you so petty?
What kind of scheme
could there be in a car ride?
The fingerprint lock at home...
I noticed it seemed broken yesterday.
It doesn't recognize mine anymore.
Re-register it for me when we get back.
Look at your character.
Even the lock rejects you.
Do you get what that means?
I suspect you sabotaged it.
You're full of bad ideas.
Did you rack your brains
and try everything
just to avoid living with me?
I've always been open and aboveboard.
Would I ever stoop to such petty tricks?
Zhao De.
Boss, I didn't hear anything.
Just say whatever you want to say.
Boss, I actually heard everything.
I thought something was fishy
when you two were talking earlier.
What's the deal?
You two are living together, aren't you?
What's your relationship?
- No way.
I just...
I'm his landlady.
I'm her tenant.
Landlady?
No way.
You're my boss's landlady?
Your vibe looks way more
strapped for cash than him, Qian Fei.
Even if you are his landlady,
how could a landlady
live together with her tenant?
Hey, we're housemates, okay?
I let him have one room in my place,
and I live in the other one.
Got it?
No way.
Absolutely no way.
Why is it impossible?
I have
some special circumstances at home.
You wouldn't understand
even if I told you.
Anyway, her place seemed decent enough,
so I'm rooming there for now.
It's just temporary, understand?
Still, it doesn't sound right to me.
Since you live together,
why do you never leave work together?
Exactly.
Isn't it because we're afraid
people like you would judge us?
If people think she's my girlfriend,
it would make me look so tasteless.
Clearly, I'm the one worried
they might misunderstand
and think I'm keeping a pretty boy,
especially one who's so blunt
and doesn't know how to behave.
You know,
just based on how
sharp-tongued you both are,
you two
make a good match.
- Get out of here.
- Stop it.
Who makes a good match?
(Jingjing: Come look
at the new house with me.)
Why are you sighing like that?
The moment I think about
how I affected Lu Ze's company,
I just don't know how to tell Jingjing.
Are you out of your mind?
Lu Ze failed to manage his own company.
What does that have to do with you?
A simple-minded person like you
wouldn't understand.
Well, I don't understand
an overthinker like you, either.
(Incoming Call: Jingjing)
Hey, Jingjing.
You're off work, right?
You didn't even reply to me.
Where are you?
Are we still going?
Yes, we're going.
See you in a bit then.
Quick.
Come check out my design.
How cozy!
What's wrong?
You barely spoke in the car.
Are you tired?
Yeah, a bit.
You designed and bought
everything here yourself?
It's just that Lu Ze has been too busy.
From the renovation until now,
he hasn't had time
to come and take a look.
But it's also because
their parent company is going public.
All the financial statements
and materials
must be provided by the subsidiaries.
He just has to cooperate, right?
Is Lu Ze coming later?
I don't know.
He's not answering my calls.
Forget about him.
I think I can put
some green plants here.
Right?
Put a taller one.
And over here,
we can place
a small fish tank on this table.
With some little fish swimming around,
it'll look full of life.
Jingjing, I want to tell you something.
It's...
Answer your phone first.
Hello?
Yeah, Fei and I are at our new place.
Let me tell you,
everything is ready now.
We're just waiting for you.
Hurry up and make
some time to come see it.
I think it's wonderful.
I'm super satisfied.
Okay.
I got it. Go back to your work.
What's wrong?
He told us to eat.
Something came up, and he can't make it.
What did you want to tell me just now?
Come home with me tonight.
I'll cook for you.
Really?
Let's go.
(Regarding Xinxin Vision...)
(You should be the one
to tell Jingjing about Xinxin Vision.)
Jingjing, I'm almost done.
Try the steamed cured meats first.
Do I even need to try it?
It smells delicious.
Just looking at it makes me hungry.
When are you ever not hungry?
If I had even half
of your culinary skills,
I probably had every man in the world
under my control.
Don't they say the way to a man's heart
is through his stomach?
Has any man ever cheated
just because the other woman
was a good cook?
Hey, you,
I made extra.
Want to eat with me?
No.
Someone already asked me out.
If you'd also like
to have dinner with me,
next time,
make a reservation in advance.
Wait,
why is he so full of himself?
I'm used to it.
He's like this every day.
Can you taste if the sweetness
and sourness are okay? Is it good?
It could be just a tiny bit sweeter.
Got it. I'll know for next time.
By the way,
look,
if Lu Ze's company...
If...
Just hypothetically, I mean,
what if something
went wrong with Lu Ze's company?
What would you do then?
What could go wrong with him?
Even if he has problems,
I'll just carry on with my life, right?
I don't depend on him anyway.
That's true,
but you are getting married after all.
So your futures
are tied together, of course.
Take your time eating.
I'm leaving now.
Just go then.
Stop talking so much nonsense.
Hey, remember to deadbolt the door
when you get back.
Okay.
Why are you acting
like a nagging mother?
If I don't tell him, he won't get it.
Otherwise, I'd have to get up
in the middle of the night to lock up.
By the way...
It's just...
If Lu...
Who is it at this hour?
Who is it?
Wang Ruohai?
What are you doing here?
I called you, but you didn't answer,
so I came up.
Jingjing, you're here, too?
What are you here for?
Let's talk inside.
No.
Just say it here. What's the matter?
Can you transfer the funds
for the house to me quickly?
Right now?
You...
You said before there was no rush,
so I'm not prepared for this now.
I wasn't in a rush before,
but I've run into
a tricky situation recently
and urgently need the money.
I really have no other choice,
which is why I came to see you.
But now, I really don't have
that much money on hand.
How about this?
As soon as I have the money,
I will transfer it to you, okay?
I'll give it to you as soon as possible.
Can you give me a specific date?
How can she give you a specific date?
She already said
she'd pay you back as soon as possible.
I really have no other choice.
Otherwise,
I wouldn't resort to this, right?
How much is left?
Five hundred thousand.
That's a lot.
How do you expect her
to just pull it out of thin air?
Magically produce it?
Do you think everyone is like you,
who can change his face
in a single day after a breakup?
Does that have anything to do with this?
Fine, no more talk.
Wait. I have something else.
Hey, can you just say everything
you have to say all at once?
Qian Fei,
can you leave the Shanlifang
due diligence team?
Why?
Take it easy.
I don't mean anything else.
On one hand, I just think
it's too much trouble for you.
Having to take the subway
must be exhausting.
On the other hand,
I can go talk to Mr. Kong
from Hejing Securities
and arrange for you
to be placed in another position.
Given our past relationship,
the public pressure
is just too overwhelming.
I think
this isn't good for either of us.
What do you mean by that?
If she can't pay you back,
she has to get lost
from Shanlifang first?
Is she an eyesore to you,
or blocking you from
dating the rich young lady of yours?
- Don't cross the line.
- What's the point of saying all this?
Why do you always
have to speak so aggressively?
That's not what I meant at all.
Okay, fine.
Let me ask you this.
If she refuses
and can't pay you back the money,
can you guarantee you
won't pull strings behind the scenes
to kick her out of Shanlifang?
We were classmates after all.
So why do you always
target me like this?
How? I'm asking you a question.
I said...
Enough, Wang Ruohai.
I'll give you my answer now.
Regarding the money, I will
pay you back ASAP, alright?
And whether I stay
in the project team is my business.
It has nothing to do with you.
If you're afraid
of rumors and gossip yourself,
then don't pretend
to care about me here.
This is your biggest problem.
You never dare to face your own heart,
and instead always
shift the blame onto the other person.
Fine, you can leave now.
And never come back.
This is my home, my house.
It has nothing to do with you.
Qian Fei,
let me explain.
No, don't block the door.
Alright, let go.
Don't push me.
Stop blocking the door, okay?
Let me finish.
Why are you always targeting me?
Enough, Wang Ruohai.
- I didn't mean it.
- I said I'll pay you back ASAP.
Alright.
Yes, I know.
Don't push me.
Why are you always targeting me?
What are you doing?
Can't we just talk about this?
Stop hitting him.
Run! Don't worry about me.
Don't worry about me. Run!
Run. Don't worry about me.
Call the police.
Wang Ruohai!
Stop hitting him.
Mr. Wang? Why is it you, Mr. Wang?
Are you alright?
Yeah.
In the middle of the night, I thought
a thug in a suit was robbing the place.
Quick, bandaging Mr. Wang up.
Alright, that's enough.
It's fine.
You guys should go in.
Careful.
Quick, go inside.
Okay.
I'm so sorry.
I really didn't recognize you.
I'm sorry...
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
What could happen to me?
I'm so manly and healthy.
No, what happened?
Don't even get me started.
It's like I've seen a ghost today.
Why did the jinx show up at my door?
What bad luck.
By the way, why did you come back?
I forgot my car keys.
Make sure to thank him properly.
What?
Should I stay a bit longer?
Just in case
there's another home robbery.
No need.
Go tend to your business.
Alright then, I'm leaving.
By the way...
Well...
Thank you.
No need for verbal thanks.
Just cook a proper meal.
Don't just invite me
only when you've made too much
and don't want it to go to waste.
Bye.
Off you go.
Oh,
after I leave,
remember to lock the door.
Bye.
Your tenant is quite interesting.
Do you still have an appetite to eat?
I'm tired, too.
Let's rest a bit
before we get back to it.
What a mess this is.
Have you finished the math?
How is it? Can you pay it back?
Don't even think about it.
My salary is fixed.
Even if the Shanlifang Hotel Group
project gets approved,
I'll only get a bonus once it concludes.
That's still far off.
I'm short by a significant amount.
Then, let me lend it to you.
No way.
That's just robbing Peter to pay Paul.
You're getting married very soon,
and that's exactly when you need money.
You are just someone
who would rather wrong yourself
than trouble others.
What is wrong with Wang Ruohai?
When you broke up, he agreed so readily,
saying himself
there was no rush to pay him back.
Now look at him, going back on his word.
Knowing that you
can't produce the money,
he asks you to leave Shanlifang.
What is this? Isn't this just blackmail?
He just wants you to leave
so that Liao Shiyu
won't be upset if she sees you.
He's such a jerk.
Yeah.
But if we stoop to a jerk's level,
won't we become jerks, too?
How about
I find a way to earn some extra money?
Maybe he really has his reasons.
You're not being kind.
Speaking up for a scumbag like him
is just being spineless.
If you dare to say another word for him,
I'll gouge my own eyeballs out
and leave them by your pillow
to stare at you every day.
All right, I'll listen to you.
Come on. You can go home.
Clean this up in a bit.
(Jingjing: I'm on my way back.
I'll let you know when I get home.)
(I hesitated for a long time today.)
(There's something
I haven't been able to bring up.)
(Part of my work
at Shanlifang Hotel Group)
(involved Lu Ze's company,
Xinxin Vision.)
(I never knew that Xinxin Vision
was going to be spun...)
(Shanlifang needs
to spin off Xinxin Vision)
(before going public,)
(and you planned this entire proposal,)
(so why didn't you tell me?)
Even if you just told Jingjing,
it would have been fine.
I'm at a loss now.
I...
I really don't understand why.
(Liao Shiyu told me)
(that you planned the entire proposal.)
Why does the new plan
happen to affect Lu Ze's company?
Why does Lu Ze
insist that I talk to Jingjing?
How am I supposed to say it?
All you do is stare at me
without saying anything.
What use are you?
Hey.
Stop playing on your phone.
I organized this gathering
specifically for you today.
The girl who's coming in a bit
is a rising star.
She'll be here soon.
I'm talking to you. Who are you texting?
Rising star? No...
(Qian Fei: When are you coming back?)
None of your business.
(When are you coming back?)
(Is something wrong?)
(Li Yifei: Is something wrong?)
(Nothing.)
(You're out having fun, right?)
(It's nothing. I was just asking.)
Qi, let me tell you,
you don't need to introduce
gentle girls to him anymore.
He's not interested.
He's fallen for his tough landlady.
No way.
The landlady
doesn't seem to be his type at all.
I don't believe it.
You should just let the good girl go.
You have no idea.
Yifei is serious
about his feelings this time,
but he doesn't dare to pursue her.
Really?
She said she would
absolutely never fall for him.
If she does,
she'll be struck by lightning,
go bankrupt, and end up on the streets.
Yifei,
to protect her life and fortune,
can only silently
keep his love to himself.
Hey, wake up.
Has your body been
taken over by someone else?
Are you still you?
What are you two doing?
Putting on a double act?
What kind of show is this?
You're criticizing me? Look at yourself.
Have you made any progress? Please?
All you know
is how to play video games all day.
You've played yourself stupid.
And you.
Actually, there's nothing much
to say about you.
All right, that's enough.
I'm heading out first.
Where are you going?
I'm hungry. Going home
for a late-night snack.
Isn't all this food here enough for you?
It's probably not as good
as what his landlady makes.
Then you should just hire a chef.
What's wrong with my landlady?
My landlady is great.
She would never do
something like showing up late.
I just purely dislike the kind of woman
who uses being late
to show off her arrogance.
I'm done talking to you. Bye.
I'm sorry. I got here late.
I don't know why,
but the traffic was terrible.
It's fine.
How was it? Not bad, right?
What are you doing?
Isn't this something Zihao would do?
How did you get corrupted by him too?
I'm just keeping my word.
Come here, let me introduce you.
This is Li Yifei. This is Jin.
Hello.
Let me give you a grand introduction.
Jun.
Not important...
He is important. He's great at gaming.
He's not important.
For this buddy of mine,
he is a bit socially anxious.
Don't mind him.
(Pretentious Li)
(Is there any leftover food?)
(For my late-night snack.)
All you ever think about is eating.
(Shiyu)
Hello?
Looking for me?
Ruohai, why are you outside?
What are you doing?
I was a bit tired from
a busy day at the company,
so I came out to clear my head
and wander around.
Why is it so dark on your side?
I can't see your face clearly.
I want to see you.
Can't you just look when I get back?
No.
I want to see you now.
Look, isn't it quite bright behind you?
I can see it. Go over there.
Okay.
Ruohai,
what happened
to the bridge of your nose?
It's nothing, just bumped it.
It doesn't look like a bump.
Tell the truth.
I had a bit of a verbal argument
with the taxi driver,
and then we got physical.
It's fine.
Why were you so reckless?
You should call the police for that.
It's a small matter.
Why involve the police?
I'm coming over to see you right now.
It's so late.
Why are you coming to see me?
No matter how late it is,
I have to come.
You're injured. Wait for me.
Alright, that's enough.
I'll take off first.
Don't do that.
She's about to go up
and sing in a moment.
Stay for a few more minutes.
Is that her?
She can sing, too?
Exactly.
Not bad. Let's listen.
Hello, everyone, I'm Jin.
Today, I'd like to sing a song
that I wrote myself.
This is for all of you.
An original?
She
is a professional.
Is that so?
♪There were so many
sweet moments in the past♪
Could a girl I introduce to you
be anything less than great?
Yes, it sounds lovely.
See?
♪There are still
so many familiar scents♪
♪So many♪
It sounds great.
It really is quite good.
Her voice is beautiful.
♪Having come here bravely♪
♪I want to tell you,
thank you for once loving me♪
♪In heaven, I'll keep watching over♪
♪Our little house, our warm home♪
You really can't judge
a book by its cover.
She's amazing.
Great singing. Wonderful.
Come here.
You sang so well. That was fantastic.
- Thank you.
- Wonderful singing.
Alright, I'll head out first.
You're leaving already?
Yifei, you're in such a rush to go home.
Do you have a very beautiful
girlfriend waiting for you at home?
Well...
Fei's girlfriend
is not only drop-dead gorgeous,
but she's also a fantastic cook.
No wonder.
I'm also a very good cook.
Fei, would you like
to try my cooking sometime?
Is that so?
That's amazing.
You can sing and cook.
Let's make it next time.
Let's meet up again next time, alright?
- Right.
- Okay.
- Let's lock it in for next time.
- Alright.
Why aren't the lights on?
Quick, let me see.
Who did this? They hit you so hard.
Did you see their license plate number?
I'm fine. It's just a minor injury.
What do you mean by "minor injury?"
Any closer and it would've hit your eye.
Take a few days off.
Take time off?
Forget about it.
Why did you say so?
What I mean is,
the company is doing an IPO,
and there's still a lot of work to do.
A few days won't make a difference.
Ruohai,
about what happened today,
you didn't lie to me, right?
No, what are you thinking?
That's good.
No matter what happens in the future,
you must tell me the truth.
=Love Has Fireworks=
(Next Episode Preview)
Did you save
this food for me on purpose?
Why?
You taught Wang Ruohai a lesson for me,
so thank you.
Let me reheat it for you.
I just want to know why.
I put in so much effort,
and I finally found a new buyer
to take over Xinxin Vision.
Li Yifei,
but you rejected this plan.
Come out!
Get out of my way!
Alright, what's the arguing about?
What are you arguing about?
♪There's no need
to know the ending from the start♪
♪Let the melody play through the chords
with the wind♪
♪There's no need
to keep every promise from the past♪
♪Leave some surprises
for the unknown in life♪
♪There's no need
to force things between two people♪
♪Perhaps I'll feel alone,
yet still find you there for me♪
♪There's no need
to dwell on right or wrong, nor fear♪
♪A hug means more
than countless apologies♪
♪I'll send you into the wide world♪
♪To live with passion
and become who you truly are♪
♪A quiet shoulder♪
♪Like a harbor waiting
for your wandering soul♪
♪I'll wait for the day
you return to a simpler life♪
♪The lights of home warm the night♪
♪A companionship that lasts forever♪
♪Shining brightly
like the stars and the moon on high♪
♪I'll send you into the wide world♪
♪To live with passion
and become who you truly are♪
♪A quiet shoulder♪
♪Like a harbor waiting
for your wandering soul♪
♪I'll wait for the day
you return to a simpler life♪
♪The lights of home warm the night♪
♪A companionship that lasts forever♪
♪Shining brightly
like the stars and the moon on high♪