[One year ago]
Well, we're all around the same age,
with similar goals, right?
We should have each other's backs.
Who knows? We might be friends after the camp.
This isn't a playground.
Have each other's backs?
We're not here to make friends.
Of course debuting is our priority.
Let's all make it so that we can be friends.
Team A, get ready for the stage.
I want to be friends with you.
Wish you luck.
Good luck.
Are you all right?
No, you're not. You're burning hot.
I'm fine.
I'm just cold.
What are you doing?
Trust me.
Just stay like this for a second.
What's with these two?
Stay still. This is a nice shot.
No, no, stay there.
Come on, take the shot. This is realism.
We can make something out of this.
Now, it's time to announce the rankings
for the next stage.
Everyone gave their best
performances during the past missions.
Sadly, the trainees with the lowest ranking,
according to the votes, will be eradicated.
Now, we will proceed
with the first round of announcements.
Hey, Soo An...
Let's make our debut.
If I offer to take you home,
I know you'll say no.
But if I let you go home on your own,
well, I'd worry for your safety.
Which do you prefer?
Yoon Soo An?
You can go ahead.
- Huh?
- You can go home.
Hey, are you okay?
Anyway, it's nice to see you here.
If you want to touch my hand,
you should ask me first.
Is this my fault?
- Huh?
- So I've got to say sorry?
No, I never said that.
Then why are you talking like that?
Why are you acting like I'm being sensitive?
What do you want me to do now?
Let's just be...
classmates.
Even now he's out here defending
some Thai guy who just rolled in,
or what,
is Shin Jae Min into him?
Say what you want about me
but leave Khun out of it.
Khun!
Want to get some ice cream?
Don't let it get to you.
Such jerks.
They're hammered.
Do you think so too?
What?
That I have tapped in out of nowhere.
No, of course not.
Okay. Got it.
Honestly, I...
I just...
Never mind.
See you tomorrow in class.
You're coming, right?
Good luck, classmate.
I knew you drank too much.
I guess you were nervous.
Could you get me some orange juice?
Business.
You used me to get ahead and I did the same,
and you already made your debut,
so isn't that enough?
What more is there? Oh, I see.
Want me to sleep with you?
[Thai pop star Khun rumored to
debut in Korea through PNJS]
I knew this would happen.
The CEO is soft on Khun.
You can say that again.
It's always us hard-working trainees
who take the brunt of it.
They're going to kick one of us out, right?
Who would it be?
Hey. Of course it's going to be Shin Jae Min.
He keeps drooling at guys like a dog.
Did you like it?
You enjoyed it, didn't you?
You think?
What's up?
Oh, hey. Did you see this?
How could you let the article go up
before we even reached an agreement?
I apologize.
But the article didn't come from our side.
The reporters wrote it on their own,
without checking with us first.
This is a matter of trust
within our two companies.
Jeez, we're sorry, okay?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Reporters nowadays don't even try
to cross-check before publishing a story.
But we know better than to let something
so trivial pull us apart, right?
If this is how things are handled,
we can't do business.
The artist's opinion is what matters now.
Well, Khun? Care to share your thoughts?
[Jae Min, we need to work on our group project]
[Where do you want to meet?]
Khun!
Stella!
How did you even get here?
You didn't tell me you were coming.
Of course I should be by your side.
You seem to be doing great.
I'm sorry I wasn't in touch.
No, it's fine.
It's good to see you doing well.
So, are you going to invite me in?
Come in.
Khun!
Stella!
I'm jealous of Hyun Jae.
Hey, if you're so jealous,
step up and debut already.
You keep getting it wrong!
I'm sorry, sir.
What a massive jerk.
Why do you work so hard?
Because I want to do it...
with you.
Jae Min.
I want you to meet someone.