♪Hey, you, you, you,
why is it you again?♪
♪Always stumbling upon
my little secrets♪
♪Falling on my brows, my lashes,
even the strands by my mouth♪
♪Like my favorite kitten
on a rainy spring afternoon♪
♪Hey, you, you, you,
why is it you again?♪
♪You effortlessly awaken
my protective instincts♪
♪Hitting all my little thoughts,
my doubts, and my temper♪
♪Like my favorite beer and fried chicken
in autumn, or spicy boiled fish in winter♪
♪Why is it you again?
That sweet way you speak♪
♪As if the whole world knows
my mind is full of you♪
♪Why is it still you?
That secret smile behind your cool facade♪
♪I might as well play along.
Let me protect you♪
♪Why is it always you?
The smile at the corner of your lips♪
♪Before I knew it, the words blurted out,
"I like you. I only like you."♪
=Love Has Fireworks=
(Based on "Investment Men and Women"
by Hong Er on Jinjiang Literature City)
=Episode 11=
You're back.
Look how happy you are.
You two must, absolutely must
be happy forever.
Congratulations again.
- Cheers.
- Come on.
Cheers.
Wake up.
Stop right there.
You don't need to go up.
Hejing Securities
is empty now.
How did you know I was going
to Hejing Securities?
Not only do I know,
but tomorrow, all the security guards
in the building will know.
Without an invitation,
you won't be able to come here anymore.
It's so annoying.
I already told him
that once he gets all his gear,
I'll let him join the guild.
But he still came to my company
to corner me.
Don't you think he's insane?
But from the way he looks,
he doesn't seem like a bad person.
Have you ever thought
that he didn't come for the gear,
but to see you?
Why would he want to see me?
Like a fan chasing a star?
Silly girl. I think he wants
to pursue you.
In his dreams.
Don't be so quick to dismiss it.
You've really fallen for her?
I really have.
Well, has she fallen for you?
We haven't even spoken yet.
It's okay. Don't rush it.
Take it slow.
Listen to me.
You have to be relentless
in your pursuit.
You see, girls
like guys who are persistent.
Really?
Okay, I'll listen to you.
Then have you been persistent
with your landlady?
Didn't you tell me last time
that you like her?
I'm different.
My situation is different.
For me...
No, we're at different stages.
Get it?
How is it different
when it comes to you?
My goal is very clear right now.
I just want to keep living here,
to live here securely,
to live here happily,
and not get kicked out.
That would be a win for me.
That would be a victory.
So pathetic.
Young Master Li, is that still you?
The love expert?
Wrong.
This isn't being pathetic.
This is called a wise man
submits to circumstances.
Fine.
Oh my mom!
What are you doing?
Trying to scare me
and taking advantage of me.
You're the one
who called me "mom", okay?
Why are you sitting here in the dark
so late at night?
I was thinking...
Why is it that people
never...
never follow the path set by their GPS?
They all go off course, more or less.
Some want to go east,
but end up going north.
Those who want to be in a relationship
end up focusing on their careers.
And those who are determined
to build a career
get tied down by family.
Isn't that strange?
Not at all.
It's just traffic.
If there's traffic,
you'll just take a detour.
In the end, the GPS will always get us
to our destination, right?
There's no such thing
as going off course in life.
It doesn't exist.
Because our final destination
is surprisingly the same.
Really? Where's that?
The cemetery.
However you live, it's still a lifetime.
Taking a few detours
to see more of the scenery
is a good thing, isn't it?
All right, that's all
for today's lesson.
To pay you back for the dinner you made.
Good night.
I knew it.
I'm screwed.
(Please wash the dishes when
you're done. Or there's no next time.)
Got it?
Hey.
What you wrote was, "Please wash
the dishes when you're done," right?
I'm not done eating yet.
Washing them now would be such a waste.
A waste of food.
What?
No.
Washing dishes is such a waste of time.
Right?
From now on, can we switch
to something like disposable containers?
That's not eco-friendly,
and it's a waste of money.
No, I mean,
how can you be so lazy?
Can't you just wash them yourself?
How about I teach you
how to do it today, step by step?
We're almost late.
There's no time, is there?
How about this?
Take my car.
It's a free ride. No charge.
And you definitely won't be late.
You're being so kind?
I've always been a very kind person.
But I do have some flaws.
I've hated washing dishes
since I was a kid.
And now that I'm grown up,
I don't really feel
like filling that void.
But I can drive.
I get it.
Leave it here. I'll wash it.
Let's go.
Please.
Wait.
You have to bend over gently.
Get in the car like this.
See? You try it again.
Come on.
Do you think you're filming a TV show?
Just drive.
Is all this necessary
just to get in a car?
What do you know?
This is called being cool.
Seatbelt.
Put it on.
Hold on tight.
Are you crazy?
Let me tell you something.
From now on,
I'll take care
of the disposable containers.
You won't have
to waste time washing dishes.
No.
I told you before I was going
to teach you how to save money.
Yes.
The first point is,
you have to avoid all disposable things.
You should use reusable things.
I think this car of yours
is pretty good.
It's nice.
Much better than the last one.
How is it better?
It's small, so it saves petrol.
Anyway,
in my eyes, all cars are the same.
The most important thing
is that it has to be fuel-efficient,
right?
The second point of saving money is
transportation.
It's so expensive.
You should be like me
and take public transportation.
Take the subway or the bus.
Wait.
You really don't
know how to wash dishes?
Yeah.
You must have been spoiled
since you were a kid.
You're not even some rich kid.
How could you not even have
the most basic life skills?
Hold on.
What makes you think I'm not a rich kid?
Okay.
You're a rich kid.
A rich kid
who doesn't rent his own place
and has to live with a housemate.
And who doesn't have money
to buy a car,
so he has to borrow someone else's.
Living paycheck to paycheck,
wearing knockoffs.
A broke rich kid.
Is that how you see me?
Me? Does it matter how I see you?
The important thing is,
you care too much about
what other people think.
That's why you buy all these things.
You're trying so hard
to use external things
to prop up your confidence.
Did I hit the nail on the head?
Fine. It seems that in your eyes,
I can't be a rich heir.
But don't be discouraged.
I believe that with my help,
and with you putting
in a little more effort,
we can more than manage
to become self-made millionaires.
Okay.
This third point is,
you absolutely
cannot eat out anymore.
Do you know how expensive that is?
You have no idea how much money
you save by cooking at home.
Don't eat out. It's too expensive.
Of course, you don't know how to cook.
You don't have that skill.
So you don't have to save this money.
It's okay. I can't cook,
but you can, right?
It's no extra trouble to cook
for one more person, right?
You can make
a little extra for me...
Stop.
What's wrong?
Pull over.
Um, Shanlifang is right ahead.
I can still make it if I run now.
I'll just get out here.
That way, no one will see me
getting out of your car
and think there's something
going on between us.
What could be going on?
You're just catching a ride.
Well, thank you, Mr. Driver.
Look at you, such a tomboy.
Stop the car! Do you hear me?
Li Yifei, are you a child?
Are you in elementary school?
Look how uncoordinated you are.
You...
You're insane!
Ms. Fang.
Dacui will be in charge
of the presentation slides.
Two days.
I need them within two days.
Okay.
Since we've helped Shanlifang Group
find such a major loophole,
it's up to all of you
to figure out how to solve it.
Mr. Li, do you have anything to add?
I have nothing to add.
Then that's all
for today's morning meeting.
I hope everyone works hard.
Ms. Fang.
You haven't assigned me any tasks yet.
Daisy,
is there anything I can help you with?
For me,
I don't need anything for now.
You can take a break.
Well, let me know if you need anything.
Okay.
Mr. Cui.
Do you need my help
organizing the presentation slides?
Not for now.
I'll call you when I need you.
Ms. Qian.
Here!
This isn't a school.
Why are you saying "here"?
I have a very tricky matter
that I need you to handle.
Come with me.
What is it? What's the matter?
Pour me a glass of water.
I'm so thirsty.
Can't you get it yourself?
Come in.
Here's your water.
Come back.
What is it? Is there anything else?
Your superior isn't finished talking
and you just leave?
You have no situational awareness.
Close the door.
Sit.
Do you know why Ms. Fang
is giving you the cold shoulder?
Whether Ms. Fang
accepts my apology or not,
I'm mentally prepared for it.
She didn't tell me to get lost
in front of everyone today,
so I'm already very grateful.
Grateful?
Do you really think she kept you here
for your own good?
Let me tell you,
the best way to ruin a person
is to let them be idle.
Well...
I supported you exposing
Shanlifang Hotel Group's
financial fraud.
But I didn't support the way you did it,
spilling everything out so explosively.
Put yourself in anyone's shoes.
No one wants their subordinate
to act so recklessly.
But I am a little curious.
Knowing your personality,
you probably would have secretly
left some kind of contingency plan
with Fang Yun
and then given us all a surprise.
So tell me.
What did you prepare?
If I were some
powerful female lead
who could counter every move,
I wouldn't have been left out
to dry by my boss and colleagues.
I was just taking it one step at a time,
but I forgot that when you can't
go any further down the road,
you're actually burdening
those walking with you.
All right.
If you need any help in the future,
just let me know.
I'm just doing odd jobs now anyway.
Zhao, please schedule a meeting
with Chairman Liao for me.
I need to do some damage control.
You're truly impressive, Chairman Liao.
You're quite impressive yourself.
I'm just joking with you.
Anyone my daughter likes
must be impressive.
I asked you to come practice with me
because I think you're a smart person.
Shiyu has high standards.
She wouldn't use worldly criteria
to choose the person she likes.
As for me,
I believe that capable people,
as long as the stage is big enough,
will shine.
You didn't have opportunities before.
That was fate.
Now, you do.
You have to seize your fortune.
Yes, you're right, Chairman Liao.
I've given you the opportunity,
but I have yet to see your ability.
The pre-listing preparation materials
for Shanlifang Hotel Group
were found by the joint sponsorship team
to have problems with the asset data.
I'm sorry, Chairman Liao.
I was in charge of this matter.
Failing to uncover
such a major oversight
is entirely my responsibility.
Young man,
don't take the blame for something
that isn't your fault.
Taking the fall for someone else
won't necessarily
earn you their respect.
These reports...
Without my approval,
who would dare to falsify them?
What disappoints me is that,
as someone Shiyu approves of,
you were the last one
to discover the problem.
Did you know
that the original financial data from
Shanlifang Hotel Group's headquarters
was dug up by that Qian Fei?
Qian Fei?
That name isn't unfamiliar, is it?
This young woman is quite something.
She wasn't the only one
who knew about this.
Her cleverness lies in
knowing how to find an opportunity.
She chose a moment
when no one
could possibly suppress it all.
It caught even
a veteran like me off guard.
Please don't worry, Chairman Liao.
I will do everything I can
to make up for it.
I heard that this Qian Fei
was fired before.
Then, she used every trick in the book
to get into the Shanlifang Hotel Group
project team.
I wonder who she was targeting.
Of course,
she only ruined a few of my minor plans.
It's no big deal.
Nothing is a big deal
except life and death.
I trust
that you have the ability
to lead the team
and cooperate with the sponsorship team
to resolve the re-auditing issue.
Remember,
before, we falsified for profit.
Now, we must discard the false
and retain the true.
Sacrificing small gains
for the bigger picture
is something that must be done right.
As long as Shanlifang Hotel Group
goes public successfully,
everything else
is insignificant.
Thank you for your trust, Chairman Liao.
I hope so.
I hope Shiyu
wasn't wrong about you.
Mr. Liao.
If I get the chance, I'd really like
to have a proper match with you.
Me?
I'm all brute force.
To play a good game,
you have to learn strategy
and calculate your shots.
In that regard,
you're the expert.
Not me. Well, a computer is even better
at calculating shots,
but it's useless
if it can't hit the ball.
My back is stiff. I can't rotate.
Sometimes when I'm on the course,
I'm afraid of others rushing me.
Why are you being so modest?
Come on.
I have to toast you.
People nowadays are so different
from us.
They agree to something,
and then they just go back
on their word.
I wouldn't dare.
You wouldn't dare?
The last time we met,
you were very clear
that I wanted you to ensure
the successful IPO
of Shanlifang Hotel Group.
You were supposed to see it through.
But what happened?
Do you think you're too clever?
I bet
that you found out about Shanlifang
Hotel Group's off-balance-sheet assets
a long time ago.
That Qian Fei
was just a finger you borrowed,
a tool you used to expose this matter.
Mr. Liao, the way you put it...
It sounds like
I was bullying a young girl.
It's all business, Mr. Liao.
Qian Fei was just doing a job
she was paid for.
As for me,
I won't explain myself.
I'm here to apologize.
I'll accept my punishment.
Alright.
You've already put me
in checkmate like this.
How can I pursue this any further?
Going through all this trouble,
putting in so much effort,
aren't you just trying to tell me
that whether Shanlifang Hotel Group's
initial public offering succeeds or not,
you're the one in control, right?
Mr. Liao,
Shanlifang Hotel Group
is your life's work,
your child.
I'm very clear on that.
Having it go public smoothly
is your greatest wish.
But we, the sponsors,
are the doctors you hired
for your child.
Wouldn't you agree?
We have an obligation
to help you remove those
malignant tumors that must be removed.
But when I tried to discuss it
with you directly,
you refused.
You even tried to threaten me
with Fulaxida,
forcing me
to help you conceal the fraud.
I really can't do that, Mr. Liao.
The law doesn't allow me
to do that either.
Chairman Liao,
I believe Shanlifang Hotel Group
is an exceptionally outstanding company.
Restating the financial reports,
in the short term,
will harm the interests
of some shareholders.
But if you look at the long term,
it has much greater potential
for growth.
What do you think?
Well said.
But without any warning,
you just went and stirred up this mess.
I heard
that your joint sponsorship team
is in chaos.
And you still haven't found a solution.
So tell me,
what exactly should be done?
Here's the thing.
I will definitely come up
with a plan as soon as possible.
I'm just waiting for your word.
As long as you give the nod,
give up those beneficial relationships
that shouldn't have been maintained.
At this point,
what else can I do?
Yifei,
ensure that Shanlifang Hotel Group
gets listed successfully.
I'm counting on you.
Okay.
I'll finish it.
It's a shame.
Why didn't Shiyu find someone
as bold and decisive as you?
By the way,
Shiyu definitely doesn't know
that you're Li Qiansheng's son.
You're quite something, kid.
You've hidden it for so long.
Well,
then Mr. Liao, you have
to keep helping me hide it.
If you cause trouble for me,
I can't guarantee
that Shanlifang Hotel Group
will be successfully listed.
Then I can't guarantee
that Fulaxida's core team will return.
Alright.
The old ginger is spicier.
No, that's not right.
Now, it's the young phoenix
that sings clearer than the old.
(Fei)
Narcissist.
(Zhizhong's Due Diligence Report on
Zhongda Games Project Summary, Li Yifei)
(Financial Forecast
for the Reporting Period)
(Table 4-3: Profit Forecast Adjustment)
(Forecast Results
After Due Diligence Adjustments)
(A project Li Yifei did
the year before last)
(actually became a textbook example.)
(So impressive.)
Mr. Li.
Here are the documents you asked for.
Look at this data.
It shows that Shanlifang Hotel Group's
previous commercial
intellectual property
strategy was unsuccessful.
In the mid-range hotel market,
they went from having a solid position
to now being pushed out of the top tier.
Financing, number of new hotels,
gross profit margin...
Shanlifang is falling behind
in all of them.
You knew that just by glancing
at the table of contents?
Continue.
Okay.
(This spoiled guy)
(Investment Due Diligence)
(is such an expert on the business.)
Zheng.
(He glanced
at the contents of the report,)
(and grasped the key information.)
(No wonder he's a top-tier
sponsor representative.)
(And I'm just here doing grunt work.)
For revenue composition
and expense analysis,
downplay the negatives.
Emphasize the operating profit margin.
Highlight that a 60% occupancy rate
is the break-even point.
High occupancy rate,
high average room revenue,
and high profit.
Also, mention the impact of commissions
and the contribution from franchising.
Excluding hotel management fees
and amortized marketing expenses,
the self-built, directly-operated hotels
have a profit margin of over 28%.
That's all for now.
Okay.
This needs to be changed.
Done.
If you don't understand something,
just ask me.
(I know I'm handsome, but it's not
appropriate for you to stare so openly.)
(Only by studying hard)
(can I become the person I want to be.)
(Keep it up, Qian Fei.)
(Financial Director)
(Shanlifang Hotel Group)
What are you doing here?
My dad asked to see you today?
He was looking for you
about the accounts, right?
Sit down and talk.
He must have given you a hard time.
He's so annoying.
The group's data falsification
was all covered up by him.
Now that his original plan
can't be realized,
he's taking it out on you.
Don't be mad.
In a few days,
I'll help you get back at him.
Don't be so childish.
After all, your dad is the chairman.
He's the one
who sets the overall direction.
So his decisions
have their own purpose.
As for me,
Qian Fei exposed so many things,
and I feel bad...
You just have a habit
of taking everything
upon yourself.
Qian Fei happens to work
for Hejing Securities.
Choosing Hejing Securities
as the lead sponsor
was my dad's decision.
Whose fault is that?
Besides,
my dad and I have
different philosophies.
I want Shanlifang Hotel Group
to go public
with a clean slate.
This is a great era for capital.
My goal is for Shanlifang Hotel Group
to ride the wave of capital
and become an international corporation.
It's not about going public
just to help my dad
and his old buddies
raise funds and cash out.
I never would've guessed.
In your daily life,
you're as docile as a little kitten.
But when it comes to work,
you're like a cheetah.
I'm serious.
My dad will get old
and retire.
In the future, I will be
the head of Shanlifang Hotel Group.
I don't want Shanlifang
to have any skeletons in its closet.
Even though Qian Fei
is your ex-girlfriend,
I judge people fairly.
She's capable.
In fact, I'm grateful to her
for clearing out the landmines
for Shanlifang in advance.
Okay.
Whatever you say goes.
Alright?
Such a strong will to survive, huh?
I tried to lead you into a trap,
but you didn't fall for it.
(I heard that this Qian Fei
was fired before.)
(Then, she used every trick in the book)
(to get into the Shanlifang Hotel Group
project team.)
(I wonder who she was targeting.)
Qian Fei.
Can you buy some medicine for me?
What's wrong?
I've had too much work lately.
I'm always staying up late.
My old problem is acting up again.
Sure. Send me the names of the medicine.
I'll go buy them for you now.
Okay, thank you.
No problem.
Hello.
Excuse me, do you have
these three medicines?
No.
Thank you.
Take care.
Here.
Review these documents this afternoon.
Okay.
Shanlifang Hotel Group.
Boss.
Where's Qian Fei?
I tried calling her,
but her phone is off.
I don't know where she went.
I saw her go out at noon.
She went out? Where to?
Maybe she went to get lunch?
It's already past two in the afternoon.
What kind of lunch takes this long?
Alright, when she gets back,
have her come see me immediately.
Okay.
Where have you been?
I couldn't find you anywhere.
I was buying medicine for Daisy.
Leaving your post without permission
during work hours.
Who gave you the nerve?
You're my special assistant now.
During work hours, you need
to be on standby at all times.
Your phone must be reachable all day.
Don't you even know this basic rule?
Let me tell you,
don't think you have nothing to do.
I need you on standby
so that Ms. Fang and I
can reach you at any time.
From now on,
anything outside your scope of work,
you are not to do.
Do you understand?
Understood.
Bind and format
the documents in your email.
Bring them to me in fifteen minutes.
(Director's Office)
Come in.
Here are the documents you wanted.
I've bound them.
Okay, just put them here.
Is there anything else?
Yes, there is.
Have you
had lunch yet?
If there's nothing else,
I'll be going now.
You're not hungry?
Come back.
Sit.
Eat.
It's working hours right now.
That's right.
This is the work I'm giving you.
Eat.
Fine.
Running errands for others
while you're starving yourself.
Aren't you silly?
Eat slowly.
Look how hungry you are.
Aren't you going to thank me?
I run errands
to get more exercise.
Besides, I'm not hungry at all
right now.
I'm just trying to complete
the task you gave me.
Yes.
No one's assigning me any tasks.
I haven't eaten either.
You haven't eaten?
Hurry up and have some.
I was busy with work.
You think I'm like you,
running errands for others
with nothing better to do?
Do you think I want to be idle?
Just eat.
Do you have any idea?
This sushi is from
the most famous place in Lujiazui.
You have to make a reservation
in advance.
I was supposed to be sitting
in the Japanese restaurant,
listening to music
and savoring it slowly.
Who knew I'd end up
eating it like this with you?
Don't tell me how much it costs.
Otherwise, I won't be able to enjoy it.
You two are really digging in.
I need to go see Mr. Liao.
So there are a few things
I need to run by you.
Sure.
Ms. Qian is getting some nice perks.
Is this Zhufeng Sushi?
Good eye.
Is it?
Well,
Ms. Fang, Mr. Li, you two talk.
I'll get going.
Okay.
Have a seat, Ms. Fang.
So, how is it?
Is Qian Fei doing okay?
I heard you criticized her today.
It was nothing.
It's mainly that I
was a bit impatient.
She's doing great.
You're all dressed up like this
to go to work?
Dressing presentably
is how I show respect for my job.
Why is it that when we went
to the subdistrict office yesterday,
they said you didn't go to work?
You went to the subdistrict office?
Yes.
To support your work, we went to
the subdistrict office specifically
to get some assignments.
Yes.
They said you took a day off.
They must have remembered incorrectly.
I was out on assignment that day.
Out on assignment where?
On assignment at the Financial Center?
You know about this, too.
You know Auntie Fang from Lane 3, right?
She's now working
as a cleaner in the Financial Center.
She said she saw you that day,
waiting outside for a young woman.
And then security wouldn't let you in.
You even got on security's blacklist.
Isn't that strange?
What happened?
There was a misunderstanding.
I forgot to bring my work ID that day.
Well, don't forget your work ID today.
Where's your work ID?
Let me see. Where is it?
Did you bring it?
- A major fire safety inspection.
That's right.
This inspection is using a method
where personnel are transferred
and jurisdictions are mixed.
I'm the only one
from our subdistrict participating.
You volunteered for this yourself,
didn't you?
The district said we need
to better supervise fire safety
and promote fire safety knowledge.
I was eager to answer the call.
How conscientious of you.
Very conscientious.
You guys eat. I'm leaving.
Okay, go on.
Where's my phone?
- Get me my phone.
- It's right here.
Here.
What are you doing?
Didn't you notice?
On his work ID,
the issue date was yesterday.
It was just issued yesterday.
That means
his reason for going
to the Financial Center is fake.
He's not going there to work.
He's going there to find that girl,
right?
That little rascal.
Is... Is it Fang?
(Shanghai World Financial Center)
Wait a minute.
You can't go in.
Sir, it was a misunderstanding before.
I have my ID.
Jun, what are you doing?
It's time to split into groups.
See? My supervisor is calling me.
Thanks.
I'm coming.
Wang, Li, Bin.
The three of you are in charge
of floors 20 to 27.
Jun.
You, me, Chen, and Song,
we'll be in charge of floors 28 and 29.
I'm going to floors 28 and 29?
Is there a problem?
No problem.
Alright.
Let's go.
Hello, are you here
for the fire inspection?
This way, please.
Dang...
=Love Has Fireworks=
(Next Episode Preview)
Let's go.
I feel like I've forgotten something.
I just feel uneasy.
It's okay.
Wait for me.
Thanks.
To put it simply,
if you want to pursue her,
you have to be thick-skinned.
So, have you won Qian Fei over?
♪There's no need
to know the ending from the start♪
♪Let the melody play through the chords
with the wind♪
♪There's no need
to keep every promise from the past♪
♪Leave some surprises
for the unknown in life♪
♪There's no need
to force things between two people♪
♪Perhaps I'll feel alone,
yet still find you there for me♪
♪There's no need
to dwell on right or wrong, nor fear♪
♪A hug means more
than countless apologies♪
♪I'll send you into the wide world♪
♪To live with passion
and become who you truly are♪
♪A quiet shoulder♪
♪Like a harbor waiting
for your wandering soul♪
♪I'll wait for the day
you return to a simpler life♪
♪The lights of home warm the night♪
♪A companionship that lasts forever♪
♪Shining brightly
like the stars and the moon on high♪
♪I'll send you into the wide world♪
♪To live with passion
and become who you truly are♪
♪A quiet shoulder♪
♪Like a harbor waiting
for your wandering soul♪
♪I'll wait for the day
you return to a simpler life♪
♪The lights of home warm the night♪
♪A companionship that lasts forever♪
♪Shining brightly
like the stars and the moon on high♪