♪Hey, you, you, you,
why is it you again?♪
♪Always stumbling upon
my little secrets♪
♪Falling on my brows, my lashes,
even the strands by my mouth♪
♪Like my favorite kitten
on a rainy spring afternoon♪
♪Hey, you, you, you,
why is it you again?♪
♪You effortlessly awaken
my protective instincts♪
♪Hitting all my little thoughts,
my doubts, and my temper♪
♪Like my favorite beer and fried chicken
in autumn, or spicy boiled fish in winter♪
♪Why is it you again?
That sweet way you speak♪
♪As if the whole world knows
my mind is full of you♪
♪Why is it still you?
That secret smile behind your cool facade♪
♪I might as well play along.
Let me protect you♪
♪Why is it always you?
The smile at the corner of your lips♪
♪Before I knew it, the words blurted out,
"I like you. I only like you."♪
=Love Has Fireworks=
(Based on "Investment Men and Women"
by Hong Er on Jinjiang Literature City)
=Episode 13=
(Asset Management Plan Appears)
Wake up. Don't sleep here.
Go home and get some sleep.
Wake up.
Mr. Li.
Why are you sleeping here?
I worked late,
so I just slept here for a while.
Come on. Go home and sleep.
What time is it?
It's already 5 AM.
Forget it.
I'll just sleep here.
Work starts soon anyway.
I'll drive you home.
I'll give you half a day off
tomorrow. Get some proper sleep.
I appreciate it,
but I work for Ms. Fang.
I still have a presentation tomorrow.
Alright, you should go.
There are cameras here.
People will talk if they see us.
You're impossible.
♪What matters to me is what you need♪
♪No more, no less.
I only hope I can give it to you♪
♪What I treasure is what I have♪
♪Bit by bit,
I only hope you're there with me♪
♪Those sweet promises and words of love♪
No good deed goes unpunished.
♪Truths, lies,
and words said for appearances♪
♪Leaving me
feeling like I'm walking on air♪
♪Harsh words, lies,
and words I can't make sense of♪
♪All dressed up in hollow splendor♪
♪Dreams, nonsense,
and the words hidden in my heart♪
♪Beneath this burning gaze♪
♪Those sweet promises and words of love♪
(Shanlifang Hotel Group)
Morning.
I brought coffee. Want one?
Thanks.
Here you go.
There's sugar and milk.
(Meeting Room)
Well...
Go get things organized first.
In ten minutes,
let's go over the proposal
you mentioned yesterday.
Okay.
(Why didn't you keep a record?)
(Why did you fall asleep?)
(Why can't you remember anything now?)
Ready?
If you're ready, let's begin.
Um...
I owe everyone an apology.
The materials I prepared
have actually been...
I took them.
Sorry.
I forgot to give them back.
While you were getting ready,
(Asset Management Plan Appears)
Mr. Li already showed us your proposal to us.
Although it's only an outline,
overall, I'm quite pleased with it.
Very good.
It's just that...
For Sections Two through Four,
I'm not entirely clear on your ideas.
I'd like you to elaborate further
on how you plan to implement them.
Of course. No problem.
Then I'll start with Section Four
and give everyone
a detailed explanation.
First of all,
Section Four is about
evaluating the existing
internal control system.
(Evaluating the Existing
Internal Control System)
(Internal Control Testing.
Deficiency Assessment)
Look at the way she's sleeping.
That's hardly ladylike.
What a sight.
Boss.
What are you looking at?
Why are you smiling like that?
Nicely done.
Just texting.
These documents need your signature.
Boss.
You've already completed
the restructuring plan
for Shanlifang Hotel Group's
financial statements.
It's far more complete than Qian Fei's.
Why not just use your own plan?
Come on.
Do I look like the kind of person
who takes credit from others?
Getting this project done right
matters far more
than taking credit from Qian Fei.
You've been with me for so long,
and you still haven't learned
any of my good qualities.
Alright. Get it out
as soon as I've signed it.
Don't hold things up.
Got it.
Hang on.
Knock before you come in next time.
Look at her.
Mr. Li.
Thanks for helping me out
at the morning meeting today.
Care to explain?
My proposal...
How did you get it?
I didn't save it, record it,
or keep a copy.
Where did you get it?
Take a look.
Now that you've experienced
the pain of losing a file,
from now on,
make sure you always keep backups.
I don't care
if it's handwritten or photographed,
or converted from PDF to Word.
You...
I'm talking to you.
Why are you looking at my private stuff?
Who's invading whose privacy?
I'll delete those photos for you.
Delete what?
I'm not deleting them.
So what?
Suit yourself.
Suit myself?
Fine, Landlady.
Then I'll send it out tomorrow.
Let the whole company see it.
Please, we're at work.
Don't call me Landlady.
And another thing.
I hope you find a new place soon
and move out of my house
as quickly as possible.
Thanks for what you did today.
If there's nothing else, I'll get going.
You...
What's gotten into her?
Qian Fei.
Ms. Fang said the task
of organizing the working papers
has been assigned to you as well.
I don't know what she's thinking.
With your abilities,
you shouldn't be stuck doing busywork.
It's fine.
I'll get back to work then.
Ms. Fang
is clearly trying
to keep you tied up.
This is an internal company matter.
No need for you to worry about it.
Could you talk
like a normal person for once?
What's not normal about it?
Hang on.
Let's go to the rooftop garden.
I need to talk to you.
Why can't you say it here?
I can't.
Come up now.
So, tell me.
Since yesterday afternoon,
you have such a 180-degree
change in attitude.
Why?
It's nothing.
It's nothing?
Qian Fei, you're the kind of person
who speaks her mind.
You always say exactly
what you're thinking.
The workplace is a battlefield.
Being too outspoken
can often lead
to you being used by others.
What do you mean?
You think I was using you?
Then let me be frank one more time.
The real reason you helped me revise
that research report
was to expose Shanlifang's data issues
right in front of Ms. Fang,
so she could stop turning
a blind eye to them.
I was just your pawn, wasn't I?
Not entirely.
I used to think
you were different from those people
who've spent years in this industry,
people who not only have
exceptional talent and intelligence,
but are also full of schemes.
At least I thought
you were straightforward and optimistic.
But now I realize I was wrong.
You're just like them.
Straightforward? Optimistic?
Do you think I wouldn't
rather face those problems
in a straightforward and optimistic way?
Can I afford to be
that straightforward and optimistic?
This isn't a fairy tale.
Not all goodness
gets to triumph over evil in the end.
You've helped other project teams
organize working papers before,
haven't you?
Did you think
you were doing a great job?
Feeling pretty pleased with yourself?
Let me tell you something.
You were simply
being taken advantage of.
No one's going
to share their bonus with you.
I know that.
Do you think I'm stupid?
So you've stayed in the back end,
dealing only with numbers,
thinking that would somehow protect
your straightforward optimism?
At the time, yes.
Because I didn't want
to deal with people.
But now you've moved
to the front office.
You have to deal with people.
But I'm still organizing working papers.
Then go talk to Ms. Fang.
Tell her you want
to help write the prospectus.
Let her see what you're capable of.
There's no reason to hide it.
Don't worry about what others think.
If you're capable
but keep it to yourself,
in the end,
people will simply assume
you're not capable at all.
Understand?
Hold fast to your principles.
Stay true to your original purpose.
Even after weathering
countless hardships,
you'll still
move forward with conviction
without losing your direction.
Now you're writing poetry?
So?
Do you still acknowledge me
as your master?
Since someone is so eager
to be my teacher for free,
I guess I'll reluctantly accept you.
Who said anything about free?
Other companies pay me
five figures just to teach a class.
I'll give you a twenty percent discount.
Either we'll deduct it from my rent,
or from my meal expenses.
So does that mean I won't have
to pay for meals anymore?
Keep dreaming.
See? That's more like it.
Come on. Repeat this poem after me.
No.
Come on, repeat it.
- No.
- It'll do you good.
I'll say a line, and you repeat it.
Hold fast to your principles.
Stay true to your original purpose.
Stop hiding.
I'm not hiding from you.
Why would I hide from you?
Then why are you so afraid of me?
Every time I hand you a document,
I can't even see your face.
You keep avoiding me.
I'm going to be working here
for quite a while.
You're creating a lot
of unnecessary work for me.
There are too many people around here.
Why don't we find
somewhere quiet to talk?
Afraid someone might see us?
Don't worry.
People have been talking
for a while now.
Avoiding suspicion
isn't going to stop them from talking.
Could you just relax a little?
The less you care about it,
the sooner everyone
will forget about it.
Wang Ruohai.
I've already moved on from you.
What exactly are you afraid of?
Could you at least act like it?
Can you separate work
from your personal life?
Can you be a man about it?
You've changed.
Compared to before,
you don't seem quite the same.
That's right.
Because my goals have changed.
I've been at Shanlifang Hotel Group
for quite some time now.
You should get used to that, too.
So from now on,
let's keep it professional, okay?
I'm going to the restroom.
What's wrong?
Why?
Why would they do this?
Shanlifang has invested
so much in Xinxin Vision.
They had such high expectations!
How could they
just give up on it like that?
No way. Absolutely not.
Liao Jinshan told me himself
that we'd go public together.
I know...
Don't panic, okay?
Just calm down first.
Let me handle this, alright?
Okay, I have to go.
I'll call you later.
What's wrong?
You don't look so good.
Do I?
Maybe I've gone too long without eating.
So this is my fault now?
No.
Come on. I'll take you
out for something good.
Ms. Fang.
I'd like to talk to you
about my work responsibilities.
Sure.
I've been waiting a long time
for you to come talk to me.
Let's go.
That's about it.
Finished?
I've put all my cards on the table.
You really know Shanlifang Hotel Group
inside and out.
I knew you'd be like this.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have kept
someone from the back end
by my side.
But you know what?
If you want to win someone over,
ability alone isn't enough.
You also need confidence.
Do you know how long I've been waiting
for you to have the courage
to show me what you're capable of?
Luckily, the wait paid off.
Alright.
You'll work with me from now on.
Really?
As for you, start with the prospectus.
Begin with the issuer's background
and company history.
That'll let you make the most
of your strong writing skills,
and your concise wording.
And besides,
if you understand every detail
in the working papers,
you'll gain a much deeper
understanding of the company.
You're okay on the finance side, right?
Do you have your CPA?
That's great.
Then at tomorrow's meeting,
you can join us
in discussing the financial issues.
Is that the only word you know?
I'm so happy.
This feels like a dream.
At least I didn't put you
through all that for nothing.
And all I get is an "Mm-hmm"?
Thank you, Ms. Fang.
Don't celebrate too early.
Keep up the good work.
I will.
(Shanghai World Financial Center)
Dang Yu.
What exactly are you trying to do?
I'm here to pick you up from work.
And take you out to dinner.
This is for you.
Come on, you're a perfectly good guy.
Why can't you take a hint?
First the gifts,
now flowers, too.
I've told you, there's got
to be a limit to this idol worship.
That's okay.
I just wanted to give them to you.
I know you don't have
a part-time job tonight.
Have dinner with me, okay?
Dang Yu. Is that your boyfriend?
Not yet.
He's pretty handsome.
- No, he's not.
- Not yet?
Pretty handsome.
Handsome.
She won't admit it.
Go get her.
- He's pretty handsome.
- He's quite handsome.
You wanted dinner, right?
My car's over there.
Let's go.
You don't want the flowers?
I'm full.
That means dinner's over, right?
I'm leaving.
Finished eating?
Can you let me say a few things?
Then make it quick.
Starting today,
I'd like to
officially date you.
What?
I know.
I didn't leave you
with the best impression before.
That's why I wanted
to treat you to this meal today,
so you could get to know me again.
And I hope you'll give me a chance.
No chance.
Just hear me out first.
My name is Jun Cheng.
My friends all call me Jun.
I'm twenty-six years old.
I'm a local from Shanghai.
Right now, I work
at the neighborhood office.
My mom likes the job
because it's close to home
and stable.
At the moment,
I'm just a junior civil servant.
But I believe
that as long as I work hard,
I'll definitely
get promoted within five years.
In my spare time,
I play video games and stuff.
But what I enjoy most
is watching you play.
Right now,
I live with my parents.
So I don't have any rent to pay,
or a mortgage to worry about.
Everything I earn is mine to keep.
As for my dating life,
honestly,
I've never been in a relationship.
There was a girl
I liked when I was in school,
but my mom told me to focus on studying
and not get involved
in that kind of thing.
So I really don't have much
experience with women.
And also...
Hold on.
Look,
you've said all that,
but other than liking
to watch me play games,
what does any of it have to do with me?
Of course it does.
I think if you can
get to know me better,
and understand me better,
you'll think more highly of me.
Then the chances
of you liking me will be higher.
So you like me?
But I don't like you.
You just don't like me right now.
Maybe you'll like me later.
I see.
Well, I've got a pretty good idea
of your basic situation now.
As far as I'm concerned,
your personality fails.
Your job fails.
And your family situation
fails even more.
We have no future together.
Let's consider tonight's dinner
your official confession to me,
and my official rejection of you.
So from now on,
please stop bothering me.
And one more thing. You're a grown man.
If you can't finish the food,
don't order so much.
This meal is on me.
Pack up the leftovers and take them home
to eat with your mom.
Excuse me.
Please pack up the rest for him.
Coming.
Sir, which dishes
would you like packed up?
Alright, stop drinking.
You'll end up
having another allergic reaction.
Why?
Can someone explain to me
why she won't give me a chance?
Boss, you've got to help him out.
Isn't that girl
your landlady's best friend?
I'm telling you,
Li Yifei
is no help anymore.
He's not
the Li Yifei you all knew.
He can't even sort out
his own problems now.
You can't even sort out your own life,
and you're worrying about others?
Boss's problems are all on me, okay?
I'll find you a girl.
Stop talking nonsense.
Why don't you two just get together?
I...
I'm leaving.
Where are you going?
You've had way too much to drink.
I'm going to play games.
At least in the game,
I can fight my way through anything
and accomplish great things.
Most importantly,
if someone makes me mad,
I can beat them up!
I'm out of here.
You're really leaving?
Take it easy.
Good luck.
When is this kid ever going to grow up?
Have a drink.
Don't get too addicted to the internet.
I'm back.
Welcome home.
What are you doing up so late?
Making congee.
Making congee?
Don't you hate congee?
Why are you being so nice to me now,
even making congee for me?
It's for Zhao De.
Doesn't he have stomach problems?
I was already making congee,
so I just made extra.
What do you mean?
You call this "made extra"?
This is specially made just for him.
I'm warning you.
Zhao De's career
is taking off right now.
Don't get any ideas.
What are you talking about?
That's disgusting.
You think everyone's like you,
always calculating.
I'm doing this for everyone's good.
Besides,
I've taught you quite a lot, too.
I'm your teacher, after all.
I thought you made it especially for me.
Playing favorites, huh?
At least you've got some conscience.
You're finally teachable.
Come on, tell me why you
made congee for me tonight.
- Take the extras
- so nothing goes to waste.
See?
I knew exactly what you'd say.
I get it. Not wanting to waste it
is the main reason.
So what's the secondary reason?
Ms. Fang is letting me
help write the prospectus.
Really?
That's great!
See? What did I tell you?
Our landlady succeeds
in everything she takes on.
Right?
Of course.
But mainly,
it's because I taught you so well.
How about this?
I'll give you a chance
to properly thank me.
For the next week,
you can be the one doing the cooking.
I'm giving you that honor.
That way, you can properly thank me.
Taking credit for yourself
and taking advantage of the situation.
How can you be like this?
I don't have money to buy groceries.
I can't afford to feed
a giant dog like you.
No money?
You're telling me you have no money?
That's rich.
From now on, my meal expenses
will come out of this.
So don't tell me you're broke anymore.
With this little money,
it won't even cover one meal.
Do you know
how expensive things are now?
Then how about this?
Once the money in there runs out,
that's when
you'll never have to cook for me again.
Deal.
So I won't have
to keep being your chef for free.
And your meal expenses
can come out of it, too.
Think of it as your cooking fee.
A master would never
take advantage of his disciple.
Right?
Thanks.
Come on.
Let me try a bowl first.
Your special late night congee
made with love.
The consistency is perfect.
Didn't expect it to turn out so well.
She's actually pretty.
Is this her?
It's all photos of this girl.
- Then it has to be her.
- Yeah.
The thing is, these photos look like
they were downloaded from the internet.
Exactly.
Look.
One minute she's singing,
the next she's dancing.
And here's
one of her working as a bartender.
Could she be an actress?
An actress? That's the worst.
An actress? Jun...
Doesn't that make things even harder?
Yeah, Jun's going to have a rough time.
Mom,
I can't eat anymore.
(Director's Office)
Qian Fei, hurry up and clean this up.
Why am I the one cleaning up?
Why?
You're the special assistant, remember?
This is your job.
Boss, I'll do it.
Why would you do it?
Let me say something.
Ms. Fang specifically told me
to let my boss give you
more opportunities to learn.
Hear that?
So this is part of your job, too.
We've still got over an hour left.
If you hurry up and finish cleaning,
the two of us can still join Boss
for a couple rounds of Landlord.
Hear that?
I'll do it.
Now that's the right attitude.
Playing Landlord isn't work.
I'm taking a lunch break later.
How is it not work?
Helping your direct supervisor
balance work and rest
helps maintain productivity.
That's part of your job
as a special assistant.
If you don't join,
we'll be one player short.
If we're one player short,
this activity can't happen.
And once this activity can't happen,
it'll directly affect
my productivity this afternoon.
Can you,
as a special assistant,
really take responsibility for that?
Can't.
Having a boss like you is the worst.
(Office Area)
Qian Fei.
Ms. Fang.
The biggest supplier
of Shanlifang Hotel Group is here.
We were supposed to have a meeting,
but something came up today.
So you and Mr. Li will
handle the due diligence meeting.
Make sure you're prepared.
Okay.
(Green Glory Group Information Summary)
(Mr. Niu Xindong,
Chairman of Green Glory Group)
(Ms. Gui Lili, Assistant
to the Chairman of Green Glory Group)
(Looks like Li Yifei
still doesn't know.)
(What's his reaction going to be)
(when he sees Gui Lili?)
(Oh my God. I can't even imagine.)
(Should I give him a heads up first?)
(Right.)
(I'd better let him prepare himself.)
I need to tell you something.
- In a minute.
- Hold on.
They're about to arrive.
Tell me later.
Have a seat.
Come on.
Alright.
Long time no see.
Come.
Hello, everyone.
This is our company's
assistant to the chairman.
Hello, everyone. My name is Gui Lili.
Chairman Niu had an emergency today
and couldn't make it.
So he asked me to meet
with everyone on his behalf.
That's alright.
I'm Li Yifei from Zhizhong Investment.
Welcome.
Hello.
Please, have a seat.
Introduction to the supply process.
Sales.
Marketing Operations Department.
Supply, Quality Control, Finance.
(Introduction to the Supply Process)
(I don't know why,)
(but today's Li Yifei)
(seems different from usual.)
(Every gesture and every move he makes,)
(seems perfectly calculated.)
(He always stops at)
(the most pleasing angle possible.)
(I really underestimated
Li Yifei's emotional intelligence.)
(I thought he was just troublesome,
spoiled, and bad-tempered.)
(But he's more calculating than anyone.)
(No wonder he's so elegant today.)
(He knows this is the best way)
(to make an ex feel heartbroken,
nostalgic, and full of regret.)
That's about everything
for today's meeting.
Does anyone have anything to add?
If not, we'll adjourn here.
Oh, right.
Assistant Gui.
Shanlifang Hotel Group
has prepared lunch for everyone.
Would you like to stay and join us?
Sorry.
I'm not feeling very well today.
So I won't
be joining everyone for lunch.
Please take good care
of everyone for me.
Sure.
- What a pity you can't stay this time.
- There'll be another chance.
Here.
I'll get going then.
Alright.
Take good care of everyone.
Bye.
Buddy,
what's the story
with that assistant to the chairman?
She's so young.
I noticed
you're pretty attentive to her, too.
She's one of the chairman's people.
As for our chairman,
who knows whether
he'd planned it all along,
or if it only happened
after his divorce.
She... Actually, she's now
the chairman's fiancée.
I figure it won't be long
before they're celebrating a wedding.
You heard that just now?
You were so cool back there.
It was like you had cheat codes on.
You've got my vote.
Look at you.
And you call that cool?
If I ever really unlocked cheat mode,
you'd be begging me
not to be so handsome.
Otherwise, you wouldn't survive.
Good thing I haven't eaten.
Or I'd be throwing up right now.
Swallow it.
Guan Xin. What are we having for lunch?
- How about hot and sour noodles?
- Boss.
That presentation you gave today
was truly "magnificent."
Masterful.
I bet it's Gui Lili.
You're overthinking it.
(Gui Lili)
It really is Gui Lili.
Not bad.
You know her surprisingly well.
Looks like you still haven't let go.
Do I understand her?
I understand women.
Give me a break.
You don't understand me.
Really?
Could it be
that you don't count as a woman?
Just kidding.
Since you understand women so well,
guess what she sent.
Qian Fei.
(Gui Lili: How has Yifei been lately?)
How has Yifei been lately?
Go on, tell me if I'm right.
Called it, didn't I?
A three.
(Gui Lili's message)
Beat that.
(Qian Fei.)
(Has Yifei ever...)
A big card...
(Mentioned me?)
Qian Fei.
(Qian Fei: No.)
What are you waiting for?
Your turn.
Stop chatting.
Come on. I'll send it for you.
I'll reply for you.
I'll send it.
(Gui Lili: No way.)
Qian Fei, have you fallen for Li Yifei,)
(and that's why
you're not telling me the truth?)
Boss, I think I smell some gossip.
Sit back down.
I'll let you win a round later.
(Liking him isn't surprising.)
(He is pretty handsome.)
(He buys groceries, washes
dishes, and does housework.)
(Whatever clothes you buy, he'll wear.)
(He looks good in anything.)
(He looks even better in nothing.)
(With someone this attractive)
(parading around
in front of you every day,)
(how could anyone not like him?)
What are you sending?
Stop sending messages.
Li Yifei.
What's with
the ridiculously flirty tilde?
Have some shame, will you?
This is between you two.
Why are you dragging me into it?
And besides,
if you don't praise yourself every day,
can you even survive?
I'm saving you. Don't you get it?
She needs to know that what
she wanted me to do
back then didn't happen,
but you've gotten me to do it now.
Let's see if she still
has the nerve to reply.
Most importantly,
she's affecting our card game now.
Do you understand?
It's your turn, sis.
Yeah, hurry up.
Oh, please. You're just bitter.
Still regretting that she cheated
on you and dumped you.
Pass.
She...
She replied again?
It really is her?
(Qian Fei, let me sincerely
give you a piece of advice.)
(So you don't get in too deep)
(and end up
getting hurt even more later.)
(People need to see themselves clearly.)
(Yifei would never
like a woman like you.)
She replied?
What did she say? Let me see.
Let me see.
Give it to me.
Where's my card?
Where is it from earlier?
Is it outside?
She... What did she say?
She said you snore in your sleep.
I...
Impossible.
I never snore.
I...
Found it.
I left it in the office.
Play your card, Qian Fei.
- Pass.
=Love Has Fireworks=
(Next Episode Preview)
If you dare
ask me to help wash vegetables again,
then the consequences
are on you.
When I was doing the laundry,
and then when I came out and looked,
the washing machine...
Nothing serious.
It just overflowed a little.
How much is "a little"?
Not much. Just enough
to reach the living room.
- No. Listen to my explanation.
- I hate you so much!
Don't look so upset.
How about this?
From now on,
I'll allow you to dream
about being a rich
second generation in front of me, okay?
♪There's no need
to know the ending from the start♪
♪Let the melody play through the chords
with the wind♪
♪There's no need
to keep every promise from the past♪
♪Leave some surprises
for the unknown in life♪
♪There's no need
to force things between two people♪
♪Perhaps I'll feel alone,
yet still find you there for me♪
♪There's no need
to dwell on right or wrong, nor fear♪
♪A hug means more
than countless apologies♪
♪I'll send you into the wide world♪
♪To live with passion
and become who you truly are♪
♪A quiet shoulder♪
♪Like a harbor waiting
for your wandering soul♪
♪I'll wait for the day
you return to a simpler life♪
♪The lights of home warm the night♪
♪A companionship that lasts forever♪
♪Shining brightly
like the stars and the moon on high♪
♪I'll send you into the wide world♪
♪To live with passion
and become who you truly are♪
♪A quiet shoulder♪
♪Like a harbor waiting
for your wandering soul♪
♪I'll wait for the day
you return to a simpler life♪
♪The lights of home warm the night♪
♪A companionship that lasts forever♪
♪Shining brightly
like the stars and the moon on high♪