ظآزHey, you, you, you,
why is it you again?ظآز
ظآزAlways stumbling upon
my little secretsظآز
ظآزFalling on my brows, my lashes,
even the strands by my mouthظآز
ظآزLike my favorite kitten
on a rainy spring afternoonظآز
ظآزHey, you, you, you,
why is it you again?ظآز
ظآزYou effortlessly awaken
my protective instinctsظآز
ظآزHitting all my little thoughts,
my doubts, and my temperظآز
ظآزLike my favorite beer and fried chicken
in autumn, or spicy boiled fish in winterظآز
ظآزWhy is it you again?
That sweet way you speakظآز
ظآزAs if the whole world knows
my mind is full of youظآز
ظآزWhy is it still you?
That secret smile behind your cool facadeظآز
ظآزI might as well play along.
Let me protect youظآز
ظآزWhy is it always you?
The smile at the corner of your lipsظآز
ظآزBefore I knew it, the words blurted out,
"I like you. I only like you."ظآز
=Love Has Fireworks=
(Based on "Investment Men and Women"
by Hong Er on Jinjiang Literature City)
=Episode 10=
Qian Fei.
Ms. Fang.
The files you brought back
from Chengdu are crucial.
They're vital to our partnership
with Shanlifang.
But you might not grasp
the full implications just yet.
So today, learn and observe more,
and talk less.
Preferably, don't talk.
- Boss.
- Okay, I understand.
Shanlifang Hotel Group has falsified data.
Ms. Fang.
We're just going to let it slide?
- So glad you could come.
- Sorry to keep you waiting.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Not at all.
I'm delighted that you're here.
- Mr. Wu.
- This way, please.
Mr. Li.
Ms. Fang.
Come on, welcome.
Please.
Come on.
Come on in.
(Shanlifang Hotel Group)
Welcome.
We've been looking forward
to your arrival.
This way, please. This way.
Mr. Li,
this is your office.
Nice.
Come on. This way, please.
This is the conference room.
The pantry.
Ms. Fang.
Not bad.
Your office is over here.
It's more impressive than mine.
What do you think? Take a look.
This is the independent office space
we've set up
for the joint sponsorship team.
Let us know if you need anything else.
Don't hesitate to ask.
We will spare no expense
to ensure you have everything you need
for the battle ahead.
Before Shanlifang Hotel Group's
review meeting,
it's going to be a test
for all three of us.
Be well-prepared, stay relaxed,
and professionally
manage the book building. No problem.
Your professional capabilities
are beyond question.
You're both benchmarks in the industry.
So,
we'll follow your lead.
As for the work itself,
once you've settled in,
we can coordinate as we go.
Okay.
It's getting late.
Let's head to the banquet hall
for lunch.
We can talk while we eat, alright?
Let's go.
After you.
Come on.
Great.
Not bad, right?
Now that everyone's here,
on behalf of the group,
I'd like to welcome you all
to Shanlifang.
Shanlifang's IPO
will depend
on everyone's close cooperation.
I'd like to propose a toast to you all.
After this drink,
we'll be fighting side by side.
Although Mr. Wu's hospitality
is hard to refuse,
we have an important meeting
after this meal.
So let's not overdo it with the drinks.
To a successful project.
Mr. Liao won't be at the meeting
this afternoon.
Ms. Liao will be attending instead.
Mr. Liao isn't coming?
Something came up
for Mr. Liao unexpectedly.
He asked Ms. Liao to attend
in his place.
I heard this Ms. Liao
is young and beautiful,
and also very capable. Is that right?
Yes, yes.
Ms. Liao is just as driven
as Mr. Liao was in his youth.
Sorry, I'm late.
Ms. Liao, it's great
you could make time to come.
Let me make an introduction.
This is Shanlifang Hotel Group's
Vice President Liao.
Hello.
And this is...
Wu, does she really
need an introduction?
Director Fang of Hejing Securities.
Who in Shanghai doesn't know her?
You flatter me.
Now that I've finally met you,
you're even younger
and more beautiful than I imagined.
This is...
Mr. Li.
Ms. Liao.
My dad often praises you to me.
He tells me to learn from you.
Now, I finally have the chance.
You're too kind, Ms. Liao.
We at Zhizhong are here
to be of service.
Here's to a pleasant collaboration.
Absolutely.
The person who will be liaising with you
is our group's Chief Financial Officer,
Mr. Wang Ruohai.
He'll be in charge of coordinating
with the joint sponsorship team.
Hello.
Great to meet you.
I'll be counting
on your support from now on.
Let's not stand around.
Please, have a seat.
Okay.
We're all one big family now.
Ruohai.
This Silver Cod
with Black Truffle and Lily Bulbs
is a new dish developed
by our Chinese cuisine chef.
I heard the cod
was just flown in today.
I can't eat seafood today.
Try it for me.
Come, Ms. Fang.
A toast to you.
I was just about to toast you.
Come on.
To a pleasant collaboration.
Mr. Wang.
I'd like to toast the two of you.
I hope our project goes smoothly.
And please, guide us along the way.
Of course.
Cheers.
Come on.
Ms. Liao.
Drink a little less.
We still have work this afternoon.
Thanks.
To you.
A pleasant collaboration.
To a pleasant collaboration.
Thank you.
Qian Fei.
Mr. Wang,
who is sitting across from you,
in our future work,
we'll be dealing with him a lot.
In a bit,
go and propose a toast to him.
(Pretentious Li:
If you don't want to go, don't go.)
Ms. Liao, come on.
I must toast you.
It's our first time meeting.
I'll toast you.
(Qian Fei: So you knew all along.)
Madam.
Right, it's not convenient
for me to drink today.
No problem.
Let's collaborate more in the future.
Mr. Wang, I'd like to toast you.
Wishing you a successful career
and a bright future.
And a happy life.
I'll drink up.
You can drink as you please.
Let's both drink as we please...
Okay, then please have a seat.
Ms. Liao, I'd like to toast you as well.
Ms. Fang, this is...
This is my assistant, Qian Fei.
Didn't you notice
Ms. Liao isn't drinking?
I'll drink up.
You can drink as you please.
Alright, it's the thought that counts.
We still have work this afternoon.
Okay.
I'm happy today, Ms. Fang.
It's my first time meeting Ms. Liao
and Mr. Wang.
So I'm very happy today.
In this moment,
I'd really like to propose a toast.
I'll propose a toast.
I suggest, since we have work
this afternoon,
we don't drink so much.
How about we use tea instead of wine?
Excellent.
Right?
That's an excellent suggestion.
Excellent. Come on.
No more drinking.
This...
Right?
- Cheers.
- Then let's hope our work ahead
goes smoothly.
To a pleasant collaboration.
It's all in the tea.
Thanks for your hard work.
Thank you for your hard work.
Please, have a seat.
Mr. Li.
I heard you made a special trip
to Shanlifang's old headquarters
in Chengdu.
That's real dedication.
Let me toast to you.
Thank you, Ms. Liao.
You're too kind.
It's what we're supposed to do.
Did you learn anything
from your trip to Chengdu?
We learned quite a lot.
Did Ms. Qian go along as well?
Qian Fei, have you had
too much to drink?
Why don't you go rest for a bit?
I'm not drunk
and I don't need to rest.
Ms. Liao,
Mr. Wang.
Shanlifang Hotel Group,
during its pre-IPO preparations,
provided our sponsorship team
and the audit department
with many illogical financial statements
and concealed a lot of real data.
Especially regarding intangible assets,
there are major discrepancies.
May I ask why that is?
What did you say?
According to CSRC and legal regulations,
a company
that severely falsifies its assets
is not allowed to pass the review.
Is Mr. Wang unaware of this,
since this is your first time
on an IPO project?
Here's the thing.
Um...
If the accounts are falsified,
even if the IPO is successful,
you can still be held accountable.
But the good thing is,
we discovered this very early.
So as long as the client provides
the real and complete financial data,
there's still plenty of time
to fix everything.
Don't worry, let's just eat and drink.
Please.
Let's just enjoy our meal.
I'm sorry.
I sent Qian Fei to Chengdu
to be Mr. Li's assistant,
but I didn't expect
that in just a few days,
she'd be poached by Zhizhong.
See? Mr. Li is just that charming.
Ms. Fang.
Alright.
Well said, Ms. Fang.
Brilliant.
Um, that's not...
Ms. Liao, here's the thing.
Actually, regarding what Qian Fei said,
I was going to bring it up with you
during our meeting this afternoon.
This kind of issue must be raised.
But I didn't expect this...
But it's okay.
Sooner or later,
it had to be said at the meeting anyway.
Let's eat first.
(Shanlifang Hotel Group,
Conference Room)
2022, 202...
Alright, let's continue.
Ms. Liao,
I'm sorry.
I really don't know why
Qian Fei is on the sponsorship team.
But don't worry.
This was all my fault.
I'll do everything I can
to make up for it.
I promise it won't affect
the company's IPO.
Come here.
I told you.
Just call me Shiyu when we're alone.
Why do you keep forgetting?
I'm tired.
Give me a massage.
We're still at the office.
There aren't even any cameras here.
Who's going to see?
Do you know this place better than I do?
Mr. Li.
- I'll get going.
- Okay, thank you for your hard work.
Qian Fei.
Come to my office at five.
Boss.
That old fox, Fang Yun,
is really something.
I can't believe she kicked
the ball back into our court.
But we're the bigger men.
We won't stoop to their level.
But I have to say,
you were amazing in the meeting today.
Reasonable, well-argued,
and perfectly composed.
Boss.
I'm talking to you.
What are you thinking about?
It's nothing.
Then let's head back to Zhizhong?
You go ahead.
I still have something to do.
I'll head back first, then.
(Qian Fei, oh, Qian Fei.)
(How could you lose
your composure like that today?)
They are here.
Ruohai, I can't eat seafood today.
You can try some for me.
Okay.
(Haven't you gotten over
that scumbag already?)
(Is he even worth all this?)
(Qian Fei, snap out of it.)
(Shanlifang Hotel Group)
Ms. Qian.
Ms. Liao, what can I do for you?
I heard you were doing odd jobs
in the back end of the investment bank.
And now, you've joined the project team.
You're participating
in our Shanlifang Hotel Group's
IPO project.
That shows you're quite capable.
I also hope you can keep your personal
and professional lives separate.
You really think too highly of me.
I just try to do my own job well
within the limited time I have.
Satisfying my superiors
and clients is enough for me.
As for other personal matters,
I simply don't have time
to think about them.
You are exceptionally capable
and even have a sharp tongue.
We already saw that at the dining table.
Right, Ruohai?
I've known Qian Fei for many years,
but it's our first time
working together professionally.
However, I trust her abilities.
I'm sure she's more than qualified
for this job.
Well then,
I'll be waiting to see.
Let's see what other
surprises you have in store for me.
Shanlifang Hotel Group
is a client we serve
to the best of our ability.
Surprising you is not my goal.
Helping Mr. Wang fill in the gaps
and participating in
Shanlifang Hotel Group's successful IPO
is my honor.
Then let me say a few words
in a personal capacity.
You've always worked in the back end.
Now that you've gotten a chance
to join the project team,
you should cherish it.
Well, thank you for the reminder,
Mr. Wang.
Then let me also respond
in a personal capacity.
Wasting a few years
isn't actually that scary.
You only realize how precious
chances are after you've wasted them.
Who hasn't run into a scumbag before?
The marketing department meeting
is about to start.
Let's go.
Ms. Fang,
I've found out everything.
That Wang Ruohai
is Qian Fei's ex-boyfriend.
He used to work at Nalan Maide Bank.
The staff there all know Qian Fei.
I heard they even bought a house
for their marriage
and booked the wedding banquet.
They were just short
of having the wedding.
So you're saying
Wang Ruohai
left Qian Fei because of Liao Shiyu?
Looks like it.
Qian Fei was desperate to get into
the Shanlifang Hotel Group project team.
She must be trying
to drag Wang Ruohai down with her
for mutual destruction.
Why else would she cause
such a huge mess?
Is Qian Fei that calculating?
Who knows?
But having Qian Fei on our project team
is a disaster waiting to happen.
I'm actually quite interested
to see how this drama unfolds.
(Grand Chancellor: Are you busy?)
(Grand Chancellor: It's okay not to
reply. Just making my presence known.)
(Hejing Securities Co., Ltd.)
Okay.
I'll leave it to you.
I'll take over this afternoon, okay?
Sure.
(Security Monitor Wall)
(Lobby, Entrance 1)
(Hejing Securities Co., Ltd.)
Ms. Fang.
Ms. Fang, I came to apologize to you.
I'm truly sorry.
You always told me
to observe more and learn more,
to speak less,
or better yet, not at all.
But this time, I still...
You're almost 30, aren't you?
How are you worse than an intern?
You've been in the workplace
for so many years.
You can't even control yourself.
I'm sorry. I was too impulsive
and reckless this time.
I've caused you and the company
such a negative impact.
I've also affected your work
and everyone else's.
I'm willing
to make a public self-criticism.
I hope you can forgive me.
Many things
can't be solved with a self-criticism.
Li Yifei was merciful today.
He didn't kick us while we were down.
Otherwise, our company, Hejing,
would have been ruined by you alone.
We could have been kicked off
the project team.
Do you realize that?
Do you think a self-criticism
can solve everything?
I know how serious this was.
But I still hope
you can give me one last chance.
You know how much effort
I put into returning to Hejing.
Don't talk to me
about how much you've put in.
Who here hasn't put in a lot?
To land this Shanlifang project,
do you know how many sleepless nights
the entire team had?
How much overtime we worked?
Does anyone in our investment
banking industry not make sacrifices?
Does anyone put in less effort?
And you think what you've done
is so remarkable?
You're not even close.
How can I dare to use someone like you?
Ms. Fang, I...
Mr. Li.
Did I come at a bad time?
No.
Please, Mr. Li, come on in.
Ms. Fang.
I brought you some apples
grown by my relatives back home.
They're organic.
Thank you.
This is such a rare treat.
Please, have a seat.
Okay.
You can go now.
It's alright, Qian Fei.
Why don't you listen in?
Ms. Fang,
to be honest with you,
I've run into a bit of trouble lately.
What kind of trouble?
Don't laugh when I tell you.
It's about my assistant, Zhao De.
You remember him, right?
He's got a bunch of things going on
at Zhizhong now.
He's completely swamped.
He has no time for my matters at all.
Just when we're short-staffed,
he pulls this on me.
I'm really...
Sometimes, I really envy you.
You're surrounded by this huge crowd...
No, I mean, you're surrounded
by so much talent.
Every single one of them is competent.
When I think about my own situation,
I just feel...
I'm so frustrated. I really am.
I'm truly envious.
I understand.
You're short-staffed, right?
Why haven't you requested someone
from Zhizhong?
I'd like to.
But ever since working with you,
when I look at the people
at Zhizhong, I just...
It's too difficult. It really is.
Are you suggesting...
Is there anyone at Hejing
you think could help you out?
People like Dacui
or Daisy, I wouldn't dare ask for them.
They're truly very capable.
I'm just looking
for a special assistant.
It would be a waste
of their great talent,
right?
I think someone like...
Well,
someone like Qian Fei, for example,
with average abilities,
would be fine
as an assistant.
Would you mind letting her
work as my special assistant
while we're collaborating?
What do you think?
(Hejing Securities Co., Ltd.)
Hello.
Hello, this is building security.
Excuse me, after 3:30 PM,
have you been the one on duty here
the whole time?
Yes. What's wrong?
Here's the thing.
Take a look. Do you know this person?
Why did he follow me here?
He's still in the lobby.
If you feel that he poses a threat
to your personal safety,
you can leave
through the back door after work.
Okay, thank you.
Sure. You're welcome.
(He doesn't need a special assistant.)
(He clearly just wants me
to run errands.)
(And what's with the pour-over coffee?)
(So pretentious.)
ظآزWhenever I look upظآز
ظآزI meet your gaze, those eyesظآز
ظآزI wish to hold on to that light of joyظآز
ظآزAnd embrace that fleeting happinessظآز
ظآزSometimes we cry, sometimes we laughظآز
ظآزSometimes we're swept away
by sweetnessظآز
ظآز Sometimes we run, sometimes we fall ظآز
ظآزSometimes I feel
having you is the bestظآز
(The person
who tied my shoelaces for me)
(can also do these things
for someone else.)
(Qian Fei,)
(this is reality.)
ظآزTo love or not to loveظآز
(Seeing a person clearly
through a different relationship.)
(This person was once
very important to me.)
(But from now on,)
(he has nothing to do with me.)
(Shanlifang Hotel Group,
Director's Office)
ظآزI've never met a sea
as brilliant as youظآز
ظآزEvery minute is so colorfulظآز
ظآزI've never known a love
as warm as yoursظآز
ظآزNothing more needs to be said,
I won't let go of youظآز
ظآزThe rain keeps fallingظآز
ظآزThe atmosphere
isn't exactly harmoniousظآز
It's pretty disharmonious.
You knew all along, didn't you?
Then why didn't you tell me sooner?
I was protecting you, okay?
Tell me,
if you had known earlier
that Wang Ruohai was
Financial Director at Shanlifang,
would you have tried so hard
to get back to Hejing
and join the project team?
Would you?
Let me tell you something.
I've been in investment banking
for so many years,
so I've met my fair share of people.
I genuinely think you have
what it takes for this line of work.
I just value talent.
I don't want to see you give up
an important career opportunity
and a turning point in your life
for some trivial,
insignificant relationship.
Also, as your master,
let me give you another piece of truth.
Don't value relationships
above all else.
In this world, only your work
will not betray your effort and passion.
I've already moved on.
Besides, he has someone new now.
I respect his choice.
At least I know
that I once loved with all my heart.
That's enough.
Are you a woodpecker?
You're so stubborn.
If you had really moved on,
would you have reacted extremely
in the banquet hall today
and exposed
Shanlifang's financial problems?
Well, how was I supposed to know
I'd run into the two of them?
I have moved on.
But when I saw them together,
I just... My anger just flared up.
I wasn't thinking straight.
It's only human.
I had to turn my anger into courage
to say it all in one go.
That's why,
whenever I see you not thinking clearly,
I'm just glad
my parents didn't raise a fool.
Think about it.
Today, in front of so many people,
you went against Ms. Fang's wishes.
She could have fired you in a heartbeat.
You worked so hard
to get into this project team.
What now?
Just a one-day tour?
Hurry up and thank your master.
It's all thanks to me
that you were saved.
Okay.
Thank you.
That's more like it.
Also, starting today,
you're my special assistant.
From now on,
you have to listen to me.
Only at the company.
Only for work.
Outside of work, I'm still your master.
Once a master, always a father figure.
You've been calling me "master"
for so many days.
You expect me to just abandon you?
In your dreams.
You want to enslave me all day?
Don't say that about me.
You're speaking my mind.
Well, you're overthinking it.
You think just because
you're my temporary boss,
I wouldn't dare make you move out?
Whether I move out or not
depends on the contract, right?
Work is work,
and living together is living together.
Let's not mix them all up.
You'd better not.
That mouth of yours
is always yapping.
It doesn't hurt to listen more,
you know?
Fine.
Looks like I gave the apples away
for nothing today.
Where did you get those apples anyway?
From the supermarket downstairs.
I knew it.
But... But it's really organic.
I was not lying.
Okay.
Farewell.
Farewell?
So dramatic.
So childish.
So?
Have you figured out
how to tell Qian Fei?
We have to tell her sooner or later.
Besides, she went to Shanlifang
for due diligence today.
I think she must have seen
Wang Ruohai already.
And I believe she's already moved on.
You ordered so much.
Sit down.
Why are you all wet from the rain?
Here, dry yourself off.
I'm starving.
I knew you'd be hungry.
Was your first day
of due diligence busy?
It's a long story.
Can I just eat first?
Sure, dig in.
Okay, eat up.
Why are you guys suddenly
treating me to a meal?
Here to show off our lovey-dovey stuff.
You're exaggerating.
How can you still laugh?
Fei.
Actually, Jingjing and I are here today
to offer a humble apology.
What are you afraid of?
If she wants to kill us,
I'll take the blame.
Just hurry up and say it.
Don't think just
because she says nothing,
- you can brush it off.
- Okay.
Did you see
you-know-who today?
You two already knew
that Wang Ruohai had gone to Shanlifang,
didn't you?
Shanlifang is Xinxin Vision's
parent company.
Wang Ruohai just became
their new Finance Director.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
I was doing it for the sake
of your career.
What if you knew
that scumbag was at Shanlifang
and you didn't work hard
to get into Fang Yun's project team?
I was thinking of you.
Don't you understand my good intentions?
How could I not understand you, silly?
It's a good thing you didn't tell me.
Otherwise, today,
I wouldn't have tried so hard
to get into that company.
Jingjing, you know me so well.
See?
Men are nothing.
To our mutual understanding.
Cheers.
Never try to guess
what a woman is thinking. Seriously.
So you two treated me to dinner today
just for this?
There was no need.
Jingjing and I are so close.
We're not like those fake friends.
Great.
Then we're splitting the bill today.
No way.
I haven't said I forgive you yet.
You have to treat me.
Fine.
About Liao Shiyu and Wang Ruohai,
they didn't give you
a hard time, did they?
They're your clients now,
the daddies who pay the bills.
I'm still a little worried.
You said it yourself, they're
the daddies.
The client is always right.
They probably won't bother
picking on a small fry like me.
Don't worry.
That's good.
If that woman, because of this,
makes things difficult for you
and fires you,
you have nothing to fear.
After we get married,
my husband will support me,
and I'll support you.
"My husband will support me,
and I'll support you."
Wait.
No, the sentence before that.
I can support you too.
No, no.
"After we get married..."
Wait, what do you mean?
It means...
Yao Jingjing.
You guys are getting married?
Didn't I tell you from the beginning
that we were here
to display our affection today?
No.
When did you propose?
Don't even get me started.
You know, that day,
I had just bought the ring.
I hadn't even set up
the proposal scene yet.
I was in the shower,
and she found the ring.
Let me tell you, in that situation,
if I hadn't proposed on the spot,
she would have forced me to produce
the mistress she'd imagined.
So he, in his bathrobe and barefoot,
knelt on the floor and proposed.
There was zero romance.
That's incredible. Really.
Too bad I wasn't there to see it.
But who cares if it was romantic or not?
Look, you're wearing the big ring.
How is that not romantic?
I never thought the day would come
when our Jingjing would be tamed.
I remember someone
used to always tell me
how terrible it was
to get married early.
And look at you now.
I, who desperately wanted
to get married,
can't get married anymore.
But you,
you've hit the jackpot
in both career and love.
Congratulations to you both.
Come on.
I must toast you.
You've captured a siren.
You've done a great service
to the people.
What do you mean, a siren?
Why would you say that about me?
We're at least
a power couple, right?
Look, Shanlifang is about to go public.
That means Xinxin Vision's
Shanlifang stock options
can be cashed out.
Won't we be financially free then?
We won't have to worry about money.
So, at a time like this,
if we don't get married and have a kid,
what are we waiting for?
So how many kids
are you planning to have?
We'll let nature take its course.
Besides, even if we get married,
we'll still maintain
our current lifestyle.
Even if we have kids,
we'll raise
and share the responsibilities together.
Right?
Absolutely.
My landlady won't let me down.
ظآزHey, you, you, you,
why is it you again?ظآز
ظآزAlways stumbling
upon my little secretsظآز
ظآزFalling on my brows, my lashesظآز
ظآزEven the strands by my mouthظآز
ظآزLike my favorite kittenظآز
ظآزOn a rainy spring afternoonظآز
ظآزHey, you, you, you,
why is it you again?ظآز
ظآزYou effortlessly
awaken my protective instinctsظآز
ظآزHitting all my little thoughtsظآز
ظآزMy doubts, and my temperظآز
ظآزLike my favorite beer
and fried chicken in autumnظآز
(Pretentious Li)
(Special Assistant,
didn't you get off work early?)
(Where are you?)
(Qian Fei)
(I'm off work.
There's no Special Assistant.)
(Pretentious Li)
(I saw that you hadn't returned.)
(What if you don't get to eat dinner?)
(I can't help but worry.)
(Want to eat the food in the fridge?)
I'll use the restroom.
(Just say it. You know how to use
a microwave, right?)
Lu Ze.
You have to treat Jingjing well
from now on.
Of course.
Jingjing is a good girl.
Although she can be
a bit willful sometimes,
it's because her family didn't give
her enough of a sense of security.
You must be more patient with her
about this in the future.
The biggest benefit
of her marrying me
is that I can accept all her strengths
and weaknesses,
as well as her theatrics
and insecurities.
Such a humblebrag.
By the way,
the preparations
for Shanlifang's IPO have begun.
We'll be analyzing simultaneously,
including yours,
the financial status
of all Shanlifang's subsidiaries.
Is that so?
I don't know the specifics.
I thought someone
would only come to oversee us
after a successful IPO.
It's already started.
As I recall,
I believe I've seen
your company's financial statements.
The numbers don't look good.
It seems a few recent financing rounds
have also failed.
It's true. The company is indeed
operating at a loss right now.
But it's the early stage of a startup.
The product hasn't been
commercialized yet,
and we need to keep investing.
So this is to be expected.
Three consecutive years of losses,
and yet Shanlifang is still keeping you
on board for their IPO.
It shows
that they value you highly.
They say capital is short-sighted,
but I feel quite lucky
to have met Shanlifang.
Chairman Liao is a good person.
But I still think...
You're back.
Look how happy you are.
You two must, absolutely must
be happy forever.
Congratulations again.
- Cheers.
- Come on.
Cheers.
=Love Has Fireworks=
(Next Episode Preview)
Oh my god!
What are you doing?
Trying to scare me
and taking advantage of me.
I heard
that your joint sponsorship team
is in chaos.
And you still haven't found a solution.
Here's the thing.
I will definitely come up
with a plan as soon as possible.
I'm just waiting for your word.
Do you know why Ms. Fang
is giving you the cold shoulder?
Whether Ms. Fang
accepts my apology or not,
I'm mentally prepared for it.
ظآزThere's no need
to know the ending from the startظآز
ظآزLet the melody play through the chords
with the windظآز
ظآزThere's no need
to keep every promise from the pastظآز
ظآزLeave some surprises
for the unknown in lifeظآز
ظآزThere's no need
to force things between two peopleظآز
ظآزPerhaps I'll feel alone,
yet still find you there for meظآز
ظآزThere's no need
to dwell on right or wrong, nor fearظآز
ظآزA hug means more
than countless apologiesظآز
ظآزI'll send you into the wide worldظآز
ظآزTo live with passion
and become who you truly areظآز
ظآزA quiet shoulderظآز
ظآزLike a harbor waiting
for your wandering soulظآز
ظآزI'll wait for the day
you return to a simpler lifeظآز
ظآزThe lights of home warm the nightظآز
ظآزA companionship that lasts foreverظآز
ظآزShining brightly
like the stars and the moon on highظآز
ظآزI'll send you into the wide worldظآز
ظآزTo live with passion
and become who you truly areظآز
ظآزA quiet shoulderظآز
ظآزLike a harbor waiting
for your wandering soulظآز
ظآزI'll wait for the day
you return to a simpler lifeظآز
ظآزThe lights of home warm the nightظآز
ظآزA companionship that lasts foreverظآز
ظآزShining brightly
like the stars and the moon on highظآز