I like you.
Do you want to go out with me?
He'd probably say no.
I want us to be something special.
You're special... to me.
Let's make it... official today.
This is all wrong. It sounds too casual.
What should I do?
A letter.
But how am I supposed to give this to him?
[Let's meet outside next time]
[Best date spots in Seoul]
You're here early.
Want to go here today?
It's supposed to be really beautiful here.
I can't.
Why not?
I've got things to do.
- Then how about tomorrow?
- I'm busy.
What do I do?
Soo An,
how are you feeling about today's shoot?
Hey.
How are you feeling about today's shoot?
Good.
It's been a while since our last shoot,
so I'm a little nervous
and excited at the same time.
Just trust me and do what I say for today.
I've prepared everything.
Sounds like you put in a lot of work.
I'll make sure to do my best, too.
Hey guys!
Stay tuned for our Reels
and behind-the-scenes today!
Get ready for some awesome footage!
Anyway, I skipped breakfast today,
so I'm starving.
Oh, look! Snacks!
Looks like Soo An packed these for us.
He's so thoughtful.
But I can't really eat right now
since I'm driving.
You go ahead and eat.
I don't want you going hungry.
What's that?
You feel bad eating by yourself?
Ah.
Come on.
Unbelievable.
This is good.
I made sure Hyun Jae had enough to eat.
Tastes good, doesn't it?
Yeah.
Khun!
[To Khun]
I'll try harder next time.
I'm so sorry.
Darn it...
Soo An is never around
when I actually need him.
Where is he?
Are you looking for something?
The mountains are definitely better
than the beach.
The air up here is totally different.
Right?
You're right. It feels great
to get out of the practice room for once.
This is amazing.
Ta-da!
Let's dig in.
Open up.
You eat it.
We came all the way out here.
Let's have some fun first.
I'm good.
Hey.
- Come on in!
- Stop it!
Let's just have some fun!
Come play with me!
Come on in!
Fine, then.
- Hey, what are you doing?
- I told you to get in.
- Khun!
- Khun.
- Please accept this.
Please accept this.
[To Khun]
[We will always be together]
- Khun!
- Please accept this.
- Khun.
Well, there goes my surprise.
Here, take this.
- Khun.
- There he is!
Get out of here. I'll hold them off.
Khun!
Remember the survival show?
Of course I do.
We used to...
do all kinds of stuff in front of the camera.
Yeah, we did.
Hey.
Everything I did then...
I meant all of it.
Me too.
Open up.
- Right?
- You're right.
I meant it all.
Me too.
But just so you know...
I didn't hit record today.
I know.
Hey, since when?
Hey, Yoon Soo An!
[To Khun]
Khun!
I feel a little shy
now that I'm actually writing this down.
But at the same time, writing your name out
gave me butterflies.
And just thinking about you right now is
making me nervous all over again.
I'm also wondering how you'll react to this.
It's amazing how one person can make me
feel so many different things.
Every new emotion I feel each day always
leads back to you, Khun.
Actually, no.
Out of everything, there's only one thing
I'm absolutely sure of.
[Jae Min]
Khun, I like you.
All right, everyone. We'll start
practicing with this demo track for now.
Anyone have any thoughts on this?
It hits you the second you hear it, right?
That's your song.
It's like it was written specifically for you.
When did you figure it out?
- How did you know?
- Shut up.
Then can I give you my answer now?
What's going on? What's with them?
Jae Min!
Hey, Jae Min.