♪Hey, you, you, you,
why is it you again?♪
♪Always stumbling upon
my little secrets♪
♪Falling on my brows, my lashes,
even the strands by my mouth♪
♪Like my favorite kitten
on a rainy spring afternoon♪
♪Hey, you, you, you,
why is it you again?♪
♪You effortlessly awaken
my protective instincts♪
♪Hitting all my little thoughts,
my doubts, and my temper♪
♪Like my favorite beer and fried chicken
in autumn, or spicy boiled fish in winter♪
♪Why is it you again?
That sweet way you speak♪
♪As if the whole world knows
my mind is full of you♪
♪Why is it still you?
That secret smile behind your cool facade♪
♪I might as well play along.
Let me protect you♪
♪Why is it always you?
The smile at the corner of your lips♪
♪Before I knew it, the words blurted out,
"I like you. I only like you."♪
=Love Has Fireworks=
(Based on "Investment Men and Women"
by Hong Er on Jinjiang Literature City)
=Episode 16=
Ruohai,
about what happened today,
you didn't lie to me, right?
No, what are you thinking?
That's good.
No matter what happens in the future,
you must tell me the truth.
I'm back.
Landlady,
are you asleep?
Have you been drinking?
- What do you want?
- Quick.
Hurry up.
What happened?
Quick, go heat up some supper for me.
Are you crazy? Heat it up yourself.
If you don't pull your foot back,
believe it or not,
I'll slam it in the door.
Go ahead.
If it breaks,
you'll have to sell your house
to pay my medical bills.
Go ahead.
You're harassing your female landlady
late at night.
Aren't you afraid I'll scream right now
and make you the neighborhood's
top gossip tomorrow?
Qian Fei,
did you save
this food for me on purpose?
Why?
Because
you taught Wang Ruohai a lesson for me,
so thank you.
Let me reheat it for you.
Coming!
What's been going on with you lately?
You're acting so strange. Look at you.
The moment you come home,
you dive into your room
and lie straight on the bed.
What is going on?
What do you mean?
I'm just getting ready to sleep.
Jun, is it because you ran into
some problems at work?
If you can't solve it, tell us.
Your dad and I will find a way for you.
Exactly.
No, there are no problems at work.
So are you unhappy with Fei?
Did you two have a fight?
How is that possible?
Then, it must be a relationship issue.
Has that girl been
distancing herself from you?
No. Aren't you annoying?
Please go out. I want to sleep.
You're really frustrating.
Can't you just talk to us?
Please go out.
Let's go.
Come on.
How outrageous.
Hey,
what do you think
is going on with our son lately?
He was rejected while pursuing a girl,
so he's lacking confidence.
How is that possible?
Our son has such great qualities.
He's the one who picks others.
Why would he lack confidence?
You still don't understand your own son.
Think about it.
Back when I was pursuing you,
I was rejected, too.
Did that dejected look of mine
not look just like our son?
Think about it carefully again.
It really did.
I've tasted
that feeling of doubting life.
It doesn't feel good.
Cut it out.
Cancel the photography exhibition
for me tomorrow.
We already made plans. Why cancel it?
Is the exhibition more important,
or is helping your son
regain his confidence more important?
You came up with a way so quickly?
Of course.
Who do you think my brain works for?
It works for our son.
Troupe Leader,
I'd like to borrow
the dance troupe's spare speakers.
Let's go.
Come on, careful.
Aren't these two speakers
from the dance troupe?
- How did they end up in our house?
- Careful.
Probably because
our house is relatively
close to the park.
Let's go.
- Mom, I don't want to go to the park.
- Going out?
Yeah, going out.
What about letting Dad drive,
and the two of you can go?
No, look,
it's the weekend. Going to the park
gets you some fresh air, right?
- The air is good.
- Open the car door quickly.
I'll open it.
Well...
Once everything is loaded...
It's all loaded.
Let Jun drive.
Let Dad drive.
Your dad drank this morning.
Just a little bit this morning.
Didn't he drink coffee?
He changed it. Get in the car, quick.
Get in the car.
Here are the keys.
Alright...
Alright.
Hurry up.
If your dad drives,
that's drunk driving.
The weather is so nice today.
Yeah.
Clear skies for miles.
Mom,
isn't the dancing over there?
This is a detour.
There's construction over there.
Follow me.
Come on.
- Follow me.
- Follow your mother.
It's over here.
Right here.
We're here. Yes, just up ahead.
Look, there's an umbrella over there.
Let's stay under this umbrella.
It's cool here.
Come, give this to me.
Mom,
didn't we come to dance?
Why are we here?
(Matchmaking)
They haven't arrived yet.
Troupe Leader
and the others should be here soon.
- It'll be fine once they're here.
- Right.
Okay.
You guys rest here.
I'll go buy some water for you.
- Sure.
- Alright.
- Come back soon.
- Hurry.
A handsome young man
born in the 1990s, 1.8 meters tall.
Won scholarships every year in college.
Mom, what are you doing?
What are you doing, Mom? Turn it off.
No...
No, Mom...
Stop shouting.
Yes, he's my son.
He looks good, right?
Take a look at my son.
He passed the civil service exam
right after graduation?
Yes.
A local civil servant is very good.
Right.
My daughter has a master's degree,
so they'd be a great match.
Yes.
If he hadn't passed
the exam on his first try,
he would've gone to grad school, too.
Exactly. He's very outstanding.
My daughter is a Fudan postdoc.
She prefers younger men.
Younger?
Five years younger is no problem.
The woman is five years older?
Then, no.
That won't do.
Let's add each other on WeChat.
Our daughter is a local Shanghainese.
Scan the QR code.
Okay.
Scan the QR code to add on WeChat.
Alright.
We'll be waiting for you.
Over here.
Let's scan the code.
Come, take your time.
Take your time.
One by one.
Step back a little.
We'll wait for him to accept.
Our daughter is quite pretty.
Over here, we want to scan the code.
Where do we scan?
Honey,
look.
Isn't that the girl we saw on the phone
the other day?
Look.
Are we done scanning over there?
How about this?
I'll find my son
and tell him to accept right away.
Alright?
We will add you.
In a moment.
Okay, we understand.
I understand.
Let's go.
Don't forget to accept.
I won't.
What's your deal?
I'm here to...
You didn't see that, right?
See what?
I just came out for a run.
Don't follow me if nothing's wrong.
Is it over there?
Looks like it, yeah.
Hurry up.
Honey.
What are you doing?
My heart condition is acting up.
I really can't run anymore.
You're letting me down here.
Why don't you take a break here first?
Okay.
I must catch up. I want to see...
I want to see
exactly why she is so arrogant.
(He has a car and a house.)
- Jun runs too fast.
- (And a Shanghai household registration.)
No way.
Honey, wait for me.
Wait for me.
What kind of physical condition is that?
What do you want from me? Speak up.
It really was
a coincidence running into you.
But since we did bump into each other,
I'll shamelessly ask you one more time.
What exactly makes me
not good enough for you?
As for me,
my relatives, friends,
and those
who have just met me,
they all think
I'm quite good,
and my qualities are excellent.
Why are you the only one
who thinks I'm not good?
Since we haven't met for a few days,
I thought you'd figured things out,
and we could still be friends.
Yet you ran over here
just to ask me this?
I really can't figure it out.
You can't figure it out
because you're still a big baby.
Really?
Aren't you?
I rejected you,
but instead of reflecting
on your own issues like an adult,
you come to me
and ask why I rejected you.
When you like someone,
you just blindly pursue them.
Have you ever considered
how much trouble
these actions of yours would cause me?
You're like an overgrown child,
disregarding other people's feelings
and only listening to your mother.
Your mom told you to drink more milk,
so you went to a bar
and ordered a glass of milk.
I'm different from you.
I live independently and love freedom.
So the kind of man I want
is not a mama's boy like you.
As far as I'm concerned,
you can only be Grand Chancellor,
and I can only be Po Ming.
Any other relationship
is absolutely impossible.
Do you understand this time?
So she is Po Ming.
A mama's boy? What's wrong
with being a mama's boy?
How ridiculous.
What are you doing?
Can't you save our son some face?
She hasn't had kids herself.
Once she has a child,
she won't think this way anymore.
Would she not feel for him?
This is so strange.
She left?
Maybe go home.
(When you like someone,
you just blindly pursue them.)
(Have you ever considered)
(how much trouble)
(these actions of yours would cause me?)
(I'm different from you.)
(I live independently and love freedom.)
(So the kind of man I want)
(is not a mama's boy like you.)
I really can't take it.
You can't even handle
this little bit of exercise?
My body can't take it.
You're amazing.
I'm impressed.
I really don't understand.
The young girl
doesn't even look that great,
yet she looks down on my son.
She even questioned
my parenting philosophy.
She doesn't understand at all.
Behind such an outstanding boy,
there must be a great mother
educating and guiding him.
Otherwise, how could there
be such an outstanding child?
Exactly.
She really doesn't know
how few outstanding
kids there are out there.
She even insists
that her man can't be a mama's boy.
Fine.
Let her go find one, then.
Iron Man? Spider-Man?
Let's see her try to find one.
Honey,
I think
maybe we should
give our son some breathing room.
Give him some space
to figure things out on his own,
alright?
I did give him space.
I gave him so much space.
Sit...
It's precisely because we were
too lenient
when it came to his love life
that you see what happened today.
What's the result?
Our son is suffering physically
and frustrated emotionally.
He needs our help.
Right.
From now on, you call the shots at home,
alright?
No way.
I won't let anyone
talk about my son like that.
I have to go find her.
Honey, the bus is here.
Landlady.
Landlady,
why are you eating instant noodles?
Aren't you going to cook?
Be quiet.
Hey, I ordered too much takeout
and can't finish it. Do you want some?
Fine. If you don't want it,
I'll throw it out.
I'll eat it. Leave it.
I'll leave it at the door.
What's going on?
You didn't even say thank you.
Seriously, what are you
doing in your room?
We haven't seen each other in days.
You're acting weird.
Why aren't you eating?
What are you trying to do
without food or water?
Are you trying to achieve enlightenment?
Are you okay, Qian Fei?
Qian Fei?
Qian Fei, what are you doing?
Oh my.
Look at your hair.
What's going on with you?
Finally finished.
Now, I can eat.
What have you been working on
these past two days?
You just vanished.
Let me reheat this for you.
It's way too cold.
No need, I'll just eat it like this.
I took on a translation gig
to make some extra cash.
The deadline was tight,
and the workload heavy.
I haven't slept in two days.
You're putting your life on the line.
Are you really that desperate for money?
Not as desperate as you.
If you need money, just tell me.
You can work for me.
My work is easy and pays well.
So you really are strapped for cash.
Don't worry,
in the short term, Wang Ruohai
can't possibly get you
kicked out of Shanlifang.
I don't even have
the strength to split my chopsticks.
Wang Ruohai can't
get you kicked out of Shanlifang.
You have Fang Yun shielding you.
Besides, you're still
my special assistant, right?
As for the money you owe him,
we have to go by the book, right?
The money you owed before,
see if there's an IOU or a receipt.
(Senior)
I'll help you look it over.
Hello, Senior.
I'm pretty much done.
I'll check and proofread it,
and then send it to you.
I won't be late. I won't delay things.
Alright. Goodbye.
I bet you're the only one
who'd dare take on such a rushed job.
You're playing with your life.
Let me reheat this for you. It's cold.
It's fine. By the time it's hot,
I'll be starved to death.
Does it taste good?
Aren't you going to eat?
(Printing Room)
Jingjing, why are you here?
Why am I here?
Why do you think I'm here?
Did you forget?
I forgot.
My bad.
I promised to go furniture shopping
with you this afternoon.
How do you not even
have time to eat your takeout?
It's cold.
Time is tight,
and the workload is heavy.
How come I don't see
anyone else working overtime?
I have to finish all this stuff
a few days in advance
so I can free up my energy
to take on side gigs
and make extra money.
Because of Wang Ruohai?
The sooner it's over, the better.
I don't want to owe him
anything anymore.
I have money. I'll give it to you.
Stop right there.
You're about to get married,
and this is exactly when you need money.
If I scrape it together,
I still have some.
Look at how exhausted you are right now.
Are you trying to kill yourself
by working this hard?
Jingjing,
today,
I can't go shopping.
Why don't you go find Lu Ze?
Alright, then.
Go on, hurry up.
If it gets any later,
the mall will close.
Do you hate me?
Yes.
You're not allowed to hate me.
Alright, get back to work.
Take care.
Don't overwork yourself.
I know.
Call me if you need anything.
Bye-bye.
Can I call you back in a bit?
It's not convenient for me to talk
about the spin-off plan right now.
Why would I tell you
all this over the phone?
I think this sofa would look
quite nice in the living room.
I know.
Lu Ze?
I'm already overwhelmed now, okay?
Listen, I'll call you back later.
Are we shopping or not?
If you have stuff, we can stop.
We're shopping.
Didn't I just hang up?
Jingjing, it's mainly because
lately at Xinxin Vision...
If Qian Fei hadn't been
so overwhelmed these past two days,
I would have had her come with me.
She could have given me some advice.
I was just saying that placing
this sofa in the living room
seems quite suitable.
Jingjing,
our company has been
going through some changes lately,
so...
Well, I don't really understand
the specifics
of your company's business.
But if it's something
like PR or publicity,
I could still help you
brainstorm, right?
Alright, let's not talk
about the company. I'm all yours today.
(Even though I have
enough money to give Wang Ruohai,)
(at this critical moment
right before the wedding,)
(asking Lu Ze for money
to lend to someone else)
(is inappropriate.)
Well...
Go ahead.
Has Qian Fei contacted you
these past couple of days?
I just said Qian Fei
has been overwhelmed lately.
On one hand,
she's busy with Shanlifang's IPO,
and on the other,
Wang Ruohai is chasing her for money.
I really feel bad for her.
So I was thinking...
You feel bad for her,
but she might not feel bad for you.
What do you mean by that?
Are you trying
to drive a wedge between us?
No, it's not like that.
I didn't mean that.
Alright, forget it.
Let's drop it, okay?
Let's look at furniture.
You're drinking without me?
My bad.
You're in a bad mood,
and you'd rather sit here drinking alone
than talk to me about it.
But I'm not just here to share your joy.
I can also help
carry your negative emotions.
It's just that work
has been stressful lately.
But isn't everything
moving in the right direction?
And sometimes,
pressure can be a motivation.
It's not a bad thing.
I understand the logic,
but I just feel
a bit suffocated in my chest.
I'm working really hard on R&D.
Day and night.
But...
I just can't deliver the product.
I want to blame someone,
but in the end, I realize
I can only blame my own incompetence.
You shouldn't say that.
I know you're a perfectionist,
but how could
good things be made so easily?
Right?
And I think you have a quality
that is wonderful.
It's what I admire most about you.
Even though you're a tech guy,
you still have a sense of idealism.
You must hold on to that.
Jingjing,
having you in my life is enough.
I'm here for Wang Ruohai,
your Financial Director.
Could you please contact him for me?
Excuse me, do you have an appointment?
Just tell him my name is Yao Jingjing.
Whether I have
an appointment or not, he'll see me.
All right, please wait a moment.
I'm very calm right now.
I just want an explanation.
Is there a problem?
Sir, please leave this place first.
We have no obligation
to discuss this with you.
It was rejected by your office.
I want an explanation. Any problem?
I can answer your questions,
but not those of a madman!
You're not the one I want.
I want Li Yifei!
Get out of my way!
Lu Ze, calm down.
Let's talk this over slowly.
Fine. Let's talk.
Talk it over slowly, right?
Fine.
I just want to know why.
I put in so much effort
and I finally found a new buyer
to take over Xinxin Vision.
Li Yifei,
but you rejected this plan.
Do you know what this means?
This is pushing me to my death!
I just don't understand.
As long as he agrees,
Shanlifang,
Xinxin Vision,
and the new buyer all win.
It's a win-win-win.
Why?
Tell me why, Li Yifei!
Come out!
Get out of my way!
Give me an explanation. Why?
- Alright, what's the arguing about??
- Get out of my way.
Zhao De, let him in.
Get back to your work.
(Director's Office,
Shanlifang Hotel Group)
You should still remember
last time at the Venture Capital Forum,
my evaluation
of your company's project, right?
Look,
you just watched the roadshow, too.
What did you think?
It was good.
Do you have any specific feedback?
The finance circle is quite small.
You see, people in venture capital
and securities all know one another.
So there's no shortage of interest for
good projects. Everyone fights for them.
But as for your project,
there are a few issues
that I'm curious about.
Please go ahead.
First,
you're currently tied to Shanlifang.
So who owns
the patent rights to this product?
Do you have controlling power?
Second,
what if
Shanlifang only wants to use this app
under their own hotel brand?
Then, what's the point of you
seeking financing today?
Third, you also mentioned just now
that this product
still has a year and a half
of development time.
Furthermore,
if Shanlifang
suddenly suspends its investment in you,
and you can't find other
financing channels for the time being,
do you have a backup plan?
Well, it's like this...
First,
I did sign a contract with Shanlifang,
but how it's developed is up to me.
And...
Sorry to interrupt.
Is how long
development takes also up to you?
If they insist
on selling it off
as a semi-finished product,
can you refuse?
Or rather,
when Shanlifang threatens you
by suspending investment,
do you have a substitute?
Do you have an alternative plan?
I will hold my ground.
Well, this isn't something you can
change just by holding your ground.
It seems you
are still not very familiar
with capital, Mr. Lu.
Yes, when it comes
to how capital operates,
I'm not very familiar.
Because I come from
a technical background.
But I can...
So, controlling power
is solely in Shanlifang's hands,
right?
Mr. Lu,
if I were an investor,
even if I were
interested in the project,
your answer just now
would have killed my interest.
You can't control
the direction or the timeline,
nor can you determine
the return on investment.
You've just painted a rosy picture,
but this picture
belongs to someone else,
and I still have to pay for it.
Then, who
in this world
do you think
would do something so foolish?
So,
you don't think highly of this project?
Alright, since you remember all that,
I won't repeat myself.
However, I should add
that the product Xinxin Vision
is currently developing
doesn't have high technical barriers,
but it has a high dependency
on the market.
So I advise you
not to limit your vision
to the hotel industry.
Maybe it could have
a better and broader...
So you're rejecting my investment
just to prove
how right your vision was back then,
and that I'm doomed to fail, right?
If you're always going
to think of me that way,
there's really no need for us to talk.
Fine.
I won't speak. You talk, alright?
Come, take a look.
These are the acquisition
and loan contracts previously signed
between Shanlifang Hotel
and Xinxin Vision.
I signed them.
Is there an issue?
Then, you should be very clear.
Back then, Shanlifang
transferred most of the funds
to Xinxin Vision's accounts
in the form of loans.
If a new investor wants to take over,
they must first
pay off the previous loans,
rather than just
acquiring the current assets.
Do you understand this point now?
So,
for the sake of
so-called book statistics,
I must reject this new investment?
Is that what you mean?
If not?
A bunch of scammers.
That's just how capital operates.
That contract you signed
with Shanlifang back then
was drafted that way.
(Shanlifang Hotel Group)
Where is he? Hasn't he come down yet?
Miss,
Mr. Wang is in a meeting.
Please wait a little longer.
A meeting?
Is Wang Ruohai that afraid to see me?
I'm sorry, please wait a little longer.
I took the day off today.
I just finished an event near you.
Are you busy right now?
If not, come down
and have lunch with me.
I'm already in your lobby.
The Financial Director
of Shanlifang Hotel Group,
Wang Ruohai,
what kind of person is he anyway?
Mr. Wang.
You're here again.
What's going on?
You finally decided to show your face.
The injuries on your face
healed pretty quickly.
Let's go inside for a drink of water.
Don't pull and drag me around.
Lest people misunderstand
and think we have some
shameful business going on.
I think it's spacious and bright here.
It's perfect for us to talk.
Perfect for you, you mean.
You could say that.
Wait for me.
So much money?
And it's in cash.
500,000. Not a penny more,
not a penny less.
Record it quickly.
Jing is amazing.
What are you doing?
I'm here to pay you back.
When you two broke up,
you explicitly said
there was no rush
to talk about repayment.
Why are you going back on your word now?
You're even using a job opportunity
to threaten and force
your ex-girlfriend to pay you back.
It's fine. You're heartless,
but I still brought the money to you.
Count it in person.
And promise in front of everyone
that you will never
harass Qian Fei again.
And this matter
between us will be settled.
Please take the money
and leave immediately,
or I will call security.
Take it.
Hello, I am the person in charge here.
If there's a problem,
we can resolve it slowly in my office.
Please don't affect
the other guests here.
The PIC is here, right?
Then, I won't hide anything anymore.
My main purpose here today
is to expose the misconduct
of Wang Ruohai,
the Financial Director
of Shanlifang Hotel Group.
His personality
will be judged fairly by us.
But making a scene here
to court publicity
is nothing more than an attempt
to tarnish the hotel's reputation.
I suspect you were sent by a competitor.
I have the right to ask you to leave.
What's going on here?
It's fine. I'll handle it.
You arranged all of this, right?
No, I came here on my own.
What is going on?
What does this woman do?
What's going on here?
Catching a mistress.
Cheating, having an affair,
and shameless!
You're crossing the line.
So, she's a mistress.
Let's just let this matter go.
Let's leave first.
How can we leave?
How can we let it go like this?
Are we going to be controlled
by this kind of man?
Doesn't he want money?
Give it back to him!
Take the 500,000 yuan away!
Let me tell you,
he only cares about money.
You are disrupting
our normal operations.
For the hotel's losses,
I will take legal action
to demand that you bear them in full.
As for the personal defamation
against Mr. Wang and me,
I will reserve the right
to take legal recourse
and may file a lawsuit at any time.
Fine, do it anytime.
What are you doing?
Don't touch me!
Please leave.
Let go!
Calling for backup
because you lost the argument, right?
What are you doing?
Tell him to stop.
What are you doing? Let go!
Don't touch my wife.
What are you doing? Take your hands off!
Let go. I told you to let go!
Let go. Don't touch me!
Stop it!
Are you okay?
Why are you here?
What happened?
To help Qian Fei pay back.
Qian Fei,
my mom is sick.
I need money.
I just want my money back.
Am I wrong?
We used to be best friends.
Everyone falls on hard times.
Right now
is the hardest moment of my life.
Why do you guys treat me like this?
I'm so sorry.
I didn't know your mom was sick.
Getting her treated
is what matters most now.
I'll find a way to get you the money.
How about that 500,000...
What?
It seems this
has something to do with you, huh?
Ms. Liao, what do you mean by that?
Shanlifang Hotel Group
spun off the subsidiary
that belongs to you
for the sake of the overall IPO.
What? Because you're unhappy,
you got someone
to pull a stunt like this?
That's a low blow.
Help me contact
a few social media accounts.
Yes, dinner together tonight.
Make it quick.
I'll give you the details in the car.
Ruohai, let's go.
Alright, it's over.
- Let's go.
- You can go.
Are you alright?
No, wait a minute.
Let's go.
What did she mean by that just now?
What happened to the company?
A spin-off?
You haven't told her yet?
Didn't you keep it from her, too?
No, wait a minute.
You both knew,
but didn't tell me?
Is that so?
=Love Has Fireworks=
(Next Episode Preview)
Make it clear.
I don't want this
to affect our sponsorship team's work.
So please resolve it
as soon as possible.
Go and apologize to Liao Shiyu.
I'm not going.
Later, when Fulaxida makes money,
make a list, and I'll handle it for you.
Helping your landlady like this...
Have you really fallen for her?
My mom used to
sew things for me like this too.
Take it and wear it.
Remember to pay me.
♪There's no need
to know the ending from the start♪
♪Let the melody play through the chords
with the wind♪
♪There's no need
to keep every promise from the past♪
♪Leave some surprises
for the unknown in life♪
♪There's no need
to force things between two people♪
♪Perhaps I'll feel alone,
yet still find you there for me♪
♪There's no need
to dwell on right or wrong, nor fear♪
♪A hug means more
than countless apologies♪
♪I'll send you into the wide world♪
♪To live with passion
and become who you truly are♪
♪A quiet shoulder♪
♪Like a harbor waiting
for your wandering soul♪
♪I'll wait for the day
you return to a simpler life♪
♪The lights of home warm the night♪
♪A companionship that lasts forever♪
♪Shining brightly
like the stars and the moon on high♪
♪I'll send you into the wide world♪
♪To live with passion
and become who you truly are♪
♪A quiet shoulder♪
♪Like a harbor waiting
for your wandering soul♪
♪I'll wait for the day
you return to a simpler life♪
♪The lights of home warm the night♪
♪A companionship that lasts forever♪
♪Shining brightly
like the stars and the moon on high♪