♪Hey, you, you, you,
why is it you again?♪
♪Always stumbling upon
my little secrets♪
♪Falling on my brows, my lashes,
even the strands by my mouth♪
♪Like my favorite kitten
on a rainy spring afternoon♪
♪Hey, you, you, you,
why is it you again?♪
♪You effortlessly awaken
my protective instincts♪
♪Hitting all my little thoughts,
my doubts, and my temper♪
♪Like my favorite beer and fried chicken
in autumn, or spicy boiled fish in winter♪
♪Why is it you again?
That sweet way you speak♪
♪As if the whole world knows
my mind is full of you♪
♪Why is it still you?
That secret smile behind your cool facade♪
♪I might as well play along.
Let me protect you♪
♪Why is it always you?
The smile at the corner of your lips♪
♪Before I knew it, the words blurted out,
"I like you. I only like you."♪
=Love Has Fireworks=
(Based on "Investment Men and Women"
by Hong Er on Jinjiang Literature City)
=Episode 9=
Hello?
Gosh, you were sleeping?
I just woke up.
HR couldn't reach you,
so they called me.
HR?
HR called me?
What for?
What else could it be? Good news.
Congratulations. Your dream came true.
Get over here.
You mean I got reinstated?
Seriously?
You know what?
I just dreamed that I got my job back.
Cut the chatter.
(Hejing Securities)
Get over here.
No.
I can't get my hopes up
for nothing again like last time.
I need to hear it from Ms. Fang
before I believe it.
I'm on my way.
You know why I asked you here,
don't you?
Why are you looking at me like that?
I'll only believe it
if I hear it from you.
Anything anyone else says,
I take with a grain of salt.
Your report was valuable.
Even financial tricks
on Shanlifang's level
were uncovered by you.
I only found the original data
and confirmed it.
Without hard evidence,
all suspicions are just speculation.
And you were the one
who found the evidence.
You proved your ability
through your actions.
So, welcome back to Hejing to assist me.
Please have a seat.
That's wonderful.
Thank you for giving me a second chance,
Ms. Fang.
I'll give it everything I've got.
I'll straighten out all
of Shanlifang's accounts and...
Don't get too fired up just yet.
You're still new here.
You need to observe more and learn more.
Don't think too highly of yourself.
Pride comes before a fall.
Alright. I'll keep that in mind.
Also, we've signed
an agreement with Zhizhong
regarding the division
of responsibilities.
Zhizhong will be the one
to formally raise
Shanlifang's financial issues.
So don't say a word about this
to anyone outside. Understood?
Understood.
I'll focus on doing my job well.
Very good.
Oh, right, Ms. Fang.
What will I be doing
after joining the team?
I'd like to prepare in advance.
Running errands.
Okay. Thank you, Ms. Fang.
You'll put this information
into the spreadsheet...
Look.
Moli, Zhaozhao, Zijun.
I'm back.
We heard about it.
We missed you so much.
I missed you guys, too.
Seeing you come back,
we're genuinely happy for you.
It proves that as long as
you're willing to work hard,
the company won't fire
a capable person for no reason.
Well said.
Hard work never lets effort go to waste.
Congratulations. Got assigned straight
to the front-office project team.
The core department
of investment banking.
But Ms. Fang told me
that I'm starting out running errands.
Still, you'll have unlimited potential,
right?
Qian Fei.
You must be thrilled.
I got transferred,
and you filled in my place.
What are you on about?
Stop pretending.
Isn't this all thanks to you?
If you hadn't snitched to Ms. Fang,
would I have gotten reassigned?
Everyone, be careful around her.
To get her job back, she'll do anything
to take someone else's position.
I'm living proof.
What's that got to do with me?
Fei, when are you officially starting?
Probably in the next few days.
I'm back.
(The landlady's mood seems off.)
(Did Fang Yun play me?)
(Was she never planning to let her
return to Hejing?)
You're cleaning again?
The place looks spotless.
Honestly,
if you put all this energy into chores,
how are you supposed
to have any left for work?
Why don't you hire a cleaning service?
Housework helps me relax.
You have a hobby like that?
Foot.
By the way, I got reinstated.
Ms. Fang assigned me to Shanlifang.
Really?
That's great. Very good.
Why are you so excited?
I...
You got your job back.
Doesn't that mean
I get extra dishes now?
I'm happy.
But something's off.
This isn't what I imagined you'd be like
after getting reinstated.
Why don't you seem excited at all?
Where's that fearless determination
you had
when you were set on joining
Fang Yun's team?
Bring it back.
Celebrate. Perk up.
I have something to ask you.
What is it?
Ms. Fang said
we have to keep this confidential.
You alone would negotiate
with Shanlifang.
Why are you talking
all of this on by yourself?
Why else?
Because I'm capable.
I like being in the spotlight.
Aren't you worried
you might completely offend Shanlifang?
I know.
What am I afraid of?
If you want to accomplish big things,
don't sweat the small stuff.
I don't care about things like that.
I really don't get
how someone like you
became the project leader.
What are you looking at?
Nothing. Nothing at all.
I still have another question.
Another one?
Well, one...
One question for one meal.
I can cook for you. Do you dare eat it?
What do you mean?
Yes, you've got guts.
But you've got no shame.
What do you mean?
(Li Yifei: Authentic
Da Hong Pao Tea Egg)
Uh.
Didn't I hide it from you?
How come?
It's my first time doing this.
I'm still figuring it out.
I suddenly feel uncomfortable.
My back hurts. My waist hurts.
Argh.
My dinner is gone.
(I even saved room for it.)
(I thought she would make dinner
to thank me.)
(I thought a feast was waiting for me.)
(Poor me.)
I'm not happy!
I made too much for dinner.
Rather than dump it in the trash,
I might as well feed some animal.
If you want to eat, come over.
Hurry up.
Look at you.
I never said I wanted to eat.
Fine, fine.
What? Not using serving spoons?
I thought you hated sharing food.
I'm afraid you'll poison me.
Eating from the same plate is safer.
How did I end up with
such an annoying tenant?
such a generous landlady
who also happens to cook so well?
You're just buttering me up.
Do you want something from me?
What could I possibly want?
I have no ulterior motive.
Eat up.
Who is it?
Who's there?
- Hello. Is Mr. Li home?
- Hello.
Li Yifei, what big piece
did you buy this time?
It's mine.
Great. It's arrived.
Come on in.
Take it apart first
or assemble it first?
- Take it apart first.
- Okay. This way.
What are you doing?
We're taking all of this apart?
All of it.
Just throw them away.
Sure.
Li Yifei, get out here.
I'm busy.
Get out here.
Careful.
Don't bump into anything.
What's wrong?
Did I ever agree
to let you change the bed?
You did.
When?
There was this one time
when you were drunk.
You had only started drinking,
so you weren't completely wasted.
You just don't remember.
Did I?
Yeah. You forgot.
Well...
If I agreed,
then go ahead and change it.
But somehow, I don't quite believe you.
Would I lie to you
over something this trivial?
That day, you told me
you'd originally planned to turn
the bed in my room
into a mother-and-child bed
after you got married and had kids.
But then, you weren't
getting married anymore.
Right? And there
wouldn't be any kids either.
You said just looking at that bed
upset you.
So I figured I'd help you replace it.
Free of charge.
Out of sight, out of mind.
And you agreed.
You even thanked me.
And now you've forgotten all about it.
Careful.
Alright then.
Go ahead and install it.
Keep the noise down. It's late.
Okay.
Sir, we'll keep it down.
♪Zhen fell in love with Qiang♪
♪On a starry night♪
This is amazing.
I can finally roll around in bed.
This is so comfortable.
You scared me.
I thought it over carefully.
I definitely never agreed
to let you change the bed
while I was drunk.
You did.
I know myself.
I'm extremely careful with money.
If I'd agreed,
I definitely would've talked to you
about depreciation on the old furniture.
But obviously, I didn't.
That's a good point.
I've seen right through you.
Don't be mad.
This bed is really comfortable. Try it.
Landlady! Qian Fei!
Don't be mad. Come on.
(Shanghai World Financial Center)
Dang Yu.
What are you doing here?
Last time, you said to contact me
when you were free,
but you never gave me your contact.
So I could only come here
and wait for you.
I forgot.
What's it?
Didn't we agree
that I'd treat you to a meal?
We'd invite Qian Fei and Li Yifei too.
I think there was something like that.
So I wanted to ask if
you're free tomorrow night
to grab a meal together.
I've got a side job tomorrow night.
What about lunchtime?
I'm busy at noon, too.
Let's do it another day.
No.
I want to lock in
a time today.
Why?
Because
the last time at Qian Fei's place,
I kind of scared her.
I want to take her out for a meal,
but I don't think it's appropriate
to ask her out one-on-one.
So I was hoping you and Li Yifei
could come along.
That sounds pretty reasonable.
I knew it. You insisted on
making it a group dinner,
and it had to be four people.
You wanted to ask Qian Fei out,
but you were too shy to say so,
didn't you?
Actually, it's not...
It's fine.
Let's do tomorrow at noon.
I'll move some things around,
and Qian Fei should be free too.
It's settled then.
Alright.
Let's add each other on WeChat.
Done.
I'm off.
See you tomorrow.
Hello, dear.
See this?
Look. Abalone, razor shells,
and prawns.
I'll blanch them
with ginger and cooking wine.
I even bought some ham.
Steam everything for 15 minutes.
Pour out the extra liquid afterward.
That's enough. Stop making me jealous.
I want to fly back to Shanghai
right now.
How come you always
cook all this good stuff
when I'm not around?
I'm celebrating getting my job back.
Of course, I'm going to
treat myself a little.
Lu Ze and you disappeared
on a team-building trip
without saying a word.
Don't even get me started.
I thought I was getting a free vacation
and lucking out.
Turns out I was the one
who got the raw deal.
(Wang Ruo Hai is in charge)
When you get back,
(of the Shanlifang IPO)
I'll make it again for you.
Is that okay?
Fei, I'm hanging up.
We're going to get dinner.
Go ahead.
Hang up for me. My hands are wet.
Bye.
♪Zhen fell in love with Qiang♪
♪On a starry night♪
♪An airplane flew across the sky♪
You said
that if Qian Fei found out
Wang Ruohai was at Shanlifang,
she might not return to Hejing.
Now that she's joined the project team,
why are you keeping it from her?
I'm worried she'll back out
once she finds out.
You have no idea how hard it was for her
to get into this team.
Even so, you should tell her.
If she knows you knew all along
and didn't say anything,
good luck talking your way
out of that one.
You think I can't smooth things over?
You think I'm wrong, don't you?
No. Absolutely not.
How could I think you're wrong?
You're right. You're always right.
How could you ever be wrong?
Cheers.
Thanks to Heaven for getting you back
into the workforce.
Have some meat.
Good, right?
This is delicious.
I love cooking for people like you.
It makes me so happy.
Your actions were a pretty honest review
of my cooking.
Why would I rate your cooking?
You cooked for Wang Ruohai for years.
Didn't he praise you?
We already broke up. Don't bring him up.
You should've broken up a long time ago.
You two were never right for each other.
From my life experience,
if you're looking for a husband,
you should find someone
who appreciates your strengths,
someone who satisfies your taste buds,
and someone you can happily
share meals with.
You put this paste
into your stir-fried eggplant.
It's really good.
You should make it more often.
I like it.
(Li Yifei: Authentic
Da Hong Pao Tea Egg)
Uh. Didn't I hide it from you?
How come?
It's my first time doing this.
I'm still figuring it out.
(What is this? It smells incredible.)
(I've changed my mind.
I don't want those extra dishes.)
I want this instead.
What's on your mind?
By your logic,
your life experience means
you should find a boyfriend
who thinks your instant noodles
taste amazing.
Instant noodles aren't healthy.
If I can't cook,
I can still order takeout.
Put away the leftovers.
I'll wash all the dishes.
Why are you being so nice?
Come over again soon.
I'll cook for you.
You just want someone
to do your dishes for free.
Fine. I can't keep mooching off
your cooking every time.
Alright. I'll clean these up.
It's all yours, then.
Go rest.
(I made too much for dinner.)
(If you haven't eaten yet,
you can come back.)
(Wouldn't want the food to go to waste.)
(In the spirit of doing our part
for the planet,)
(I may reluctantly come back)
(and help solve
this food surplus crisis.)
(No need.)
(The stray dogs downstairs are hungry.)
(Qian Fei)
(Hands off! They're all mine.)
(Why are you fighting with dogs
over food?)
(A single man like me
is more pitiful than a stray.)
(Fine. The dog food's all yours.)
I'm fast, right?
What are you laughing about?
Uh.
I just snagged a pack of tissues
on a flash sale. So cheap.
That goofy grin on your face.
I bought this for you.
Remember to use it.
I love you.
It works really well.
Take good care of yourself.
Alright.
Well, you've been broken up
for some time.
Have you thought about
looking for someone new?
Not interested.
How can you not be interested?
You're still young.
You can't swear off dating
just because of one jerk.
You're acting weird.
You don't worry about yourself,
but you're worried about me.
I...
Is there something
you're trying to tell me?
Stop beating around the bush.
Someone wants to take you out to a meal.
Who?
(Lujiazui Dongyuan Subdistrict Office)
What are you treating me to today?
Which girl are you texting this time?
What girl?
I'm not eating with you today.
The landlady saved me some food.
I'm heading home to eat.
You can't betray your friend.
I told my mom
I wasn't going home for dinner.
If I go back,
there won't be anything left to eat.
Your mom is not going to let you starve.
What's there to worry about?
I was just passing by to check on you.
Seeing that you're still
sturdy, healthy,
and rosy-cheeked, I can rest easy.
Now go home and eat.
Have you actually fallen
for your landlady?
With my standards?
You think I'd fall for her?
You're too close to see it.
Listen to my analysis.
The last time I ate at your place,
I thought something was off.
Didn't you notice
you two didn't use serving spoons?
Did we not?
I probably forgot.
Fine. Then let me ask you this.
When you drive,
other than girls you like,
you always make other women
sit in the back.
And where does your landlady sit?
Of course, she sits in the...
Front passenger seat.
Makes sense?
You see,
I borrowed this car from the steward.
I'm not that particular.
It has nothing to do with the car.
It's about your subconscious.
The fact that you're not even sure
whether you like her
means you've fallen for her.
Nonsense.
You've been single all your life.
And you're questioning
a love expert like me?
Getting a little full of yourself,
aren't you?
Go home and eat.
Don't forget about the plan tomorrow.
I know. You treat, and I pay.
See you.
Bye-bye.
Me and him?
No way.
Why not?
You know each other.
And he said,
to ease the awkwardness from before,
he wants to take you out for a meal
and apologize properly.
I think it's a great opportunity.
You can eat and get to know each other.
If you get to know him more,
who knows...
He never told me.
He's probably shy.
When did he tell you?
He came to see me after work today.
He was really sincere.
He especially came to see you?
I'm not going.
I...
I'm busy.
Come on, it's the weekend tomorrow.
I'm really not interested.
Not even interested in a meal?
If the conversation goes badly,
just treat it as a free fancy meal.
Free fancy meal?
He's the one getting
three free meals a day.
You have to go.
I've cleared my schedule for tomorrow.
I want a free fancy meal.
Just the three of us?
Oh, I forgot to tell you.
Four people.
You, me, Jun Cheng,
and Li Yifei.
He... Likes me?
Is this a prank?
What prank?
He's a nice guy. Very sincere.
Very sincere?
That's why people need to
get to know each other.
I... I can't.
We're familiar with each other.
Why go out for a meal?
Don't you think it's weird?
Oh, come on. It's just a meal.
Stop dragging it out.
Are you going or not?
Fine, fine. I'll listen to you.
But just so we're clear.
I'm only going for the free meal.
Okay. As long as you go.
What are you wearing tomorrow?
No idea.
How old are these clothes?
You wore this back in university,
didn't you?
This one.
It's stretched out.
You're still keeping it?
Oh my goodness.
What is this?
Barbie pink?
Flamingo?
How old are you?
What's wrong with it?
And this?
A dragon fruit?
What even is all this?
Please.
Throw out every piece in this color.
Are you helping me pick an outfit,
or sorting out my wardrobe?
This one isn't bad.
You actually bought this brand?
It's a gift from Jingjing.
I knew it.
This works.
Let's go with this.
But...
Puff sleeves?
Isn't that inappropriate
for the occasion?
Why wouldn't it be?
What's wrong with puff sleeves?
A young man
sincerely invited you to a meal.
Show some effort, okay?
This is the one.
I don't see it that way.
Alright, it's just a meal.
I'll keep the conversation going.
It won't be awkward.
Okay.
I'm counting on you.
It's getting late. I should get going.
There won't be any cabs left.
Okay.
I...
What a coincidence.
When did you get home?
You didn't make a sound.
I'm leaving.
Okay. Bye.
Bye. Take care.
Come in.
I...
You're not planning to
wear this, are you?
What's wrong with it? Can't I?
This?
Seriously?
You'll look like a turkey.
Let go.
You are a turkey.
I'm not going.
That's right.
I thought you'd been busy
with work lately.
Turns out you've been thinking
about this stuff instead.
Look at you.
You just broke up,
and now you're going on a blind date.
You leave one jerk to find another one.
Aren't you tired?
Good. If you're not going,
then I can finally relax.
Li Yifei,
do you have split personalities?
Are you testing me?
Why would I test you?
You're the one who invited me.
And you're the one
calling yourself a jerk.
Messing with me at home wasn't enough,
so you went to ask Dang Yu
to arrange a meal?
You said you liked me?
Is messing with me fun?
Is it amusing?
Get out. I don't want to see you.
No, wait. Hold on.
Out!
Hold on.
I said I was a jerk?
I like you?
I get it now.
I get it.
Are you insane?
Jun Cheng invited you.
Didn't I tell you?
Who did you think it was?
So it was all a misunderstanding.
A misunderstanding.
I've never been wronged like this
in my entire life.
Poor me.
There's no way
I could clear my name.
Aren't you going to make it up to me?
I'm so sorry.
It was a misunderstanding.
I thought you were inviting me
to a meal.
I thought you had...
Feelings for you?
Yeah.
You overthought it.
That's definitely overthinking.
It's fine.
When someone's always on your mind,
misunderstandings happen.
I understand.
What are you talking about?
Are you saying I have feelings for you?
You're overthinking now. I really don't.
You see,
I don't have the time or the energy
to like anyone right now.
Don't worry.
I swear. If I have the slightest
improper intentions toward you,
may lightning strike me down.
Fine, fine, fine.
That's a bit much.
I'll take your word for it.
But let me add one thing.
Jun doesn't like you either.
Jun doesn't like anyone.
He's only interested in gaming.
When he said he wanted
to treat everyone to a meal,
he meant exactly that.
Got it?
Got it.
The same goes for Dang Yu.
She has too many side hustles.
It's easy to misread
other people's kindness.
Now that I know
you're not interested in me,
I can finally relax.
(What does that mean?)
(What's wrong with me?)
You know, we're landlady and tenant,
plus colleagues.
It's more than enough for me.
If there's anything else on top of that,
I'd completely lose it.
Come on, master.
This toast is for you.
After this drink,
let's pretend
nothing happened tonight.
Cheers.
Another game.
Still playing?
Come on.
Still drinking?
Hurry.
Come on.
Let's play a game.
Ready.
Three, two, one. Look over here.
You lost.
♪Hey, you, you, you,
why is it you again?♪
♪Always stumbling upon
my little secrets♪
♪Falling on my brows, my lashes♪
♪Even the strands by my mouth♪
♪Like my favorite kitten♪
♪On a rainy spring afternoon♪
♪Hey, you, you, you,
why is it you again?♪
You effortlessly awaken
my protective instincts♪
♪Hitting all my little thoughts♪
♪My doubts, and my temper♪
♪Like my favorite beer
and fried chicken in autumn♪
♪Or spicy boiled fish in winter♪
♪Why is it you again?
That sweet way you speak♪
♪As if the whole world knows
my mind is full of you♪
♪Why is it still you?
That secret smile behind your cool facade♪
♪I might as well play along.
Let me protect you♪
♪Why is it always you?
The smile at the corner of your lips♪
♪Before I knew it,
the words blurted out♪
♪I like you. I only like you♪
Landlady, I must say,
you're actually pretty cute
when you're drunk.
You're nothing like your normal self.
Normally, you're too much
of a tough girl.
It's a little...
Asleep?
Such a lightweight.
Yet you still have the nerve
to talk big.
I'll give you a hand one more time.
Come on. Put your arm around me.
Good.
Let's go.
Up we go.
One, two, three.
Why do I suddenly think
the landlady looks pretty?
It's the alcohol.
It has to be the alcohol.
I must have alcohol poisoning.
No way.
(Yifei)
Hello?
In the middle of the night?
What's wrong?
I'm in trouble.
You were right.
I think I've fallen for my landlady.
What are you looking at?
Why aren't you wearing the turkey?
Didn't I tell you yesterday?
Don't bring it up again
after the drinking session.
Alright. I won't.
But honestly,
you look pretty nice dressed like this.
This is how I usually dress
when I take the bus.
Good. This is the real you.
Let's go.
Do you know
how drunk you got last night?
I was really sorry about
what happened last time.
Today, I'd like to
properly apologize to you,
Big Sister Qian and Big Sister Dang.
Sorry for causing you trouble.
Hey.
Who are you calling big sister?
Miss.
Pretty Miss. Pretty Miss.
I'd almost forgotten about that.
That's great.
Sit.
Let's order. See what you want.
Qian Fei, you choose.
I'm fine with anything.
You take a look too. My treat.
That's rare.
Jun has never treated me.
That's because
his mom keeps all his money.
What are you playing?
She's just playing a game.
Don't stick your nose in.
Done. Take a look.
You decide.
I don't dare order.
Then I'll place the order.
What are you doing?
Wait.
Hold on. Your username.
Your username.
What are you doing?
Hey. Hey.
- Let go.
- What are you doing?
- What are you doing? Calm down.
- Wait...
What are you trying to do?
She is...
We're in public.
Whoever she is, you can't act like this.
She is...
Calm yourself down.
This is a public place.
Want to get thrown over
my shoulder again?
She is Po Ming!
I'm going to beat you up!
She's your idol?
Po Ming! Yes.
I watch her streams every day.
- Even so, calm down.
- He watches my streams.
I can't calm down.
We're in public. Keep it together.
Look how excited he is.
I'm...
I'm Grand Chancellor.
He's your fan.
What?
Grand Chancellor.
You're Grand Chancellor?
Yes, Grand Chancellor.
Wait.
- The one who joined the team.
- Keep it together.
You met each other now.
Alright. Let's focus on the meal.
Wait. How could he be a woman?
What's wrong with her being a woman?
I'm going to the restroom.
Look.
Calm down.
I can't calm down.
Do you want there to be a next time
or not?
Don't get yourself thrown over
her shoulder again.
Calm down.
Oh my goodness.
Alright. Calm yourself.
It's okay.
I must abscond. Dear, enjoy the meal.
I'll make it up to you later.
Easy, easy.
Calm down.
- Easy. Life is full of surprises.
-Um...
She's gone.
See?
I told you.
You scared her off.
I told you not to get so worked up.
You guys eat.
What are you doing?
Don't get yourself thrown over
her shoulder again.
Po Ming Bro,
where are you going?
We haven't eaten yet.
I've got a side job. I totally forgot.
I'll drive you.
No need. I'll grab a cab myself.
A side job?
You're a receptionist, a bartender,
and a streamer.
You still have another job.
You're amazing.
Don't be impressed. I'm amazing.
Po Ming!
What?
My admiration for you
is like the endless waves
of the mighty river.
Like Yellow River, it flows on without
an end and is impossible to stop.
I never imagined that
the legend I've
dreamed about day and night
would actually be standing
right in front of me.
My admiration
has broken free from gravity
and shot straight into the sky.
You're like the bright moon in the sky.
Unattainable!
Po Ming!
What are you doing?
I memorized that speech
a long time ago.
I've always dreamed that one day
I'd be able to say it to you in person.
Yes!
- Please.
- What's wrong with him?
Give me a chance to get up close
and personal with my idol.
Please let me drive you.
I've received your admiration.
You should head home early.
Po Ming!
Please let me drive you. Please!
Where's your car?
Over there.
Let's go.
Where are you going?
Leave this place first.
I've wanted to tell you this
several times.
But I felt sorry for you,
so I held back.
Gui Lili isn't living
at my place anymore.
And we're both single.
If we keep sharing an apartment
like this,
uh,
it's really inconvenient.
Is it? I think it's pretty convenient.
That's just what you think.
Other people won't see it that way.
We're both going to work
at Shanlifang tomorrow,
and we're on the same project team.
Being colleagues is one thing,
but if people find out
we're living together,
it's going to be awkward.
Just ignore them, right?
Hold on, landlady.
Judging by what you're saying,
it sounds like you're abandoning
your master.
I helped you get your job back, didn't I?
And now you're kicking me out?
Is that something
a decent person would do?
I wouldn't dare.
No, you would.
What's wrong with sharing an apartment?
It's normal for men and women
to share an apartment these days.
Why are you so conservative
and old-fashioned?
No. I just remember
that we agreed before.
Once your finances improved a little,
you'd move out.
If you'd just cut back a bit,
you'd have enough money
to rent a place like mine.
Why insist on living with me?
Nothing's wrong.
Once my finances improve, I'll move out.
Let me show you my finances.
This is all the money I have
across all my accounts.
If there were money in them,
I'd move out immediately.
- I'm not looking. No.
- Check. Check it.
Check it.
I'm not checking it.
Why would I check that? Take it away.
Fine. Don't look.
Your salary isn't exactly low.
But you're always throwing money around.
Where does it all go?
Forget it. To help you move out sooner,
I'll teach you how to save money.
You'll teach me how to save money?
I'm all ears.
How exactly are you going to teach me?
Saving money is my specialty.
Excuse me.
Could you pack this up for us?
Thank you.
How much can that possibly save?
Two days' worth of meals.
=Love Has Fireworks=
(Next Episode Preview)
You two already knew
that Wang Ruohai had gone to Shanlifang,
didn't you?
Shanlifang is Xinxin Vision's
parent company.
Wang Ruohai just became
their new Finance Director.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Ms. Fang,
I've run into a bit of trouble lately.
Is there anyone at Hejing
you think
could help you out?
Someone like Qian Fei, for example.
Would you mind letting her
work as my special assistant
while we're collaborating?
What do you think?
♪There's no need
to know the ending from the start♪
♪Let the melody play through the chords
with the wind♪
♪There's no need
to keep every promise from the past♪
♪Leave some surprises
for the unknown in life♪
♪There's no need
to force things between two people♪
♪Perhaps I'll feel alone,
yet still find you there for me♪
♪There's no need
to dwell on right or wrong, nor fear♪
♪A hug means more
than countless apologies♪
♪I'll send you into the wide world♪
♪To live with passion
and become who you truly are♪
♪A quiet shoulder♪
♪Like a harbor waiting
for your wandering soul♪
♪I'll wait for the day
you return to a simpler life♪
♪The lights of home warm the night♪
♪A companionship that lasts forever♪
♪Shining brightly
like the stars and the moon on high♪
♪I'll send you into the wide world♪
♪To live with passion
and become who you truly are♪
♪A quiet shoulder♪
♪Like a harbor waiting
for your wandering soul♪
♪I'll wait for the day
you return to a simpler life♪
♪The lights of home warm the night♪
♪A companionship that lasts forever♪
♪Shining brightly
like the stars and the moon on high♪