It is said The Hunter is The
Protector of the two worlds,...
...the final frontier
between human and jinns.
Our world is made
of two realms.
The hidden realm and
the physical realm.
In the physical realm,
humans...
...originally created from clay,
are the successors.
In the hidden realm, Jinns,
created from fire, rule.
It is the nature of
jinns to be envious,...
...to desire power in both realms,
greedy, arrogant...
...because they believe
fire is nobler than clay.
Conflicts between the warring
two realms often erupt.
From the human race, a group gifted
with the power of sight emerged...
...entrusted to protect
the physical realm...
...against the beings burning
with desires of revenge and evil.
In ancient times, they were
warriors from amongst the learned.
Today, their descendants
still serve...
...in a special unit existing
with no official records.
They are the enforcer,
the judge and the executioner.
And this sacred trust
will be revoked if...
...they are found to have
betrayed and killed their own kind.
They are called...
The hunters.
Hey, wait for me!
Arif, hurry up,
it's almost Maghrib.
There's a feast after this.
The villagers...
...will complain
our class finished late.
Okay, Ustaz. Peace be upon you.
-And peace be upon you.
Arif!
I worship you,
the burning desert.
the corrupted flesh.
I worship you,
the bloodied heart.
from seven feet under.
Save your servant from
the night that destroys.
Arif!
You know right?
Who are you calling
when you recite that incantation?
How did you know my name?
This incantation
is to protect me.
No, Arif.
That incantation...
...is to summon.
Summon who?
I want to dedicate
a poem to the bride.
One two, the cats
are on the run.
Sara and Amin
are now truly one.
I've been divorced once before.
But God willing.
I'll find a new wife tonight.
Hold on a minute.
Hold on!
What if it's my mom calling?
Go to hell with your mother!
Damned Hunter!
You're so rude, you know that?
My mom isn't even dead yet.
You want me to stuff
chilies in your mouth?
You humans will never win!
Your Protector will fall!
The dead shall rise!
I will never die.
I am the Jinn of the Grave!
I will remain eternal!
Remain eternal?
Don't bet your head on it.
Hello, Chief.
-Mikael, where are you?
Sorry, I was just sending some
things back to their hometown.
We have a new case.
A new case?
Enough with these
insignificant little jinns.
How long are you going to hole
yourself up in those places?
I'm doing a service to the country,
keeping the mischief down.
You're elite, Mikael.
We need you back.
This is a major
murder case, Mikael.
I wouldn't call you
if this wasn't serious.
People killing people,
that's normal, Chief.
I'm busy here.
-This isn't a common case, Mikael.
Many have died.
All in the same place.
A schoolboy was
playing hockey...
...bashed his friend's head in.
A 20 year old girl...
...never raised her voice
in her life went berserk.
Killed her friend while
they were partying.
Another old woman threw
her pregnant niece into a well.
All these cases happened
within three consecutive days.
It's insane, Mikael, insane!
These are crazy times, Chief.
Crazy weather, climate change,
extreme technology,...
...people have
also become crazy.
I want you to go in
and scan that place.
And report back
your findings.
About your sister,
I know you like to work alone.
But I can activate a
special task force for you.
Brother!
Khatijah Hassan
Mikael's sister
A special task force
can't help me, Chief.
Mikael.
You go in.
You recon.
You come back.
What's the name of the place?
-Kuala Gerbang.
Near Kuala Gerbang
Kuala Gerbang,
Nature Heritage Site, Living Stone
Inspector Mikael.
Inspector Mikael!
I'm Sergeant Kok.
I've heard many stories.
Hey, turn off that music!
Like I was saying,
there are many stories about you.
All the strange cases,
you solved them.
This.
Inspector Mikael's famous car.
This car must be fast.
And I heard Inspector doesn't allow
anyone to touch this car, right?
Inspector, I've just been
transferred from headquarters.
This is my hometown, eh, no.
This is my parents' hometown.
Be careful, sir.
This victim,
name, Nam.
Sorry, Man.
Man Sate.
Age, 23. Male.
Confirmed dead.
Speaking of death,
my parents are dead.
They died when I was young.
I was raised in KL instead.
Sometimes I miss them.
I look at their faces, I...
You're talking so fast, why?
Nervous?
A little, sir.
Because your reputation
is big.
Sir.
25 corpses.
25 people hacked to death
outside during a feast.
Sir.
Headquarters needs
to send some backup.
This is the fourth case
like this in a row, sir.
This one is
the most horrific, sir.
What's the story with Arif?
Just the usual stuff, sir.
An orphan.
Quiet.
Weird.
Always being bullied.
Didn't like to talk to anyone.
Even when he did talk,
it was to himself.
I've already
interrogated him.
It's confirmed,
he was quiet.
Weird.
He is an orphan.
I'm an orphan too.
But I'm not weird.
Or perhaps, sir,
he just snapped?
But 25 corpses, sir.
That's excessive, isn't it?
Sir, this is definitely
a strange case.
What is that, sir?
An ancient incantation.
The ancient incantation
is used to summon a demon.
Take me to the coroner.
It might explain...
...the pattern the corpses
are arranged in.
A pattern?
Calm down.
Calm down, everyone stay calm.
The police from KL have arrived.
Tok.
We need to call a shaman.
Matters like these, the police
definitely can't solve them.
Am I right, everyone?
Besides, it's not
like the police...
...are going to say
our town is cursed.
Wong, don't talk nonsense,
alright?
But it really is cursed, tok.
The weather has turned so hot.
The crops have died, wilted.
Our water has turned
black and muddy.
Our people, our relatives, have
all been hacked to death, tok!
Mak Su.
Be patient, all these trials
are only temporary.
But our town is getting worse.
We need to do something, tok!
-Penghulu!
Our families have all been settled
here for a long time, you know?
All this time
it's been peaceful.
Strange things have started
to happen because of this project!
Wong.
Don't recklessly talk nonsense.
There's no connection at all.
Listen here, everyone.
You all elected me
as the village head.
We will face hardships
and good times together.
I will make sure...
...that all of us
and this town are safe.
Can his promise be trusted?
Hello, doctor.
Doctor Zaid.
Zaid Masood.
I'm Inspector Salma from KL,...
...sent by headquarters...
...to assist in the investigation
of the wedding feast murder.
Inspector Salma.
Salma Hayek?
Sexy.
This town is so small.
Boring, quiet.
There's no coroner here.
I'm the only doctor here.
We don't even have a proper
place to store the bodies.
We're forced
to use this hall.
Usually, we just
get common fevers.
The worst
is a snake bite.
This one, he.....
This one is worse than
a snake bite, isn't it?
You're joking, right?
Want to see the groom?
Handsome, wasn't he?
Handsome.
But he's dead.
I'm not trying
to imply anything.
It's just a fact.
Handsome, fair, tall.
Long legs.
But no matter how
long those legs were,...
...they still weren't
fast enough to run away.
Arif.....
One shot!
I heard he even got
a pedicure, manicure.
That wedding package
was expensive.
But in the end...
...the hands that were
manicured became strange.
Look.
Blackish.
In the end,...
...we're all just human.
No matter how
handsome he was...
...no matter
how tall he was...
...even if he was the
district's star football player...
...we all end up the same.
Ah, Sarah.
I know why Sarah
chose him...
...even after she read
that letter I sent her.
Yet she still died.
Sarah...
It's just a fact.
Such is life.
There's never been a female
inspector here before...
...or even male inspectors.
As the Westerners say...
...you are truly attractive.
Who's there?
It can't be you?
Sarah is mine!
Fine, Sarah is yours.
You take her!
Let go!
Doctor Zaid, hey!
The corpse came back to life!
It came back to life just now,
after an inspector arrived.
An inspector?
There was a female
inspector here just now.
Sir.
-Her name was Salma.
Salma Hayek.
-Salma Hayek?
No, no Hayek.
Just Salma.
Sir, where are you going?
Sir.
Is it true the corpse
came back to life?
Where's the boy?
The boy is
at the station, sir.
Sir, people say
this place is cursed and hexed.
That's not true, right?
Sir!
They say...
...people who don't believe
in this kind of thing...
...will be the next victim,
is that right?
It's usually like that.
Please be advised.
The public is advised
to be cautious...
...and not to go out late...
...until the authorities
have further details...
...about the recent
crime cases.
What's that?
-Our PA system.
From the war era.
It's still under warranty.
Sometimes the phone lines
here are down.
In Kuala Gerbang,
there are two unique things.
First, the living stones.
Second, our PA system.
Sir, we really do need backup.
This is the first time
we've had a case with 25 corpses.
Look.
There are so many reports to file.
This case is truly bizarre, sir.
Ishak! Did you turn on
the air conditioning?
It's on,
it's extremely hot today.
Okay, continue with your report.
My ancestors used to live here,
in the village across the way.
But they sold that land
to others a long time ago.
All this greenery
you see...
...will change soon.
There's a major development
project here...
...and here.
Ishak!
The lights!
They've been like
that since last night!
A lot of strange things
have been happening here.
But I'm a policeman.
I have to look after them.
But now I'm confused too.
I've never encountered
anything weird in my entire life.
Sir.
You want to see Arif?
Kok.
Rub this oil under your eyes.
If you see anything
strange inside.....
Be cool.
Alright?
I'm always cool, sir.
Strange case.
Ishak.
Arif.
Do you know what is this?
Do you know?
I had seen these when I was little.
My late father warned me.
He told me to be careful
with this thing.
Not to play around with it.
But I was stubborn.
It's not that
I want to bring it up.
But what's done is done.
One has to take
responsibility for it.
Only a mixture
of mountain salt,...
...soil and black pepper
can stop this thing.
He gave it to me.
He said he would protect me.
Protect you from what, Arif?
Protect you from whom?
Protect me from the thing
that disturbs me.
When I go to school.
When I go to pray.
When I go to bathe.
When I try to sleep.
That thing
always disturbs me!
You damned Hunter!
Kok, wake up!
Leave this boy, demon!
Jinn Level 13
Sergeant Kok.
Quickly, take him.
Damned Hunter!
We, the Jinn 13...
...can't wait to meet you
at the cursed ground!
Don't shoot!
Leave it, don't shoot!
Brother!
It hurts like hell!
Your sister is now with us.
The End will return!
Sir.
What was that just now?
Didn't all of you see it?
Why am I speaking Cantonese?
Just now, didn't
all of you see it?
See what, sir?
There was nothing.
Never mind. You take Arif
to the clinic first.
Now, quickly!
You're right, Kok.
We need to call for backup.
I know.
You know.
Every one knows.
With me, I sell
all sorts of things.
Right? But everything
I sell is special.
However, today...
...the most special
and premium item.
A three day,
two night...
...diamond honeymoon
package to Phuket.
Okay? It's a yes?
-No, I...
Datuk, it's only RM1,500.
My place has the best price.
Other places don't have
prices like this.
I'm the only one offering
such a cheap package, Datuk.
Winston, I'm looking
for something else.
Winston has the solution.
This one.
A magic pillow.
Because your face looks like you
haven't had enough sleep, right?
This pillow can
massage your back.
So, every night you will
only have sweet dreams.
All night long.
Winston.
-All night long.
Can you be quiet for a moment?
I actually...
I want a protective charm.
I think I've been
hexed right now.
Many people are envious of me
and dissatisfied with me.
No, no, no.
Datuk.
A vacation package is fine.
A massage pillow, no problem.
But messing with
these dark things.....
Do you think I sell that
kind of superstitious stuff?
But my friend said...
-No, no, no.
Your friends should be
telling you to pray.
Remember God.
Do good deeds.
A talisman with the
tears of a fairy.
Can be called a protective charm.
Only RM39.99.
This is what I want.
-Good.
I want two.
-Excellent.
Sure you don't want
to go to Phuket?
No.
I'll keep the change.
But, next time if you need
to find me, look for me, okay?
Look for me, as long as
we won't end up in jail.
Peace be upon you.
How come you show up suddenly?
You're just scaring
my customers.
Your face looks so fierce
when you look like that.
You should have called.
Why didn't you call me?
You're using a cheap line
for your phone.
Even if I call,
I can't get through.
Your excuses.
Do you have any new stock?
Everything you
gave me is finished.
Finished?
What did you use it all for?
You know my goods are rare.
Limited.
You treat my stuff like you're
handing out candy at an orphanage?
Or were you the
one who ate them?
Chasing after those little
jinns is pointless.
What's that?
-That's nothing, move along.
That's for a different story.
New item.
This one I got from Medan.
Do you know what it's made from?
The bones of a Garuda bird.
Wow.
-Impressive, right? Yes.
It's very hard to find.
I don't even know how he...
Hey, take it easy.
This item is truly powerful.
You know why?
When you shoot a demon,...
...two or three times,
they'll be in and out of hell.
No time to even rest.
And this one,
salt bullets.
However, the salt is
extracted from mermaid scales.
Know what mermaid scales are?
If it hits a demon.....
It dissolves turns into water.
If this salt isn't
used for exorcism,...
...I could just put
it in my fried rice.
Leave the jokes to me.
Don't even try. They don't land.
And this one...
...the tears of Mahsuri.
But from before
she was executed.
Just be careful, if you use this,
all truth will be revealed.
You could try shooting
a politician.
See what happens when
you use this thing.
Winston, I have a new case.
-You've gone back to taking cases?
A kid killed 25 people
at a wedding feast.
A wedding feast?
That's why
I don't like weddings.
It's already hot,
and on top of that,...
...I have to wear
tight clothes. Why?
I tried to exorcise
the jinn possessing that kid.
Turns out.....
Jinn 13.
13?
13, that's very
high ranking.
Isn't that a Lieutenant
of the Jinn Kingdom?
This...
What is it?
Look at this.
"Whoever seeks
the sacred relic...
...shall meet the
tormented hand turning black."
This is a prophecy.
This is big, Mikael.
What prophecy is this?
-A prophecy of end times.
Okay, listen here.
"Within seven days,...
...if seven Protectors
commit seven sins,...
...then the Prince Jinn will
cross over and destroy the world.
"Only the power of the
sacred relic can stop him."
Why have I never heard
of any of this?
Because this thing is very,
very ancient.
Level 13,
this is big.
The sacred relic.
What is this thing?
-I don't know.
Actually, earlier when I was
fighting that thing,...
...I saw Tijah.
That thing said Tijah
is already with them.
Don't believe what
a jinn says, Mikael.
It's all a trick.
They're trying to mess with you.
But I've been searching
for Tijah for two years.
In this world, in the Jinn world,
found nothing.
Then suddenly today I saw
Tijah in that small town.
If Tijah is involved in this,
it's bad news, Mikael.
The gravy has already been
spilled on the rice,...
...you can't take it back out.
You can't U turn.
You see that turn in the road?
You have to keep going straight.
This is game over, Mikael.
Raining frogs.
Oh God.
This is a bad omen, Mikael.
Be careful.
There's something here.
Even at a time like this,
you can fart.
I'm scared.
When I'm scared, I fart.
Hey.
-What?
The stuff is in my car boot.
I'll give you a signal.
You're really going
to do that, Mikael?
One minute.
-That thing is dangerous!
I don't like this.
Mikael.
Mikael!
Hey.
Looking for me?
Winston!
One minute!
What the.....
Okay.
Cable. Battery.
I'll just leave the keys here.
Mikael, I'm coming.
Okay.
Winston, hurry!
Wake up!
Mikael!
Why is this broken?
Are you okay?
One, two, three!
-I'm okay.
I'm back.
Can you please not do
things like this?
I may have a big body,
but I'm a coward, you know?
Winston.
You're coming with me.
We're going to Kuala Gerbang.
-Me?
Oh, no, no, no.
I have to mind the shop.
And besides,
when it comes to shooting,...
That's your job.
That.
But Winston, we have...
We have a responsibility.
Winston.
It's dark,
it's late.
It's too late,
people want to sleep.
I'm very tired.
Winston!
Brother. Hurry up,
everyone is waiting.
Intan said
we can't have lunch...
...until our
police hero arrives.
Who's the hero?
It's fine, let's just wait
until this 'hero' gets here.
You're the one
who gave her to us.
Brother.
Tijah!
-Mikael!
Inspector!
Inspector, Inspector, Inspector.
-Just a moment.
Inspector!
Inspector, Inspector, Inspector.
Just a moment.
-We have an emergency case.
They were playing Mahjong
at the kopitiam.
Then, Uncle Wong
won from the Wall...
...and realized
it was a false win.
After that, he took the
Mahjong tile, and he.....
I don't know how to explain it.
Sir, you have to come.
You'll follow me, yes?
Hey, Kok.
-Yes?
Do you know what I mean
when I say 'just a moment'?
But sir, you have to hurry.
I know.
Can't you see I'm getting ready?
Uncle Wong.
-Kok.
Uncle Wong, stop.
Stop it.
Inspector.
Help me.
He forced me.
Stop it!
Demon!
You want to kill me like you
killed your sister, Hunter.
Do you know where she is?
She's here!
So it's you again.
Where's my sister?!
Please don't hit me.
Please.
Uncle Wong, stop!
All of you will fall...
...and you will all
become our slaves.
Uncle Wong, don't move!
I am the police!
Let me see your IC
and driving licence!
Hey!
Thirsty?
Dew from Mount Lighting!
Your Protector will fall!
And you will all
become our slaves.
Mikael.
Get up.
Just now you
seemed almost dead.
Thanks.
I was just about
to get him under control.
Oh, really?
-Yes.
Alright.
You said you didn't want
to join in. Why did you come?
I was thinking.....
You were right.
We have a responsibility.
Besides, I don't want
to be at the market later...
...if that jinn comes back
and I'm all alone.
But consider yourself lucky.
If not, you kind of.....
You should be thanking
this thing.
Winston.
We need to find out
who the Protector is...
...that the jinn
was talking about.
Oh, right.
Hey.
Kok.
Winston.
Isn't Winston a guy's name?
Right?
Kok isn't a name.....
The last time
I saw Saiful was...
...after Arif
went on a rampage.
After that,
no one has seen him.
And, he didn't
come home last night.
Understood. Okay.
Later I'll ask around,
see if anyone has spotted him.
Saiful has never
done anything like this.
Usually, wherever he goes,
he would tell someone.
I hope the boy is okay.
Thank you.
Tok!
What has happened
to our village?
First, it was Arif.
Then, Uncle Wong.
Our town is cursed.
Look at this insane eclipse.
What's next?
Flooding?
Tsunami? Tornadoes?
A river of blood?
Tok, this is indeed illogical.
But if we look at the correlation
that Uncle Wong mentioned...
...this is related to
the developers who came here.
Our town is cursed, Tok.
We should just call a shaman.
Just cancel this project, Tok!
It's not a solution
to the paradox,...
...but it can be
considered, Tok.
Be patient.
Everyone, please calm down,
can't you?
Inspector!
So, what is your hypothesis,
Inspector?
There is a prophecy
that says...
...the Jinn Kingdom
will conquer this world.
But the Jinn Prince
can only cross over...
...after seven Protectors
are defeated.
I believe...
...the seven Protectors
are connected to this town.
But I am not sure...
...what is
the actual connection.
His talk is crazier than mine.
Mak Su, Dr. Zaid, everyone.
Why don't everyone
just go back first?
If there's anything
we will update.
Ishak, please take
them back for now.
Like that,
even I can be the police.
Confirmed it's a
case of black magic.
Inspector, look.
We're just worried about
what's happening to our town.
If you need any help,
I can assist.
I just want this case resolved
as quickly as possible.
Don't worry. We'll solve it
Thank you.
-Okay.
Hello, Chief.
Any news, Mikael?
I need to find
the seven Protectors.
I don't even know
how much time I have.
Protectors?
What do you mean?
Come back to headquarters first.
This thing is big.
We need to plan our response.
No, Chief.
I need to stay here.
I have a feeling something
is about to happen.
Okay.
Be careful, Mikael.
Okay, Chief.
Hello.
What are you doing?
-Nothing.
Give me that.
Sorry, meant to do that.
I'll kill you all!
Tijah!
This is not something
to be taken lightly, Tijah.
We're talking about
the unseen realm.
If you meddle with the unseen
realm, your life will be affected.
Do you think I can't handle it?
Don't be stubborn,
listen to your older brother.
I don't want you
to get hurt, Tijah.
I can take care of myself.
I don't need you.
Okay, fine.
Hey.
You want to be stubborn,
is that it? Do whatever you want.
Since that time you never...
...found Khatijah again, Mikael?
No.
-It's alright,...
...you'll find
her eventually.
Just, if possible, don't forget
to take care of yourself too.
Guys, I've matched the incident
locations on this torn map.
There are strange markings.
I don't understand them.
These are marks
of the Protectors.
Osman.
The boy with the hockey
stick lived in this area.
Marina.
The birthday girl
who went berserk.
Here.
Fatimah.
The old woman at the well.
Arif.
The orphan.
And Uncle Wong.
These areas are
their ancestral lands.
Wait.
Saiful.
Here.
His land is in this area.
He went into the jungle,
and now he's missing.
So if Saiful
is a Protector,...
...that means he's the
sixth Protector, right?
Yes, all this can be stopped
with the sacred relic.
Only...
...we don't know what it is.
If you want to place a barrier in
an area that bridges two realms,...
...it's usually a watery
place like a lake...
A toilet.
-Gosh, so stupid.
Or a river.
It's time for us
to go into the jungle.
Into the jungle?
I worship you
the corrupted flesh.
the bloodied heart.
May your servant's
wish be granted...
...on this black night.
Your reward awaits, Qabil.
A reward greater
than this town.
You will rule the world.
Power will be given to you.
Worship me just once.
And when you are satisfied
with your desires,...
...you worship back your God.
Accept my sacrifice.
Sir.
This jungle is huge.
How are we going
to find the relic?
We'll know it when we see it.
Move aside.
I have a way.
See this talisman?
If there's a sacred
treasure or anything,...
...this talisman will find.
Look.
It's already sniffing.
This way.
Reminds me of the
old Girl Guide days.
Sticky.
-Same as me.
I was a scout once.
I don't have a family, right?
So I joined the scouts.
Could do cool things like this.
Go into the jungle,
have a bit of adventure.
Brother!
I hated it.
Brother.
Brother!
My mom forced me.
She didn't want me
to end up like my dad.
Cooped up at home.
Smoking. Watching TV.
You want to know why
my dad named me Winston?
Because it was
his cigarette brand.
Your name isn't Winston?
-It isn't.
You think my name is
Winston binti Jamal or what?
How would I know?
It sounds alright, though.
Where's Mikael?
Mikael!
-Sir!
Hold on a second. Mikael!
Mikael!
Tijah!
-Brother.
I think if I work hard,
follow orders,...
...one day,
I would get a promotion.
Become the Commissioner.
Winston.
Are you listening
to what I'm saying?
Winston!
-What?
I said, I've always
wanted to be a policeman.
But this isn't what I wanted.
But they said...
-Yeah, yeah.
I hear you.
You said you want a promotion.
Yes.
Follow orders,
and one day,...
...I'll get a promotion.
I'll become Commissioner.
Tijah.
I've been searching for you
for so long, little sister.
How could you let me die?
You were supposed to protect me.
But you let them take me.
It's my fault.
I failed.
Please forgive me, Tijah.
I should have protected you.
But I let them all take you.
I'm in pain, Brother.
I'm suffering.
Forgive me, Tijah.
Forgive me.
You left me
to be tormented.
You are no longer
worthy of this duty.
One day...
-You'll get a promotion.
I will get a promotion,
that's right.
Kok?
We have arrived.
Tijah!
It's me, your brother!
Go in, go in, go in.
This place
just looks creepy.
You're scared
of a place like this?
Winston.
Did you fart?
-No.
No.
It's normal,
this forest has many sounds.
Many smells.
This...
Let's go.
Let's find the relic,
then I want...
...to be somewhere
with air conditioning.
Serves me right for
eating six boiled eggs.
This looks like
a place of worship.
No one has ever mentioned
this place before.
Commissioner Kok.
-Yes, that's me.
Tijah.
I love you, little sister.
Kok!
Tijah.
Winston!
Save me, Winston!
I'll save you, Kok!
Shit.
Saiful! Let me go!
Just give up.
We've got a whole gang here.
Winston.
Aisyah.
-Kok.
Saiful.
Mikael, are you okay?
-Sir.
Hey, do you hear me?
-Sir?
Sir?
Sir!
Mikael!
In the age before Time,...
...the war between humans
and jinns has begun.
Once upon a time there
was a great war,...
...the jinns nearly
conquered the physical world.
The King of Jinns gained
immense and extraordinary...
...during the
red solar eclipse.
Humans join forces to create
a great weapon against the jinns.
Seven righteous
persons were sought...
...to use their power
of the Protectors...
...to forge a sacred relic.
The power from this weapon
from the union of seven...
...banished the King of Jinns
from the physical world...
...and imprisoned him in
the Hidden Realm until now.
Hey!
Wow!
Did you see? I was like the
narrator from 'Today in History'.
The sacred relic is huge.
Winston, I saw Tijah earlier.
Tijah?
-I fought with her, Winston.
She's been possessed.
So, I assume you used
your prayer beads...
...to settle your sister and...
...the jinn has left her body?
-No.
Then?
-It's not like that. She...
She has changed, Winston.
She has become a part
of the Unseen Realm.
Okay, guys.
I've finished with this map.
So, it's confirmed...
...Saiful is
the sixth Protector.
Be patient.
-Poor guy.
Jinn worshipper.
-That's considered his major sin.
The crossing point.
We, from clay, return to clay,
the earth is the anchor.
The promise of
the seven Protectors...
...is not only
to preserve knowledge...
...but also a trust
to protect human lives.
That's what imprisoned
the Jinn Prince.
And he will cross here
after the final ritual.
But isn't the middle.....
-The living stone.
No wonder they've been so busy
buying up land in this area.
Protector one, two, three...
...four, five six, seven.
Here is the seventh.
That's my ancestral land.
My family's land.
But it's been a long time.
I don't know if they bought it
or got it from someone.
But the land is abandoned.
I once thought about
planting durians.
But then I prefer
eating rambutan.
It's sweeter.
I'm the seventh Protector?
Sir, I'm not afraid.
I'm perfectly okay.
Sir.
-If you're not afraid, that's okay.
But right now, we're
the ones who are scared.
Is everything
sprinkled underneath?
Yes.
Sir!
What if we destroy
the living stone...
...so they can't come through?
Do you think it's that easy to
destroy an ancient site like that?
The problem is, the jinns
can still cross over.
Sir!
What if we find them
before they cross?
We can do that, right?
Instead of going
to look for demons...
...let the demons
come look for us.
Winston, you take
the shift watching Kok.
Okay.
I'm hungry.
-Same.
I'm hungry too.
Okay, fine.
Eat.
-Thanks.
You seem to easily trust
people you don't know.
Not really.
Who says I trust you?
You think I trust
you easily?
Today you're helping us
fight the jinns.
Tomorrow you could also
stab me in the back.
I'm here to find
that sacred relic.
I'm not here to save the world
or anything like that.
Why are you looking
for the sacred relic?
Don't you have anything
else better to do?
Do you know how many
collectors out there...
...are waiting for a
mystical artifact like this?
Your motive is money?
There's no reward
for this case.
What's the point
of being rich...
...if this world is destroyed
and consumed by jinns?
Earlier I overheard you're
looking for your sister.
Is that why you're here?
She's missing.
She entered
the Unseen Realm.
I always told her...
...not to mess with the Unseen
Realm, but she was stubborn.
She wouldn't listen to me.
She went against me.
No.
All this is my fault.
I failed.
I was supposed to look
after my sister.
Protect my sister.
But I failed.
I'm not scared.
You look tired.
Go and rest.
It's alright,
let me watch him.
I'm concerned about you.
I think you need some sleep.
Not at all.
I'm not even sleepy.
Just a little hungry though.
Here.
Thank you. But I won't be long,
just a moment.
It's fine, go eat
until you're full.
Okay.
-Let me watch him.
It's alright,
don't worry.
Winston, please bring
two curry puffs.
Penghulu.
Are you okay?
Why did you come here?
Nothing. I just wanted
to make sure you're safe.
You're our most
promising officer.
Don't say that.
Thank you. I've always
felt for a long time...
...that I truly
have potential.
Your future is bright, Kok.
This town is
too small for you.
You should lead
one whole country.
Everyone should know your name.
Commissioner Kok.
Worship me just once.
And I will grant you...
...all the desires
of your heart.
And when your desires...
...have been fulfilled...
...you worship
your God again.
Worship just once.
Until my dreams come true.
Just once.
Until your desires
are satisfied.
Yes.
Worship just once.
Until I get what I want.
Just once.
That's right, Kok.
But the problem is...
...humans are never
satisfied with what they have.
We are never satisfied.
Enjoying the food?
Is there any left?
I'm hungry.
Who's watching Kok?
-Penghulu.
He told me to take a break.
He's so kind.
He told me to rest and eat,
so I came here.
Please be advised.
For your safety,...
...all town residents
are ordered to report...
...to the police
station immediately.
Isn't that Kok?
Rub this under your eyes.
It's fine,
I have my own 'eyes'.
So you can see it too.
Where did you get
that ability?
Let's just say I do.
You will all lose!
Your Protector will fall!
And all of you will
become our slaves!
You already said
that the other day.
How many times are you
going to repeat it?
Winston, go check on Kok.
Okay.
I offer you burning desert.
I offer you a black sacrifice.
The blood of the innocent.
I summon you to rise
as an army of the damned.
I offer you corrupted flesh.
I offer you the bloodied heart.
I offer this to you
from under seven feet.
The last sacrificial offering.
This is the final sacrifice.
It smells like petroleum!
Petroleum is not
a protective charm!
Send my regards to hell.
Hey, Wong.
Go. Quickly.
This town
is too small for me.
Sergeant!
What are you doing, sir?
Sir!
This is my right!
This is the final sacrifice.
Kok!
Don't play around, Kok!
This is my right.
Kok.
Snap out of it, Kok,
it's Winston!
Kok!
Wake up, Kok!
Harden yourself!
Don't go soft!
Use your head!
This is the final sacrifice.
This town
is too small for me.
Mahsuri.
It's your time.
I offer you corrupted flesh.
I offer you the bloodied heart.
I offer this to you
from under seven feet.
The final sacrificial offering!
Kok.
Kok!
Penghulu?
Winston?
-Get up!
Why are you here?
Was I dreaming just now?
-I also.....
You didn't even notice, Kok.
Open the door!
Why are you all here?
A feast?
Seven times seven innocent
people are sacrificed.
Bludgeoned.
The first protector - Osman
Stabbed.
The second protector - Marina
Hacked.
Third protector - Arif
Pushed.
The fourth protector - Fatimah
Tortured.
The fifth protector - Uncle Wong
Destroyed.
The sixth protector - Saiful
The final victim
is betrayed by...
...the trusted
seventh Protector!
Soon,...
...freedom and the
destruction of the human world.
Mikael!
Khatijah! Return to our world,
little sister!
Remember who you are, Khatijah.
Who's the hero?
It's fine, let's just wait
until this 'hero' gets here.
Mikael.
You cannot deny your
own flesh and blood.
You who traverse both realms.
The Hunter.
The Hunter
as the Protector.
With you, we do not need
a seventh Protector.
You have the power
to stop this war,...
...and have peace and calm.
You don't have to worry
about humanity's fate.
Worship me just once,
and all this will end.
And eliminate all who
stand in our way, Mikael.
Tijah!
Didn't I warn you not
to play with the Unseen Realm?
It's dangerous.
Quick, Tijah!
We only have one minute
to get out of here, hurry!
No, Big Brother.
I'm fine.
Don't worry, okay?
I can.....
-Tijah!
Big Brother!
Tijah!
Don't let go!
It's your fault.
You caused your sister's death.
No, no, no.
No!
Tijah!
Worship me!
How could you let me die!
You let them take me!
Worship me!
-You let me suffer!
You are no longer
worthy of this duty.
You let me die in agony!
Break your oath,...
...kill those
who stand in our way!
What are you doing?
Mikael!
Big Brother!
Big Brother,
it's me, Tijah.
Big Brother, come back.
Big Brother,
it's not your fault.
Big Brother, let her go.
If I don't let go,
we'll both die, Big Brother!
Tijah!
I've promised
to protect you, Tijah.
Don't let go, Tijah.
I have to let go, Big Brother!
-Tijah!
Tijah!
I didn't kill Tijah.
I didn't kill Tijah!
Foolish human.
Break the oath...
...of the damned Hunter!
Mikael!
How come the ritual
is still going on?
You didn't commit
a major sin right?
Unless, I am no
the seventh Protector.
I am the final sacrifice.
Without the
seventh Protector,...
...your great sin
is killing a human...
...completing the requirement.
I want you to go in
and scan that place.
What's the name of the place?
-Kuala Gerbang.
These areas,
are their ancestral lands.
My ancestors used to live here,
in the village across the way.
I don't know if they bought it
or got it from someone.
You have killed a human...
...and betrayed
your sacred trust.
Hunter...
Hunter
The seventh protector - Mikael
Tijah!
Stay with me, Tijah.
Forgive me.
I didn't know...
...how powerful
the hidden realm is.
No, no, no.
I'm sorry, Tijah.
I couldn't save
you that night.
I should have always
been with you.
Haven't you always
been with me?
Aren't you...
...my police hero?
You have caused
trouble for me...
...for the last time...
Hunter.
Torsim - Prince of The
Jinn Kingdom
Big Brother!
That sergeant dares
to drive my car.
Sir.
Has the Jinn King been dealt with?
-Khatijah?
She.....
She's gone.
Sucked back into
the Unseen Realm.
It's alright, sir.
You have us now, right?
Be patient, Mikael.
You will find her again.
Maybe I should get a new team.
Maybe...
...can help me find
my sister together.
Since when did I tell
you to sit on my car?
You look pretty
pleased with yourself.
Look at your size,
no wonder it's so smooth.
This, this.
-Wait.
who said I want to join your
team to find your sister?
Eh, that's right.
Aren't you a thief?
We should be a bit careful, no?
Excuse me.
I dare you to repeat that.
-Sir. I need to explain something.
My name Kok isn't that bad, in
Chinese it has a different meaning.
But it's still bad.
A woman named Winston
is bad too, right?
Eh, I already explained.
My dad.....
Don't forget, I'm a police officer,
I can arrest you.
Why are you all
bickering so much?
Just look at the dawn.
Beautiful, isn't it?
Call Jadian.
The war has started.
Dan Bront Palarae
as Chief