Now that we've made up.
What are we now?
Somporn and Anan's unfinished story.
A writer can't abandon
their characters
or their readers.
Please go ahead, sir.
Yes, thank you.
"Good morning, everybody."
"I am Somsak Prasitphithaya."
"I'm an adventure novelist."
"I write under my pen name:
Harn Chanprai."
I bet you young bucks
don't know who I am.
Anyway.
Today, I bring you
very important news.
"Actually,"
"the author of"
"'Between Us in the Deep Forest'"
"is not my nephew, Save."
"I am the real author."
I admit that
I couldn't bring myself
to tell the truth originally.
The world I knew
when I was at my peak
and the world today
are... vastly different.
I began writing this BL novel
because.
I needed to pay off my debt.
When I first put pen to paper...
Heh.
I was at war with myself.
Nothing made sense.
"But I learned,"
"and kept writing
until the latest chapter."
"In the end, I discovered"
"that it was I"
"who had been narrow-minded."
"Because love,"
"in any form it takes,"
is always beautiful.
My nephew,
his friend,
my niece,
all the children of Saeng Karun's,
my own children,
everyone I met
while searching for ideas,
all of you readers...
Oh...
and the characters in this novel,
Somporn and Anan.
They all led me into
an entirely new world.
And at last, I realized
that what I've done
is not wrong,
but one of the most meaningful
and honorable things I've ever done.
And so I can now say
with the utmost pride...
I am proud of this novel.
"Apologies to those
I did not tell the truth."
Plainly, my age
has not made me wise.
"If anyone is at fault,"
"it is I alone."
"Please forgive my nephew."
"He merely"
"did me a great kindness"
"after I begged him
to pose as the author."
"I apologize, everyone."
"I am partly responsible for this."
Excuse me. A question from a viewer.
'What kind of debt, Grandpa?'
Certainly.
I run a foster home.
It's called Saeng Karun Foundation,
a legacy passed down
from my grandfather.
For several scores of years,
the royalties from my novels
kept this place afloat.
But with each new book,
the sales grew smaller and smaller.
Until, about thirty years ago,
I had to start borrowing money
to meet the expenses of this place.
Over time, that debt grew to
more than twelve million baht,
owed to the bank.
Everyone here
has been doing their part
to help raise money.
And I was determined
to write this novel
to earn enough to pay off our debt
and preserve this home
for the children who need it.
"I hope you will"
"continue reading my novel."
"Thank you."
- Very nice, Dad.
- Yeah.
Sit, sit.
Hmph.
Feeling better, Grandpa?
The truth will save you.
Yeah. A load off my chest.
Mm-hmm.
So, any comments from the readers?
I saw a few gripes and complaints.
Most of them were supportive.
Whew.
Should've done this long ago.
- Heh.
Trust me.
You'll grow more fans for sure.
Dad?
What's wrong?
See how we are all relieved?
Why the frown?
Dad, some readers are still upset.
They started a thread
and caused quite a stir.
And let's not forget
that Ajarn Thaworn.
He criticized Save
right in front of you.
Oy.
I chose to face the truth.
I don't care about them.
That's great, Father.
Don't waste your time on them.
Besides, I believe.
I'm doing the right thing.
I have nothing to fear.
I don't want to hide anymore.
You get me, right?
I chose to face the truth.
I don't care about them.
Guy.
Be my boyfriend.
The world keeps
turning every day.
And we keep turning in its play.
Just open up, we'll learn it in.
We just might see
the world within.
Let's walk together, day by day.
Come take the step,
what do you say?
Just open up, we'll learn it in.
We just might see
the world within.
Let's walk together, day by day.
Come take the step,
what do you say?
Class, please turn to page 76.
Hey, hey. Their hands are touching.
- Hey.
- Woo.
What? What's going on?
Hmm?
Kornkan and Supawit.
Who forgot to bring the book?
They didn't forget.
They want to use the same book.
- Tad, tad, dad.
- Yeah.
Alright. Quiet down. Quiet.
Miss, may I go to the restroom?
- Yeah...
- Restroom break?
Calm down. And read the book.
I didn't say you two could go.
Why did you shout
in front of everybody?
Ow... you didn't want to
sneak around anymore.
So I made it loud.
Well, yeah.
But there are different ways.
Which way then?
I don't know.
You're not okay?
I'm okay. Just a bit embarrassed.
I knew it. I knew you'd be okay.
So this means we're...
a couple?
- Hey.
- Heh.
- There you are.
- Well, well.
Heh.
Sorry I didn't tell you guys.
Come on.
We've known for the longest time.
Hmm?
You think you could
hide something this big?
Hey, congrats.
But if you want us to stop teasing,
dream on.
Yeah, yeah. Whatever.
Let's see you hold hands.
- Hey.
- Heh.
You hold his hands.
- Hey, hey. I see what's going on.
- My boys.
Hey, Mom.
Keep watching and
tell me who's coming on TV.
Hmm... is it this channel?
This doesn't seem right.
Is it today, really?
Hold on. Just wait, Phi Sorn.
Here, here. It's coming on.
"Good morning, viewers."
"Speaking of the latest
online sensation,"
"nothing has brought half of social
media to tears quite like this."
"Khun Somsak has revealed himself"
"as the author of
'Between Us in the Deep Forest.'"
"Readers have been showering him
with support"
"and admiration
for creating this BL novel,"
"which has captured
the hearts of young readers."
- Hmm?
- A delivery?
I didn't order anything.
Then, go see
who rang the bell, please.
Dad,
how about a smile?
Dad, you have a guest.
Ajarn?
Can we talk for a bit, Khun Sak?
I apologize for
holding back the truth.
The moment I read the first page,
I knew you wrote it.
I've read all your novels,
many times over.
How could I not recognize it?
Anyway, forgive me if my remarks
placed you in an awkward position.
It's all right, sir.
Two souls are seldom of one mind.
I came today for no other reason
than to have you hear it from me,
not through hearsay.
Yes, sir.
I will petition the Association
to strip you
of your senior membership.
I fail to see
that your novel is morally sound.
Do as you wish, sir.
I shall not object.
I would remind you of one thing,
however.
We cannot stop the wheel of time.
Of course, neither can I.
Even if I must perish
with my generation,
my convictions will not change.
I've always admired
your convictions.
My words are spent.
Take care, Khun Sak.
Likewise, sir.
So long, sir.
Thanks for the news, Khun Chai.
Writer's Association, Dad?
They're in a meeting.
Don't worry
if they actually do it, Dad.
No membership, no problem.
Yes, Father.
You don't need people like that,
clinging to the past.
I couldn't care less.
Try to relax, Father.
The Association
may not rule in his favor.
Really, Dad.
You're better off
without a friend like that.
Easy for you to say.
They've been friends
for half their lives.
We were the closest of friends.
But I suppose that is no more.
Save, here you are. Just in time.
I've got good ideas
for the new chapter.
Okay.
Grandpa, I've got news.
Good or bad?
Guy and I are officially a couple.
- Officially?
- Yeah.
- You two patched things up?
- Mm-hmm.
We just made it official today.
Isn't it too soon?
No way. It's been too long.
You heard of protection, right?
Hmph... what are you talking about?
Just making sure.
So what now? The two of you
are at which stage?
We're not going so fast.
Just got started.
Anyway, I'm happy for you.
Don't upset him again.
I won't.
Back to the novel.
What was the last chapter?
Fifteen.
Okey.
Dokey.
Oh, your eyes. How are they?
Still blurry.
But I'll scrape by.
And then...
Ow?
"Phi Cha, Climax Studio."
Hey...
- Yes, hi.
- Hi, Save.
Are you free for the audition
this Saturday?
No idea what they'll have me do.
- What do I need?
- You need talent.
Thanks, but I have none.
Anything, really. Just show them.
Maybe they just want to see
you're not shy.
A triple front flip?
A jump through a flaming hoop?
Go for it if you can.
Hey, how about coming with me?
Why? Stage fright?
I've never done this before.
Yeah, I'll go with you.
- For real?
- You got it.
Awesome. My boyfriend's
coming to my audition.
I don't know who else to ask.
Come on. You'd ask me to come with
anyway.
You're right.
Ready, Save?
Uh...
Kind of. Heh.
Oh, and is this Guy?
You both did livestreams
selling snacks.
Oh, this is him.
Sorry, he's the shy type.
How about...
you both do the audition?
Ha?
Uhm. Is that a good idea?
I'm just here...
to keep him company.
Well, you're here.
Might as well try.
Up to you. I've got your back.
Good morning, everyone.
What do you want to show us today?
Singing talent.
Are you ready?
The floor is yours.
The clock keeps ticking,
never still.
As time rolls on
beyond our will.
The seasons turn
in endless style.
We break down and cry.
Sometimes we smile.
Nothing stands still,
even if we try.
Let us be real,
not dreaming away,
We'll walk in the light
of a new day.
No one can tell
what tomorrow may say.
Wherever the gentle wind blows,
let our hearts flow,
soft and slow.
And land where
our hearts both grow.
The world keeps
turning every day.
And we keep turning in its play.
Just open up, we'll learn it in.
We just might see
the world within.
Let's walk together, day by day.
Come take the step,
what do you say?
And, Guy, go right ahead.
- Please take a break, Save.
- Sure.
Singing talent too?
Ow? What did you bring for us?
Guy.
You think I'll make it?
Sure you will.
You had a star-like aura.
I don't believe you.
Your soccer juggling just killed.
Me? I didn't do anything...
just went in there to see you.
You were impressive.
They're in luck if they pick you.
Well, well. Are you excited?
Oh-ho. Very much so.
This is our first time.
Oh, really?
For your first audition,
you're doing amazing.
Wow.
We're all impressed
by your potential.
Next time, we'd like you
to make up a script
and do a cold scene.
Sound good?
Of course. Okay.
Uh.
Yes, okay.
- Heh.
- You got it.
Great. Just great.
Thanks.
You just had an audi...
audition, right?
Mm-hmm.
They've produced
several hit series.
And they want us to sign
with the studio.
You sure they're not cons?
No, they are the real deal.
See, if they sign us,
we could star in a series.
Hmm?
Can you act?
Stop stammering would be a start.
Grandpa, my diction is impeccable.
You sure you can do it?
Well, I'll try.
Opportunity has come knocking.
If I make it big,
there's serious money in it.
Hmph. You're all talk.
Did you rope Guy into this?
No, sir. It looked like fun,
so I jumped in.
- Mm-hmm.
- Hmm. I'm glad.
They want us to rehearse a scene
for the next audition.
Guy suggested we use one
from your novel.
May we, sir?
You mean Somporn and Anan?
Exactly.
Are you really up to it?
The characters are too far removed
from what you are now.
We'll have you to coach us, sir.
Coach?
I've never coached
or directed anyone before.
I can't do it.
Yes, you can.
Just explain the characters,
their thoughts and emotions.
Then we'll bring Somporn and Anan
from the pages to life.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
So...
we have your permission?
- Yeah.
- Hey.
- Yay.
Listen, you two.
Promise you'll do
the characters justice.
My name is riding on this.
- Of course. We'll do our best.
- Yes, sir.
- Heh.
- Hmph.
Then it's settled.
I'll help coach you and your friend.
Your boyfriend, that is.
In exchange,
you will help me type up
the remaining chapters.
The finale is around the corner.
Okay?
You got it, Grandpa.
My, my. I'm about to become
the mother of a TV star.
I'll need new glamorous outfits
to go on TV with, huh?
Not so fast, Mom.
We're not stars yet.
See? This is why
I don't tell you stuff.
Listen to him.
Huh. Nothing I do is right.
Guy, is he always like this?
Save, don't tease her like that.
She's just so happy for you.
Sure, take her side.
Heh.
Hey, Save.
You're gonna become an actor
without even asking me?
Do I have to?
Ow, you're entering showbiz;
what about school?
Everybody studies and works
at the same time now.
But if you can't maintain
your honors standing?
Ow, Dad?
Will you let them
run their own lives?
Don't be a grown-up
they don't look up to.
Okay?
- Okay?
- Heh.
My best wish to both of you, okay?
Of course, Mother.
So sweet. Hehe.
Let me see.
- Hey. It's growing.
- Mine too.
Oh, no.
Everyone else's is growing but mine.
Whose fault is that?
Jingjai, did you forget
the fertilizer?
No, no. I did fertilize the pot.
Liar. We'll be short of vegetables
because of you.
Did you have to run your mouth?
How do you know she forgot?
And even if she did,
couldn't you tell her nicely?
You didn't have to be so mean.
Right. There are vegetables
in those other plots.
We never yelled at you when
you forgot to water these plants.
Jingjai, don't mind him.
He always puts others down.
Yeah. Don't let it bother you.
You must learn to handle mean kids,
so they can't bully you.
Thanks.
Ever since I came here,
you've been the only ones
who look after me.
Friends support each other.
Friends?
Do you
think of me as a friend?
Ever since we let you
read BL novels with us.
Thanks a lot.
You make me want to
stay here forever.
Huk. Huk.
Huk. Huk. Hngh. Hngh.
Don't cry.
Don't cry now.
Huh.
Crying again.
You should stop that.
I have one more thing to tell you.
What is it?
I actually forgot to
put fertilizer in his pot.
- Jingjai.
"Available in print in 15 days.
Pre-order now."
"Posting."
Your pre-orders have now
passed ten thousand.
Really? This morning, they were just
around eight thousand.
They just keep coming in.
Grandpa.
Very well.
I'll entrust my book
to your publishing house.
Yes, sir.
I am truly honored.
I'll make sure
everything goes perfectly.
Not a single typo.
Well. Thanks a million.
Please excuse us.
Very well, sir.
Alright. Let's get back and write.
- Thank you.
- Yes.
"Guys and girls. Pre-order
Between Us and the Deep Forest yet?"
In just fourteen days,
we'll dive into the pages
of Somporn and Anan's story.
Can't wait to see which character
postcard comes with my copy.
Every copy includes one,
so why wait?
Pre-order your copy today.
Their quest was never for
riches untold or glittering stones,
but for what lay between them:
an important friend
in times of need.
Not a friend to the end.
He never wanted his friend to die.
So, for lack of a better word,
they were simply "friends."
He wanted only to
keep Anan in his life.
Distance did not trouble him.
What strengthened their bond
was knowing Anan was safe.
Should harm ever come to Anan,
he would wish to be the first
to stand at his side.
Even if he had nothing to offer,
his unsure presence
would still matter.
The world around him shifted,
as though touched by a silent spell.
Only the flutter of two hearts
kept softly beating as one.
Their eyes met one final time
before what remained of Somporn
ventured deeper into the forest
that knew no bounds.
The End.
"The End."
Very touching.
Mm-hmm.
You glazing me?
No glaze.
Look at you, keeping up
with the latest slang.
Snow taught me.
And...
that was the end, huh?
Why? You want a sequel?
Not that.
It feels...
sudden
after several months
with this novel.
Same here.
It's a sudden emptiness
every time
I write "The End" on a novel.
I can't wait to publish this...
masterpiece.
Yeah, well. I owe you big time.
Your painstaking work
has saved me from serious rehab.
I owe you one too.
For not bailing out.
See? My faith in you has paid off.
Yeah.
Let's call it a night.
I'm retiring.
Yeah. Sack time.
Tomorrow, I'll read it again
before sending to Phi Phuri.
Hmph.
All good, Grandpa.
Here.
Hmph.
Okay. Here you go.
Okay.
Scoot over a bit.
- Back?
- Forward, yeah.
Alright. Gently.
- Good night.
- Heh.
Good night.
Sit here, Dad.
- Dad.
- Hmm?
What would you like
to celebrate with?
Now that you've finished the novel.
Anything will do.
Everything tastes
ten times better now.
Sorn, have you checked
the deposit on the pre-orders?
I have.
It should cover
several debt payments.
Good. Once it's published,
we'll make a lot more money.
Yeah. You're the best Dad ever.
Soon, we can pay off all of it.
- Heh. Mwah.
- Hey!
- What are you, five years old?
- Heh.
Grandpa, come here.
"Microsoft Word:
Error accessing file."
Can't open the files.
Don't know what's wrong.
Hmm?
Can't open any of them?
Just the last two chapters.
Well, I'm headed to a repair shop.
Hey, wait.
I thought you had an audition.
Yeah... but...
Khun Phuri is waiting for our files.
I'll hurry back.
Oh, here's Save.
Ready for the audition?
No, I can't go yet.
I need to fix my laptop.
I couldn't open the files.
Ow.
Aren't they expecting them by ten?
Exactly, Mom.
You go first, Guy.
Hold up.
We go together.
- It could take long.
- It doesn't matter.
I go wherever you go.
- Then we go to a repair shop first.
- Okay.
I'll be back, Mother.
Yeah, yeah. Hope you get it fixed.
Be careful on the road.
Put it there.
Be safe.
Get it fixed.
"Phuri, Publisher."
Hello?
How's it going, sir?
We've been expecting your file
as discussed.
Can I have a little more time
to fix it up?
If we could help,
my proofreaders are standing by.
I see. Great help.
Let me give it a final touch.
Okay?
Alright, I won't bother you.
Email me as soon as you can.
- Dad, it's Save.
- Yeah?
The hard drive failed.
Unrecoverable.
What? What are we gonna do?
Guy said his expert uncle
would take another look.
Yeah, pass it along.
Call us if he finds anything.
I'm sorry, Grandpa.
My uncle says there's really
nothing he can do.
- What?
So what do we do now?
We'll have to type it up again.
What? Type it up again?
Do you even remember, Dad?
Huh.
There's really no other way?
Well, that's just our luck.
It had to fail now of all times.
Fine.
I'll rewrite them.
What?
I'll ask Khun Phuri
for an extension.
No, no.
His people are waiting on this.
In over thirty years of my career,
I've never missed a deadline.
We're getting this to them
by the end of the day.
- Mm-hmm.
- Phi Sorn.
He...
You go take the order. It's my turn.
Wait, wait. He...
- It's okay, Dad.
- Take the order.
- He, he.
- Yeah.
I just came back to see you.
No word of love.
No confession.
Hmm... keep reading.
Hey, is there anything
your wife can't do?
Ow?
Heh.
Keep going, Father.
Yeah.
No confession.
Hello.
Hi, we've got the second round
audition today. Right?
Yeah, I remember that.
I'm rushing through
this brutal traffic.
I'm on my way.
Move to the next line.
Mm-hmm.
And, uh...
And Somporn...
"Phuri, Publisher."
Dad.
Khun Phuri's calling.
Tell him to hold on.
Yes, sir.
Still nothing from you yet.
Uh, Dad asked me to tell you...
just wait a bit, please.
Hello?
Dad.
What's next, Grandpa?
Give me a moment.
Composing a line isn't
like tossing a coin.
Oh, oh. I got it. Was it like this?
'before what remained of Somporn'
Yes, type that.
- Go with that?
- Yeah.
The End.
- Hey.
- Yes, we're done.
Oh, did you save it, Save?
Already did, Mom.
- Then send these out.
- Okay.
"Send Email."
"Sending."
- Yes.
Okay, brilliant.
You two, it's time to dash.
- Yes, sir.
- Let's go.
- Come on, Guy.
- Yeah.
- Take care out there.
- Thanks.
We're heading out.
- Good luck.
- Bye, goodbye.
We're off.
- Let's go.
- Yeah.
Hello?
Hi, hi. Where are you now?
Almost there. Just a bit more.
Well, if you're late,
you might get disqualified.
Yeah, I'll be there.
Come.
Oh, Dad took the bike for delivery.
What now?
Let's just get a cab.
Hey, he's back.
Hey, Dad. Stop, stop.
- Stop.
- What?
- Get out, get out.
- Yeah, yeah. What's going on?
Come on, we're running out of time.
What's the rush?
Father, I'm sorry.
Yeah, yeah.
You're going with him, huh?
Okay, come on.
Easy, easy.
- You got it?
- I got it. Hmph.
Come on, come on.
Let's go.
Well... what in the world was that?
Alright, drive safe. Take it easy.
Oh.
"Wedding Invitation: Anong
and Somporn" I must go now.
Time to go pick up Anong.
Yeah, go on.
I don't know what came over me.
I burst into tears mid-scene.
Nothing during rehearsal.
I don't know either,
but while writing, I cried too.
Are you ready, Father?
I've been ready.
Can't wait to see clearly.
The world keeps
turning every day.
And we keep turning in its play.
Just open up, we'll learn it in.
We just might see
the world within.
Let's walk together, day by day.
Come take the step,
what do you say?
Let us be real,
not dreaming away,
We'll walk in the light
of a new day.
No one can tell
what tomorrow may say.
Wherever the gentle wind blows,
let our hearts flow,
soft and slow.
And land where
our hearts both grow.
The world keeps
turning every day.
And we keep turning in its play.
Just open up, we'll learn it in.
We just might see
the world within.
Let's walk together, day by day.
Come take the step,
what do you say?