And they want us to sign
with the studio.
You're gonna become an actor
without even asking me?
Can't open the files.
How's it going, sir?
Can I have a little more time
to fix it up?
Okay.
- Let's go.
- Yeah.
Ugh.
I'm sorry. We're late because of me.
Hey, don't apologize.
I don't really wanna be an actor.
I'm here just to support you.
Cut it out. Don't spiral.
Tell you what?
I'll try calling Phi Cha.
Don't bother.
I doubt she'll pick up.
Let's just head back.
Hey, wait.
What are you two doing here?
Well,...nobody was there
in the casting room.
What? We're in the other room,
right there.
Come on, follow me. Quick, quick.
I'm sorry we were late.
Something...
completely out of our hands came up.
Going forward,
please try to be on time.
Of course. It won't happen again.
So...what have you prepared
for us today?
A scene from my grandpa's novel.
Between Us in the Deep Forest?
- Yes.
- Seriously?
Uh...what's it even about?
Oh, come on.
How do you not know it?
It's a BL novel
his grandfather wrote. Really good.
Uh...I'll give you a moment.
- We'll start in five.
- Thanks.
Hey, take a breath.
Huh.
I don't know.
I suddenly feel so nervous.
Well.
It happens
when something
really matters to you.
I get it too
before big soccer matches.
My coach just says we train hard
to enjoy the game.
Hmph.
Grandpa trained us well too.
So let's just enjoy the scene.
Mm-hmm.
Why did you pick this scene?
Hmm...when I read it,
I felt the weight.
I thought it would pull me in,
and the audience too.
But it's tough.
Grandpa,
always trying to kill our vibe.
These roles don't feel like you
right now. Will it land?
I'm worried the judges
will send you packing.
I don't think
it's that far off from us.
And we're about
Anan and Somporn's age.
For something this hard,
we should score big
if we pull it off.
Fair enough.
Any questions before you go in?
Hmm...how about Somporn's life?
How broken is he, really?
Feelings ain't exactly fan speed
you can just dial up or down.
He is real sad.
He'll never see Anan again.
And if by chance he does,
it won't be the same between them.
But if...
they loved each other that much,
shouldn't Anan
try to hold Somporn back?
Back then,
a love like that was frowned upon
making a life together impossible.
Even the two of them
didn't fully understand
what they were feeling.
And Anan's love for Somporn
was deep enough that he was willing
to let Somporn go.
Wow, Anan really is something else.
Yeah. He was that resolute.
And did Somporn truly love Anan?
Hey, Save.
Have you actually read my novel?
I did. I'm just
not sure about this part.
I feel he's torn. Hard to read.
Not all that goes unwritten
between the lines
is lost.
Go back and carefully read it again.
Try to fathom
what Somporn is feeling.
It's been a long time.
How have you been?
Nothing much. You?
Nothing new, really.
I dream about the forest a lot.
Do you ever?
Sometimes.
A fun adventure turned daunting;
we nearly didn't make it out alive.
Luck played her part
and saved our lives
from the tiger's claws.
Mm-hmm.
It almost had us though.
Come to think of it.
It was fun because of you.
Had I gone solo or with anyone else,
it wouldn't have been fun,
lonely even.
We should return
to the forest again.
What say you?
Yeah.
Next month,
the rainy season will end.
Get yourself ready.
I'll let you know the date.
You know,
I want to go.
But I won't be able to.
Oh? Why not?
"Wedding Invitation: Anong
and Somporn, December 15, 2026."
You're getting married?
Mm-hmm.
Who is Anong?
Daughter of Mom's friend.
Oh, the one you mentioned before.
Mm-hmm.
Big news.
Should've told me sooner.
So I could get a sharp suit
tailored for your wedding.
I'm sorry.
Still working through it.
Yeah.
Congratulations. Best of wishes.
Thank you.
Come to the wedding if you could.
Absolutely.
I wouldn't miss it for the world.
It's your big day.
How could I miss it?
Will you...still go to the forest?
Of course. The forest is my life.
Mm-hmm.
Live it well.
Leave some for me too.
Yeah.
Don't worry.
You'll be on your own.
Just watch your back.
In a tiger's claws,
no one comes to your aid.
Then I shall eat that tiger.
I have to go now.
Time to pick up Anong.
Yeah, go.
I'm off.
See you at the wedding.
Huh.
Drive safely.
Groom-to-be.
Mm-hmm.
Huh.
Phi Cha,
when will we hear the results?
Uh...not sure yet.
We'll need to talk it over
a bit more.
There're dozens of people
auditioning today.
Hey, once we have the results,
I'll call you right away.
Yeah?
Okay, thank you.
- Thank you.
- Sure, sure. Get home safe.
You think...we made it?
Yeah.
Really?
Maybe.
But it's out of our hands now.
Did you give it everything?
Mm-hmm.
Then don't overthink it.
Wait for the call.
Yeah.
I just said don't overthink it.
I didn't.
Then why the face?
Let me drop you at your condo.
Go.
How did it go
with the publisher, Grandpa?
They're proofreading it now.
What about you?
Did you make it to the audition?
Just in time.
What did they say?
Hmm...
Let me ask you this.
I don't know what came over me.
I burst into tears mid-scene.
Nothing during rehearsal.
Really?
What happened to me?
I don't know either,
but while writing, I cried too.
Nop. There you go.
"Wedding Invitation:
Kanda and Somsak"
Congratulations, Sak.
Thanks a lot.
You and Kanda are perfect
for each other.
Hurry and find yours.
Mine still hasn't come along.
Hope you'll find yours soon.
I think in this life,
I'm meant to stay single.
Probably no kids either.
I'll just help raise yours.
Not sure I can come to your wedding.
Consider this...an early gift.
Hold onto it for me.
A memory, okay?
I'll keep it safe.
I have to run.
Mm-hmm.
Nop...
So when you were writing
the parting scene, you teared up.
Mm-hmm.
Hmm? Is this clean?
I can barely make it out.
Let me.
It's as clean as it'll get.
Just throw it away.
So...do you understand Somporn now?
I do...
maybe.
Put it back in the cabinet
where it was, would you?
Please...
just bear cucumbers already.
Been tending to these for months.
I'm so hopeless.
Once we get the cucumbers,
I'll make stuffed cucumber soup
for everyone.
Should be right around
the school break.
Let's see one cucumber first.
Hey, guys.
This school break, let's ask Grandpa
to take us on a trip?
Yeah? Can we?
Of course. If his novel sells,
he'll take us out for sure.
Where do you want to go?
Hmm...the beach. I've never been.
Got it. I'll ask him.
Thank you.
Jingjai, come with me for a sec.
What's going on?
Come on, quick, quick.
Okay.
Where's she going?
Hey...
Ow.
Hmm?
Is something off?
Hello.
Mom, can I stay?
Let me stay with my friends.
Jingjai, don't be difficult.
I came all this way.
You have friends
back in Lampang too.
But I want to stay
with my friends here.
You're the one who brought me here.
Now you're dragging me
somewhere else?
Snow said Grandpa's taking us
to the beach.
You've never taken me once.
I want to go with my friends.
Huk. Huk.
I don't want to leave.
Hngh.
Jingjai.
No. I'm not going. I'm not.
I'm not going.
Jingjai, don't be difficult.
Thank you all so much.
I'm not going.
Hngh...
Please, Auntie.
- Don't take her away.
- That's right.
She is our friend.
Please don't take her.
We'll look after her well.
We promise she'll be happy here.
You can leave her with us.
Whenever you miss her,
just come visit.
- Please, we're begging you.
- Please, don't take her.
- Can we ask you this?
- Please...
Excuse us a moment.
Kids.
Jingjai is going home
with her mother today.
I'll give you ten minutes.
Say your goodbyes.
Thank you all so much.
Come back whenever you miss us.
Reach out anytime.
The others gave you some snacks.
For the train ride.
Take care.
Don't cry now.
Jingjai. Let's go.
Yes.
- Jingjai.
Jingjai.
- Have a safe trip.
- Safe trip.
- Good luck, Jingjai.
- Bye.
Thank you all, kids. Well then...
Bye.
We'll always think of you, Jingjai.
That's just how life goes.
All meetings end in partings.
But if you're meant
to find each other,
you'll meet again.
- Ho. Ho.
- Yeah.
- Has the studio contacted you?
- Not yet.
Hmm.
Is anyone home?
No one. Dad's out delivering.
Mom, Grandpa, and Snow
are with the kids.
Hey.
Plotting something?
Us, alone in an empty house?
What do you think?
You locked it?
So no one will interrupt.
Whew.
Come here.
Now?
What's the matter?
Chickening out?
I won't push you
if you don't want to.
How do you know I don't want to?
You're blushing.
No, I'm not.
Sure, you're not.
Don't tease me.
Did you ask my permission for that?
You stole a kiss on my cheek.
Fair point. We're even.
Hey.
That's it for today.
To be continued.
Come on.
Hey.
I got the Anan card.
Mine's Somporn.
- Wow.
- Oh, wow.
Feels like ages
since we last picked up a book.
True. It's been many years.
- All is well?
- Oh, yes, sir.
Every order has been delivered.
All is well.
Thank you for the publishing
and delivery.
Doing all that myself
would have been a mess.
- Heh.
- Happy to help, sir.
Very well.
Uh, and no commission cut, right?
Oh, none at all.
Khun Somsak hired us to
handle the printing and delivery.
He holds the copyright
to this novel.
- Yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
And when does
the next print run start?
About a month from now.
Pre-orders keep coming in.
- Hoo.
- Heh.
So.
Grandpa, we're going to be rich.
- Heh.
- Haha.
- Oh, my.
- Silly girl.
- Haha.
Everyone, snacks and novel are
now available in the live stream.
E-book versions are available too.
"Are you two together now?"
How about that, everyone?
Does it show?
If it doesn't yet,
we'll make it more obvious.
Save, come here.
Not now, Mom.
The views are climbing.
Come now. Guy too.
Help me carry these.
Huh, just when
it's getting good, huh?
Great-grandma, you're in charge.
She must keep moving.
It's the rules.
Hey.
Here...slowly, okay?
Don't overdo it.
Keep an eye on her.
We'll be right back.
- Go.
Thanks a lot, Great-grandma.
Oh, no. This is bad.
What?
Everyone, did she eat the sweets?
Let me cut the stream.
Be right back.
What happened?
If she has the sweets,
Mom's gonna be in big trouble
for adapting her Royal recipe.
Now she knows.
I'm truly sorry, Grandmother.
I really need to adjust the recipe
for modern tastes.
That's right.
Otherwise it wouldn't sell.
People nowadays can't handle
throat-burning snacks anymore.
We added other ingredients
just to...mellow the flavor.
Oh.
Hmm? Looks like she likes it.
Hmm?
We've kept it from her.
- But she actually likes it.
- Mm-hmm.
I told you.
You were overthinking it.
Good things speak for themselves.
- Yeah.
When did you tell me exactly?
I don't remember.
I told you, why bother
hiding it from her?
Phi Sorn, you were just
as scared of her reaction.
That's why we've been hiding it.
Come on.
Oh, hey.
- She's having more.
- Yeah.
Hmm...
All right.
- Guy.
- Yeah?
What's wrong?
Acting strange all day.
Am I? I'm fine.
Not fine.
If you're fine, we'd have
gotten back here for dinner.
Instead, you've had me take you
all over town.
Come on. Let's go inside.
Hello, Phi Cha.
Hello.
Oh, hi Phi Cha.
What brings you here?
Hmm? Didn't Guy tell you?
I wanted to surprise you.
I'm here to tell you that
we'd like to sign both of you.
Seriously?
Absolutely. But you mentioned
your father had some concerns.
So I'm here to
clear things up with him.
Oh, no concerns now.
Well, a grown man
makes his own choices.
Really?
Really. Just don't
let your grades slip.
You've come a long way.
So what do they need to do next?
We'll arrange for them to come in
and sign the contract.
You are welcome to come along.
Yeah.
Please come,
in case I panic or something.
Hey, you're grown.
Start handling things yourself.
Hmph.
- Uh, sir. There's one more thing.
- Yes.
Our studio would like to
acquire the rights to
Between Us in the Deep Forest
to adapt as a series.
Might I ask if you'd already
sold the rights to anyone?
So have you
sold the rights to anyone yet?
Not yet.
You're actually the first to ask.
Would you consider us?
Yes,...absolutely.
She asked your grandpa.
Well, if you want to turn this into
a film or a drama, no objections.
Just one condition:
keep the heart of the novel intact.
The rest you can adapt
however it suits you.
Thank you so much, sir.
Your novel is truly wonderful.
We promise to honor
the source material as best we can.
Can I have some say in casting?
Right now we're looking at
Save and Nong Guy for the leads.
Hey.
Well...no objections.
Grandpa, time to wake up.
Grandpa.
Oh...Grandpa.
Today, you're going under the knife.
I'm a person, not a piece of pork.
Come on. Up, up.
Ugh, what were you thinking?
Are they doing both eyes today?
See? You weren't
listening to the doctor.
One at a time, two weeks apart.
Oh, now I remember.
Walk slowly.
Watch your step.
Ready, Father?
I've been ready.
Can't wait to see clearly.
Yeah.
Nothing to worry about.
You'll be perfectly safe.
Thank you.
Heh.
Shall we go then?
- Mm-hmm.
- What about Sun?
He'll meet us at the hospital.
Oh, okay.
Wait, wait.
Yeah.
- Let's go.
- Yeah.
The left eye surgery went smoothly.
So I'll have normal vision again?
Yes, the cornea may still be
a little swollen at first.
Your vision will improve gradually,
but not quite a hundred percent yet.
You can go home now.
See you in two weeks
for the right eye.
Thank you very much.
Okay.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
"Two weeks later"
We're home, Dad.
Easy now, easy.
Careful, careful.
- Gently, Dad.
- Easy. Right here.
- Oh?
- Easy, easy.
Alright, alright.
I can see. I can walk on my own.
It's not the vision
I'm worried about.
It's the age.
Didn't you take a tumble
in front of the nurses?
He did.
My, my.
You two are finishing
each other's sentences now.
Haha.
Take it slow, Dad.
- Grandpa.
Gently, gently.
How are you feeling?
Good and fine.
Ahem.
"Check: 200,000 baht"
Here you go.
Saeng Karun alumni from nearly
every generation sent this.
Did you go around
collecting from them?
No, they caught the news
about your novel and did this.
I won't accept it. Give it back.
Nope, can't give it back.
They said to keep it.
They want to support the home
that raised them too.
- Just accept it, Father.
- Mm-hmm.
Here.
Could you sign this for me, sir?
Oh, of course.
Doing my grandfather a favor.
- Sure.
- Hand it over.
He said you inspired
his entire generation.
Me?
Yeah, his grandpa used to just
sit around at home.
Now he gets up
and paints every day.
He always dreamed of
being an artist.
Oh...good for him.
Well then,
may he find great success.
- Thank you so much.
- Yeah.
Come on. The first episode
of the series is coming on.
Hmph.
It's our debut. Don't go too hard
on the comments, okay?
Okay, I'll tone it down.
Aw...I'm feeling it already.
"We go in and the only way out
is through."
"Do I look terrified?"
"Just making sure one last time."
"I reckoned danger awaited.
Yet here I stand with you."
"Then...swear you won't die."
"Only fools swear
to something like that."
"Fool or not, just swear..."
"that you'll walk away from this."
"I'll walk away with you,
even through hellfire."
"That I swear."
- Wow.
- Sweet.
What's wrong? Heh.
It's so sweet, Phi Save.
They just hold hands.
"Oh, ugh."
"Tch."
Deeply in it, huh?
Thank you.
From all of us, together.
Selling sweets, selling novels.
In Thai and English too.
Audiobooks.
Selling the novel rights
for the series adaptation.
And...Save's acting fee.
Haha.
The remaining bank debt is down to
just two million baht.
- Yay.
- Yes...
Hmph...unbelievable.
Everyone's done an incredible job.
You helped manage
the household accounts,
so we could plan a large repayment.
Happy to help.
- This calls for a celebration.
- Yay.
Then we'll celebrate you
getting your sight back too.
I have to thank everyone once more
that Saeng Karun is
still standing today.
Now I could face my grandfather,
unashamed.
Oh, by the way,
our reader-fan next door
has a bunch of oranges for us.
Guy, take some home for your family.
- Yes, Dad.
- Mm-hmm.
I'll help you carry them.
Sure. Let's go now.
Looks like your dad
is warming up to Guy.
Will you finish all of those?
I can pass them on to the neighbors.
Feeling better?
My dad's coming around to you now.
Honestly, he's been nice to me
for a while.
Well, you're easy to like.
I told you he'd soften up.
You think...we'll change?
You mean when we get more famous?
Mm-hmm.
Maybe...a little more
full of ourselves.
Seriously.
Oh.
Hmm...
Who knows what the future holds?
Our series might be a total dud.
Or you might
get tired of me first.
But right now, I love
having you by my side.
Figuring it out together.
Same.
There's still so much
I want to do with you.
So don't get tired of me yet.
"Bank deposit: 47,500 baht"
Hmm?
I got a bank deposit?
I...sent you that money.
What for? And why?
Well, since I graduated,
I've never really
given you anything.
Whenever I tried, you'd say,
"Only if you stand
on your own first. I'm fine."
I've saved up...for three years
from food delivery runs.
After family responsibilities, I had
about this much.
It's not a lot.
But I wanted to give it to you.
You did good.
I always knew...
you had it in you.
Heh.
Me? I've always had it, Dad.
- Just keeping it low-key.
- Yeah.
Alright, I'mma help Mart
with the sweets.
Yeah.
Not turning in yet?
Not yet. Taking a break, really.
Okay.
- Has Uncle Sun filled you in?
- Hmm?
People are loving the first episode,
and raving about the source novel.
Sales are going to shoot up.
I have to thank you too,
for making all of this happen.
You should be thanking yourself
most of all.
Hope your series really takes off.
Sathu...
Keep it coming
so I can take care of you.
Oh, I'm fine.
I can take care of myself.
There's still so much I can do.
Clear eyes, sharp mind, huh?
See what I'll cook up
when my eyes are fully healed.
Cook up what?
Brand new thing.
Huh?
"Guys, gals. Between Us
in the Deep Forest is insane."
"And I heard through the grapevine"
"that Save and Guy
are actually together."
"But keep it quiet."
"They'd rather sell their work
than that angle."
"You and your nephew are huge now."
"Congrats on Save's series too."
"Thanks.
I am very proud of him too."
"Can you share your key to success?"
"Key to success?"
"It depends on
how you define success."
"As for me, I'm not sure I've ever"
"held the key to my own success."
"But...if I must answer..."
First, my family,
for their unwavering support.
Second, keeping an open mind.
When I had to write a BL novel,
I started talking more
with my grandchildren.
I learned more
about the modern world
and exchanged ideas
with a younger generation.
It broadened my perspective.
I think the reason more people
are reading my novel now
is because
I was willing to change.
"Anything you would like
to say to young people"
"who want to find success?"
"Young people today
put so much pressure on themselves."
Really, they should grow
gradually at their own pace.
Life isn't a race.
There's no need to rush.
If they fall, rise and walk again.
Too hard to go on?
Then sit and rest.
Make every moment count.
Change will come. Learn to adapt.
But more than anything...
no matter fortune
life brings one day,
be it fame,
money, or worldly gain,
remember that none of it lasts.
Happiness is fleeting.
And suffering, too,
shall pass.
One day, we all leave this world.
Part of who we were
may linger in the memories
of those still here,
and may eventually be forgotten.
Eventually, all things turn
in the great wheel of life.
Everyone...
Look at this.
- Everyone.
- Oh-ho.
- Wow.
Look...
Come, come.
- Oh-ho.
- Wow.
At last, vegetables to eat.
- Yay.
- Yes.
- Grandpa.
- Hmm?
What's the bell for?
To wake up the kids.
What about...your bugle?
Can't manage it anymore.
Where did you get it?
It was Grandpa's.
He used it back in the old days.
If it still works, use it.
- Come on. Give me that.
- Ha?
I'll help. Come here.
Easy, easy.
Hang it here?
There...
Six o'clock. Right on the dot.
Exactly.
Rise and shine, everyone.
The clock keeps ticking,
never still.
As time rolls on
beyond our will.
The seasons turn
in endless style.
We break down and cry.
Sometimes we smile.
Nothing stands still,
even if we try.
Let us be real,
not dreaming away,
We'll walk in the light
of a new day.
No one can tell
what tomorrow may say.
Wherever the gentle wind blows,
let our hearts flow,
soft and slow.
And land where
our hearts both grow.
The world keeps
turning every day.
And we keep
turning in its play.
Just open up, we'll learn it in.
We just might see
the world within.
Let's walk together,
day by day.
Come take the step,
what do you say?
"Chapter 1"
The world keeps
turning every day.
And we keep
turning in its play.
Just open up, we'll learn it in.
We just might see
the world within.
Let's walk together,
day by day.
Come take the step,
what do you say?
Let us be real,
not dreaming away,
We'll walk in the light
of a new day.
No one can tell
what tomorrow may say.
Wherever the gentle wind blows,
let our hearts flow,
soft and slow.
And land where
our hearts both grow.
The world keeps
turning every day.
And we keep
turning in its play.
Just open up, we'll learn it in.
We just might see
the world within.
Let's walk together,
day by day.
Come take the step,
what do you say?