MY ROYAL NEMESIS
Boss, I think there's
a woman standing in the way.
I have eyes, too.
Drag her out.
Tear it all down!
- Yes, sir.
- What the…
- Who's that?
Who the hell are you?
Cha Se-gye from Chail E&C.
You don't know who I am?
I don't. Why should I?
Get him! Damn it.
Hey! Get him! Damn it!
Get him!
You bastard.
Hey!
Police. Stop what you're doing
immediately.
Shin Seo-ri.
Are you okay?
Cha Se-gye.
I'm here.
Talk to me.
It is so bright.
The light is blinding.
Shin Seo-ri.
Damn it.
EPISODE 13
TWIST OF FATE
Dan-sim. Open your eyes, Dan-sim.
- Dan-sim. Oh no.
- Oh dear.
Dan-sim, are you coming to?
Are you okay, Dan-sim?
My name
is Seo-ri. Why are they…
Your breathing
has stabilized considerably,
and your overall vitals
look good, Chairman.
As long as there is
no secondary infection or bleeding,
you should be able to go home
in about two weeks.
Chairman,
I know nothing about that.
I had nothing to do
with Mr. Cha's company or your accident.
I just thought President Choi Mun-do
and I could be good partners.
Provided you maintain absolute rest,
we can also expect
- a gradual recovery of memory function.
- Okay.
Thank you. I'll be careful.
Contact the Commissioner.
Let him know I'd like a meeting.
Are you okay?
About what?
No.
I'm just asking if you're doing okay.
Perceptive punk.
Nothing gets past you.
What can I do?
I cannot turn back the time
that has already passed.
It is too late for bitter tears now.
I have to live in the moment.
I have to do what I can.
What's wrong?
Did something happen?
Cha Se-gye.
You know,
life…
always felt like a prison sentence.
Every single day…
felt like I was being punished.
The gall of that wench.
That foolish girl threw herself
into the river like it was nothing.
I handed the bondage deed over,
but she does not even know
her own name yet.
She does not know her head
from her tail. What is she to do?
What choice does she have?
You can still be a slave
without knowing your name.
Send her away as soon as she gets up.
Unbelievable.
Why was I born just to be punished?
What a gloomy face on this girl.
Bad luck written all over it.
Keep acting this way,
and there will be
nothing left of you to find.
- Hey!
- Where are you going?
You brat!
Hey!
Lock her in the shed.
Do not give her a drop of water.
If this is all life had in store for me…
Let me out!
But that commoner's time will soon be up.
These are the end times.
Right? She is nothing but lowborn.
Perhaps it would be better…
But who knows for sure?
It could be a curse meant
to bring about the Queen's death.
GRAND PRINCE CHEONGHEON
…if I had never been born into this world.
Even when I came here,
I told myself to think of it as a reward,
as my second chance at life.
I tried to convince myself.
But I once again arrived at punishment.
I began to wonder what kind
of suffering this life would bring.
But the strange thing is,
I think
I have smiled a bit since coming here.
Meeting Grandmother and meeting you
brought my heart some peace.
For the first time in my life.
So I am just going to call it even.
I shall truly consider it as a reward.
As if I am collecting
all my overdue rewards at once.
That is how I shall view it.
Cha Se-gye.
Let us grow old together.
Okay.
I won't let you go.
I'm not letting you go anywhere.
No need.
I am not going back.
There is no need to anymore.
Because I have returned
to where I belong.
She had a high fever last night,
but after medication,
she's doing well today.
The air is chilly,
so don't stay out too long.
Grandma.
I am here.
Your granddaughter is here.
Please look at me.
Young lady.
Is the young man with you
your boyfriend?
Yes, I'm her boyfriend, Grandmother.
My, you're a handsome young man.
Just like my husband was back in the day.
He may not have earned much money,
but he was a fine-looking man.
He really was.
Well, I make good money too.
As I said last time,
I am quite a capable man.
This boy's got a silver tongue.
Still putting on airs
when you are flat broke.
But who are you, miss?
Why are you being so nice to me?
Who else?
I am his girlfriend.
Don't cry.
Come on now.
What was yesterday about?
You summoned me out of nowhere.
What was I supposed to do?
They just barged in.
I was shocked too.
That's why you should've given me
a heads-up.
And that backdoor deal
with Inspector Lee as well.
"Backdoor deal"? Watch it.
And let me offer you a deal.
Are you seriously trying to make
a plea deal
with an active-duty police officer?
Not a plea deal. Just a sharing of intel.
The way I see it,
the cartel within the police
runs way deep.
In a one-on-one fight,
timing is everything.
The same goes for attacks.
It's also time for you
to do some fieldwork.
Keep an eye on that restaurant.
No telling when they might hit again.
It'll do her good
to get her out of her room
and into some fresh air.
Could I also have
a word with you, Ms. Shin?
You have high standards, young man.
You chose a good one.
How can you tell that
just by looking at her once?
What do you mean, "once"?
She's my baby.
I raised her with my own two hands.
Listen.
I have something to tell you.
Hold on. Let me get Shin Seo-ri.
No.
Not Seo-ri, you.
I have something to tell you.
So it wasn't possession, but a return?
Not a hostile takeover,
but a triumphant homecoming?
You were dropped into Joseon at 12,
served as a court lady,
and died by poison.
And now, you've returned
to the present day.
I've never seen
a regression-possession-reincarnation
like this before.
This is like discovering a new continent.
No wonder.
The hwagyeong felt off. She had your face,
but she wasn't
like Your Highness at all.
You must have seen her.
Anyway, the point is,
I have no reason
to look into the hwagyeong
or channel any dang spirit whatsoever.
I offer you
my deepest congratulations, Your Highness.
Hey, come on now.
You must stop calling me
Your Highness now.
Call me Seo-ri. Shin Seo-ri.
That is my name.
Right. Shin Seo-ri.
All right then.
This is truly a fresh start for you.
To make a proper fresh start,
I will have to weed out
the rotten stems first.
THE WOMEN'S KINGDOM 2
FINAL EPISODE
Receive the royal command
from His Majesty.
Royal Noble Consort Kim
has disrupted the order of the court
and committed a grave sin.
By royal command,
you are to take this poison.
Is it a sin to have
once loved His Majesty?
I must see His Majesty.
Let me see His Majesty!
Make her drink.
You wenches! Unhand me at once!
Bring me His Majesty!
Bring him to me now!
I will not die like this!
Bring it in.
So you are determined to see me dead?
Very well!
Let this day claim us both.
Let us see this through!
Amazing.
You killed that poison-drinking scene.
What a dopamine rush.
Like you'd actually drunk it before.
Practice makes perfect, even with poison.
If ratings skyrocket,
they better know it is thanks to me.
The director was saying
that in Season 3,
you could return as a twin
with a mole on your nose
and storm the palace.
Come on now.
But still,
dying young is a wretched feeling.
Next time, I shall outlive them.
Makeup team!
Please wipe the blood off Seo-ri's mouth.
Shin Seo-ri is sure enjoying herself.
Hey, you there.
Get me some water.
Right.
Gosh.
Thanks.
Where's the wrap party
for Seo-ri's last shoot?
Wrap party?
Weren't you invited?
Well, I…
What's with Shin Seo-ri?
She used to take such good care of you.
Guess that relationship went south.
What's that supposed to mean?
"She took care of me"?
You didn't know?
Shin Seo-ri got you this part.
So much for
the high and mighty favor hires.
A falling-out already?
She's so fickle.
Who is she to have a wrap party
and decide who gets to come?
She says she's a member
of the nurse's family.
Security tried to stop her,
but she refused to leave.
REVEAL THE TRUTH
Why is she here? This isn't Biojei.
Perhaps someone
from Mr. Cha's side leaked it?
Get rid of her.
Before any unwanted rumors start.
Yes, sir.
Wow, it's actually over.
Seriously, I'm so over this.
You all worked so hard.
- The beer's really good too.
- Shall we drink to that?
- You have to give a toast!
- Go on!
Yeah, give us a toast!
All right!
My sincerest thanks for coming
to celebrate my grand finale.
May you all be blessed with health within
and prosperity in all things without,
as you return home in triumph.
Everyone, shout it with me!
Yahoo!
- Yahoo?
- Seriously?
- Ya…
- Yahoo.
Yahoo?
Come on. Yahoo!
Yeah. Yahoo!
- Cheers!
What's your deal?
Are you even friends with Shin Seo-ri?
No, but Gwang-nam
kept insisting that we come.
We just couldn't say no.
Right.
Forget the effort.
It's the reward that counts.
The head of our agency
will be treating us today.
Please enjoy yourselves.
- Wait.
- Jeez.
Gwang-nam.
Take a break from pouring
and have a drink with us.
- Have a drink.
- Let's drink. Cheers!
I have to drive,
so please have my share too.
Oh my, you're so sweet.
That voice is so soothing.
Total ASMR boyfriend material.
Really?
Well, my glass can have water.
- Just clink some glasses.
- Cheers.
Look at you having a ball.
Hold on. What's going on?
- Are they gifts for us?
- Why so many?
No way.
Are those for us?
- What are the gifts…
- Damn.
Here you all are.
Wait, Cha Se-gye…
Mr. Cha, what are you doing here?
When I heard Biojei's beloved ambassador
was celebrating her grand finale,
I decided to prepare
a small gift for her crew.
First, the Dynaestie Premium 3-Piece set
to keep you glowing.
A Chail Conic Bluetooth speaker.
That's amazing.
And the Chail Tech full package.
A watch, a tablet, and earbuds.
No way. That's amazing.
- Shin Seo-ri!
- Here they come!
- This is insane!
- Come on now.
- Shin Seo-ri!
- It's nothing, really.
Shin Seo-ri!
Bent on sealing your ruin?
Why blow cash
when it is already over and done?
I'm not blowing cash. It's an investment.
This industry's tiny. Never know
who you'll run into on the next drama.
Consider it an investment
in your reputation.
With compound interest.
Investment in my reputation?
Worry about yourself.
Blowing money
after tanking your company?
Are you going to just bum around
like this forever?
What's this, Shin Seo-ri?
Worried about me day and night?
I'll be busy for a while.
What will you do when you miss me?
What the…
Screw all these couples.
- Gwang-nam.
- Yes?
How long do you plan
to be Shin Seo-ri's manager?
Does your family say anything?
Actually, my parents keep asking me
to move back home.
But the country life is not for me.
What's wrong with it?
A country house is my dream.
- Kinfolk style.
- Kinfolk…
Kinfolk, my ass.
Didn't you say anywhere
but Gangnam is the boonies?
Can't live below the 20th floor.
Reverse-acrophobia or something?
I've never said that.
Well, I might've mentioned
that the lower floors in Seoul
have poor air quality.
- You're absolutely right about that.
- Yeah.
I live on the second floor
of a boarding house.
The moment someone lights
a cigarette downstairs, just forget it.
The room's so tiny.
Smells never clear out.
It's the absolute worst.
You live in a boarding house?
Why?
What do you mean, "why"?
It's because I don't have
the deposit money.
Hold on, but why wouldn't you have
the deposit money?
Wait, was it intentional?
Your parents wanted
to foster your independence?
- Right.
- "Independence"?
No, that's not it.
My parents always used
to keep around five million won on hand.
But they got scammed last year
while buying stock for their corner store.
- Corner… store?
- Yes.
My family runs a corner store.
The Thousand Won Department Store.
But still, in our neighborhood,
it's treated like a general store.
I see. Thousand won…
Thousand Won Department Store…
How amazing.
But you know what?
Hardly anything there
actually costs 1,000 won.
With inflation these days,
most things are at least 3,000 won.
What gives you the right to talk
about people you know nothing about?
I mean, it's not like I was making it up.
These were your words.
On the phone, you said
your parents owned a department store.
So you were eavesdropping
on someone's call.
Mr. Baek Gwang-nam,
I am incredibly offended right now.
That attitude of yours.
It's not just today.
It's been consistently unpleasant.
At some point,
I have to put my foot down.
You're done being my manager.
- You're fired, effective immediately--
- No! I quit!
I'm so done with this crap.
Did you just throw those keys down?
- But you're a manager.
- And does that make me less of a person?
Some kind of servant?
To hell with this place.
I hope it burns to the ground. Damn it!
Baek Gwang-nam!
You won't get away with this!
Wait. Hold on.
Why are you coming back? What's up?
Return this to the office.
What in the world?
Hey! How am I supposed to get home?
Once Seo-jun's school paperwork
is sorted, you can take over for now.
- Until we find a new sitter.
- Yes, sir.
And get me
two baseball tickets for this weekend.
Seo-jun will love that.
You must be Chairman Choi Mun-do.
I'm Inspector Lee Han-su
from Seobu Police Station.
I'm here to ask you a few questions
about the death of Nurse An Seong-hui.
Her death?
I believe he's referring to the case
involving Mr. Cha Se-gye.
I see.
I doubt
I could provide any insight on that.
Se-gye and I aren't very close.
I'll be the judge
of whether there's any connection.
It's a routine inquiry.
Appreciate your cooperation.
I see no reason to comply
with a voluntary summons.
If you have questions,
issue a formal summons.
Chairman Choi.
REFUSAL TO COOPERATE
According to Inspector Lee,
President Choi Mun-do's side
is playing dumb for now.
They want a formal summons.
I'm worried we're just giving him
time to prepare.
That was the intention.
I'm trying to track
the movements of a busy bee.
A busy bee?
Not one indictment,
despite all the bid-rigging
during his construction days.
He must have quite the tight-knit cartel.
I'll shake that up first.
Starting from the construction company.
The foundation of Choi Mun-do's power.
That cop from earlier
is from Seobu Police Station.
He summoned Mr. Cha last time.
Looks like Se-gye's feelings are hurt.
Lost face in front of a woman, did we?
As if sending one low-ranking officer
is going to pressure anyone.
Prepare a press release.
"Former Biojei CEO Cha Se-gye
didn't get pushed out."
"He escaped,
pocketing hundreds of billions of won
after bleeding retail investors dry."
Like that.
Yes, Chairman.
Sir, you should check online.
BRIBERY AND BID-RIGGING ALLEGATIONS
FROM HIS CONSTRUCTION DAYS
His signature move. Manufacturing
public outrage out of thin air.
When you're on the receiving end,
it can really mess with your head.
And now, for the real attack.
I'll put the brakes
on Choi Mun-do's key project,
the resort development.
His illegal deployment of contractors
during the land acquisition
will undermine the project's credibility.
Then we leak to investors that there's
an international airport bid
for Jusan City, 10 km from the site.
Then internally,
they'll demand early repayment.
Externally, he'll be branded
a corrupt businessman.
And the construction
comes to a full stop.
You think Choi Mun-do
will just sit there and take it?
Of course he won't
just take it lying down.
He'll attack me.
Who will be the lesser of two evils?
The media will be confused
about who to criticize.
So what's your exit strategy?
No exit strategy.
Why?
Because I have nothing to lose.
Korea's top conglomerate Chail Group
finds its succession
mired in corruption allegations.
Top succession contender Cha Se-gye,
former CEO of Biojei,
and Interim Chairman Choi Mun-do
are both under fire.
Cha is embroiled in controversy
over profits from his stake sale.
Choi faces bribery allegations
in the construction bidding process.
It has also recently come to light
that Chairman Choi deployed
hired hands to secure the resort site
for the group's flagship project,
fueling mounting controversy.
Those allegations
of illegal land acquisition
are entirely baseless.
If you're going to suddenly demand
early repayment
based on unverified fake news--
I hear they're building an airport
next to the resort site.
Only 10 km away, no less.
Well, that's…
Good thing we have connections
at Jusan City Hall.
Otherwise, we wouldn't have known
a thing until they broke ground.
If they build an airport
next to the resort,
it means noisy planes will be flying
overhead all the time.
Does that make any sense?
Who's going to want to stay there?
I believe the airport bid
is still at the planning stage.
And where exactly did you hear this?
Well, it turns out the current mayor
of Jusan is gunning for re-election,
and her key campaign pledge is
to build an international airport.
The mayor…
of Jusan City?
Yes, the resort will proceed
without a hitch.
We'll announce the construction schedule
at the upcoming
50th anniversary celebration.
I'll take that as a promise.
After Songjin City,
you'll support Jusan City.
A resort is certainly better
than an airport, after all.
Her aide says that until a month ago,
it wasn't even a key pledge.
The pivot came without warning.
It appears…
some sort of deal was struck.
Mayor.
After claiming you couldn't handle it,
you're just crushing
the three kings of cardio hell.
You'd better come through.
I'm only building up my stamina
because I trust you, Ms. Mo.
Of course. I'll open up that path
for you to the Blue House.
Why walk when you can fly?
Shall we try some strength training now?
Should we? This way.
The Mochang influence is no joke.
One word from you
and an airport materializes.
Se-gye, you only ever take from me.
Will you ever pay me back?
Come on now.
Once Jusan Airport is built,
the duty-free will be your playground.
From your jewelry line
to Mochang's restaurant
and even the outdoor line.
Well, I'm not running a charity here.
Did you think I did it
because I like you, Se-gye?
Right. I like that mindset.
I look forward to working
with you as partners.
Okay. Let's do that.
Chail Group's flagship project,
the Songjin Resort,
has hit a roadblock.
Questions over the resort site's viability
have emerged
after Jusan City, just 10 km away,
formally announced
its international airport bid.
Unless the design is fully revised,
analysts say it will be difficult
to move forward with the project.
As these concerns have come to light,
some investors have begun pushing
for early repayment of their investments.
Once seen as the man
to reform Chail Group,
Interim Chairman Choi Mun-do
now faces his greatest crisis yet.
Dogged by bribery allegations
from his days in construction
and setbacks with the resort project,
he faces mounting pressure.
Some are drawing parallels
between Choi's escalating troubles
and the ousting of Cha four years ago…
Damn it.
They're bad-mouthing me again.
We did it without lifting a finger.
When did you win over the Jusan mayor?
The more out in the sticks you are,
the more you crave
a National Assembly seat.
All I did was give her a nudge,
and her ambition did the rest.
Chairman Choi must be livid.
He's just reaping what he sowed.
Choi Mun-do's been banking
dirty deeds for years.
I'm just cashing them out, one by one.
You just show up without even calling now?
You said you were busy.
Then why are you just sitting at home?
You are not even watching anything.
What? You want to watch something?
Hey, that is you.
- No, it's not.
- What?
No, I am sure it was you.
- No, you saw wrong.
- I'm sure I saw you!
I am positive it was you.
- Hey!
- Just drop it.
- Damn it.
What brings you two to my place?
What do you want?
Fine. Let's skip the formalities
and get down to business.
Okay, Se-gye.
I think it's time
we seriously consider joining forces.
As you know,
Grandfather isn't
in a good place right now.
And the company is a mess.
I think it's only right for the family
to stick together at this juncture.
Look, why do you think
Chail Group is called Chail?
Because it's the Cha family's company.
But the head of the company
is Choi Mun-do right now.
That's not Chail. It's Choi-il.
The name alone doesn't make sense, right?
Right. Choi-il just won't do.
Right? It won't. No, it won't.
But since when were we family?
Wasn't I the rat who came
to clean out the vaults?
Se-gye.
Listen. Sure.
I admit we weren't exactly
the most affectionate aunts and nephew.
But when did we ever treat you like that?
Right. Not a sneaky rat.
Just some stray mutt.
Hey!
You'd better watch your mouth!
With Father having collapsed,
we came hoping we could at least unite.
Let's be honest here.
You didn't come to unite.
You came to beg.
Hoping this mutt will throw you a bone.
Cha Se-gye!
How dare you speak so crudely
in front of your elders?
I told you we shouldn't have come here.
This is what we get for thinking
we need to protect family.
What kind of rotten attitude is that?
That is rich coming from you.
Cha Se-gye, why are you sitting here
listening to that garbage?
- Come on.
- Kick them out already.
What in the world are you doing here?
What is this? Are you two official now?
What? You know her?
How do you two know each other?
It appears you have not wised up
after that taffy thrashing.
The rod was too gentle.
Sis, you got beaten up?
- Did you hit Shin Seo-ri?
- What are you talking about?
It was a total one-sided thrashing.
You're not the type of person
to go around getting beaten up.
Aunt.
Calm yourself, Cha Se-gye.
I was not struck even once.
It is true that it was
a one-sided thrashing.
Oh my!
Exactly!
I'm telling you, I was the victim!
And yet you crawl back here
to harass your nephew.
This will not do.
What? What now?
What? What are you doing?
- Why are you pulling that out?
- Oh my.
Damn it.
For one who has lost their senses,
a good thrashing is best.
Damn hoodlum!
Fine, bring it on! Bring it.
- I'm not alone today, you know.
- Oh my goodness.
- What the… Hey!
- Hey!
Hey, what are you doing?
Damn.
What was that?
Were you protecting me?
Scared I'd get jumped by my aunts?
They call themselves aunts
but never once protected you.
Cha Se-gye, do not worry.
I taught them a lesson.
They will be quiet for a while.
Yeah, I was so scared.
What would I have done without you?
What a suck-up.
Wait. Are you okay?
You're not overdoing it, are you?
You might collapse.
You feel a little warm too.
That's it. We're going to the hospital.
Okay, let us go.
A fresh start calls
for a proper introduction.
Introduction? To who?
Let us go see your grandfather. Together.
How are you feeling?
The doctor says recovery is going well,
but your memory still hasn't all returned.
I'm sure it'll come back eventually.
And if it doesn't, so be it.
It doesn't bother me.
You should keep an eye on the chairman.
I have a feeling he is up to something.
His memory loss seems like a total lie.
The way the police and the media
are all moving at once,
I suspect it wasn't
just Mr. Cha acting alone.
As long as you're okay with it, Uncle.
For now, just focus on your recovery.
And stay away from the news for a while.
Okay.
Good.
You know there's no rush, right?
What's with the urgency all of a sudden?
You said your grandfather
wanted to see me.
Well, I mean, it's not like
he wanted to see you right this second.
Look who decided to show up together.
Have you already forgotten?
I believe I asked you
to stay away from this hospital room.
Haven't you heard?
I don't listen to anyone.
If you care about Uncle's health,
you'll watch what you say.
There's no need for him to hear
about all the trouble at the company.
The elderly can leave us in a flash.
Let them in.
If you have half a brain,
you'll hear what I'm saying.
Wait here. I'll let him know you're here.
I really owe you a lot, Ms. Shin.
Every time I'm in a bind, there you are.
Enjoy your visit with Uncle.
Stop.
A word?
Are you sure it's okay for us
to be alone like this?
Se-gye is the jealous type.
Having fun?
Toying with people.
I don't do this for fun.
It's about survival for me too.
I have nothing against you, Ms. Shin,
so don't hate me too much.
I've staked my entire future
on this resort business, after all.
Right. The ends justify the means.
I once knew someone just like that.
Someone exactly like you.
And what happened to him?
Did he achieve his goal?
He did.
He ascended a blood-soaked throne
and treated his people like cattle.
Before withering away and dying all alone.
Yet history recorded him as a sage king.
Since it was written by the victor.
Shall I…
tell you a little secret about life?
Good fortune and bad karma
always find their way back to you.
What goes around
comes around without fail.
And your reckoning is only just starting.
Is that a curse?
It means I will no longer
stand idly by and just watch.
Enduring it once was enough.
In this life,
I shall protect my people and myself,
no matter what.
A declaration of war, I see.
We shall see
if you can indeed protect
everyone you wish.
Barging in at this hour
without any notice.
Who said you could come see me?
I never ask you for anything.
All you have to do is nod and smile.
It's not that hard, is it?
You get out.
Who knows what you might say?
I'm not going anywhere.
Do as Grandfather says and wait outside.
Listen, if he says anything crazy,
come out immediately.
Why that rotten punk…
I don't like you, young lady.
You have no parents,
and you're all alone
with no one to rely on.
You're not right for my Se-gye.
And my opinion on that hasn't changed.
I understand.
I felt the same way until recently.
But…
I just could not help it.
Now that I have been given a new life,
I cannot even imagine my life
without Cha Se-gye.
I never want to let go of his hand.
Fine. If you've made up your mind,
why did you come to me?
- Did you come to inform me?
- Yes, I came to inform you.
That I am going to make
your grandson happy.
I will never
leave him alone again.
You can trust me.
Sir, Detective Cho is here.
Jurisdiction was suddenly transferred
to Seobu Police Station.
They say it came from above.
I suspect someone higher than the chief.
I'm sure it'll come back eventually.
And if it doesn't, so be it.
Someone higher…
The way things stand,
if the investigation expands,
it'll be hard to contain.
Worst-case scenario,
we're looking at prosecution.
Best to tie up loose ends now.
Yes.
I suppose it is time to tie them up now.
Let us see this through!
Just look at her.
Look at that venom in her eyes.
Oh my goodness.
She's about to give me nightmares.
- She's not scary.
- You wench!
I think she's just beautiful.
You still recognize your granddaughter?
Even in that state,
you still only have eyes for her.
The vixen has turned into an angel.
The vixen has arrived.
Oh my, when did you get here?
Your granddaughter's here.
An angel in the flesh.
- An angel?
- Yeah.
Not a vixen?
I will tear you limb from limb!
We shall see, Your Majesty.
- Grandma.
- Yeah?
What are you looking at?
Do you see something?
A stop.
A bus stop.
Why are you in such a rush to leave
when I just got back?
There is so much I want to tell you.
You are so eager to leave.
Your granddaughter is here. Say something.
You could at least look at me.
What is this?
A glamping date. Awesome, right?
At this point, call it a house on wheels.
Why put wheels on a house?
Fleeing a war?
It's not the Korean War.
Why would we flee?
Want to go watch the stars with me?
As if I thought
we'd be able to see stars in Seoul.
You'd have to go to at least
Gangneung or Sokcho to maybe see a few.
Why go so far?
This yard is so spacious.
I think it is great.
Yeah, what a great view
of apartment buildings.
Sitting here by the fire like this
reminds me of when I was young.
Once, a tiger appeared,
and I had to run for my life.
I fell into a lake and almost died.
Seriously? Right now?
That's what you want to talk about? Now?
I am just saying
this is worlds apart from back then.
It is warm in front of the fire,
and I have you next to me.
Jeez.
Through a lifetime of breathless twists
and turns, here I am at last.
It feels like I am in a dream.
I still cannot believe it
if I am being honest.
That I have returned.
That this is my home.
Just imagine what I'm going through.
I even dream about it every night.
Are you still having those dreams?
Forget it.
He's a moron.
I'm different from that guy.
Yes, you are.
You are a different person.
The first person who saw the good in me
and filled my empty heart.
When I think of you,
I feel like I could fly.
Then I suddenly fear losing you.
My heart skips for you
dozens of times a day.
But I do not hate it.
Could this be love?
The thing people call love…
Could this be it?
Hey, are you trying to steal my thunder?
Men are supposed to say
that kind of thing first.
Who cares about gender?
Do not be such a traditionalist.
This doesn't count. I'm doing it over.
I'll throw money at it
and make it the most romantic--
You just do whatever you want now?
Even at home--
Even on the lips--
I shall do what I wish now.
I told you, use it or lose it. Did I not?
Jeez!
Stop it.
Please just stop.
- Do it inside!
- He said we should go inside.
You can go inside
and rub salt in my wound from afar.
Does that mean I can sleep over?
Jeez. He makes it sound like
we rubbed it in his face.
He just popped up out of nowhere.
We had no choice but to come inside.
Yeah, no choice at all.
- What? Is the boiler off?
- What?
Is it broken?
You slept in here?
Why? What is the issue?
Are you trying to freeze to death in here?
How is it colder inside?
It feels like springtime in here.
Do not be a baby.
Back in the mountains,
during one harsh winter,
I was sure my nose would fall off.
That's enough of that.
We're going to my place right now.
How can we? We have been drinking.
Oh right.
You were really downing it.
Gosh.
Cha Se-gye.
Get in here. Let us share.
No. I'm not cold in the slightest.
I run hot, you see.
Just a ball of fire.
Yeah, right. Your nose is bright red.
Freeze. Hands up.
- What?
- Arms up. All the way.
What?
How is that? Warmer now?
Seriously, who asks for a hug
by telling someone to "Freeze"?
It is because
you have the face of a bandit.
What is it?
It's nothing, sir.
You had a lot to deal with recently.
Why don't you take some time off
and go on a trip?
A trip, sir?
Take a few days, go overseas,
clear your head.
Consider it a bonus vacation.
Also, starting tomorrow,
you don't need to pick up Seo-jun.
Just keep guard
over the Chairman's hospital room.
SONGJIN GENERAL HOSPITAL
She must be at the bus stop again.
Maybe I should have bought a bigger one?
Gosh.
You're here.
We were just about to call you.
Is she at the bus stop again?
Her condition has rapidly deteriorated.
We moved her to the ICU.
She had a sudden seizure
and was transferred to the ICU.
We barely stabilized her with medication.
She's held on well, all things considered.
You listen to me carefully.
As you go through life,
there will be torrential rains
and bolts of lightning.
When that happens,
don't just try to shield her
with an umbrella.
Stand with her and face the storm.
As long as you have one person
to walk with you,
you can endure it.
Can I trust you?
You have to protect her, no matter what.
You can't die before her either.
Understood.
Yes.
I will protect her.
I promise.
Go get some sleep. I can stay here.
No. Who knows when she'll wake up?
You should just go.
How can I leave you here alone?
Then stay here. I'll get you
some fresh clothes and some food.
Grandma.
Grandma, are you awake? Are you okay?
The doctor… Should I call the doctor?
The doctor…
The bus…
stop…
Stop…
The bus stop…
You want to go to the bus stop?
The bus…
Where is it going?
Where…
am I going?
Why do you keep saying you are leaving?
You cannot go now.
There is no time.
Grandma.
- Where am I going…
- Grandma.
Just a minute. Hold on.
Just wait a second.
Just a second. Okay?
Grandma.
You are on your way…
On your way to…
Grandma, you look great today.
I know. I'm feeling great today.
Should we make a run for it?
Make a run for it? Right now?
Yes, right now.
Quickly.
- Hold on!
- Hey!
- Where's the guardian?
- What the…
- Oh my gosh, ma'am!
- What is this?
We sneak out of the hospital room.
Stop them!
Oh no.
- Ma'am!
- Miss!
They start chasing after us.
- Ma'am!
- But we lose every single one of them.
- Where are they? Damn it.
Ma'am!
- Go. Let's go!
- Let us go!
No one can stop us.
A bus is waiting for us at the stop.
You get behind the wheel, and we go.
Here we go.
This is so nice.
The sky is so clear.
And I've got my granddaughter with me.
We drive on the mountain road,
passing cars.
When we drive really fast,
the wind just rushes by.
Every time we stop at a bus stop,
people see us and cheer.
Clapping and laughing.
Come on, hop on.
- Welcome.
- Where have you been?
- Ma'am!
- It's been a while!
It's so good to see you all.
- Hey there.
- Hello.
So, where are you off to today?
We're going somewhere nice.
Let's go!
Yes, right! Here we go!
Let's go, Grandma!
- Let's go!
- We're off!
Come on, sing us a song!
A song! A one, a two!
A one, two, three, four!
The sun will shine bright again someday
Hey!
I came here with a dream
Yes, I have come
Hey!
Forget all your sadness and your pain
There's nothing you can't do
If you just try
The sun will shine bright again someday
Hooray!
And so,
just like that, everyone…
happily gets on the bus.
Happily…
Happily.
And we…
drive and drive some more
to arrive at the end of the world.
There are no tears or sadness there.
Everyone blesses you with a smile.
Saying you did well, that you worked hard.
That this life was a success.
Of course.
It was a success.
This life…
I hit the jackpot.
And that is how you go back.
To the place you came from.
Back to your true self.
Smiling and happy.
You're here.
My sweet girl.
Grandma!
Grandma.
Grandma…
Seo-ri's here.
Seo-ri's here…
Grandma.
Seo-ri's here.
Seo-ri…
- Mom!
Seo-jun.
- Hello.
- Bye.
- Bye. See you.
Your sitter was busy.
- You'll be with me today.
- Okay.
Hello, sir.
What about Seo-jun? Is he asleep already?
No, he's not home yet.
- What do you mean?
- The sitter said
that your driver picked him up.
Pull all CCTV around the school
and track them down.
Search everywhere Seo might be.
AIDE SEO
Where are you right now?
At the hospital with the Chairman.
Why there? Why!
The Chairman said he wanted
to see Seo-jun.
Uncle,
what do you think you're doing?
What? Is it wrong for a grandfather
to want to see his grandson?
You should've brought him
as soon as he came back to Korea.
If it weren't for Aide Seo,
I would've never known.
Are you threatening me right now?
Why would you go this far,
involving Seo-jun like this?
Yes,
I knew long ago
that you had a black heart.
But I never knew
the darkness ran this deep.
It was my mistake
to trust an animal like you
with my legacy.
You're not even human.
So why should I treat you like one?
Even beasts cherish
and protect their young.
Don't you know someone else's child
is just as precious?
Why do you keep going after a child
who grew up without his parents' love?
There is a limit to my patience!
If he's so precious to you,
why didn't you look after him sooner?
The scars you get as a child
last a lifetime.
It hurts so much
when you see your child fall.
Earlier, it felt like all the blood
was draining from my body.
If you hate me,
you should have just hit me directly.
Why would you go after my child?
Your threat…
was loud and clear.
And you crossed a line you shouldn't have.
What happens now is all on you, Uncle.
Bear the consequences.
SEORI'S NOODLE SHOP
She never even wore them.
Saving something like this…
She shouldn't have saved them.
Are you going to keep this up?
Not eating or sleeping.
Are you just going to stay like this?
If you have no appetite,
maybe some fruit will help.
I'll be back.
It may look ordinary,
but this painting holds two secrets.
In the Joseon era,
it was rare for a woman's face
to be preserved in a portrait.
This was due to the Confucian belief
in the separation of men and women.
So this painting was done in secret.
By the hand of her lover.
What is it?
There were terrible rumors.
THE SEONGHYEON PAVILION DIARY
She says that when a demon harbors
a tender heart, it can only end badly.
But she says the lovers
who had their time cut short 300 years ago
will soon be reunited. Like fate.
Silent night, holy night.
It's Christmas Eve.
Tonight is finally the last night
the ill-omened star
will be visible from Earth.
Is this really how it ends?
My goodness.
The word "last" always seems…
Oh please. Please, no.
Your Highness, please return to us.
Silent night, holy night.
It's Christmas Eve.
Tonight is finally the last night
the ill-omened star
will be visible from Earth.
The word "last" always seems to leave
a certain wistfulness behind.
It seems the ill-omened star also wants
to leave us with a meaningful farewell.
GRANDFATHER
- Thank you.
- In the night sky tonight,
they say a meteor shower will appear
as the comet disappears.
Maybe we could briefly join the stars
on their final journey
as they pour down like rain?
Perhaps this Christmas Eve
will be one you'll never forget.
Excuse me.
Damn it.
She'll be waiting for me…
Your Highness, please return to us.
Do not die, Cha Se-gye.
You cannot die, Cha Se-gye! Do not die!
Do not die, Cha Se-gye!
His blood pressure's dropping.
85 over 55, pulse 130.
Ma'am, you need to wait outside.
Sir!
His pressure's still dropping.
Heart rate, 120.
- He's in cardiac arrest.
- Start CPR.
He will not die.
Your Highness.
You are…
- not the fortuneteller.
- Do not worry.
You can save him.
If you, Your Highness,
sever the chain of fate.
The chain of fate?
Your beloved is fated to die,
be it in Joseon or here.
So you must go back
and save the Grand Prince.
Then this fate will not be repeated.
You only have to pay a small price.
Tell me.
What is the price?
I will pay any price!
Even at the cost
of never returning here again?
I can never return?
No.
You will not be able to return.
Never again to this place.
It really is shining.
Now that I am with you.
You're the only one, Shin Seo-ri.
I will make sure you are not alone.
You can trust me.
Cha Se-gye.
Let us grow old together.
MY ROYAL NEMESIS
You can save him.
If you, Your Highness,
sever the chain of fate.
I am back in Joseon.
I heard you were once assigned
to Seonghyeon Pavilion.
Your Majesty wishes to send me
to the Grand Prince?
He is still alive. I can save him.
You must not drink that. It is poison!
I was used as bait.
Who do you think you are?
Where is Shin Seo-ri?
What, can you not find her?
Did she run away?
Can't you please stop making me wait?
I can't breathe,
Shin Seo-ri.
I will
save you this time.
Subtitle translation by Justin S. Kim