We'll get you!
Just watch!
Shake it off.
Go! Go! Go!
Defense! Defense!
Finish them!
Girl, you're here!
Did you catch
that final clutch?
He killed it! Look!
Awesome.
I'm not feeling well.
I should probably go.
Jesus!
You're bleeding!
I just tripped.
No way.
Let's go. I got ya.
I'm fine.
Go back to Jiang Fan.
Hey,
didn't see you back there.
I crushed them.
That's awesome.
We're grabbing food.
You coming?
Me?
Gotta go back to work,
so I'll have to pass.
Are you gonna run from me forever?
Who did this to you?
I just tripped...
Cut the cr*p.
Who did this to you?
It's fine...
I asked you a question!
Who did this?!
Luo He...
Take it easy, dude!
Watch the road!
You're dead, man!
Get his a**!
Get him!
Wreck him!
Let's go!
Why did you
even get on the court
with him?
No, not him!
It was that big guy!
He just charged and tackled him!
He kept punching him!
- Damn right!
- So not true!
He started it!
He's lying!
Who the hell are you pointing at?
I saw it, you jerk!
Officer,
she's making stuff up.
They're the ones who jumped us.
What's the deal
with you two, really?
Unbelievable.
Asked you before,
got nothing.
You're hurt now, and still nothing.
No, it's not...
So how'd you bang up your head?
You couldn't just run?
You dodge me fine.
Why not him?
I messed up my foot...
He did that to your foot, too?
The cops are here!
- OK.
- Don't lose it.
Lu Xixiao?
All of you,
come with me.
Don't be a dumbass
next time.
Call the cops.
He plays dirty as hell.
I let it slide on the court,
but he's jumping us...
Drop it, man.
We just left the precinct.
Bon appetit, sweetheart.
Thanks.
Mood's a little sour, huh?
You kids fighting?
Not at all.
Young blood,
hot temper...
Listen, son.
A real man,
no matter what,
never takes it out on his girl.
Show some class.
I'm amazing to her.
Clearly not good enough.
Hey...
Here, let me.
Thanks, really...
Which foot?
It's fine, really.
Tell me.
Right one...
Don't dodge me any more.
Have it your way.
Thanks...
You think that's the word
I wanted to hear?
I won't shut you out again.
But there are secrets
I need to keep.
Can you just let them go?
Please?
No more running, huh?
Anything like this happens again,
you let me know.
No secrets.
Nobody touches you,
got it?
They don't scare me.
Honest...
Still sore?
It's fine now...
It's totally messed up.
Fine, it hurts...
Why'd you always have to play tough?
Hop on.
Which block?
That one.
Just drop me here...
Seriously...
Hold on.
It's so cramped here...
Sorry...
This is far enough.
Right here...
Change the dressing, OK?
You alone?
Where's your grandma?
I lied...
She's still in the hospital.
Lu Xixiao!
Thank you...
[Dad,]
[am I a horrible girl?]
[I gotta save Grandma,]
[but I don't want to]
[hurt him in the process.]
[If this is a sin,]
[let me suffer alone.]
[Wan,]
[how many more lies]
[are you gonna feed me?]
[How many times will you]
[rip my heart apart?]
["Hope these make you smile."]
[From Ms. Zhou.]
[Wan,]
[if this is really]
[how you want it,]
[I'll play along.]
[Your secret stays safe.]
Grandma,
once I pack up,
I'll bring it all to you.
Just wait for me,
OK?
The hell are you doing here?
Find the wrench yet?
Why are you here?
It's dying.
Fix it.
Did you forget to water it?
Lilies need a lot
this time of year.
One sec.
I'll write it down for you.
Lilies are a one-shot deal.
Since they're already trashed,
you'll have to wait till next year.
Snip the dead ones off,
like this,
then add fresh feed.
Here.
When the stalk goes yellow,
cut back the water,
or skip it.
By winter,
new buds form.
Are you even listening?
How's that foot?
Change the dressing?
I did...
Did you catch everything?
Nope.
Run it by me again.
Forget it.
Just stick to the notes.
Hey,
got a flashlight?
Coming!
Any luck?
Almost there.
You need a tutorial,
or should a real man take over?
He's good at this.
You're keeping track of his skills?
His pipes are always busted.
He's got
all the gear.
I'm also great at keeping things alive.
So he's your go-to guy
whenever something breaks?
I called a plumber,
but he's swamped today.
Tomorrow's the soonest...
I know your place inside out.
Just call me next time.
All good?
God, you're soaked!
Here, dry off!
The plumbing's too old.
Rusted through,
probably bent.
Let me.
It's not the pipe.
It's the joint at the valve.
Water doesn't care who got there first.
It flows where it belongs.
He really fixed it!
You're dripping wet.
You need a dry shirt.
You keeping some guy's clothes here?
I can lend you something.
Let me whip up some lunch.
My treat,
to thank you both.
You wanna eat in a puddle?
My place.
I'll help you
clean up after.
Got food in the fridge,
or should I grab some?
It's full. Take whatever.
What are you making?
Your signature
chicken?
I'll whip up whatever's there.
Get ready to be amazed!
Put this on.
It's brand new.
Use my room.
That's the two of us, way back.
I'll get you a new shirt.
Don't bother.
Funny, me winding up at your place.
I did it for her.
You stay wet,
she'll feel guilty.
You're pretty protective of her.
Got a thing for her?
Xixiao! Can you handle spicy?
You guys aren't starting beef, are you?
Nah.
Cool. Keep bonding.
Listen...
Something on my face?
No, it's just...
you don't look like
yourself in that.
Kinda adorable.
You sure you didn't
order delivery?
Just admit I'm a chef.
This is fire.
Here.
I've got it.
Wan, sweetie.
Mrs. Jiang.
Mom, you're home early.
I called in sick
today.
Oh, got a guest?
What are you doing here?
Jiang Yan,
explain. Now.
Mrs. Jiang,
my pipes burst.
He's just our classmate.
He was just helping out.
Son, show him out.
I won't have him here!
The Lus are rotten to the core!
You won't see me again.
I should leave too, Mrs. Jiang.
So...
Nothing you want to ask me?
you know the whole story?
On his birthday,
I saw him with your father.
[Jiang Yan!]
[I was just having dinner with my dad.]
I'm so sorry...
If you hadn't come over,
that scene wouldn't have happened.
I've got plenty of people to hate.
You're nowhere near the list.
We got so much!
I'm glad you're into art,
sweetie.
Ridiculous, isn't it?
He's six months older than me.
Is that the reason
you two fought back then?
That's only part of it.
See ya.
Hey...
Don't let your past
define your future.
Is that actual concern?
Yes, it is...
It'd better come from the heart.
Right,
my flowers.
Keep it alive.
Honestly,
it has a better shot with you.
Typical.
Off to the hospital?
Need to check on Grandma.
What did Luo He want with you?
Just typical street punks.
Spot a girl,
start pawing at her.
Did he come after you
after the game?
No.
He doesn't do the collections.
His goons handle it.
Hey,
short on money these days?
It's all sorted.
C'mon, Grandma's waiting.
I'm coming.
Out of everyone at school,
you choose to
run with a Lu?!
I'm cutting ties with him.
Don't you ever forget
how they
humiliated us!
[Zhongyue is done]
[with you.]
[Walk away.]
[We will never]
[return to this place.]
I know.
Good.
If Wan wants to
throw herself at those bastards,
let her!
She's not that kinda girl.
Wake up.
You think a fancy college degree
makes you set for life?
If you stay a nobody,
who
do you think
she'll pick?
Here's good.
I'll take it in.
Thanks.
Y'know, Might as well
introduce myself to her.
Though I look like
a total dork in this.
She'll probably think
you're a perfect angel.
Hey, I can be an angel.
Alright.
Grandma... How long have you been at the door?
How long have you been at the door?
Ma'am.
Who's this handsome boy?
Name's Lu Xixiao.
He's the friend who sent the soup.
Just a friend...
Oh, the soup boy!
Awesome!
Come on in, kid.
Brought you
another batch today, actually.
Thanks, kiddo.
It's nice
to have some life in here.
Sit.
He got these flowers for you.
Appreciate it, son.
Take a seat.
Huang Xuefen, payment.
Coming!
Time to pay up?
I'll go later.
What,
don't trust me?
Or are you worried
she'll replace you
with me?
Don't get cocky...
Go on.
We'll get to know each other.
Fine.
Go.
I'll be right back.
You're paying a bill,
not flying to the moon.
You alright?
It's nothing, sweetie.
Just the
usual aches.
I'll be fine.
Take a seat.
It'll pass in a second.
Now, Lu...
Xixiao.
Just call me Xixiao, please.
OK,
Xixiao.
It's our
first meeting,
but I need to ask you for a favor.
Anything.
Wan is
a bit of a loner.
Jiang Yan's her only friend.
But there's something
special with you.
So
I'm hoping you'll help me
get her out of her shell.
She's too sweet.
She's always here
instead of being
an 18-year-old.
She deserves to
live her life.
So please,
be there for her.
Take her out to see the world.
Absolutely.
Bless you, son.
Hello, Mrs. Huang.
Got a visitor?
Quite a looker.
Let us through,
please.
Make yourself comfortable.
Mrs. Huang,
things are getting a bit tricky.
After consulting
with the board,
we believe
you need
a kidney transplant.
A new kidney...
That must cost a lot.
Honestly, it's a lot of money.
What's the damage?
About 300 grand.
300 grand...
Can we skip it?
Look at yourself.
You can't skip this.
[Hey, Doc!]
[What's up, kid?]
[How's she]
[doing?]
[Relax.]
[If she gets]
[the transplant,]
[she's got a real shot at making it.]
[When will it happen?]
[As soon as they can]
[clear the bill.]
[She did say]
[she was asking her mom to cover the bill.]
[She's Guo Xiangling's]
[own kid.]
[God knows]
[what game]
[they're playing.]
[Why the hell are you here?]
[Short on money these days?]
[It's all sorted.]
[I've told you everything already.]
[Can you just let them go?]
[I did something unforgivable...]
[I hate myself for it...]
[But I've crossed the point of no return.]
B*tch...
you're behind all this!