Come in.
What's up?
Shall we continue tomorrow?
What?
Didn't you say you'd help me?
Well,
I don't
know where to go anyway.
Jiang Fan said he has an idea.
Gu Meng's coming too.
Where?
You in or not?
I'm in.
It's so cool here.
How did you think of
coming to the amusement park?
Well, inspiration
comes from joy.
Isn't an amusement park
the happiest place in the world?
Just admit it you wanted to ask Meng out.
- No.
- Exactly.
We're just friends. More people, more fun.
You owe me one for this.
You dragged me into this act at midnight.
I had to improvise the whole thing.
I owe you?
Did you hear yourself?
Gu Meng did a way better job than you.
You sprung it on me at midnight.
I...
Give me some credit, I improvised.
Besides,
why
make it so complicated?
Why not just ask her out directly?
That's none of your business.
If I can just ask her out,
why would I need you here?
You owe me a favor,
anyway.
No, I don't.
No way.
What do you mean?
I...
I helped you out.
This is how you repay me?
This is insane!
Awesome!
Is it fun?
Wait for me, Jiang Fan.
Fan, the yellow one.
Hit him!
That one, that one.
Fan, that one.
Hit him.
Don't run.
Still think I suck?
Why are you chasing me?
He's after me.
Xixiao, get him!
Bump him!
You're terrible at this.
You're awful at this.
Hit him, Xixiao!
Think you can get away?
Get him!
Why were you picking on a kid?
Picking on...
You made him cry.
He started it, okay?
I said I wanted the blue one.
He wouldn't let me have it
and fought me for it.
And...
No more crying, okay?
Here, this is for you two.
Racing King of Pingchuan!
He hit you, too. Didn't you see?
You still gave him candy?
That's the
point of bumper cars.
That's right.
So I bumped him.
I told him
to bring it on.
He kept crashing
into my car and talking trash.
So I hit him back.
Then he started crying.
That kid's got no guts.
I told him
as a boy,
he's got to be brave.
Let's ride the Ferris wheel.
I've wanted to do it since I was little
but never got the chance.
No, wait...
Come on.
Baby, look.
The Ferris wheel's so tall.
Yeah, so tall. It's fun. I'm not scared.
Only cowards get scared.
Excuse me,
it's really windy. Is this safe?
Yes.
It's safe.
Hey, wait, wait.
Come over here first.
It's our turn.
Wait a sec.
You scared?
Who says I'm scared?
Then let's go.
Give me a second,
seriously.
Please, just wait a bit.
The wind seems pretty strong.
The Ferris wheel might shake a bit.
I'm hungry.
Let's go get some popcorn.
Come on.
Sorry.
Seriously? Jiang Fan left you
with the camcorder
while he
went to ride the roller coaster
with Meng.
Now you're stuck here.
It's fine.
This works too.
So,
feeling inspired yet?
Have you decided what to paint?
Tell me,
Zhou Wan,
why do you keep trying to help me?
Do I need a reason?
It'd be weird if I didn't.
I'll give you one more chance.
Tell me the truth.
I'm telling the truth.
You're really bad at lying,
honestly.
No, I...
Do you know
every time you lie,
you stare straight at me
with those big eyes?
Like this,
"I'm telling the truth."
Do I? No, I don't.
Spill it.
I just...
I just want you
to do what you love.
I don't wanna owe you too much.
You've been helping me all along.
The tutoring fees weren't a small amount.
I don't know
if I'm doing this right,
but
I really want to help you.
The camcorder's dead.
You were telling the truth.
So I'll get you flowers.
Are you gonna buy all of them?
You wish.
Have you figured out what to paint?
It's a secret.
Sir,
how about flowers for that lovely lady?
I'll take a bunch. How much?
Ten yuan.
Ten yuan? I'll take that one.
Okay.
More people, more fun.
We're just friends.
He kept crashing and talking trash.
Tell me the truth.
I'm telling the truth.
Spill it.
I just want you
to do what you love.
Come in.
Lu Xixiao,
Jiang Fan...
What's wrong?
What are you doing?
Just painting.
Not very good though.
Jiang Fan said you...
What is it?
You're acting weird.
How am I weird?
Jiang Fan? What about him?
He said
to check your phone.
You haven't replied to him in ages.
Is that so?
He said it's urgent.
You need to go find
him right away.
Stop staring, go on.
Gu Meng, happy birthday.
No, no, no.
That's bad.
My smile looks so fake.
Let's do another one.
Gu Meng, happy birthday.
I...
Happy birthday.
Who are you filming? I'm over here.
Dude, you've been at this forever,
and all you can say
is happy birthday.
Even if I record it,
it's a waste of storage.
You're usually chatty.
How are you stumbling over
a birthday message?
What I want to say is different from yours.
You don't get it.
What do you want to say?
I
kind of,
maybe,
possibly
like Gu Meng.
You...
Are you serious?
You're kind of, maybe,
possibly an idiot.
When did you figure this out?
That day we
all went to the amusement park together.
This is so fun!
Yeah, it's fun.
A grown man scared like that?
You shouldn't even have gotten on.
What a disgrace.
Exactly.
You were screaming behind me,
like a toddler
crying for his mom.
You have the nerve to laugh at him?
You...
Let's go.
She's so cool.
You like her because she stood up for you?
Fine. At least you finally realize it.
You figured it out long ago?
I figured it out before he did.
Then why didn't you tell me?
Why did you
drag us here in such a rush?
I need your help.
Wan,
just say it. Stop dragging it out.
Or I'll get impatient.
I...
I want to ask
if you have a crush.
Sounds like
someone's got a crush herself.
Come on. Who is it?
Let me weigh in.
No, I don't.
Lu Xixiao?
No way.
You don't like him?
Don't change the subject.
So you like him.
No, I'm the one asking you.
Do you like anyone or not?
I like Lu Xixiao.
Look at your face. You care so much.
No way.
Fine.
I wanna share
a theory with you.
See,
the body acts before the heart does.
What do you mean?
It means
whoever you think of
first when you open your eyes,
your body
will naturally gravitate toward him.
It's instinct.
By the time you realize it,
it's too late.
So?
So it means when the time comes,
you'll understand.
After this summer, he and I
won't cross paths again.
When two people first meet,
isn't it too sad to already think
about the ending?
I think
when you're together,
you should cherish every moment.
That way
you won't have too many regrets later.
So if you
feel the same way about me,
this summer,
Gu Meng,
would you be my girlfriend?
How was it? How was it?
How's that?
Just make things clear.
The angle, do I look good?
How's the vibe?
It's alright.
Do I look natural?
You really think it's going to work?
I won't know unless I try.
I can't just keep
being friends
with her.
Aren't you afraid if this fails,
you two can't even be friends anymore?
No.
So your grand plan
is to take her out
for a meal
and show her this video?
More than that.
I'll make her 18th birthday
one she'll
never forget.
Tutor Zhou,
I checked everything out for that day.
There's no one at school that night,
and I've already talked to
the security guard
You'll
bring Gu Meng
straight into the school.
Hello? Hello?
Tutor Zhou,
[can you hear me?]
[I'm already in the gift box.]
[Good.]
Everything's ready on my end.
Just bring Gu Meng into the school.
[Meng,]
wanna go back to our school?
Back to school?
We already graduated. Why go back?
Let's go sing karaoke.
[Come on.]
No, no, no.
Wait.
Tutor Zhou,
find a way to get her in.
[If she doesn't go in,]
[my whole plan is ruined.]
Meng,
we're passing by anyway.
[I haven't been back in so long.]
Yes, yes.
Fine, but there's no way we can get in.
It's summer break.
[You can definitely get in.]
Tutor Zhou,
I've already
told the security guard.
Whatever reason you give,
he'll let you in.
[Quick.]
[Just make something up.]
Let me think.
Just say we're going
back to see our teachers.
Okay, let's go ask.
So? Did you get in?
Thank you.
Thanks.
The school gate
is where
our story began,
where she first wrote my name down.
There'll be wind chimes
hanging in the tree near the gate.
And as you walk in,
every spot
holds a memory of ours.
Look at that.
This is so pretty.
Who did all this?
[It's summer break.]
[No one's even here to see it.]
Exactly. This...
These lights would look nice in a room.
Look at that wind chime.
It's hanging
so low. What if it scratches one's face?
[Meng, wait for me.]
No, why is she leaving?
[I decorated the whole tree,]
[and it looks different from the others.]
[She won't even take a close look?]
Meng, where are you going?
To the field.
Straight to the field?
Don't go there yet.
That part comes later.
There are more surprises up ahead.
To see the surprise
you prepared for me.
What surprise?
There's no surprise.
There is. I knew it.
[Remember to]
[cover my eyes later.]
[I love surprises.]
Slow down, slow down.
Please. I'm begging you.
The big moment comes
when she gets to the center of the field.
That's when you come in.
I'll be standing here.
Then you pull me over.
Quick.
Pull me over.
Then you
hand me the gift
and push me toward her.
Gu Meng,
happy birthday.
No way.
I can't do it.
Why not?
It must've been 35 degrees that day,
and you want me to wear this?
You'd be killing me, man.
Plus, I've got other things to do.
What could
be more important than this?
My portfolio.
I need to polish it
before I meet the professor.
That is important.
It's fine.
I'll just
ask the security guard
to do me a favor.
[Hey, where are you?]
[The captain's looking for you!]
I...
I'm in the bathroom.
I'll be right there.
Hello?
Dude?
Pick up.
Where did he go?
Even worse than Lu Xixiao?
I...
Great, my phone died.
Hello? Anyone there?
Stupid feet. Don't step around.
There's barely enough air in here.
Is anyone out there?
Hello? Can anyone here me?
I'm trapped in here!
Help!
Security!
What's this about?
Almost there.
Three,
two,
one.
Wan, you set all this up?
Please watch the video.
Is anyone out there?
I don't wanna die.
Help.
Relax, you're not going to die.
Xixiao?
Xixiao,
I knew
you wouldn't leave me hanging.
Quick, push me over there.
Stop crying.
Don't tell anyone
I came to rescue you today,
or you're finished.
This was all Jiang Fan's idea, right?
You guys are too good to me!
This is so beautiful!
How much did you spend on all this?
All these flowers
and this huge box.
Did you get me a car?
I love it!
Jiang Fan, you're dead!
How long have you been hiding this?
Take this.
Hey, hey, wait.
Let me see you.
Let's check out the birthday gift first.
Gu Meng,
happy birthday.
It wasn't supposed to be like this.
It's okay, it's okay.
The cake was beautiful.
It's all melted now.
It looks terrible.
It's beautiful!
You...
No, it's not.
Sir.
- Let's leave them alone.
- The box isn't right either.
- Let's go.
- I messed up.
It's pretty cool.
I spent
so much time getting
this box custom-made.
Alright, alright.
I even spent all my gift money on it.
It's cool. Really.
The fog machine broke.
It kept going off inside.
I couldn't
breathe in there at all.
Today was supposed to
be perfectly romantic.
It's romantic.
It's a great surprise. It's cool.
Sir,
why are you still here?
The school gate's that way.
Let me walk you out.
Are you hot?
Let me buy you a bottle of water.
It's hot.
Wearing that thing can't be easy.
I'll get you some water, so you can
cool off a bit.
Why not take the mascot head off?
It must be so stuffy.
Aren't you burning up?
Fine. There's a convenience store ahead.
I'll go buy you a bottle of water.
How's the cake?
A little melted,
but still good.
Gu Meng,
I like you.
Can we be together?
No.
Why?
You're always acting on impulse.
You say you like me
and blow so much money
setting this up.
How are you going to provide for me?
I...
I spent all my money on you.
Besides,
we'd be
doing long distance.
I don't want a long-distance relationship.
I...
I can fly over to
see you whenever I have time.
No.
Having trouble opening that can?
Let me help.
Didn't you say you weren't coming?
Jiang Fan begged me
to come.
How did you know it was me?
There's no
security guard at school as tall as you.
This mascot costume does suit you.
Thanks.
Did he succeed?
Hard to say.
What about your portfolio?
Yeah,
the portfolio.
Jiang Fan was supposed
to return the favor,
but he's gone,
Guess that falls on you then.
Let's head back first.
What are you doing? Just take a cab.
That's a waste of money.
We can get some fresh air this way.
I can't ride this thing.
You can ride a motorcycle
but not this?
I'm just not used to
riding on the back.
Drop the act.
I've given you a ride before.
Get on.
Can you actually ride this thing?
You're questioning my skills?
You're too heavy.
Too heavy? Me?
Hold on tight.
Slow down on the downhill.
Such a good moment.
Look at the camera.
What are you doing?
Let me take a picture.
Delete it.
There's a little antenna on your helmet.
See?
Hey.
Look this way.
Where's your helmet?
You call that a helmet?
I can't see with it on.
Don't you know you can't carry
passengers on scooters?
I'm so sorry, officer.
It won't happen again.
I'm so sorry.
Again?
No, there won't be.
Hand me the helmet.
This place is beautiful.
Not bad, right?
Xixiao?
What brings you here?
Mr. Li.
It's been a while.
You've gotten even taller.
Go sit over there.
I'll get you drinks.
Okay.
Have a seat.
Here.
Have some soda.
Thank you.
You treat us to drinks every time.
How do you even make money?
You
sent Muyi so many things before
and wouldn't take any money.
Besides, you brought a friend today.
It's the least I can do.
Mr. Li, can I have a look around inside?
Sure, make yourself at home.
Thanks.
How have you been lately?
Pretty good.
Same old, huh?
Yeah. Nothing's changed.
Are you here to paint today?
There are so many paintings in here.
They're beautiful.
Xixiao's mom
painted all of them.
Boss!
Coming.
Wait a second.
This way. Have a seat.
You came here a lot when you were little?
Yeah, pretty often.
Stop looking.
The boy in that painting is you, right?
Don't ask.
I can tell your mom
really loved you.
It's a lie.
A lie?
She still left me here
all alone.
Xixiao, help me out.
What happened?
Shall we get another one from the shop?
My dad said he's not restocking
this week.
This is the last one
in his shop.
Perfect, then.
Muyi, you're too little to fly a kite.
It can be dangerous.
Let's play with water instead.
I don't want that.
I want my kite.
Xixiao,
please climb up and get it for me.
Please!
I...
Zhou Wan?
Just leave the climbing to me.
Careful!
Be careful.
What should you call me?
Wan.
You've got this!
Take it slow.
You're amazing!
I got it.
You got the kite.
You're so cool!
Be careful, Muyi.
Got it.
God, you scared me.
Thank you.
Run, run, run!
So high.
It's up!
Watch this.
I've never seen
Xixiao this relaxed before.
And this is the first time
he's brought anyone here.
I can tell
he really likes you.
Really?
His mom
used to bring him here
to paint that big hackberry tree.
After things happened to his family,
he was left on his own.
He'd sit under that tree for a whole day.
He was so lonely.
I asked him but he said nothing.
But I can see
he's a lot more open now.
If his mom
could see him like this,
she'd be so happy.
I...
I'll go join him for a bit.
Go ahead.
So have you figured out
what to paint for
Professor Qin?
Kind of.
It's still the same scenery,
but I
feel like I can paint
in a way my mom never did.
Is there anything I can do to help?
Then I'll leave you to it.
Just stay here with me.
What was
your mom like?
I barely remember.
I get it.
Sometimes I
can't quite remember
my dad's face either.
Whenever that happens,
I get so scared.
I'm scared that one day
I'll really forget him.
His voice,
the traces he left in my life,
they're fading.
But the older I get, the more certain
I am that he loved me.
Maybe it's just because
your memory is blurry.
Sometimes the blurrier the memory,
the more we tend to romanticize...
That's not it.
Actions don't lie.
If you truly didn't believe
your mom loved you,
why would you miss her so much
and keep coming back here?
You're done?
What did you draw?
What do you think?
You're my inspiration.