Zhou Wan.
Thanks for today.
Good night.
You've lived here a while now.
Getting used to it?
How's Grandma?
I've set aside
the rest of the money.
Also,
I asked around for you.
About the kidney donor,
we can arrange it later.
See?
Everything I promised you,
I've delivered.
What about you?
Helping that Lu Xixiao
with his portfolio?
What are you thinking?
Zhou Wan, I'm coming in.
What are you doing here?
Nothing.
You two got back so late.
I just wanted to check on her.
Get some rest.
Don't stay up.
Off to bed now.
Night.
Forgot to give you this.
For me?
What about Professor Qin?
This one's not for him anyway.
It's for you.
You drew this for me?
Come on.
It's no big deal.
What did she just say to you?
Nothing really.
Just said
I haven't been studying much lately,
just checking up on me.
Did she give you a hard time?
No. She's my sponsor,
why would she?
Haven't gotten to study properly lately.
I'm gonna study for a while,
you go back and rest.
Alright.
Sleep well.
Oh right,
Jiang Fan wants us to hang out tomorrow.
You head over first,
I need to sort out
the drawings for the professor.
Okay.
He heard everything?
He didn't.
Why did he come to see you?
It's none of your business.
I have a feeling
you've got a crush on Lu Xixiao.
You look more nervous than I am.
No wonder.
You like him,
that's why you're always opposing me.
I advise you
to send him away for good.
Don't come any closer.
Or I'll tear it up.
Who drew this?
Answer me.
He did.
What's it for?
It's
for Professor Qin.
You've got some nerve.
Just tell him Ms. Chen
tossed it by accident.
Are these skewers done?
What's wrong? You seem distracted.
I'm fine.
No, you're not.
Probably just worn out lately.
After that night,
did you two get together?
No.
He's so impulsive.
Why date him just 'cause he confessed?
That'll be long-distance.
He owes me a plan for
how we'll make this work.
So you didn't turn him down?
I do like him,
a tiny bit.
But I can't just go along with his whims.
Only a tiny bit?
Yeah.
What's it like getting confessed to?
Why do you wanna know that?
I'm only human, after all.
Everyone gets silly
when they're crushing on someone.
Didn't I tell you? Your body reacts
before your brain when you like someone.
What nonsense.
What "body reacts before the brain"?
Were you eavesdropping on us?
It means I didn't think it through.
- I just...
- I came for the skewers.
I wasn't eavesdropping.
I want some of this
and just happened to walk by.
Watch out, don't bump into him.
Stop messing around, okay?
I want this one.
It's alcohol. It's not for kids.
I'm not a kid,
I'm an adult now.
Thanks.
What for?
The drawing I gave you.
I couldn't have finished it without you.
You like it?
Yeah.
Glad you do.
What does being drunk feel like?
Nothing special.
You just get wasted.
Once drunk,
all joys and sorrows fade away.
We've got enough skewers.
Stop grilling, come hang inside.
Go inside, I'll handle the grill.
Need me to take over?
Just take a seat.
I've got this.
Wanna try some?
For me?
You're eighteen now.
It's fine to have a sip.
Don't tell anyone I gave this to you.
It's so good.
Of course.
Ms. Chen,
these two silk garments
need hand-washing.
Got it.
This is...
Xixiao's.
Where'd he go?
I don't know.
Wan went with him?
That's good.
He's usually a loner.
But ever since Wan came,
he's got someone to keep him company.
Yeah.
Off you go.
Zhou Wan,
you lied to me.
So pretty.
One, two, three, four, five.
Follow your...
She's drunk, isn't she?
Who gave her alcohol?
One, two, three, four, five.
Let's...
You've been drinking, right?
Did you drink?
You gave it to her, didn't you?
You did it?
Ping, you gave it to her?
Didn't you?
Not me. I had gloves on.
Let's sing together.
I picked this song,
but I don't know how to sing it.
Here, take the mic.
How does this song go?
It hurts.
Lu Xixiao,
my leg hurts.
This one?
Or this one?
You're totally drunk.
My head's just spinning.
Why'd you
drink so much anyway?
Because I'm kind of sad.
What's making you sad?
I did something terrible.
I regret it so much.
But I don't think I can turn back now.
It's like
I sacrificed everything
just for one single thing.
I even turned into a bad person.
But in the end,
I might gain nothing,
and fix nothing at all.
The only thing that changed
is that I've gone rotten.
So what if you're bad?
Don't you hate bad people?
I'm not a good person anyway.
You are a good one.
Lu Xixiao,
you might not realize it,
but you're honest,
kind,
and gentle.
No matter what,
you could never be bad.
Then you have terrible taste in people.
No way.
Everyone I care about is good.
You,
Gu Meng,
you're all such wonderful people.
I adore you all so much.
Talking about this
makes me sad again.
I'm not a kind person.
That's why I wanna treat you well.
If I'm good to you,
does that make up for
some of my mistakes?
Then maybe I'm not
completely awful.
Wan, it's okay even if you're flawed.
Someone will love every version of you.
Lu Xixiao.
Did you bring your portfolio?
Yeah.
You'll definitely pass.
What?
Speak up, I can't hear you.
You'll definitely pass.
Bye.
Wan.
Come take a look.
Aren't these flowers beautiful?
Would they suit my wedding?
As long as you're happy.
Is that how you talk to your elders?
Come here.
I need to talk to you.
What's up?
You aren't gonna invite me
to your wedding, are you?
Nah.
Our deal
is off.
You can move out of here now.
What did you do?
What did I do?
I just finished
what you were supposed to do.
What did you do to the portfolio?
Isn't it lovely?
Zhou Wan.
Stop wasting your time
on the Lu family.
Focus on your studies.
Let's both live our own lives.
If the portfolio's gone,
Lu Xixiao will know
it was you.
You wouldn't dare.
What are you trying to do?
You swapped his portfolio.
You want him to blame me.
Stop.
If you step out that door,
don't expect any more money.
Let go. I don't want your money anymore.
Guo Yan,
our deal is over.
Starting today,
leave Grandma
and me alone.
And stay away from Lu Xixiao.
If you try to stop me,
I'll expose everything,
and drag you down with me.
What's the hold-up?
Don't know.
Probably an accident up ahead.
Drop me off here, thanks.
Hey.
My car won't start.
Fix it for me right now.
Hurry up and fix it.
See for yourself.
My car won't start.
Professor.
- You're...
- Sorry to bother you.
Sorry.
I'm here to deliver
Lu Xixiao's portfolio.
There was a family issue.
He grabbed the wrong one
when he left.
But he put a lot of effort into this.
Please take a look.
I'm sure you can tell
his mindset this time
is different from
last time.
He really wants to keep drawing.
Could you give him another chance?
Don't turn him down straight away.
The pieces are quite good,
but many areas
lack depth,
I'll go over
these flaws with him
once he's out.
Out? Where'd he go?
I haven't seen the pieces he brought.
He asked
if he could draw live
and let me critique it.
I wanted to see
his live creativity
and attention to detail
before discussing further.
Turns out
he's actually
full of creative inspiration.
So you haven't rejected him?
Not yet.
I thought
I'd decide after he finishes drawing.
Great. Thank you.
He should be out soon.
Would you like to wait for him?
I have other things to do.
I won't intrude any longer.
Alright.
Your technique's great,
and your emotions really shine through,
but some parts are over the top.
Learn to tone it down.
This piece feels rushed and frantic.
Understood.
Still, thank you
for giving me this shot, Professor.
Maybe it was the time pressure today.
You couldn't show your full potential.
But your portfolio
carries far richer
emotional depth.
You've looked through my portfolio?
I'd planned to check it later,
but you'd grabbed the wrong folder.
Someone rushed over
to drop it off for you.
Who was it?
A young girl.
Thin and small-framed.
She left right after.
Where'd she go?
She mentioned this morning
she was visiting her grandma.
She's probably still at the hospital.
Wait.
What's this?
Found it on her desk.
It's torn to shreds.
Didn't know
you're into crafts.
Could you knock before coming in?
Didn't wanna interrupt
your creative flow.
Well, well.
A living thing in your room. That's rare.
I mean that potted flower.
I looked into
what you asked about.
Guo Xiangling was married before.
She didn't lie about that part.
But she also has a daughter.
Your good classmate.
Zhou Wan.
What?
Zhou Wan
is Guo Xiangling's biological daughter.
Gotta say,
those two are so calculating.
They're scheming their way
into our family.
One wrong move,
and both you and your dad
would've fallen right into their trap.
She's not like that.
Not like that?
Then why did she lie to you?
God knows what schemes
she's plotting with Guo Xiangling.
This coffee's terrible.
I'll get you some good beans later.
See ya.
Zhou Wan.
So this is
the secret you've been hiding?
Then why'd you help me today
and deliver my portfolio?
Dr. Chen, you're still working?
Wan.
Good news.
The surgery is scheduled.
Thank you so much, Dr. Chen.
- It's my job, don't mention it.
- Thank you.
Thank you so much.
But we need
a partial payment upfront.
If you're free,
come finish the paperwork
tomorrow or the day after.
I know
this sum might be a real burden
for your family.
It's okay.
I've already planned for it.
If you can't cover it,
just let me know.
We can adjust the plan
and switch back
to conservative treatment.
If we stick with
the current treatment plan,
how many more years
will Grandma have left with me...
The surgery has to happen.
You only need to
sign the loan contract.
Mr. Fang.
This is the payment Luo He
collected last month.
Go collect these few.
Yes.
Alright boys,
collect the money.
How much can you lend me?
A hundred thousand.
Two hundred thousand.
But you have no collateral.
How can I lend you that much?
Uncle Fang,
may I call you that?
Grandma came to see you once.
She said you're a straightforward man.
Your grandmother?
Huang Xuefen.
Ten years ago, you let us
live in the old factory building.
We were the ones
paying rent to cover the loan.
Huang Xuefen is your grandmother?
She was a formidable woman.
I remember her well.
Back then,
before I'd made
any real success for myself,
she gave me a meal when I had nothing.
That's why I let your family
keep the place
all those years.
You're a man of honor.
My grandmother and I keep our word too.
I wouldn't come to you again
if I wasn't truly desperate.
Fine.
I'll lend you the amount you asked for.
But think this over carefully.
And bring the signed contract back to me.
I owe Mrs. Huang
this favor.
Right, Ms. Chen,
where's my drawing?
Xixiao saw it the other day.
I asked if he wanted it,
he just took it without a word.
He saw it?
Where are you off to?
Grandma's not doing well.
I need to go home for a few days.
I thought she was still hospitalized?
She's been discharged.
While she's not doing well?
Did I say you could leave?
I just don't wanna stay here anymore, okay?
That's not like you.
You're giving up this easily?
Don't you wanna be my family anymore?
Or keep currying favor with me?
You already know everything, don't you?
There's still stuff I don't know.
You can tell me.
If you say it yourself,
I won't blame you.
I've said all I need to say.
Hey beautiful,
I've been calling you but no answer.
What's going on?
The boss wants to know
your answer.
I'll tell you when I've decided.
Zhou Wan, listen.
You're not the one in control here.
Tomorrow.
I need your answer tomorrow.
Got it?
Zhou Wan.
I can't wait to see
what happens
when I've got you.
You should know...
Luo He, itching for another beating?
Watch how you speak.
Lu Xixiao.
Are you out of your mind?
Why do you pop up everywhere?
Stalker.
Look,
I didn't start anything this time.
He's just here to collect rent.
I'm heading back to work now.
Running from me?
I'm not.
I'll be late for my shift.
"Running from me?"
Stalker.
What do you want with her?
Wanna know?
None of your business.
If you really wanna know,
you'll have to pay a price.
You dare make demands of me?
So no deal then?
Fine.
Let's make a bet.
Name the game.
If I win, you tell me everything.
If I lose,
I'll do anything you ask.
Don't back out.
Go, go, go!
Come on!
What're you staring at, kid?
Take him down!
Score!
Nice shot!
Go, go, go!
Cut the games, a fight
broke out by the basketball court.
Who's fighting?
Luo He and Lu Xixiao.
Basketball match.
Luo He's just playing dirty.
Yeah, let's go check it out.
Okay, let's go.
Can I leave early?
Go ahead.
Don't rush.
Come on, come on, come on!
Foul!
Wait.
What?
What? Foul?
No way. Where's the foul?
Come on, come on!
How's that not a foul?
Hey!
You okay, Ping?
Yeah, fine.
Uncle.
You all right, Ping?
- I can't go on anymore.
- You hurt?
That's a dirty play!
No call on that?
That's how you play ball?
It's fine.
Is that all you've got?
We're here to play ball.
Focus on the game first.
We'll sort this out later.
Come on!
Bring it!
Nice one, Jiang Fan!
First half's over.
Second half,
I'm gonna destroy Lu Xixiao.
What should I drink?
This one.
Look who it is.
Our leading lady.
Play nicely.
No cheap shots.
Me, cheap? How so?
I just don't like you.
And I hate
Lu Xixiao all the same.
I'll make both of you miserable,
mark my words.
Why'd he agree to play you?
Wanna know?
None of your business.
Zhou Wan.
You know what?
You're actually really pretty.
Don't touch me.
You little vixen, you've totally got
Lu Xixiao wrapped around your finger.
All you can say
is gross garbage.
Zhou Wan.
Don't forget.
Your Grandma's life is in my hands.
I didn't forget.
I just feel sorry for you.
Because you'll never
beat Lu Xixiao.
You go through all this trouble
just to beat him once
on a tiny basketball court.
But even if you win,
you won't win fair.
Everyone'll snicker behind your back,
look down on you.
You think
I won't hit a girl?
Chill, bro, come on.
Back off!
Is that so?
I don't think that at all.
Hitting girls is just what you do.
Bro, bro, bro.
Easy, easy.
Come on, bro.
What did you say? Say it again.
Am I scared of him?
You're not.
Am I?
Not one bit.