Xixiao...
you know,
my dad used to say
that the kindest souls
go to a better place.
I'm sure she's
looking down
on you,
still protecting you.
Whatever.
If she saw me acting like a loser,
she'd probably hate it.
Don't say that!
She wouldn't.
She'd be proud!
I promise ya!
She'd love you!
You're a good kid!
Easy there... please...
You like that?
Whoa, hold on...
You hungry?
I'll whip something up for you.
Awesome...
I'm famished.
Move it!
Let's go home.
What are you...
doing with that?
Keeping you company.
Put that down.
I'm gonna teach you a thing or two.
Really?
Babe, I barely know
how to boil water.
Go wash this.
Um...
You good?
Hey,
I'm so clumsy...
I used to bump my head too.
What? Are you a baby?
Too hot?
Let it sit
for a second.
This is fire. Let's eat!
A six-course feast!
We literally
only do this for Christmas!
What's that look?
Nothing.
It's just crazy.
I've been
crashing here alone forever,
and it finally feels like
a real home tonight.
It's only everyday cooking.
But it will
keep you fed when you're
on your own.
Take a bite.
How is it?
Tell me! Is it good?
I swear, this is the best thing
I've ever tasted.
Stop lying!
I mean it.
My chef makes them,
but hers taste
like cardboard.
This is the real deal.
Did you pay attention
to the recipe?
I took mental notes on everything
my beautiful instructor said.
Well, if you get stuck,
there's
always YouTube.
It just takes
a little patience.
You'll master it
eventually.
But you'll probably be
hitting up
fancy spots over there.
You won't even
remember my cheap cooking.
Never.
I'm gonna hold onto
every single detail.
Now eat.
You worked so hard on this.
Have a wing.
The ribs still have my heart.
They both taste fire to me.
They both rule!
Need a hand?
I've got this.
Go on!
Just relax.
I'll be done in a sec.
Sit!
The rag!
Why are you doing this?
Weren't you staying for fine arts?
Nah...
But you wanted to
study under Prof. Qin so badly...
I don't believe
you'd just abandon your passion
for no reason.
I'm just a flake who gets bored easily.
And the bike?
You worked yourself
to the bone
to get it back.
Why dump it now?
Because I wanted to
take some weight
off your shoulders.
It's all I had to offer.
You don't need to help me.
I want you to chase your own dreams.
My dreams don't
mean sh*t
if you're not OK.
You really like them, huh?
I'll give you the keys
before I leave.
You can take over.
Drop by
whenever
you feel lonely.
You're way more
responsible than Jiang Fan.
I promise you,
I'll keep them safe.
It hurts knowing
you're leaving as soon as summer's over.
We didn't even get
a single holiday to hang out.
It's not fair...
We'll have our moment.
Just in case
this is our last summer,
I'm wishing you
a happy everything
right now.
Alright, let's hear it.
Happy New Year, Xixiao.
Merry Christmas, Wan.
Happy Turkey Day!
Happy Labor Day!
Happy Halloween!
Happy Mother's Day.
Happy Fourth of July.
Happy Lunar New Year.
No fair! I already claimed it!
Since when are you the holiday police?
New Year is New Year!
Those are two different...
Happy New Year's Eve!
Happy Wan's Spanking Day!
You're such a jerk!
Happy D-Day!
Yeah, and Happy Cinco de Mayo to you too!
Happy Valentine's Day.
Happy Our Day.
Xixiao...
I don't just want you to be happy on holidays.
I want you
to be happy every single day.
Just be free,
do your art,
and be yourself.
Go be
who you want to be.
I will. For you.
I never actually
showed you around the mansion.
Since I'm trusting you with my keys,
let's make it
official.
My lady.
Whoa, so this is
the whole set.
I haven't finished that one yet.
Your mom...
she loved you with all her heart.
She was just trapped
in a place she couldn't escape,
and she couldn't
see you reaching out for her.
That's why
she let go.
Hey,
would you be
my girlfriend?
If...
if I say yes,
will it make everything better for you?
I think it would...
Don't feel
pressured.
Sleep on it.
No leftovers,
period.
Yeah, yeah.
I'll dump it.
Don't pinch pennies
on your health.
Grandma!
What are you doing up?
Look,
since we're just waiting on a donor,
she's better off at home.
Is she even fit to leave?
Who's gonna do her dialysis?
She's good.
She just has to show up
for her sessions.
Yeah.
Staying in this depressing ward
is only making her worse.
Damn right!
How often does she have to come in?
Every three days.
If you wanted to leave,
you should have
given me a heads-up.
I would've packed your bags.
Why didn't you
tell me?
I'm the grown-up here.
I don't need your OK.
I can make
my own decisions.
I've been losing my mind in here.
And I have a
bridge game waiting for me!
Take the soup.
My bag...
Give'em here.
- OK.
- I'll bring it back.
Alright,
cool.
You get going first.
Let the doc finish his nagging,
then I'm out.
Come home early, OK?
Yeah, I've got
a game to catch.
Now go on.
See, I'm solid.
Alright,
catch you at home.
Be careful out there!
I will, sweetheart.
Are you in pain?
I can manage.
Doc,
promise me
you won't tell her a thing.
My lips
are sealed.
But how are you gonna explain
blowing off the surgery?
She's sacrificed everything for you.
We finally got a match lined up,
and you're just giving up.
It's because
she's busted her a**.
I'm not gonna drag her down with me.
[You home?]
[You still owe me a yes or no.]
[I know.]
[Take your time.]
[I put you on the spot today.]
[I'll ask you properly later,]
[and I want a real answer.]
[We can handle the distance.]
[Just trust me.]
[Sweet dreams.]
Night.
This is her set...
Where are mine?
This is crazy...
Did you lose something?
My keys.
I swear they were here...
Take your meds yet?
Yeah, yeah,
where are they...
I saw them
on the table earlier.
Where are you off to?
They
told me about a spot.
Said I should go pray.
Pray?
I'm going with you.
Give me a sec to change.
Nah, stay put.
You look like you're running on fumes.
Go check the mirror.
Here.
Those bags are huge.
Just a little tired.
I'm still a ten!
Damn right!
Nobody can deny
my girl
is gorgeous.
It feels like yesterday
you were a baby.
I used to carry you,
but soon
I'll be the one leaning on you.
You're not allowed to age!
I'm keeping you around
forever
and ever!
My sweet girl.
Actually,
I've got some news.
Let's walk
and talk.
If you start nagging,
my ears will bleed.
Stay here.
We'll talk tonight.
Besides, after I pray,
I promised Mrs. Li
we'd...
Play cards!
I knew it!
You just wanted
an excuse to gamble.
Just help me find these keys.
Just leave it.
I'll just
open the door for you.
You staying cooped up today?
Girlie,
if you got plans, go do your thing.
Don't stay out
all night.
Yeah, yeah, MOM!
[Summer's almost dead.]
[You got my answer yet?]
[School yard,]
[7:00 PM.]
Since when do they
bust their ass
to update the board during break?
They kept my suspension notice
up forever,
but the second I need a photo,
it's wiped.
Sup, dude!
[Yo.]
What's Meng's deal?
What kinda stuff is she into?
Bro,
I'd share
my last dollar with you,
but not her. I'm crazy about her.
Cut the cr*p
before I lose it!
Holy sh*t! SSR edition!
Take notes, dude.
He drops
serious cash on me
just for some school archives!
This SD card is
literally a lifesaver.
You're the best.
Meng, yo!
This is the one!
Oh, that? Why didn't you just say so?
She's gonna love it!
For real?
Hell yeah! Your first photo together
is dope.
Gotta roll. Thanks.
Calling dibs on being the maid of honor!
[Hello.]
[Is that Huang Xuefen's granddaughter?]
[Well, well, ]
[Zhou Wan...]
[Or is it "Mr. Bow?"]
[Hand it over!]
[Who knew our golden girl]
[was running a black market?]
[Damn,]
[you're desperate for money, huh?]
[Can't a girl]
[just wanna be friends?]
[What's with the urge to go abroad?]
[Just sick of]
[my old man controlling my life.]
[I've got your back.]
[What are we anyway?]
[Tutor and tutee.]
[Everyone who came here]
[only saw a sketchy alley.]
[But you...]
[you actually saw the rose.]
[We did everything]
[we could.]
[I'm incredibly sorry]
[for your loss.]
[Where's Dad going?]
[He's not going anywhere, kiddo.]
[He's gonna be right here,]
[watching your back.]
[So dry those eyes.]
[We gotta stay strong for him.]
[Be strong, sweetie...]
[Grandma,]
[what about you?]
[Will you leave Wan too?]
[Never!]
[Look,]
[I'm tough as nails.]
[Imma live a long life]
[just to see you]
[grow into a beautiful woman.]
[I'll do it]
[for your dad.]
[Promise...]
[I promise...]
[Pinky swear...]
Enjoy
toying with me?
I'm sorry...
My phone was dead.
Hey,
why is the door wide open?
Where's Grandma?
She just
finished this scarf...
in this heat...
I told her to hold off until fall,
but she was stubborn...
I told her
to zip her purse...
It's still open...
Said she was going to pray,
but the whole prayer
was about me...
Listen.
Whatever comes next,
we face it together.
I promise.
I'm right beside you.
I'm not leaving.
I'm right here.
I'm here...
Here.
Ride safe, OK?
Let me take those.
I'm good.
She used to
crave this all the time.
But she had to
cut them out.
Thanks.
She loved being surrounded by people.
We gotta give her
a proper send-off.
Let's get the whole block together
to say goodbye.
I can only get ahold of
Mr. Kang right now.
Go grab the fruit.
I'll meet you later.
Yeah.
Hey,
relax.
I'm right here.
Grandma is gone.
She hasn't even...
chosen a portrait for the funeral.
I need your help.
We're on a tight schedule.
Why are you
just standing there?
She gave me
a spare key.
Thanks... I mean it...