Finally.
Why didn't you tell me?
Lu Xixiao,
is there
something we should do?
What?
Should we
tell everyone
we're together?
Give me your hand.
Sit still.
So fast?
I've been wanting to post it for a while.
I've been waiting for you to give me the chance.
When did you take this secretly?
No.
How is it?
Can't I keep a record for myself?
You didn't even tell me.
Secret.
You?
It's coming.
So pretty.
Are you satisfied?
Who is he?
A junior in school.
Senior,
do you really have a boyfriend?
I wanted to visit you
in your city after graduation.
Junior?
He's not my boyfriend.
He's indeed my junior.
You have a lot of boyfriends.
I'm honest.
You can see it.
When I was away,
you had a lot of suitors.
You're ungrateful.
Don't be a hypocrite.
I can ask Lin Na
if you have a conscience.
I'm going to ask Lin Na.
I'm going to ask her.
Are you still asking?
Who?
Okay, okay, I was wrong.
I'm done with you.
You can't talk about me.
Why is my name tagged as "6"?
Because your last name is Lu,
And six is your number.
I was too embarrassed
to put your name,
in case someone saw it.
In case someone saw it?
Am I that embarrassing?
It's because
you have many admirers.
I'm afraid of being hated.
Now you
are turning the tables.
- I find... - It's true.
What are you looking for?
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
It's not too late to tell you now.
I like you so much, Lu Xixiao.
Zhou Wan,
I'm hungry.
What do you want to eat?
I'll cook for you.
Lu Xixiao,
let's go cook.
Are you trying to strangle me?
Put me down, now!
Let's cook.
No, no, no!
No!
So Jiang Fan
pretended to buy your house
from you,
and then you remarried?
Not exactly.
He just didn't want me
to sell the house,
and he didn't want a divorce.
I was really upset.
I thought this time when I went back,
I would have a big fight with him.
I must get a divorce.
But as soon as I walked in the door,
everything was just the furniture and decorations I wanted.
And there was a whole wall of photos.
I cried my heart out
when I didn't see him.
You know what?
He's always been the same.
Yeah.
He's always had me wrapped around his finger.
You're the one who has him wrapped around your finger.
I'm not.
You've been together for seven years
and married for three. It's been a long time.
Every time you had a little fight,
he still can't live without you.
I feel like I can't live without him either.
So what do you think is the difference
between marriage and dating?
There's a difference.
When dating,
two people go out from their own homes
to have a date,
drink milk tea, and so on.
But after getting married,
you go home together
after work.
You always have someone
waiting for you.
No matter what happens outside,
you don't have to face it alone.
Where are we going?
We'll be there soon.
Don't peek.
Okay, I won't.
We're going downstairs.
Be careful.
It's okay. Just follow me.
One step down.
Two steps down.
That's it? You made it so mysterious.
We're here.
Just a bit further.
Open your eyes.
This is the one from the game room.
Yeah, I bought it.
It's been years
since we played this.
Ten years.
It still works.
You bought this back?
What?
You want to keep competing with me?
Mr. Gong,
you were right.
I went easy on you back then.
Tonight, I'll make you cry.
You forget how hard you worked
at that time, Zhou Wan.
How can you make me cry?
I'm not afraid of you.
I'll teach you how to play.
Come on.
You teach me?
You are my defeated opponent.
I let you win at that time.
I'm dead.
What's going on?
Why didn't you dodge?
I didn't want to.
Lu Xixiao,
you could have dodged
countless times in the past,
but you chose
to lose to me.
This time,
I'm willing to lose to you too.
I like you.
I like you, Lu Xixiao.
I've liked you for a long time.
I really like you.
I like you so much.
The old Zhou Wan
was too timid.
She never dared to believe
that we would have
a happy ending.
Thank you.
Every time I shrink back,
you come to me firmly.
Every time I encounter difficulties,
you are the first one
to rush in front of me.
Thank you.
Thank you for
falling in love with me,
who is helpless, weak,
poor,
and not kind.
Thank you for making me believe
that the future can bring
good luck and happiness.
Silly girl.
Will you marry me?
Will you marry me, Lu Xixiao?
Yes, I will.
I will.
I'm very willing to.
You know you have work today,
yet you stayed up so late last night.
You don't have to go with me.
You can stay at home
and help me confirm
the guest list for the art exhibition.
I want to sleep a bit more.
Get up and eat something before you sleep.
Or it's bad for your stomach.
No.
I want to sleep for another hour.
Alright, go to sleep.
It's a good day.
You won't be the only one sleeping.
No!
You can't tickle me!
You're cheating. Will you sleep or not?
I don't want it!
I'm up, I'm up!
I'll have breakfast, I'll have breakfast!
Alright, I'll have breakfast.
I got it, get up.
Get up, sit up.
Sit up.
I'm really speechless.
I'm not talking to you anymore.
Don't tickle me.
Same old routine.
Hang some paintings other than
the First Snow series
at the entrance to the exhibition hall.
And then in this area,
hang fourteen paintings
of the First Snow series.
The four most valuable paintings
will be hung here.
I'll also
add some snow-like decorations on the floor,
to give the audience
an immersive experience.
This
most prominent spot
is reserved for you
to hang your four most important paintings.
This main background board,
I want to hang the most mischievous painting
of the two of you.
Hang it in this most conspicuous spot.
Okay.
Okay, no buts.
Just do as you say.
It's up to you.
It's up to me?
What?
It hurts.
But when have you
ever listened to me?
Bro, tell me the truth.
Do you have some terminal illness?
If you do,
you must tell me right away.
I can't live
without you.
Cut the crap.
I'm listening.
I know
you're back together
with your little antidote.
Seeing you like this,
I'm truly happy for you.
How's life treating you lately?
A'Xiao is preparing for an art exhibition.
I'm here to deliver an invitation to you.
I quit my job.
I should let go of my past
with Lu Zhongyue.
I'm taking my mom out for a trip.
When?
Tomorrow.
So sudden.
I've been thinking for a while.
I used to think about success,
but when I look back,
[I still don't know]
[what I really want.]
[I'm leaving.]
[Zhou Wan.]
[Even if we're no longer friends,]
[I can still wish you well.]
[Take care.]
[Jiang Yan.]
[Live for yourself from now on.]
It feels like the days of working together
were just yesterday.
Xiao's art exhibition has already opened.
Yeah.
I looked it up before.
L's paintings
are mostly winter-themed.
I've heard that too.
Why is it called "Scorching Summer"?
You're all here.
Sister Wan, long time no see.
Let's go in together.
Why are you...
- Xiao hasn't come yet. - Yeah.
- Where is he? - His exhibition.
He should be inside.
They should be together.
Why do you call her Sister Wan?
Call her Sister L.
What's going on?
All right.
Is Wan your bestie?
When did this happen?
You didn't tell me.
Do you need to think about it?
You guys figure it out.
When Wan said
she would treat us to brunch,
it turned out to be Xiao who paid the bill.
That's right, no need to say anything else.
The audience's message
is addressed to Wan.
The first snow is a natural blank,
and regret is the brushstroke of life.
Alright, I'll stop talking.
I'll go see the exhibition first.
No, Wan, tell us.
What exactly happened?
Tell me quickly.
What's going on? When did it happen?
On which day?
What's going on?
The confidentiality work is excellent.
In Mr. L's exhibition,
you can see
most of the paintings
are themed by snow.
And the four paintings
in front of you
are the four special paintings
in this exhibition.
From my left to right,
they are spring, summer, autumn and winter.
You scared me.
These four paintings
were not created
by Mr. L himself.
I believe
there are many
senior fans of Mr. L here.
You can guess
who else
participated
in the creation of these paintings?
Who?
These four paintings are actually
the works of Mr. L's mother.
Unfortunately,
before this painting of Winter was completed,
his mother passed away suddenly.
What we see now
is Mr. L's continuation
of the painting.
That means,
this painting
was completed
by the two of them.
Exactly. Thank you, Mr. Lan.
Besides these four paintings
on special display,
we also
set up a snowy area
on the other side of the venue.
Mr. Lan, where's A'Xiao?
[to appreciate the paintings.]
You don't know.
How would I know?
I thought he was already here.
I have a question.
Call him.
We want to take a photo with the artist.
Where is he?
Yeah.
Mr. L
should be
somewhere in the venue.
During the exhibition,
you will
meet him.
He is the absolute protagonist today.
He can't be absent, can he?
Of course not.
Mr. L never misses
his own art exhibition.
Please rest assured.
Okay.
I won't bother you
to appreciate these paintings.
If you have any questions,
you can come to me.
Okay.
How do you like it?
Do you like it?
I've been waiting for you.
I held a solo exhibition
for you.
What do you think?
Not bad, huh?
Over the years,
I've traveled to many places.
But
sometimes when I go somewhere,
I don't know how long I'll stay.
My rule of thumb is,
when it's
the first snowfall,
I'll sneak away.
Because I don't want to see the snow alone.
Just kidding.
So, have you noticed
that these paintings
are missing something?
Me.
You know you're missing too.
I want to go to all those places too.
Really.
I'll take you there in the future.
So,
I've always wanted to create a painting
that includes everything,
with you and me,
and where we can watch the snow together.
I want that too.
Really.
How come it's snowing?
After waiting so long for today,
We need some props.
I've already proposed to you.
Let me do it again.
Put your heart into it, okay?
Will you marry me?
Blazing Summer.
I don't know which episode.
The last episode.
We...
Got married.
We're married.
Xiao Liu, you are so cute.
Is it okay?
Yes, you are so cute.
Is it good-looking?
Yes.
Okay.
We are media, too.
No showing affection in official interviews.
Okay, Chief Editor Gu.
Let's start.
Alright, our first question.
Let's ask L.
Some people have clear goals
and a thirst for fame and success.
Others are confused about life,
taking one step at a time.
What were your dreams
when you were studying?
Dreams when studying?
I didn't have any dreams.
I was decadent at that time.
Right?
Why did you choose
painting
as your career?
The First Snow series
that interests everyone
seems to have been created
when you were 18.
Because
I met Zhou Wan.
Actually, when I first met her,
I was going through a tough time.
She helped me
get out of a dead end.
So ever since,
I've been very clingy to her,
insisting on being with her.
Of course, neither of us
are not saints.
I don't love saints.
When I first
met her,
I saw her sharpness
and edge.
I love her light
and all her scars.
Because it's all these things
that make her the most vivid person.
She's open, pure, free, and happy,
and she dares to love and hate.
I have so many advantages.
Yeah, don't you know?
You summed it up pretty well.
So, in the end,
if it weren't for her,
there wouldn't be me today.
Actually, in this world,
there's snowfall every day.
But if I don't
see it with her,
it's just
an ordinary snowfall.
So if I have to
talk about a dream,
I do have one.
What is it?
It's you.
Chief Editor Gu,
cut this part.
Why? No.
No. I'm shy.
No.
Xiao Liu, should we cut it?
Okay.
Zhou Wan,
if you have to use one word
to describe L,
what would it be?
Parachute.
Why?
For a very long time
in the past,
my life
has always been in a
falling state.
I became the person
I disliked the most.
I also let down
the person I love the most.
But fortunately,
all of this
stopped because of you.
He's like a parachute,
always catching me
before I fall to the bottom.
It feels like
I'm flying.
I'm not falling.
Okay, the last question.
When did you start
to fall in love with each other?
Summer, 2016.
Right?
I can cut it out if you can't remember.
Isn't it 2016?
2013.
I fell in love with him
before he knew me.
2013?
What? When?
I'm sorry.
Your grandmother's condition
was discovered too late.
It's now irreversible.
We can only control it with medication
to prevent it from getting worse.
What?
[Our first meeting was]
[after I found out about her illness.]
[You were the only one]
[who reached out to me.]
[Well,]
[don't tell anyone.]
[The second time we met,]
[even though it was]
[a bit awkward,]
[I recognized you]
[right away.]
A little bit to the left.
Here?
Yes.
That's it.
Okay, three, two, one.
Say cheese.
[That was actually our]
[first photo together.]
[Although your face]
[wasn't even clear.]
[I've given it my all.]
[I have no regrets.]
Lu Xixiao, what are you doing?
[Every time you appear,]
[you're like a rainbow,]
[You bring color]
[to my dull life.]
[I've always been afraid]
[to tell you how long]
[I've liked you,]
[until]
[that summer came.]