[Never-Ending Summer]
[Episode 12]
It doesn't look good. Take it away.
Right.
Yours is crooked.
Right. Straighten it.
Xixiao.
When did you get back?
I invited some of your dad's friends
from academia tonight.
Do you want to stay for dinner?
I'll pass. I have no appetite.
But I do have something
I want to talk to you about.
Zhou Wan's mother.
What do you really want?
Let me talk to you instead.
Don't make things hard
for Zhou Wan anymore.
So if I agree to go abroad now,
and you marry into the Lu family,
will you give her the money?
[Inpatient Building]
Mom.
I came to see you again.
How are you doing lately?
Are you feeling any better?
I'd be discharged if I were better.
I'm getting old.
Recovery takes time.
Mom.
It's my fault these past few years.
I'm useless.
Haven't been able to help much.
You don't need to.
It's not easy for you
to maintain your current life
either.
Just take good care of yourself.
Don't worry about me.
How could I not worry?
If I could help out,
then Wan wouldn't...
What about Wan?
Didn't she tell you?
What is it?
Forget it, Mom.
This girl has grown up.
She's got her own mind.
No one can talk her out of them.
Wait.
What exactly is going on?
It's really nothing, Mom.
-Go to sleep.
-No.
You... You make it clear.
Even if you're not her mother anymore,
I'm still her Grandma.
Don't leave me hanging.
Make yourself clear.
I need to know what it is first
-so I know how serious it is.
-Okay. Alright.
Don't... Don't get too excited.
Listen,
dating isn't a big deal
at her age.
But the boy she's with, Lu,
comes from a wealthy family
and is a real rich kid.
I'm afraid she'll be fooled.
Lu?
You mean Lu Xixiao?
I know that kid.
You know him?
Yes.
He's got good character.
Well...
Maybe we'll wait and see.
If they really work out,
it'd be like childhood sweethearts.
I'm just worried.
I'm afraid
that she's with him for the money.
That's true. Well,
why would Wan need money?
What would she need money for
anyway?
It's useless.
Right, Mom?
Good character, huh.
I heard you passed
Professor Qin's exam.
At least you got one thing done.
Prepare well from now on.
I'm not going
to Professor Qin's school.
Didn't you want me
to study finance abroad?
I agree.
No other conditions?
Just get my mom's painting back.
That's it?
Get out. Close the door behind you.
Done talking?
What about you?
That's not a small sum of money,
but I'll have it ready.
You can't blame me.
I'm not kicking you out.
Studying finance abroad is a great thing.
The family's paved the way for you.
It's an opportunity
-so many people would kill for.
-Please. Stop acting
in front of me, will you?
When will you keep your promise?
What are you talking about?
Since when am I acting?
I'll transfer the money
as soon as you get on the plane.
We're going to be mother and son soon.
We should have some trust.
If outsiders ever
found out about my relationship with Wan,
it wouldn't
be good for her either.
[Party B: Zhou Wan]
The money will be in your account
in a couple days.
Remember to check.
What are you talking about?
I'm saying you've got skills.
You actually pulled it off.
Pulled what off? Say it clearly.
Lu Xixiao is going abroad.
Didn't you know?
[Zhou Wan]
Hello,
the number you have dialed
is currently un...
Good boy, Doggie.
Wan, Doggie can shake hands now.
Wanna try?
[Big Ocean Motorcycle Workshop]
Wan!
Lu Xixiao,
where exactly are you?
[Inpatient Building]
Be more careful.
You're holding a knife.
Don't cut your hand.
I'm not a three-year-old.
You've been knitting
all afternoon.
It's summer. Take a break.
You have no idea
how boring it is in the hospital.
At least knitting this scarf
keeps me occupied.
You know, 30 years ago,
I would stand for
8 hours straight at work
without getting tired.
You were a model worker.
I've said that?
I can memorize it.
But it's still a long time
before winter.
If you finish it so early,
it will just gather dust.
It's not that early.
What?
I said it's not that early.
Years go by
so fast.
Look at you,
all grown up in the blink of an eye.
I'm old now.
I've become a burden to you.
Grandma!
Don't ever say that again.
Okay.
Here, have an apple.
I've got the medical bills covered.
Once we find a matching
kidney donor,
we'll get the surgery done,
and then you'll recover.
Everything will be fine.
Can we talk about something else?
Like what?
How is that young man
named Lu treating you?
Pretty good.
He takes care of me.
How did you meet?
Didn't I tell you?
We're classmates.
You two don't seem like
just classmates.
I don't know if it's a coincidence
or a mistake.
You like him.
Grandma!
Don't be shy.
You're still young.
There are many things
waiting for you to do.
Don't spend all your time
stuck in the hospital.
If you really like him,
you should follow your heart.
Go find him.
Enjoy this
pure affection.
Did he say anything to you?
He didn't say anything.
But I can tell
he likes you too.
If you think
he's someone you can count on,
just tell me,
and I'll kick you out right away.
Why would you kick me out?
You know,
you nag me every day.
Like nonstop.
-It's annoying.
-I'll keep nagging.
I'll nag you for the rest of my life.
I'm sticking with you.
I'm not going anywhere.
Okay.
Don't go.
Stay.
You can't leave me.
I won't.
All this top-notch gear
and expensive parts—
you're just selling it like this?
Why not
-give me a few parts?
-Your feet.
Why sell it cheap to Ping?
He's so old.
Riding a cruiser is enough.
A sportbike just doesn't suit him.
So what if I'm old?
Even if I can't ride it,
can't I collect it?
It's not suitable.
None of your business.
I want it.
But Xixiao,
why are you
selling your bike suddenly?
I'm going abroad.
The procedures are too troublesome.
Xixiao.
You were painting just fine.
Why go abroad now?
-And why did you give this to Ping?
-Sign here.
You used to
give it straight to me.
Why sell it this time?
I can deal with it
however I want.
Ping,
give me the money as soon as it's sold.
Xixiao.
-I'm leaving.
-Give it to me if you don't want it.
Xixiao!
He's not selling the bike.
He's clearly short of money.
Him? Short of money?
Can't you see that?
Bed 23's blood pressure and blood sugar
have stabilized, right?
Yes, they are stable for now.
Then let's schedule
the surgery for next Wednesday.
Okay.
Alright.
Dr. Chen.
Wan.
Okay, you two go ahead.
Excuse me.
How is the kidney match
for my Grandma going?
Don't worry about that.
She's already on the waiting list.
I'll let you know
as soon as there's news.
Thank you.
What's wrong?
You seem a bit down.
You need to take care of yourself,
or your friend
will worry about you.
Did Jiang Yan come by again?
Not Jiang Yan.
It was a
tall guy
without wearing glasses.
Lu Xixiao.
That should be him.
He cares about you a lot.
He kept asking about the surgery fees.
300,000 is not a small amount.
He probably wants to help you out.
I'll leave you to it.
[Nurse Station]
[Big Ocean Motorcycle Workshop]
Where's Lu Xixiao?
Why ask me? How would I know?
I was going to ask you.
Then what's with the bike?
He said he's going abroad.
He couldn't take the bike, so he sold it.
He's going abroad?
Yeah. Didn't he tell you?
Where is he now?
Probably at the arcade.
[Class Group Chat]
[Who's that?]
[Someone's about to jump.]
[Should we call the police?]
[Probably didn't do well on the exam.]
[I saw it when I passed by.]
[It's so high.
She'll die if she jumps off.]
[Why is Lu Xixiao there too?]
Don't come over.
You don't understand
my pain at all.
Don't take another step.
Don't come over.
You don't understand
my pain at all.
Don't take another step.
Don't.
Step back!
Everyone get back!
What are you doing?
Come back!
So you jump.
And then what?
Then...
Once you're dead, there is no "then."
I don't have a future anymore.
Mom.
Go
live your own life
from now on.
No.
Calm down first.
Lu Xixiao!
What's going on?
Xue Xi?
You know me?
I saw you once when I was on duty
at the school gate.
I thought your short hair
was really pretty.
It left a strong impression.
He said the same thing.
But what's the point?
His parents told us to break up,
and he just did it.
You're still young.
Your future
still holds so much.
Just come down first, okay?
It's too dangerous up there.
What future do I have?
I'm not like you.
My grades are bad.
I'm not pretty.
I don't have the future
or the life that you have.
My mom only forces me
and controls me.
If I don't do what she says,
she hits me and yells at me.
I'm nothing but
her accessory!
And now?
I've lost even the last bit
of hope.
I'm so tired.
You envy me?
I envy all of you.
My dad left when I
was little.
He was drowning in debt.
Everyone called him a deadbeat.
My mom couldn't take it,
so she abandoned me and left too.
When I saw her again
years later,
she pretended not to know me,
like she never had
a daughter at all.
Then my grandma fell seriously ill.
I missed the college entrance exam
due to an accident.
[Admission Ticket]
You see.
All those things you envy,
I actually don't have any of them.
I've tried everything to make money.
I got scholarships
just to make
my grandma's life
a little easier.
But I've been lying all along.
I lied to a lot of people.
I've even
hurt people
who matter to me.
Xue Xi.
You think I want
my own future and life?
I don't even dare to dream.
I'm just like you.
I used to think,
maybe I should just let it go,
maybe I should just give up,
and leave it at that.
But then I thought of my dad,
my grandma,
and all the people I care about.
I don't want to let them down.
And I believe
we have more possibilities ahead of us.
Come down first.
We'll figure it out together.
Xue Xi.
I believe
you can do it.
Just hold on a little longer.
Just a little longer.
Okay?
Make way!
Step back.
This is her family.
That's her daughter up there.
My daughter is up there!
Xi! Xi!
Don't!
Xue Xi.
Don't come up!
Xi! Don't!
Don't jump!
Don't come up!
Xue Xi.
Don't touch me!
If you touch me,
I'll jump!
I won't touch you. I won't move.
Just calm down.
Calm down.
Don't jump, okay?
I'll stay with you.
I'll go with you
to talk to your mother.
Okay?
It's useless. Useless!
If I go down,
she'll still hit me and yell at me!
She just doesn't understand anything!
What do you want?
I'll do anything you ask!
What about him?
Do you really like him?
Xue Xi!
Xi! Don't!
He's just a coward.
If you really jump today,
what about the people who care about you?
How would they feel?
You'll become an indelible
shadow in their hearts.
At least you still have
people who care about you,
don't you?
My mom back then was exactly
like you are now.
Standing right on that edge.
She jumped right in front of me.
I still can't forget
that scene to this day.
I see it every single time
I close my eyes.
So I'm begging you.
While you still have a choice,
don't leave the people
who love you and the people you love
with that as their last image
of you. Okay?
While you still have a choice,
you can still start over.
[Public Security]
Come on, everyone step back!
Everyone step back!
-Hurry up. Please leave first.
-I'll leave.
Leave first, okay?
Third floor, over here.
Stop filming.
The world is big.
The future is long.
There are so many pages
in the story of your life
you haven't read yet.
Come down first, okay?
We'll help you
figure this out together.
Come down first.
Don't come any closer.
Stop talking.
Stop talking!
No!
Let go, Zhou Wan.
You can't hold on.
Zhou Wan!
Don't grab my hand.
I need to examine you.
Just cooperate.
Where's Zhou Wan?
The girl who came with you,
right?
She's fine.
She was still conscious
when she fell.
She's getting examined now.
You don't need to examine me.
Doctor, I'm fine.
Where is that girl?
On the third floor.
Which room on the third floor?
Hey,
can't you even wait
for this little while?
Just stay here
and cooperate with the exam.
Stop moving.
I'm really fine, doctor.
Just tell me
which room she's in.
-I beg you.
-Room 302!
Room 302.
Where are you going?
The exam isn't done yet!
Thanks, doctor.
[Room 302]
What's the problem?
I can't sleep.
For how long?
♪ If I could, I want to become ♪
Almost two months.
Two months.
Anything happen recently?
♪ An astronomer ♪
Excuse me.
Was there a girl
♪ Lost in your night sky ♪
named Zhou Wan here?
She already finished and left.
♪ Then fall and fall and fall ♪
♪ Maybe it's your gravity ♪
♪ That held me back from losing control ♪
You...
[Neurosurgery & Psychology Clinics]
♪ When you passed by me by accident ♪
Miss,
are you looking for
the boy who came with you?
♪ I finally learned to fall ♪
Yes.
He just finished his exam and left.
Already left?
Never seen someone so scared of heights.
You were fine,
but he passed out.
♪ Countless, unforgettable ♪
Where did he go?
♪ No time left, so I ♪
I didn't see it.
♪ Can only fall toward you ♪
Thank you.
[Neurosurgery & Psychology Clinics]
♪ Too dazzling, too lonely, it's alright ♪
♪ I believe in this encounter ♪
Excuse me,
was there a girl
named Zhou Wan here just now?
She just left.
Just left?
♪ Landing in the ruins of the galaxy ♪
[Neurosurgery & Psychology Clinics]
♪ Exchanging our comets ♪
♪ Suddenly I am certain ♪
♪ This mud all over me ♪
♪ Is the proof of love ♪
♪ I can't remember and can't go back ♪
♪ If you can't hold it tightly, let me ♪
♪ Fly without hesitation ♪
♪ Sorry, I'm too capricious and obsessed ♪
Zhou Wan!
♪ The Milky Way is drowning ♪
♪ If one day you fall into ♪
♪ The gap a light-year away ♪
♪ You'll find ♪
♪ The scattered ashes ♪
♪ Burns my heart ♪
-Are you okay?
-Are you ok...
The doctor said I just have
a slight muscle strain.
I'll be fine after some rest.
Me too.
You're lying.
The doctor told me
you have a severe fear of heights.
Just now on the rooftop, you...
Let me speak first.
There is something
I don't want to hide anymore.
Guo Xiangling is not my sponsor.
She is my biological mother.
I know.
Actually, I've been hoping
you would tell me.
You never did.
But it doesn't matter anymore.
After all, you held on to me
up there,
didn't you?
Lu Xixiao.
Next time you plan to die,
give me a heads-up first.
Otherwise, I won't have time
to arrange a proper funeral for you.
Auntie.
Can I borrow him for a moment?
I...
[Children's Medical Center]
[Registration & Payment]
[Outpatient Pharmacy]
Zhou Wan!
Are you even
listening to me?
You brat.
You're not gonna jump again, are you?
My head hurts already.
Give me a break.
Who would've thought?
Now that I'm in trouble,
you're the only one in the family
who came to see me.
Feeling down?
Did you only just
realize today what
your family relationships are like?
So if you go abroad,
your dad'll be happy,
grandpa'll be happy,
and Guo Xiangling, of course—
she's finally marrying into the family.
She's probably popping champagne at home.
So, me leaving
is a win for
everyone, huh?
Of course.
The whole world will be happy.
So go already.
What are you waiting for?
Waiting...
to say goodbye to someone.
Thank you, Zhou Wan.
I'm going to start over,
and go to college out of town.
Congratulations, Xue Xi.
Thank you.
So,
you and that guy...
We decided to break up after all.
Maybe
our personalities just aren't compatible.
Perhaps
incompatible personalities
aren't necessarily a bad thing.
Just like you and that Lu Xixiao?
I think you two
are quite a good match.
He and I
are not what you think.
As for you,
don't be so impulsive next time.
Never hurt yourself over a breakup,
or
because of some guy.
There's so much more out there.
It wasn't really about the breakup.
After going through so much,
you should be able to understand.
I just feel like
maybe everyone has
their own burdens to carry.
[Time Store]
Why did you want to come swing?
Because
I used to come here
with my mom a lot.
Today I guess I'm
remembering some things from back then.
Actually,
I only became
afraid of heights
after my mom jumped.
It's fine.
I want you to know everything
before I leave.
And you're the only one
who can ask.
So,
what really happened?
My maternal grandparents
came from aristocratic families.
My mom
was sheltered her whole life.
After she graduated and returned,
she met Lu Zhongyue
at a cocktail party.
It was love at first sight.
At that time, my maternal grandparents
also tried to set them up.
My paternal grandfather
also highly favored
this marriage.
He made the final decision.
And they got married 3 months later.
Their wedding
was front-page news
in Pingchuan back then.
Lu Zhongyue used that marriage
to change my grandpa's
opinion of him.
He gradually started
taking over the company.
My mother, on the other hand,
spent most of her time at home,
painting and writing poems.
[Happy Wedding. A Lifetime of Joy.]
It was said to be a very happy time.
At least it seemed so.
[Happy Wedding. A Lifetime of Joy.]
Soon, my mother got pregnant.
You know what happened next.
Lu Zhongyue hid it very well,
until my mother found out
about Jiang Yan.
She was always
strong-willed
and proud in everything.
It was
bad enough that her own marriage
was in ruins.
And she realized...
she was the one who came second.
She just couldn't
accept the fact.
Actually, it wasn't that bad initially.
She just wanted to leave the family.
It wasn't until she sent me
to stay with
my grandparents
that I found out from my aunt
what really happened
back then.
Lan?
What are you doing
hiding here alone?
Where did you take Xixiao?
What is this?
You had me investigated?
After all these years,
what else don't I
know about you?
[Divorce Agreement]
I will never divorce you.
But I can promise you,
I can leave all of them.
You even had
a child with someone else!
When she got pregnant,
I had no idea.
By the time I found out,
it was too late.
The child was already born.
What was I supposed to do?
What do you want me to do?
All I can promise you is that
this child will never
come near Xixiao!
She wanted to leave,
but she couldn't.
Later, she got depression.
At first, the family didn't agree
to let me continue living with her.
I begged Grandpa desperately
just to be able to visit her occasionally.
And then...
Mom!
Xixiao.
From now on,
go live your own life.
Lu Xixiao.
You know what?
My dad told me that
kind people
always go to heaven.
I believe your mother
is definitely up there,
watching over you,
always by your side.