come back to me, okay?
Just like when we were kids.
So you're here
to make a deal
with me?
Of course not.
I just want you to see me.
What if I say no?
Jiang Yan,
I like Lu Xixiao
not because he helped me.
Lu Xixiao did all this for me.
We never
need any exchange.
If you come
to threaten me
to make a choice
with these proofs,
then you already know the answer.
Why?
From childhood to adulthood,
from the beginning,
from ten years ago,
I've always told you
that I've always sincerely
considered you as my good friend.
I also sincerely
trusted you as a friend.
Including the accident ten years ago,
I knew it was you who leaked my whereabouts
to Luo He.
But I still believed
that wasn't your intention.
Back then, only a few people knew
I returned to Pingchuan.
I just don't understand
how you could use
Director Wang's case against me
as a bargaining chip
to get me to leave Lu Xixiao.
I...
Let's go our separate ways from now on.
You met Jiang Yan?
How did it go?
We may not be able to get
the evidence from him.
It's okay.
I found
the dealer who worked with Mr. Wang.
If we can make him
talk,
we still have a chance.
Let's go talk to him tomorrow.
What's the reward?
What?
You went to meet my love rival,
leaving me alone
waiting here for an hour.
Don't you have to show some appreciation?
You insisted on coming yourself.
I don't care.
I'm jealous.
You have to coax me.
Alright.
I'm done with you.
Let's go home.
Yes, ma'am.
I put you in charge of Phase II.
Why did I find out about Shengshi
last?
By the time I knew,
it was already done.
Why didn't you
tell me right away?
Don't you know that Star Sea Entertainment
is the partner I brought in?
With the Shengshi Huayu,
Star Sea Entertainment will be abandoned.
I remember
you told me that
you need someone experienced like me
to take control of the Phase II project team
for the headquarters.
If anything goes wrong,
I should communicate with the headquarters in time.
With my experience,
I don't think there's anything wrong
with this.
On the contrary,
it will add luster to the project.
You're starting to learn
to play word games with me, aren't you?
I can put you
in this position,
and I can also take you out.
Mr. Lu,
please help yourself.
You think I'm still that kid
who can be manipulated
by a few threats and promises?
Wait.
Son,
listen to me.
You are my son.
Compared to Lu Xixiao,
you're a hundred times better.
You can treat me like this,
and you can treat others like this.
You inherited my qualities.
If you keep doing this,
you will definitely
achieve great things one day.
Trust me, baby.
Baby.
Mr. Lu.
Well...
What's up? Say it.
Someone saw A'Xiao and Zhou Wan
go to Wang Yongli's house together.
I'm so angry!
Two ungrateful sons!
One by one,
they all come to oppose me.
Fine!
Zhou Wan is just trying to
hold onto his father's
past mistakes, isn't he?
Well,
as for the Yingshan Workshop,
I don't need your reminder.
Dad, don't go.
He promised to help us.
You don't have to hide anymore, right?
It's not the time to solve the problem.
I don't want to drag you down.
Take care of your grandma
and study hard.
Wang Yongli,
you're finally home.
Do you have money to pay back this time?
Give me some more time.
I don't have
money right now.
No money?
What's your excuse this time?
Do you think I'll still trust you?
Lan Yue's men came to your house,
bringing food and drinks.
You must have made a fortune
from your factory.
Lan Yue's men?
Cut the act. Let go of me.
Let him go.
You've been in the bathroom for so long.
The information company has sent me
the address.
I'll wait for you in the garage.
Li Xin needs me for something.
I'm already at the elevator,
heading down.
Alright, no rush.
Do you want to go after dinner,
or should we go straight over?
Let's go straight over.
Hello?
Hello, Zhou Wan?
Zhou Wan, hello?
Pull up the security footage
the three elevators on the first floor of Building A.
Come on, hurry up.
These three, these three.
Zoom in, zoom in.
Just go over there.
Why is it this person?
Director Lu, do you know him?
When the police come later,
you tell them
this person is Wang Yongli,
He used to be
the director of the Yinshan Furniture Factory.
When they get here,
tell them to focus on searching
around Jinshawan and
the Yinshan Furniture Factory.
Director Lu,
are you leaving before the police
arrive?
What happened?
Get away from me now.
Did something happen to Zhou Wan?
How dare you ask?
Wang Yongli took Zhou Wan away.
It's all because of you.
Get in the car. I'll go with you.
Wang Yongli doesn't have many places to hide.
I've investigated.
He was hiding
in the old site of Yinshan Factory.
I know where it is. Hurry up.
Lu Xixiao,
I'm sorry for what happened
in Luo He ten years ago.
I was too concerned about my background
that I kept making mistakes.
Are you serious
talking to me about this now?
I hated Lu Zhongyue
and you for years,
but it doesn't matter anymore.
Let's not live in the past.
Instead of
talking to me,
we've already arrived.
Jiang Yan,
you've liked Zhou Wan for years,
but have you
ever protected her?
Listen,
if something happens to Zhou Wan today,
you'll never repay me.
I know, it's my fault.
I just
don't want to admit it.
Why are you always ranked ahead of me
in everyone's eyes?
Your identity
is like this in Zhou Wan's eyes,
in the Old Master's eyes,
and even in Lu Zhongyue's eyes,
it's the same.
But I never thought
- I would hurt Zhou Wan. - All right.
Stop telling me these.
Just drive.
Lu Xixiao.
There are many factories.
Let's split up.
You're awake.
Do you know where this is?
The Yishan Furniture Factory
was relocated to Jinshawan.
The predecessor of your factory
should be near
the raw material source.
Do you know?
At that time,
I bought this land,
and with my brothers,
we built up the business
piece by piece,
and then made it bigger.
Later,
I bought this land.
I suffered a defeat
and ended up in such a situation.
I can only hide here.
And all of this
is because of Lu Zhongyue.
I can understand.
I can totally understand.
Lily must have told you
about my experience.
Lu Zhongyue used the same trick
to frame my dad's factory,
causing my dad to go bankrupt
and be burdened with huge debts.
Later, my dad
died of depression.
Mr. Wang,
I really want to help you.
Because helping you
is also helping my dad.
Stop lying to me.
I know
you and Lan Yue
are in the same camp.
That day,
the man who followed you to my yard
was Lu Zhongyue's son.
What else
do you have to say for yourself?
If you really want to help me,
then tell me,
where the evidence I gave you
has gone?
I can explain about the evidence.
I can also
get it back.
I assure you.
It's too late.
Do you think I'll trust you again?
That evidence
might already
be in Lu Zhongyue's hands.
I have nothing now.
Mr. Wang, calm down.
Think about it.
You still have your daughter, Lily.
Let's get the factory
back to normal.
Shut up.
Mr. Wang, Mr. Wang.
You don't deserve
to mention my daughter's name.
I've already
prepared the evidence,
and even written my will.
I believe the police will
uncover Lu Zhongyue's crimes.
Zhou Wan!
Stop right there!
You must be Lu Zhongyue's son.
You've come just in time.
Let Lu Zhongyue
taste the bitterness of losing everything.
Calm down.
Mr. Wang,
please calm down and think.
I'm Lu Zhongyue's son.
If you need anything,
you can use me as a bargaining chip
to threaten him.
Harming Zhou Wan
will do you
no good now.
Think about your mother
and Lily.
Let Lan Yue explain
the furniture factory incident.
You won't have to hide anymore.
They can all live
a peaceful and stable life.
As long as you don't hurt Zhou Wan,
I'll do
whatever you want.
I'll do anything.
Just let me see her.
Let me know she's safe.
Okay?
Enough.
It's useless to say all this.
Don't come any closer.
Turn around.
Hands behind your back.
Zhou Wan,
are you okay?
Are you hurt? Are you okay?
How dare you trick me?
I shouldn't have trusted you!
None of you should live!
Let's end this!
Let's see who survives
and makes a difference!
Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
None of you can escape!
Are you okay?
Your hand!
It's fine.
I arrived just in time, didn't I?
Thanks.
Recently,
Wang, the owner of the furniture factory in Yinshan,
was arrested on suspicion of kidnapping.
He claimed that his factory
was bankrupt due to
unfair competition.
Now the police are
conducting an investigation.
Don't move.
Stay still.
No, my legs are too long
to stretch out.
I mean your hands.
When you take a bath later,
when you take a shower.
Don't let the wound get wet.
I can't guarantee that.
I hurt my right arm.
Your arm is not broken.
I've sealed it for you.
It'll be fine.
Turn around.
It seems that
you're all right.
I worried too much.
No way.
My arm is still
killing me.
Put your hand down.
Who let you...
Thanks to your skills,
my wound
didn't even get wet.
Really.
My arm still...
Even lifting it...
Who let you be so naughty?
You're acting again.
No.
Do you still want to dry your hair?
No, I won't do it for you.
Yes, yes.
No, yes, yes.
Let's stop here.
I'm out of patience.
Don't go, don't go.
I have something to tell you.
You're not going to...
No, I'm not.
I really have something to tell you.
Really?
Go ahead.
Wang Yongli
is facing criminal charges,
but he can still
appeal against Lan Yue.
Also,
I've found
more evidence
about the Yishan Furniture Factory.
With the evidence
Jiang Yan left,
can we finally reveal
the truth about the factory?
There's bad news too.
The supplier who scammed your dad,
who set your dad up
died in a car accident.
So,
we've lost a key lead.
Even if we
win the lawsuit,
we still can't prove
what Lu Zhongyue did to your dad.
I know it's hard
to pursue my dad's case,
but it's fine.
I just want to expose his evil deeds
to the public.
It's me.
I saw the news.
Let's meet.
You've changed a lot.
You've become more mature.
This is the coffee I ordered for you.
What do you want from me?
I have nothing
to talk to you about.
This is for you.
Take a look.
You've worked so hard
for so many years.
Is this what you've been looking for?
These are all documents I handled back then.
There are some evidence
from the building materials factory and dealers.
At that time,
I just wanted to leave myself a way out.
Now, I don't need it anymore.
I've thought a lot these years.
I want to live a different life.
Why do you help me?
I didn't expect you
to investigate this far.
I always thought
we were the same kind of person.
But
I just realized
that being scheming
and giving it your all
are not the same.
You're doing well now,
better than me.
That's good.
My daughter, I wish you happiness.
This one is on you.
You're welcome.
Do I really not need to come with you?
Didn't we agree
that this matter involves the Lu family,
I don't want to make you uncomfortable.
Then,
I'll wait for you at home.
This matter
has caused a lot of noise,
and has had
a very bad impact on the company.
Today, someone must step up
and take responsibility for this.
Mr. Lu,
to be precise,
because of the malicious
acquisition of the Yingshan Furniture Factory.
A'Xiao and his team
were just conducting a routine investigation
and encountered extreme retaliation.
No matter how you look at it,
the blame doesn't fall
on them.
Aren't you
shifting the blame?
The incident of the Yishan Furniture Factory
is just a rumor.
What credibility
can a villain have?
It's just
a desperate smear.
But those project leaders
in the company
ignored the interests of the company
and acted on their own,
causing such a big mess.
I suggest we dismiss them as soon as possible.
No need for you to do that.
I'll resign now.
This is the board of directors.
Who do you think you are to come in here?
I specially invited
Miss Zhou here.
She's a witness to the incident back then.
Everyone, why don't you listen to
what she has to say?
What do you all think?
What do you think?
This is Director Lu.
The Old Master
was very angry
when he heard about it.
He asked me
to hold a board of directors immediately.
I think
the Old Master also wants to hear
the story from the party concerned.
General Manager Lu,
what do you think?
I'm sorry
to resign from
the Lanyue Phase II Project.
I'm sorry
to cause you and Mr. Lan any trouble.
Before I leave,
I have two important documents
that have been distributed
to your email.
Please check them.
The first one
is about the evidence of sabotage
and contract fraud
in the process
of land acquisition
for Lanyue Phase II project.
Before
the acquisition of Yishan Furniture Factory,
Wang Yongli, the director,
was sued for using
inferior products.
The factory was closed.
But in fact,
the purchasing personnel
of the factory
colluded with the dealer
who provided raw materials
to forge the quality inspection report,
causing issues
with their products,
which forced Wang Yongli
to sell his land to Lan Yue
at a very low price.
What nonsense
are you spouting?
Mr. Lu,
you must...
Mind your manners.
Have a seat.
Coincidentally,
you did the same thing
20 years ago.
I wonder if you remember
the Jun'an Building Materials Factory.
During the land acquisition process
of the Lanyue Phase I Resort project,
Lu Zhongyue colluded with a dealer
and used the same method
to cause the bankruptcy of the factory,
and then it was acquired by Lanyue at a low price.
Over the past 20 years,
how many families
have been forced
into bankruptcy,
and how many people
have been killed because of you.
I know for you,
it's just a
shady deal,
but for those
who have experienced it,
it's a long-awaited
truth that has been waited for 20 years.
I have sent the materials
in your hands
to the relevant departments.
I believe that someone will come soon
to intervene in the investigation.
As the leading enterprise
of Pingchuan,
Lan Yue has developed to today.
I believe it relies on honesty in business
and people-oriented.
I believe all the directors
will make the best choice
for the long-term development
of Lan Yue.
By the way, Mr. Lu,
do you remember
the name of the director
of Jun'an Building Materials Factory?
His name is Zhou Jun.
Dad.
Lu Zhongyue has been
punished by law.
The truth
has finally come out.
A'Xiao, I told you
she's not the right person for you.
Why are you
always so stubborn?
Grandpa.
You should know
I'm not like Lu Zhongyue.
I don't need someone like my mom
to be by my side,
telling me what to do every day
to keep me on the right track.
Everything I've done over the years
has proven that.
I'm grown up.
I can
make my own decisions.
I don't care
what people think of me.
So you don't have to
scare her with these things
and force her to think about me.
I know what I want,
and I know
what I can achieve.
This is
between her and me.
I was young and immature before.
I was naive and my words carried no weight.
I had no choice.
But now, whether to forgive her
or not,
it's up to me.
The promises you made to her before
no longer stand.
You should tell her not to show up
in front of me again.
You never asked me what I thought.
Grandpa,
this isn't fair.
You've always been good at judging people,
so you should know
that whether two people are together
isn't just about
being compatible.
Look at my mom and Lu Zhongyue.
If they had just
divorced back then,
would there have been tragedies later on?
I truly hope
the Lu family
can be warmer.
So, Grandpa,
what I want to tell you
is actually simple.
I only care about Zhou Wan.
She's the only one
I've never let go of.
She's the one
this world is
worth living in.
So I don't want anyone
but her.
She's been scheming
since she met you.
She's using you.
And you don't care?
I don't care.
I told you,
as long as I'm with her,
even if I fall flat on my face,
or hit a wall,
I'll be happy.
I'll do it.
Sit down.
Have some tea.
Jiang Fan, open the door!
The agent called me,
saying you're not answering your phone,
and you're not handing over the house.
What's going on?
Open the door!
First time visiting the house.
It's so big. Do you like it?
This is just
my dream kitchen.
We can put
a six-person dining table here.
That way,
Wanwan and my parents
can all eat here.
Okay.
Here,
we can set up a wine bar.
Honey,
I also want to put
all those dolls and stuff up there.
Sure.
The TV wall is so big.
Let's not put a TV there.
I'll set up a projector screen.
I know.
I'll put all the videos
we took
on it.
You're so smart.
But I don't like the curtains.
Honey,
I want something warmer.
How about beige?
Let's try
all the warm colors.
Sure, let's go with beige.
Warm tones are cozy.
And here,
I want an eight-seater sofa.
That way, even the dog can lie down.
We'll cover this wall with
all our photos
from childhood to now.
That's so sweet.
But isn't that a bit too big?
I love you, honey. I love you.
Jiang Fan, I love you so much.
I love you, Jiang Fan.
You are so nice.
Honey, I love you. I love you.
I love you too, honey.
Love you.
Honey,
I used to think
as long as I made more money,
became better,
and constantly improved
our life quality,
we would always
be happy together.
I thought that after getting married,
our feelings would never change
and we would never be apart.
But only now do I realize
that marriage is just the beginning
of managing this relationship.
I'm sorry.
I haven't been paying
enough attention to you for a long time.
I haven't been looking at you
like I did today.
But trust me,
from now on,
I'll always put you
first in my heart.
Will you give me another chance?
Does your leg hurt?
No.
If you say it hurts, I'll say yes.
So you're saying yes?
Do you have anything else to say?
Do you have anything else
to say?
After A'Xiao's exhibition,
I'll take a long vacation.
Wherever you want to go,
I'll go with you.
If it's not good,
I'll make you stay here
forever.
Okay.
Then we'll stay at home
until we get moldy.
We'll stay here
until no one in the world
can find us.
Get moldy together.
I just like you this way.
As long as you like it.