Don't just stand there.
Say hi to him.
Hi.
I'm leaving.
Come back.
So rude.
Sit down.
Why does it look like
you two know each other?
Were you classmates?
We were…
not close.
You skipped school.
So you knew no one.
You know,
her grades.
Too bad.
Why didn't she take the gaokao?
Well,
She was frail growing up.
She had a fever on gaokao day.
So it affected
her gaokao score.
And after that—
I'll retake it.
Ms. Guo promised
to support me
through college.
Right.
She found one up north,
a prep school.
She'll be leaving soon.
You're so kind.
Never saw that side of you.
If that's the case,
Wan needs a prep year,
Xixiao has art school applications.
Why don't you stay with us?
Xixiao doesn't study much.
Stay by his side,
set him an example.
No need.
I… I'm usually
used to being alone.
Exactly.
Don't pressure her.
She hates being a bother.
Too much pressure.
Fine by me.
I can learn a lot
from you.
Really?
See? Xixiao agreed.
Why be
shy?
Ms. Chen.
Set up Xixiao's old room
from childhood.
That room.
He drew a lot there.
The walls are messy.
Please don't mind.
I'll give you one year.
But…
Your mom's school
is hard to get into.
Are you confident?
Yes.
Listen, Lu Xixiao.
If during this year,
you stir up trouble
at home,
any trouble at all,
then don't you dare
pretend
you're working hard.
Are we clear?
Go abroad properly
and study finance.
Promise?
Fine.
Fine then.
It's settled.
Let's eat. Come on.
Waiting on who?
Go play.
You'll live
together every day.
Must you be
Awkward?
What?
I said,
you'll live
every day anyway.
Why make it awkward?
I'm asking.
If one day,
Gu Meng became family,
what then?
What else?
Get along with her.
Gu Meng and I
aren't like you two.
We're special.
We have a deep bond.
What's with you two?
Tell me.
Do you know how many times
my name was in her notebook?
Fifty-seven times.
Fifty-seven times, man.
Know what that means?
Unforgettable.
Sometimes I admire
how your mind works.
I mean it.
You can fool yourself that hard.
I could never be that blind.
You call yourself not blind?
Deep down,
you'd be happy.
What? Say that again.
Drop it.
Forget it, okay?
Finish the story, Wan.
What's up
with you two?
She's in hospital.
She's worried about me.
That place
is near the hospital.
Who asked you that?
I mean you and him.
And you two
added WeChat back.
They let you visit too.
Then why
fight again?
It's messy.
Tell me more.
The woman who
helped me
is sort of his stepmom.
He dislikes her.
Our bond
was never pure.
Then what
are you two now?
Live-in roommates,
god-siblings.
You two beat
Mom's soaps
hands down.
All right.
We should get going.
He likely doesn't
want to see me.
Then why let you go?
If it's a mix-up,
then clear it up.
If you messed up,
then apologize.
It's simple.
You must…
You scared me! Are you crazy?
Movie, remember?
Come on.
I told you to wait there.
I'll go from Wan's.
Why bother?
Look, what's this?
Look, what's that?
I came to pick you up.
So cool.
No cab needed.
Cool or not?
It's okay.
Go watch it.
I'm leaving.
Bye.
Fine.
Remember my words, Wan.
I'll get it.
No.
This way.
Thank you.
Here.
I've packed your
luggage.
What I said at dinner
wasn't just for him.
Right?
I know.
Go on.
About the wedding,
we may need to push it back.
Dad says wait
until Xixiao leaves next year.
Also,
You…
know your place
in this family.
In this family,
I have enough
trouble already.
Got it.
Miss me.
And that…
so-called little girl of yours.
Watch her.
Careful.
This room
has no private bathroom.
The bathroom is outside.
This is it.
Thank you.
Come in.
Tell me
if anything's missing.
Thank you.
Get some rest early.
Need anything,
tell me.
Thank you.
Okay.
Not at all.
Lu Xixiao.
I never thought
I'd get this close
to your childhood.
I… didn't know
it was occupied.
Don't you have
your own bathroom?
Bossing me now?
Done?
Now that you've moved in,
should've come say hi?
I thought you hated me.
And you?
Want to see me?
I…
didn't know it'd go this way.
I didn't mean to upset you.
And the result?
Still the same?
Do you have time?
Wan.
Bathroom's occupied.
Use mine in my room.
Come on.
Your godmother's calling.
Little one.
Is moving in fun for you?
Did you think
this would scare me?
Of course not.
I didn't choose this.
It's for Grandma, that's all.
It's been a while.
Still not used to
me as your daughter?
Dinner's ready.
Mom.
I washed some fruit for you.
Here.
Have some fruit.
Well…
Wan.
Guo Yan and I
haven't been in touch for years.
Sending so much at once…
That feels off.
What's wrong with it?
Aren't we family, Mom?
If she wants to,
just accept them.
These years,
Wan has really grown up.
Your love wasn't wasted.
I brought dinner.
I'll do it.
No need.
Leave it. Leave it.
I'll do it.
You're making it worse.
Get the dishes.
Mom, I'll get going then.
150,000 yuan.
It's for Grandma's treatment.
A transplant costs 300,000 yuan.
This is only half.
The rest has a condition.
What terms?
Don't you think
one year is too long?
If he studies finance,
after this summer
would be perfect.
You want him gone
to join the Lus.
Zhou Wan, I have ways
to make him go.
It's just that
you need to do your part.
You want me to
make him leave.
Yes.
Great.
If you manage it,
all the Lus will thank you.
After all, no one
wants him to do art.
I won't agree.
This money
was owed to me.
Grandma needs treatment.
Are you going to choose
between Grandma
and Lu Xixiao?
Grandma's illness is serious.
She can't wait long.
What if I
expose you?
Crazy, Guo?
Expose me for what?
Go expose me.
You'd have told him.
Xixiao would know by now.
But he doesn't.
Because you care.
He'd get hurt.
so you hid everything.
Besides,
What good would it do
to kick me out?
If I'm broke, how can I pay?
We're family.
We rise and fall together.
Don't you get it?
What he studies
or wants to do
isn't up to me.
And this is
what he wants most.
That's none of my business.
I need him abroad ASAP.
Then I can join the Lus.
He has to leave.
This money isn't free.
Xixiao.
Let me see. I'll…
He's sick. You knew?
No way.
You two live together.
I've been caring
for Grandma.
I didn't see him.
Thought he was out.
Unbelievable.
So close,
acting like strangers?
Ms. Chen.
Wan.
I bought some things.
He might like them.
Exactly.
He didn't touch his food
or his meds.
Take these to him.
He won't let me in.
How could that be?
If he agreed to let you move in,
he must want to see you.
He doesn't want to see me.
Go on.
Take his medicine too.
Go.
What now?
You just left.
Why are you back?
It's me.
Come in.
I got you some Sanxian noodles.
Eat a little.
So you came.
I thought you were mad.
So you feared I was mad
and stayed away?
Fine.
Good enough excuse.
Then I was angry.
You're… not mad?
Take your medicine.
Turn the AC up.
Bundle up
sweat it out.
Rest for two days.
I'll head back.
Wait.
Leaving?
So heartless.
How'd I get sick?
That day,
I went back for you.
You were gone.
Then I'll stay longer.
Take your meds.
Are you okay?
He didn't bother you?
No.
Don't worry.
Will you come back soon?
You said stay,
Still busy.
I did nothing.
This is my phone.
You what?
Got me sick.
You said you'd stay,
bring me things.
You call this company?
What counts as sincere?
Share my misery.
Catch my cold too.
So annoying.
Eat the noodles.
I'm off.
Come in.
I hope you like it.
From Miss Zhou.
Okay.
Then I'll go.
Morning.
Is your cold better?
Much better.
Thanks to you.
That's good.
Come eat.
Feels like a family.
Xixiao, sit.
I'm full. I'll go.
So early? Where to?
Moon-gazing.
Moon…
Ms. Chen.
Why the rush?
Xixiao's seeing Prof. Qin.
He has his portfolio.
This was on the table.
Maybe he forgot it.
I'll take it to him.
Go slowly.
Prof. Qin.
I want the truth.
What's wrong
with it?
Are you sure?
It may sting.
Absolutely not.
So confident.
If I feared the truth,
I'd still be on that road
racing for my life.
Are these
all your works?
Yes.
You're good.
Honestly,
it should be fine.
But I have little interest
in tutoring you.
I can't help you.
How could you not?
Prof. Qin, if you
were my tutor,
it would help a lot.
Prof. Qin.
I don't know
how to help you.
You keep drawing
what your mother once drew,
don't you?
You're very smart,
like your mother.
But what I see is only imitation.
I can't see where you are in it.
What you truly
want to express.
Your inner emotions
are completely absent
from your work.
Prof. Qin.
I can prepare again.
Listen.
Come back at month's end.
I'll send it.
But this will be your last chance.
Okay. I understand.
Prof. Qin.
Well…
what do you think
I should draw?
It's very simple.
Art is really about expression.
Expressing your own thoughts,
your own feelings,
your own heart,
your own emotions,
what you feel inside,
what you want most,
what you fear losing most.
The only difference is whether you
can face yourself.
You're not foolish.
I think you know.
I know.
But…
What I want
is only in dreams.
Dreams are good material.
The real question is
what it means to you.
I can't see where you are in it.
What you truly want to express.
Your inner emotions
are completely absent
from your work.
What should I draw?
Your own heart,
your own emotions,
what you feel inside,
what you want most.
You know.
What now?
Are you fishing?
Sweet?
Isn't this sweetener?
Trying to fool me?
Sweetener's still sugar.
Doctor said
your medicine's been bitter.
After meds,
hold it, then spit it out.
It'll help the taste.
Don't worry about me,
okay?
Your prep year starts soon.
Focus on
your prep year.
With my grades, why worry?
Forget paying tuition.
Even with scholarships,
they'd beg me
to enroll.
I know you're smart.
I know you're outstanding.
But it hurts me.
Look at other kids.
All they need to do
is study hard.
But besides school,
you worry about me too.
Grandma only hopes
after your prep year,
everything will go smoothly.
I don't expect
your life
to be successful
or dazzling.
I only hope that
even if your life is ordinary,
and plain,
you live kindly and happily.
Grandma.
What makes someone kind?
You are already very kind.
Hello, Jiang Yan.
I need your help with something.
Can you?
Mr. Lu.
Are you booked
to volunteer at ten?
Yes.
Please register here.
We've arranged
a volunteer
to guide you.
Don't worry.
Wan?
With the kids
for morning play.
I'll be your guide.
I often visit this home.
I know it well.
Questions?
Ask me.
Jiang Yan!
Back to class.
Play later,
okay?
Okay.
Lu Xixiao.
I was wrong last time.
Wan chooses
who she sees.
Her choice.
I shouldn't meddle.
I shouldn't
have dragged her
into this.
Don't waste her care.
Lead the way,
Mr. Jiang.
Zhou Wan thought it
might spark something.
Most kids here
keep to themselves.
But after a while,
you'll see their
innocence.
If one gets tricky,
come to me or Zhou Wan.
How hard is it?
The tiger is hunting.
The deer and the piglet
run into the deep woods.
Oh no.
The old man fell down!
Which one is the old man?
Read on your own for a bit.
I'll join you later.
Sit here.
You really came.
I was free anyway.
Why not
meet the kids?
Everyone, look.
We have
a new friend.
Introduce yourself.
Start.
Go, Shengsheng!
Go!
Be careful.
Go, go, go!
You're really into this.
He's going to lose.
No.
Against me?
Wan!
Go!
Get up.
Wan, go!
Okay, okay.
I won.
Wan won!
Didn't you eat?
No.
Did you eat?
I didn't.
Say, "I didn't eat."
Harder.
From then on,
they became best friends
and lived
happily ever after.
Applause!
Did Jiang Yan do well?
Yes!
Let's thank Jiang Yan.
Thank you, Jiang Yan!
Next,
Xixiao's turn.
Okay?
How does this work?
A little sheep.
Reach inside.
I want one too.
Later.
I want a little lion.
Now we'll hear
a new story.
Quiet down, everyone.
Get ready.
Long, long ago…
Same line again?
So boring.
This is no fun.
Long, long ago…
there was
a little black sheep.
She went to look for food
and met a big gray wolf.
I'm scared.
She thought
the gray wolf
was scary.
But then,
the gray wolf
didn't want to hurt her.
The gray wolf
lived alone in the forest.
He wanted no animals
near him.
Because
he looked so different,
he hid away.
He thought she
would fear him.
But to his surprise,
she wasn't afraid at all.
She wanted to play with him.
And the two of them
had a great time.
He invited her home.
He thought
she wouldn't like it.
But to his surprise,
the little sheep said
his home was
the most beautiful,
most beautiful place she'd seen.
They kept playing
and playing together
until it was getting dark,
and she had to go home.
Before she left,
the wolf stopped her.
He gave her a flower.
From his garden,
he took out a rose
he'd treasured for years.
The little sheep asked why.
Why?
Deep in the forest,
I built a garden.
Everyone who came
saw only the gloomy path.
Only you
saw the roses.
So…
this rose is for you.
Thank you, everyone.
Let's thank Xixiao
and Wan.
Thank you, Xixiao.
Thank you, Wan.
You're welcome.
Xinyi.
What did you draw here?
This is a Ferris wheel.
This is a carousel.
What's this one?
This is a bumper car.
What's wrong?
Does it not look right?
Of course not.
You drew it very well.
When I was little,
I rarely went there.
so I didn't recognize it at first.
It's okay.
On my next birthday,
come with me.
Okay?
Okay.
So?
Got inspired?
What a day.
I'm exhausted.
I'm off.
Want to try again?
Next time.
It didn't work?
You did all this for him.
Why?
I can't do much.
Besides,
I owe him this.