Zhou Wan,
so you're targeting
Lu Zhongyue.
Regarding tomorrow's
IP meeting,
I've pre-selected
some suitable companies.
Please take a look.
What did you promise me?
No work at home.
I'll treat you to some jelly.
Calm down.
That's it?
No sincerity.
One more bite.
Not enough.
Still not enough?
Is that okay?
What do you want to do?
You...
I want to create
our own intellectual property
for Lan Yue.
But
we don't have
any experience in this area.
So we can't just dive in blindly.
If we want to do this,
we must find a partner
with relevant experience
in this area.
After you mentioned this requirement,
I've already screened
all companies of this type.
There's one that meets our project needs
and has significant IP
operational experience.
I found one that I think is pretty good.
Shengshi Hua Yu.
That's the one I'm looking for.
No, Xiao, wait.
Shengshi Hua Yu
has already shut down
all its theme parks a few years ago.
And there are rumors in the industry
that there were operational issues.
No, it's not just that.
As far as I know,
there's more to it.
But we won't know the details
until we get in touch with them.
Xin,
did you manage to contact
the person from Shengshi Hua Yu
I asked you to reach out to?
Yes.
I spoke with their lead in Pingchuan,
Lena.
She's willing to meet,
but she wants
to talk to Mr. Lu himself.
Personally?
Yeah, that's what she said.
Wait,
she wants me to talk to her?
Exactly.
If she wants you, just go.
So, who's coming with me?
Me, bro.
I'll go.
Wait, you scared me.
Why are you so proactive this time?
Well,
I heard from them
that Lena is a beauty.
I...
So,
this beauty wants to
talk to Xiao.
Does she have any ulterior motives?
Don't be so sure.
I can't steal Brother Xiao's
spotlight. Alright, alright.
You...
Deputy Director Zhou,
what do you think?
I'll follow the company's arrangement.
That was a mistake.
Fine.
Then the company arranges
you come with me.
Okay.
Xin'er, let's...
As for Wanxiang Queyu,
we should also...
Okay, just a simple handover.
Right, and I think...
When is Mr. Lin coming?
I've been waiting for over an hour.
I didn't expect him to be so unreliable.
Please go over there and wait.
Would you like some tea?
No, thanks.
When will Mr. Lin come?
I'm sorry.
Mr. Lin went out temporarily.
I'm not sure
when she will come back.
But we made an appointment in advance.
I know.
I'm really sorry.
Ms. Lin
changed her schedule last minute.
She probably didn't get a chance to tell you.
Can you give us a definite answer?
Then we can decide
whether to wait
or
make another appointment.
Alright,
I'll make a call and ask.
Hello, Ms. Lin.
You can go up now.
Okay.
Ms. Lin said
she's back now
and she's upstairs.
If you don't mind,
you can go up there to find her.
Okay.
I'll take you there.
Okay, let's go.
Okay.
Watch the stairs.
This way, please.
Mr. Lin.
Please.
Mr. Lin,
I'm Lu Xixiao, the manager
of Lanyue Phase II.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Zhou Wan.
Excuse me,
could I get another glass?
Well,
maybe you should save it for after work.
Please have a seat.
Thank you.
Lu Xixiao,
you don't recognize me?
Ms. Lin,
or should I call you Lena?
We've had a few dates,
and you don't even recognize me?
I'm Lin Na.
Forget it.
You wouldn't remember anyway.
No,
I do remember.
I just didn't recognize you at first.
Now that you mentioned it, I remember.
About what happened back then,
I wasn't very appropriate.
I was young then.
I hope it won't
affect our conversation today.
You were always late
when we dated.
I waited for you so many times,
but you just left
without a word.
Now I make you wait for me,
it's even.
But you are more wronged.
I'm here to work.
Don't worry,
it won't affect your work.
Thank you.
I've sent your cooperation invitation
to the headquarters.
But the chairman refused it.
It's not my fault.
I have no choice.
May I ask
the reason for the chairman's refusal?
I'm not at liberty to disclose it.
Is it the same reason why
Shengshi Huayu
all the amusement parks?
How do you know?
I'm just guessing.
Could you give me some time?
What are you going to do?
I want to give your chairman
a small gift.
A gift?
Do you know
what he's up to?
I'm not sure.
But if he's doing this,
there must be a reason.
Are you his girlfriend?
You're right.
Don't worry.
You don't need to mind me.
I met Lu Xixiao
in the summer
after the college entrance examination.
We haven't
met each other for several times.
He's always been distant with me.
I always thought
he was just
a straightforward, unromantic guy.
But seeing you two today,
I realized
he's actually quite passionate,
just with a poker face,
and he sweats a lot.
Don't you think he's
a bit too tall?
Right?
I look so short next to him.
So he likes
girls like you.
It's good.
Right?
Thank you.
How much longer, Lu Xixiao?
How much longer?
Almost done.
You're the Master Painter L.
I think our chairman
will like it.
This is my first painting
that's not winter-themed.
Please tell him that
his story inspired me.
Okay.
Anything else
you want me to tell him?
I hope
you can consider
our cooperation proposal.
Lan Yue will invest in construction,
and Shengshi Huayu
will handle the core business operations.
Together, we will create
the latest vacation IP.
Lu Xixiao,
I didn't know you were so talented.
All my
inspiration comes from
the lady beside me.
Zhou Wan.
You're really trying to save yourself.
Don't worry.
I'll send it to
our chairman as soon as possible.
I'll let you go.
Take care.
Okay, thank you.
See you next time.
Have a drink next time.
I'll pay.
See you later.
Taking your new girlfriend to meet your ex,
you're really something.
Wait,
I never got a chance
to tell you what happened
between us.
I was having nightmares every night,
but you were out dating every day.
No, it's not like that.
Listen to me.
Zhou Wan, Zhou Wan, Zhou Wan.
Listen to me first.
Do you remember
when we broke up,
you owed me some money.
I was at a bar that day,
drinking.
I was drinking,
and then your transfer message
came in.
While I was reading your message,
someone asked me out.
I said yes on impulse.
At that time...
No.
But we haven't seen each other much.
We lost contact in a few days.
Nothing happened
between us.
Really? You'd better be.
What did you mean
to the chairman?
Because I investigated his story.
It is said that
he has a girlfriend
who he has been dating for eight years.
They are in a good relationship
and are about to get married.
Just when they were about to get engaged,
his girlfriend went diving
and had an accident with him.
She didn't come back up.
So I was thinking,
what else can't be crossed
except for life and death?
At least now we can
choose to be together,
right?
Don't you think
that's romantic?
What does romance have to do with you?
I'm a very
romantic person.
How so?
Here.
You can do magic?
Remember this?
It's unforgettable, right?
I should've told you earlier.
Zhou Wan,
want to date me?
Yes or no?
Aren't we dating?
Where did you
get this balloon?
I won't tell you.
I know what you're going to do.
I can help you.
I got news from Shengshi Huayu.
Come here.
Hello.
The chairman said your work
touched him.
He likes it very much.
He asked me to thank you for him.
And,
he seriously considered
your cooperation plan.
He said...
What did he say? Come on.
He said he was willing to try,
but all the IP,
the core design of visual expression
and core design
must be led by you.
Wan,
I wish Lan Yue and
Shengshi Hua Yu a happy cooperation.
Director Zhou and Director Lu
have won an important partner
for Lan Yue.
It's such a happy thing.
Wan, we should celebrate.
Right.
I'll treat you to the most expensive
tea restaurant downstairs.
Have tea.
But it's on Director Lu.
Thank you, Xiao.
Okay, no problem.
I'll pay.
Director Lu and Wan
are a good match.
Why do you say that?
They are revolutionary friends.
Why do you think
they are in love?
-You don't understand.  -Right.
Only people who are tacit
can work together
and understand each other.
It's like a peace talk.
What's the difference?
All right.
Let's go to eat. Stop it.
Are we eating or not?
Yeah, yeah, let's have some tea.
Let's go eat.
Let's go.
Meeting's over.
Still saying you don't deserve it?
Wan.
Dad, Grandma,
we're here to see you!
I brought someone
very important with me today.
Grandma has met him,
but Dad hasn't.
Sir, Ma'am,
my name is Lu Xixiao,
Zhou Wan's boyfriend.
I'm here with Wanwan
to visit you.
Don't worry,
I'll take good care of her
when you're not around,
and make sure she's well taken care of.
I won't let her
suffer any injustice.
When I was little,
I loved to
lean on my dad's shoulder.
I always felt
the safest place in the world
was my dad's shoulder.
Later...
Everyone, please don't leave yet.
Can you give me a few more days?
I'll find a way, I promise.
I know you're all struggling,
but I'll sort this out
in a few days.
This is all...
Let's go get our money back!
Calm down, let's talk this out!
Don't go rushing in!
Don't!
Sir,
When are you going to
pay us the wages you owe us?
No.
I've already paid
some of it to you.
Right?
I'll find a way to pay the rest.
Give me some time, okay?
Give you time?
No, you can't...
Who's going to give us time?
Our family
relies on this for food!
Don't go!
Come here!
Come back!
Listen,
as long as you have money, Dad,
we have food.
But our child
doesn't even have food!
You are like this now.
If you die,
who will we go to for money?
Zhou Wan,
I'm not the one who killed your dad.
You think you are smart,
but you even hate
the wrong person.
Lu Zhongyue has been scheming all his life,
cold-blooded and selfish,
harming too many innocent people.
Some things
come with a price,
but the time hasn't come yet.
Because of Lu Zhongyue,
my family was destroyed.
Even so,
my dad was misunderstood by everyone.
But he was such a good person.
I can't let him
bear the blame forever.
I want to reveal the truth
and clear his name.
I believe
justice will prevail.
Zhou Wan,
do what you want to do.
But I don't want to drag you into this again,
or put you in a difficult position.
After all, Lu Zhongyue is your father.
I'll always be with you.
No matter what happens,
we'll face it together.
I tried so hard
to get into Phase II
just to
get some clues.
Unfortunately,
I haven't found any evidence.
But I found this.
This is a furniture factory
acquired by Phase II.
The board hadn't decided
to have an internal bidding,
So this project
is still in Lu Zhongyue's hands.
Yinshan Furniture Factory
has always been stable.
It's an old factory.
If it wants to make money,
it would have expanded long ago.
It stays in Jinshawan
to control the quality of the products.
This is also the period when Lan Yue
acquired the Phase II land.
The furniture sold
has such big problems.
So you suspect Lu Zhongyue
is doing the same thing again.
It's a good breakthrough.
But we still need
to find evidence.
So I want to go to Jinshawan.
I'll go with you.
I think you shouldn't go.
Did you forget?
I just promised your grandparents
that I would
never let you face
or bear these things alone.
I'll take good care of you
and protect you.
Okay.
Let's go together.
It seems to be this house.
Excuse me, sorry to bother you.
Are there any adults at home?
Grandma.
Who are you?
Hello, grandma.
Sorry to bother you.
Grandma.
You... you are...
Who are you?
We don't accept interviews.
We are not the media.
Not the media.
We've tried calling
your family,
but no one answered.
So we thought
we'd come and talk.
There's nothing to talk about.
My family will repay the money.
Now, if you'll excuse us.
We're not here for money.
Just go.
Alright, let's go.
Go.
Let's go.
What if I can prove
that Mr. Wang's factory issues
were set up?
To be honest,
I've been through
what you're going through.
I get it.
I genuinely want to help you.
If Mr. Wang
is willing to accept our help
and tell us about
what happened to the factory,
we will do
our utmost
to bring you justice.
Miss,
can I borrow a pen and paper?
Thank you.
Grandma,
this is my contact information.
If you encounter
any issues in the future,
not just the factory problems,
but also your sister's problems,
or any difficulties,
you can call me.
I'll call my son.
I can't guarantee he'll accept it.
It's okay.
We'll wait for your reply.
We just got here.
We bought you some food and drinks.
And some for your sister.
No, no,
don't bother.
It's okay.
We'll put this inside.
We'll put it in your room.
Put it in the room.
We'll
visit you often.
Sis,
study hard,
study well,
and read good books.
Academic scores aren't as important
as learning ability.
Thank you, sis.
Thank you, bro.
Okay,
You need to sign here.
Sign here.
So we have to wait for the buyer
to come back from abroad
to finalize the contract, right?
Yes, Mrs. Jiang.
They will give you
the deposit first.
After he returns to the country,
they will give you the final payment
and handle the transfer procedures.
But the house...
Here's the thing.
The buyer
wants to move in right away
when he comes back,
so we need you
to vacate the house now.
No problem. I understand.
Thank you, Mrs. Jiang.
Here are the keys.
I'll take this call.
Make yourself at home.
Mr. Wang,
you can come by this afternoon.
No problem.
Jiang Fan,
I've sold the house.
I'll transfer the money to you later.
Remember to give the key to the agent.
Okay, I got it.
Daddy!
I missed you so much!
Guess
what delicious food
I bring you.
Grilled chicken wings.
Dad, look.
Those are all brought by
Sister Wanwan.
Brother A'Xiao also said
he would sponsor my study.
Sit down first.
Lily,
what did I tell you before?
Don't trust others easily.
I got into
this situation
because I
trusted someone.
Dad,
Sister Wanwan and Brother A'Xiao
are not like that.
You just met them.
How do you know
they're not like that?
That girl,
when she was little,
she was just like us.
Before the first phase
of Lanyue Resort was built,
do you remember the building materials factory?
I think
they're both good people
They're genuinely here to help us.
I know.
I've already agreed
to meet them.
Mom,
don't worry about it.
See?
Where did you learn to make
soft-boiled eggs like this?
Thank you.
I loved eating
soft-boiled eggs when I was a kid,
especially with tomato and egg noodles.
But my mom thought it was too much work,
so we stopped eating them.
It's good to be an adult.
You can eat whatever you want.
I've been thinking a lot about
when we first met
as kids.
I never understood
why you always dodged me,
avoided my questions,
and were afraid of troubling others.
But now I understand.
You experienced
too many changes as a child.
You've been losing things
since childhood.
So you force yourself
to face the world
in a very calm
to deal with the world.
Every time I think about it,
I feel like
if I had met that little Zhou Wan
sooner,
I would have told her
not to be afraid,
not to worry,
and that I would be there
to help her grow up.
So,
you have to understand,
soft-boiled eggs aren't a hassle,
and neither are you.
And I actually like it when you need me.
Why are you so good?
I wasn't good enough to you before,
but from now on, I'll try harder,
even better than how you've treated me.
You said it.
Then that promise
should start counting
from tonight.
Okay.
Then...
Is anyone home?
Lily.
Hello, you're here.
Hello.
How are you doing lately?
Pretty good.
Grandma,
why are you here again?
Has Mr. Wang returned?
Did he agree to meet?
Dad,
the older brother and sister are here.
Mr. Wang.
What else do you want?
Here's the thing.
we know
that someone set up the factory
to acquire the land.
But we need some evidence
to reveal the truth.
My dad means
why didn't you come
with the man who came last night?
Man?
What man?
Wasn't the man who came last night
wasn't he with you?
I've given him all the evidence
of the land acquisition.
Do you know his name?
Are you
from the Wang's factory?
My name is Jiang Yan.
This is for you.
-A small gift. -No, no, no.
I don't want it.
Don't be afraid.
I'm here to help you
with the factory case.
Yinshan Furniture Factory was forced to close.
It's because of the dealers.
Right?
I've dealt with similar cases before.
I know how to help you.
Thank you,
brother.
But someone is already
helping us.
Someone?
May I ask who they are?
Sister Wanwan
and Brother A'Xiao.
What a coincidence!
We are together.
You can rest assured.
I didn't expect them
to be more anxious than me.
Is Manager Wang at home?
Yongli?
Yongli.
A guy surnamed Jiang.
Isn't he
with you?
We know him.
But he's not
with us.
I called him.
He's been
our colleague for years.
Don't worry.
I've given him
what you wanted.
Miss Zhou,
I'm not hoping
to save my factory anymore.
I just want to pay off my debts
and stop making Lily
live like this.
I understand.
I'll do my best.
Thank you, Wanwan.
Excuse me.
Zhou Wan, let's talk.
Alone.
We'll be going.
Sorry to bother.
Goodbye, brothers and sisters.
Study hard.
See you.
If you don't know the truth,
the scenery here
is really beautiful.
It wasn't this beautiful before.
That used to be a factory.
This was a large open space.
My dad taught me
to ride a bike here.
He told me that
life would get better
and we would live in a bigger
and better house.
I didn't understand it then.
I just felt
that living with my parents
and grandmother
was very happy.
It was a simple wish,
but it could never be realized again.
I've seen the materials
Mr. Wang has.
There are his records
of dealing with the dealer,
chat logs,
and the evidence he collected
of the dealer's
close relationship with Lu Zhongyue.
It's a pity that
this dealer
is not the same person
who caused your father's
factory to close down.
So I was right.
You went to Mr. Wang
after you found out
about my dad.
How did you know?
As the Strategic Director,
it's easy for me
to see the materials.
Besides Mr. Wang's,
I also found some evidence
of irregularities in the project.
Zhou Wan,
I can do everything
Lu Xixiao can do,
and I can also do
what he can't do.
I can help you
expose Lu Zhongyue
and give you a better life.
Come back to me, okay?
Just like when we were young.