[The Legend of Rosy Clouds]
[Episode 1]
Legend has it
that in a remote southeastern corner,
far from the central lands,
disasters plagued the region
year after year,
and the common people lived in misery.
At that time, a towering hero emerged.
Both brave and wise,
he brought order to the realm.
With the support of the 9 families—
Qi, Zheng, Fan, Wei, and others—
he planned with foresight
and carved out an era of prosperity.
He was the co-lord of the Nine Cities,
Qi Hua.
The 9 families who aided him back then
are the very Nine Noble Families of today.
Thirteen years ago,
the mayor was struck by a grave illness.
His sons fought for succession,
plunging the land into chaos again.
Once again, the Nine Noble Families
stepped in to restore order,
but at a devastating cost,
suffering heavy casualties.
In the end,
only the youngest son,
Qi Zheng, remained.
The Nine Noble Families earned
the admiration of the people,
and their stories have been passed down
through generations.
[Fan Yun, the Young Lady
of the Fan Family]
And so,
in gratitude for their sacrifices,
the common folks named the land
beneath their feet the "Nine Cities."
Teacher! Teacher!
I have another question.
Go ahead.
Then, is the current mayor
a qualified mayor?
You mean Qi Zheng?
I believe
a qualified mayor
must be diligent in governance
and personally attend to all affairs.
[Huiyun Pavilion]
[Mayor, Qi Zheng]
Today, the sky is clear
and the air is refreshing—
perfect for reading documents
and reviewing memorials.
Yan Jiang.
Yan Jiang!
[Yan Jiang, Assistant Officer
of the Bureau of Affairs]
I'll leave
these tasks to you.
These? I...
Yan Jiang.
Yan Jiang, your writing flows
with brilliance—every word like a gem.
You'll surely complete the tasks
I've assigned you
in one smooth, masterful sweep.
I have full confidence in you.
Wait.
My Lord.
This isn't how the idioms
are supposed to be used.
Also,
you are the mayor.
These memorials should be reviewed
by you personally.
You and I are as close as brothers.
It makes no difference who handles them.
Have confidence in yourself.
But...
Don't let me down.
I believe in you.
Where are you going?
To relax for a bit.
Teacher. Teacher.
If the current mayor
had a teacher like you,
he'd surely be able to do it.
If one day
I become the mayor's teacher,
I'll make sure he governs with diligence
and works for the well-being
of all the people.
As for you,
make sure you study hard
to make the Nine Cities
stronger and better.
Understand?
-Understood.
Gao Ran?
-Mr. Gao Ran.
[Gao Ran, the Fan Family's Adopted Son]
You must all be hungry.
Come here.
Mr. Gao Ran.
What did you bring?
-I want some too.
-Take it slow.
-Mr. Gao Ran!
-Careful.
-Thank you, Mr. Gao Ran.
Everyone gets some.
I want some too.
Here, be careful.
Thank you, Mr. Gao Ran.
Class is over for today.
Hurry home, everyone.
Goodbye, Teacher.
Let's go home.
Let's go. Hurry.
Fan Yun.
I'm here to take you home.
Let's go home too.
Go ahead, what's the agenda today?
I'll just second it.
The ancients once said,
"a wife is a husband's greatest support."
[Lyu Wenzhong, One of
the Three Elders of Nine Cities]
[Zheng Yuan, Master of the Zheng family,
One of the Three Elders of Nine Cities]
Yet look at our mayor—
since coming of age,
he's been holding selections
for a wife every year,
but to no avail.
[Zhao Chang, One of
the Three Elders of Nine Cities]
As the old saying goes,
"cross that bridge when one comes to it."
But now the bridge
is broken.
So, in your opinion, Lord Lyu,
you think the mayor should start a family
before
pursuing his great cause?
Exactly.
Let's find
a virtuous wife for the mayor
who can subtly and positively
influence him.
I think...
Wait, let me finish.
Perhaps
it will be of great benefit to the mayor.
That's all.
You're done, right?
I say we stop discussing it here.
Let's just pick one for the mayor
and be done with it.
Lord Zhao,
you truly are
a veteran of the battlefield.
Look at you...
Don't you know
that there are already rumors going around
saying that we 3 old men
have been sidelining the mayor,
and that's why
he's been neglecting state affairs?
Is that so?
Then, Lord Lyu,
do you have a candidate in mind?
[Fan Residence]
I owe so much rent for
this private school.
It's so frustrating.
If only this house
were worth more.
I'm so poor.
-He blew up the kitchen again.
[Fan Qi, Manager of Qilin Pavilion]
Father!
-Lord Fan Qi.
-Is the pot alright?
Don't come over!
I can do it!
You may be able to hold on,
but this kitchen can't anymore.
Father, how many times has this been?
Come here!
Let me check my pot. Did you...
Did you burn another hole in it, Father?
Dear father,
you must be a pot seller's best customer.
Well,
I just wanted to make tea.
I didn't expect it to end up like this.
Who's this important guest that even
our Lord Fan Qi—
who neither exercises
nor knows his crops,
has to make tea for them himself?
It's Lord Lyu.
Is he important enough?
-Lord Lyu?
Lord Lyu,
please have some tea.
Father.
Don't tell me
you just used this well water
to make tea for Lord Lyu.
Lord Lyu.
Warm tea.
Please enjoy.
I wonder what brings you here today,
Lord Lyu?
There is something I need your help with.
If you are willing to accept it,
the reward is 500 taels of gold.
This 50 taels is a deposit.
I accept.
Just tell me what you need.
Anything.
F-Fan Yun.
Miss Fan.
Come on. Come on.
Come sit, and let's talk.
I want to discuss with you guys
to let Fan Yun
enter the Qi Residence,
marry the mayor
and become his wife,
and Gao Ran will be specially
granted permission
to enter the Qi Residence
as the Head of Guardian Corps.
L-L-Lyu...
Lord Lyu.
This matter...
Is non-negotiable.
This matter is non-negotiable, indeed.
Wait, but...
You scared me.
Why are you hiding here
drinking alone?
I have something to discuss with you.
Let's go visit their residence tomorrow
and return all the gold...
No.
Why?
Lord Lyu wants me
to enter the mayor's residence
to influence him in a positive way.
Since I've always wanted to be an official
since I was little,
we might as well enter that residence
and check it out.
We might actually be able to do something,
right?
I still think it's inappropriate.
Gao Ran.
Let's think about it from another angle.
We received a betrothal gift of
500 taels of gold.
That's 500 taels of gold!
With this money,
we can support the private school,
right?
Am I right?
Right?
Gao Ran, that's 500 taels of gold.
She hasn't even entered the residence yet,
but the Three Elders have already
sent their test.
Look at this.
Fan Yun.
These gifts from the 3 families—
how do you plan to deal with them?
The meaning of a gift
doesn't lie in receiving,
but in giving.
Since the Three Elders are
showing such kindness,
if I were to send these back,
wouldn't that be rejecting their goodwill?
Besides,
I've never even worn
such expensive silk brocade before.
So you mean...
I mean...
Just wait and see.
♪ Spring winds, autumn rain ♪
♪ Flowers bloom for a single season ♪
♪ Fallen petals turn into mud ♪
♪ Nurturing all living things ♪
♪ Never once asking for
even a single cent ♪
♪ Yet willing, in the name of the clouds ♪
♪ To ignite myself ♪
♪ For the people under heaven ♪
♪ Bright moon, clear breeze ♪
♪ Accompany a heart without dust ♪
♪ All the noise and chaos ♪
♪ The rises and falls of life ♪
♪ What does hardship matter? ♪
♪ In the moment of looking back ♪
♪ This life is worth it ♪
♪ When longing for dawn ♪
♪ Who are the dream-walkers? ♪
♪ Facing the light ♪
♪ Singing a long song along the way ♪
♪ I am willing to become ♪
♪ A long-lasting lantern ♪
♪ Lighting the path ahead ♪
♪ Bypassing right and wrong ♪
♪ Prejudice and fanaticism ♪
♪ Until this road ♪
♪ Has no more obstacles ♪
♪ Time flows like water ♪
♪ Not wasting years of perseverance ♪
♪ I am willing to become ♪
♪ The countless lanterns ♪
♪ Lighting the path ahead ♪
♪ Warming the world ♪
♪ Flickering like a galaxy of stars ♪
♪ Looking at this scenery ♪
♪ Still like in youth ♪
♪ Eyes clear and pure ♪
♪ Mountains and seas change over time ♪
♪ Someone will remember ♪
♪ As long as the heart's light remains ♪
Master.
♪ There won't be loneliness ♪
She's wearing our silk brocade—
a single-layer robe embroidered with
a golden "double happiness" butterfly pattern.
She's wearing our plain Jiang silk—
a stone-blue Kesi brocade ceremonial skirt
embroidered with auspicious cloud,
golden bat, and golden dragon patterns.
She's wearing our Kesi
golden "double happiness"
and butterfly pattern front-opening jacket
with an embroidered collar.
Her Ladyship
sure knows how to be impartial.
I've waited for 4 whole hours.
How much longer do I have to wait?
This is so uncomfortable.
So this is what the inside of
the Qi Residence looks like.
So many rare treasures—
how much money must they have cost?
As a mayor,
he ignores the livelihood and safety
of the common people
yet lives such an extravagant life
in his residence.
I'm so mad.
My Lord.
If the Three Elders find out
that you didn't go to your wife's room
on your wedding night...
So what if they find out?
The matters I handle every day
are all important matters.
-Each one concerns our state and people.
-The mayor?
How can I be distracted?
Then, about tomorrow's morning meeting...
Of course I won't go.
So he...
J-Just left?
My Lady, please have some tea.
[Suyin, Maid of Qi Residence]
You...
Who are you?
My name is Suyin.
I've been appointed to serve you, My Lady.
I see.
It's okay, it's okay. Come on, get up.
I deserve to die!
I'm sorry!
I didn't mean to!
Please forgive me, My Lady.
It's okay.
I'll just wipe it clean myself later.
Come on,
get up.
You don't blame me, My Lady?
Why should I blame you?
It's just a teacup.
Doesn't this happen all the time?
What's there to blame?
But...
But
from now on, with me,
you don't have to be
so formal.
You can be more relaxed.
You are truly the best lady I've ever met.
So you mean
there are other ladies in this residence?
No, no, absolutely not.
His Lordship only has you as
his one and only wife.
You are unprecedented in all these years—
absolutely one of a kind, utterly unique,
the only lady
His Lordship has ever fallen for.
A message from His Lordship.
My Lady,
His Lordship is tied up with
important matters tonight
and will not return to the room to rest.
He specifically sent me here to tell you.
Got it.
Then,
I will take my leave.
So the rumors I heard before
about the mayor keeping away from women
turn out to be true.
Being the mayor
is really easy.
You all may leave.
Even my wife was chosen by
the Three Elders.
How should I get rid of them?
They'll only oppose
what I'm going to do next even more.
Suyin,
do you think
the mayor
will come to our place today?
According to Attendant Wei,
His Lordship
probably won't come back to sleep
these few days.
How am I supposed to start teaching
if he doesn't come back?
I see.
Alright then.
Suyin, why don't you
tell me something about the mayor?
You entered the residence earlier than me.
You must know more than I do.
Come on. Don't just stand there.
Sit down and talk.
I wouldn't dare.
Come on, sit down.
Haven't I told you
that when you're with me,
you don't have to be so formal?
Be more relaxed.
Go ahead.
Look,
as the mayor's new bride,
I haven't seen my husband
for 5 days in a row.
I suppose there's no one
more miserable than me in this world.
After coming of age,
His Lordship has been very perfunctory
in official matters.
He rarely participates in
important state affairs,
but loves to have fun.
He loves most to
drink and have cricket fighting
in the residence for fun.
If you can have fun
along with him, My Lady,
it'll definitely please His Lordship
greatly.
His Lordship once said
that these are all for the inspiration
needed for poetry writing.
That's what he said?
He's really good at inventing excuses.
A-Actually, His Lordship
isn't always like this.
I see that he usually loves studying
quite a bit.
He often reads alone in the study.
In the study?
Come catch me!
I'm here!
There's someone here.
I got you!
Let me feel who you are.
Why are you so chubby?
Wei Zhu.
Why do you have a beard today?
Let me see.
I said I didn't want to play,
but Wei Zhu insisted that I play.
This person has been
wandering around here.
What is he doing?
Sir,
do you need any help?
No.
Alright then.
Wait.
Can you take me to the Qilin Pavilion?
Qilin Pavilion?
So you were just lost, Sir.
Of course not.
Stop talking nonsense.
Are you going to lead the way or not?
Come with me.
This way.
I told you it was this way.
This is Qilin Pavilion.
Basically all the books you want
can be found here.
Should I thank you or something?
I told you I could find the way.
I told you,
if it's more than 30 paces away,
you're bound to get lost.
[Go Tactics]
Weren't you coming to Qilin Pavilion
to look for a book?
Yes.
I happened to come to Qilin Pavilion
to borrow a book.
[Wei Ying, Commander of
the Guardian Corps]
I was lucky enough to
have run into this gentleman today.
He brought me in.
Did he bring you in,
or the other way around?
Wei Ying!
By the way,
what's your name?
My name is
Fan Yun.
-Fan Yun?
My Lady.
I am Wei Ying,
Commander of the Left Guardian Corps.
And this is...
Yan Jiang, Assistant Officer of
the Bureau of Affairs.
I'm also the son of your uncle,
Lord Fan Hui.
So we are all family.
Yes, exactly.
Then thank you both
for lending me the book today.
I will study it carefully when I get back.
-Alright.
-Sure. Sure.
Well then, I'll take my leave.
Take care, My Lady.
Goodbye.
So...
This is the mayor's wife,
Lord Fan Qi's daughter?
It's rare to see you
being so kind to a woman.
Well, I'm not like you, Lord Wei.
You always have women flocking to you.
So inside Qi Residence,
there's such a beautiful place.
No wonder everyone wants to get in here.
♪ Watch how flowers bloom and wither ♪
♪ Count how many springs
and autumns pass ♪
♪ Why the sighs and regrets? ♪
I...
I didn't mean to pick it.
♪ Lovers wait a lifetime ♪
Anyway,
it's yours now.
♪ Love cannot be cut away ♪
♪ How to let go? ♪
Thanks.
Where's the Go manual
that was still on the table a while ago?
You're the great Commander of
the Left Left Guardian Corps,
yet you're making a fuss over a Go manual?
That's no ordinary Go manual.
It holds the mayor's secrets.
Secrets?
What secrets?
It records
the mayor's personal notes
on food, drink, and entertainment,
as well as...
All the bad things he said
about each official.
What?
H-He wrote down bad things
in a little notebook?
Then... If the old scholars find out
about this,
they'll never stop nagging him about it.
Exactly.
Don't even get me started.
I, Wei Ying, am the grand Commander
of the Left Guardian Corps,
and you are
the youngest official
in the history of the Bureau of Affairs.
We should both have bright futures.
Yet we end up
idling around in this place every day
and wasting our youth.
Well,
since the mayor just got married,
maybe his wife will be able to
keep him in check from now on.
Are you really sure
that lady can keep the mayor in check?
I hope so.
Sir.
Sir?
You
still haven't finished reading yet?
I'm not in a hurry.
Maybe you should hurry up, Sir.
It's getting dark.
I still don't know who you are,
flower-admiring gentleman.
How about this?
Once I make tea
with these phoenix flowers,
I'll definitely let you taste it first
as a return gift.
My name is...
My name is Wei Ying.
Wei?
You are Wei Ying?
I'm Wei Ying, Commander of
the Left Guardian Corps.
This person is dressed in a noble-woven
cross-collared wide robe,
wearing a pure white
mutton-fat jade pendant
and ice-silk silver thread ribbons,
with tiger-patterned Liuhe boots
on his feet.
Only the mayor...
The mayor?
So you are
the famed Commander Wei.
I've heard a lot about you.
They say you are the mayor's favorite.
It's an honor to meet you today.
You truly live up to your reputation.
Truly a great "genius."
And who are you?
I...
My name is Fan Yun.
So you are my...
I mean, the mayor's
wife?
I've only entered the residence
and already met you, Lord Wei.
How fortunate.
Being near you, it seems
I can feel some of the mayor's...
The mayor's...
Radiance.
What kind of radiance?
Just... The mayor's
dazzling radiance!
The mayor's brilliance shines everywhere,
and we can all feel it.
I have important matters to attend to,
so I'll take my leave.
Thanks for this.
Saying he's Wei Ying?
Why would he call himself Wei Ying?
The two of them have finally met.
Indeed they have.
Married for days
and nowhere to be seen.
It seems the mayor's wife
is nothing special.
Better to find someone else soon.
I've started looking. I have.
I beg to differ.
Look, those two
just got married
and aren't very familiar with
each other yet.
If they get to know each other more,
maybe they'll become inseparable.
Let's wait a bit longer.
Wait a bit longer.
Lord Wei?
Please don't let anyone else see me.
Dressed like this, sneaking around—
where are you going?
I...
I wanted to
sneak out of the residence.
How dare you?
How could the mayor's wife
leave the mansion freely?
Didn't your maids tell you the rules?
I have no choice.
Lord Wei.
You don't know,
it's been many days
since I entered the residence,
and I still haven't seen the mayor.
I know the mayor must be very busy
and diligent,
so
I was thinking when I see him
for the first time,
I could give him a gift
to make him happy.
What thing can't be found
in the Qi Residence
that you have to go outside to buy?
The things in the Qi Residence
are indeed abundant and good,
but the mayor definitely
won't find them novel.
But
it's different outside.
There are many
fun and entertaining things
on the bustling streets.
Oh, right, there are also
countless strange and novel stories.
Lord Wei,
I beg you.
Please be generous
and let me out,
okay?
The bustling streets,
strange and novel stories?
How fun
and how novel are they?
Well,
they are just very fun
and very novel.
Considering your sincerity,
I might just let you go.
Really?
But you have to take me with you.
This is the East Market.
Nobles often gather here.
Look,
there are brush shops, taverns,
jewelry stores,
and so on.
In short,
no matter how rare the item is,
you can
find it here.
[West Market]
And this is the West Market.
Commoners usually make a living here.
The environment here used to be very poor,
but it has improved a bit
in the last couple of years.
So these shops
opened up one after another.
Could it be that the sight
before the mayor has touched him?
Teachable.
Well, Lord Wei,
you command the Guardian Corps after all.
Why do you look like
you've never
been out on the streets before?
I'm usually busy with official duties
and rarely have the leisure
to stroll around the market.
Well, Lord Wei, you may not know,
this street is for leisure to you,
but to many people,
it's their livelihood.
Aren't you thinking of buying a gift
for the mayor?
I think these two are not bad.
Lord Wei,
don't you want to check out
the West Market more?
They all have a hard time.
Isn't this the joy of
strolling down the street?
However,
compared to the West Market,
this East Market
is indeed much more prosperous.
You know your stuff.
It's not too much to ask you
to stroll with me for a bit, is it?
No, no.
Not at all.
I'm best
at this.
Let's go.
I knew it.
Since you've got so much money
to squander,
I'll help you out.
Sorry.
I'm really sorry, Mayor.
I had no choice
but to take a little "commission"
off the top.
Just think of it as taking from the people
and using it for the people.
If you want to blame someone,
blame Lord Lyu.
Who would have thought
he was paying me the gift money
in installments?
This way,
I'll have enough for next month's rent
for the private school,
Father and Gao Ran's
living expenses,
and the students' ink and brushes.
I can even renovate the private school.
But when I have money in the future,
I will definitely pay you back.
I promise.
Wait for me!
[Huan'e House]
Lord Wei, do you want to go in?
You have acquaintances
in this kind of place as well?
Who knows?
Follow me.
Please come in, guests!
Come on, two VIPs!
This place is called Huan'e House.
It has only been established
for a few years,
but it's already the top tavern
in Ling'an City.
It connects to the central road
in the front
and the river passing through the city
in the back.
Whether you ride a horse, walk,
or come by boat,
it's extremely convenient.
Therefore, the composition of
the coming and going people is complex.
All factions in Ling'an
and all channels and news
converge here.
Wait for it.
The show
is about to start.
Lord Wei, have some water first.
Bravo! Bravo!
Welcome everyone,
to Huan'e House.
Our Huan'e House
is different from ordinary taverns.
We sell both talent and news.
This is what makes our boss, Miss Hu Die,
so remarkable.
Only those who spend enough money
to enter her boudoir
can get the news.
This is the famous
"Seating Ceremony" in Ling'an.
Interesting.
Isn't it?
This is my first time seeing an auction,
and it's actually for
a chance to ask questions face-to-face.
How is it?
Isn't it more fun than the Qi Residence?
Lord Wei.
You can give it a try too.
Is there anything you are curious about,
or anyone?
How could there be anything I don't know?
Let's keep watching.
If you don't bid,
how can I get my commission?
10 taels.
I bid 30 taels.
I bid 50 taels.
80 taels.
I bid 100 taels.
120 taels.
150 taels.
300 taels!
Let's see who dares to
compete with me today.
300 taels...
Lord Wei.
You bid 300 taels.
I don't think anyone would dare
to compete with you.
Anyone else bidding against
this gentleman?
No matter who bids higher,
I'll double it.
[Lou Qiyan, Owner of Juyun Pavilion]