[The Legend of Rosy Clouds]
[Episode 2]
[Lou Qiyan, Owner of Juyun Pavilion]
Who...
Who is that man?
Double?
Just expected
of the boss of Juyun Pavilion.
Is Young Master Qiyan
also lusting after Miss Hu Die's beauty
and dying to see her in person?
He's just a lecher.
Now, he's trying to acquire Huan'e House.
Who knows what his real purpose is?
So, he is
Lou Qiyan, head of Juyun Pavilion.
Lord Wei,
it was this man who harmed
the businesses in the West Market.
We must not lose to him.
One hundred taels of gold!
Well done!
Two hundred taels of gold.
Two hundred and ten taels of gold!
I thought you'd offer more.
Five hundred taels of gold!
Five hundred taels of gold?
Could you offer a higher bid?
Five...
Five hundred and ten taels of gold!
Today, I'll fight you till the end.
Adding ten gold taels at a time...
Are you here to mess with me?
One thousand two hundred taels of gold!
-One thousand two hundred taels...
--One thousand two hundred taels...
How is he so rich?
I don't think Miss Hu Die and I are
meant to meet up today.
Goodbye, Miss Hu Die.
You are Young Master Qiyan, right?
The fact that you offered
1,200 taels of gold today
for a meeting with Miss Hu Die,
you must have
an important question to ask.
Given that, I should kindly do you a favor
and let you have it.
No, no, no.
We can also have an important question
to ask.
Won't it ache your heart to quit so soon?
Raise the bid, please.
No, it won't.
Just call a higher bid.
How about you offer 1,200 taels of gold
and I pay an extra ten?
I-I don't have that much money.
Alright.
Congratulations, Young Master Qiyan!
For god's sake, you're the Nine Cities'...
Well,
I mean you command
the Nine Cities's Guardian Corps.
How can you let him walk all over us?
The pattern on his collar
seems to be exclusive to the nobles.
Is Juyun Pavilion secretly connected
to the Nine Noble Families?
What?
I'll pay you three taels to do me a favor.
Three taels?
You really think
money can get you everything, huh?
Ten taels then.
Tell me. What favor is it?
What beautiful music.
Beautiful music?
Boss,
aren't you tone-deaf?
This leader of merchants reeks of money.
Why is he suddenly in the mood
for refined art?
I've long heard
that the owner of Huan'e House
is incomparably gorgeous
with excellent erhu skills.
You truly live up to your reputation.
Sir,
have you heard this piece before?
No, never.
Then why would you...
I've never heard it,
but I know the meaning of it.
I can feel...
that it's an ode to vastness
and freedom.
Sir, that's quite
a unique insight.
I must have made a fool of myself.
I just hope you, who's keenly
appreciative of my talent,
aren't disappointed.
Keenly appreciative, huh?
Young Master Qiyan,
I wonder why you went to great lengths
for a chance
to meet me in my boudoir.
You and I both know the reason.
Let's not beat around the bush.
You must've figured out my real purpose,
so you repeatedly turned away
my men from Juyun Pavilion.
You're mistaken, sir.
I'm only running
a small business here.
How could I have expected
that it would catch your eye?
No need for modesty, miss.
Since you don't know much
about Juyun Pavilion,
it's only reasonable
that you feel wary.
Truth to be told,
this time, I came all the way here
to buy out the entire Huan'e House.
You...
You're looking to
acquire Huan'e House?
The tavern business in Ling'an
seems lucrative.
But the interests involved
are tangled and complex.
That has caused countless merchants
to suffer failures.
Nonetheless, your house managed to rise
to the top in just a few years.
There must be an expert
guiding you from behind.
Miss Hu Die, I wonder
if you could introduce me to this person.
I...
Well...
Young Master Qiyan,
please ignore those street rumors.
How about this?
Pay me the deposit
for the Seating Ceremony first.
Then we can have a nice talk.
What do you think?
Girls!
Make sure this young master
is well entertained.
Perhaps when he finds it enjoyable,
he'll come pay for service here every day.
You ladies...
Fancy a fun time, mister?
Mister.
Come have fun with us!
I'll pay you ten taels of gold
to obtain the fabric pattern
from Young Master Qiyan's collar.
Why...
Why do you want that?
Because it looks pretty.
I'll have the Garment Manufacturing Bureau
produce something alike.
As long as...
there's adequate pay,
I'll do all your bidding.
Deal.
Consider the task done.
What's going on?
You really are not Miss Hu Die.
Greetings, Young Master Qiyan.
How about
we meet again another time?
Until the next time we weet!
Guards!
-Boss.
-Go get her!
-Yes.
Mr. Lou.
[Owner of Huan'e House, Miss Hu Die]
Miss Hu Die.
Lord Wei! Lord Wei!
How did I do?
Impressive, huh?
You really are something.
Stop there!
What is this about?
Hurry, hurry!
Run!
Get a move on!
Halt!
You lot, go catch them!
-Yes!
How satisfying.
Turn Ling'an upside down if necessary.
Just find those people for me.
-Yes.
[Juyun Pavilion]
You must be tired from all the studying
at the Directorate of Education today.
[Zheng Shi, the second young master
of the Zheng family]
You should have some pig brains
for nutrition.
These are spicy pig brains.
These were cooked with garlic.
These were braised with sauce.
I had these dishes
prepared especially for you.
Thank you, Grandfather.
But, Grandfather,
I already learned
what the Directorate of Education
is teaching now back in Jingcheng.
The old tutors here
are not as good as expected.
Mind your language.
Master!
Young Master Shi, you're back.
What's that gibberish?
Shi just came back from the directorate.
He's already exhausted.
You're right, Master.
Those old tutors...
Have they really let you down?
Zheng Yi,
inform the Directorate of Education
tomorrow
of getting Zheng Shi
a new
primary tutor.
Not just anyone can teach
the children of us Zheng family.
Got it.
Grandfather.
I'm full.
I'll go study in my room then.
Would you like a cup of hot tea?
Which flavor do you like?
I'll have the kitchen
make it for you tomorrow.
Don't bother!
I'll have the staff serve
all the flavors again tomorrow.
Thanks, Grandfather.
What are you laughing at?
Master,
you're truly doting on Young Master Shi.
Of course.
Among all my grandsons,
he resembles me the most.
Come on, slowly.
Drink up!
Gao Ran,
it's too late for him and me to go home.
So, tonight,
he and I will both sleep here.
Oh, right.
This is Lord Wei.
He's utterly brilliant.
Let me walk you to your room.
No need!
Come this way.
I don't need help at all!
See you tomorrow.
-Take care then.
-I can go back to my room on my own.
Where to go?
This way, come on.
Back to my room...
Have we met somewhere before?
How come you look so familiar to me?
I work in the Guardian Corps now.
So I often show up in the Qi Residence.
It's no surprise that you've seen me.
Today, new books arrived
at Qilin Pavilion.
I don't think
Lord Fan Qi will come back tonight.
So you can stay the night in his room.
No need to walk me there.
Why is my entire body aching?
My head hurts.
Every part hurts.
Lord Wei!
Why are you up so early?
Come over.
What's the matter?
Let me ask you.
How long has that bedroom been vacant?
Last night, the bed that I,
the honorable...
slept in gave me a terrible backache.
The Fan family is wealthy.
Can't you pay a little sum
to have it fixed?
Your judgement's really clouded
by the high walls of the Qi Residence.
There's something
you don't know, Lord Wei.
For commoners,
living in a house like this
is already a luxury.
Then I have another question.
Why is this tree of yours so withered?
You mean this tree?
Well, it used to be
towering and majestic.
Look at the bells on it.
When I grew taller every year,
my mother would hang a bell there
as a mark.
Unfortunately,
she is no longer around.
Lord Wei,
you've never seen anyone
with extreme hunger,
have you?
Those usually
kind and amiable old ladies,
and the men and women
who used to lovingly pat my head
and call me "young miss"
would fight fiercely till they bled
just for a leaf
or even a sour steamed bun.
Every day when my mother opened the door,
she could see starving people everywhere.
Living souls perished
from hunger in every single day.
They died right before my eyes.
It was also the time
when my mother passed away
for overexertion.
My father said
my mother's death
was exactly caused
by such cruel reality.
Under these circumstances,
what can I do?
In the Nine Cities,
if I am to do something for the people
or to make a contribution,
how do I make it happen
without an official post?
Your Excellency,
have you never thought about
changing the future of the Nine Cities
and enabling the people here to live
a life without worries
about food and clothing?
When did you know I am the governor?
Deceiving a superior is a capital offense.
I knew it from the very beginning.
The very beginning?
So you already figured out my identity
when we were in the Phoenix Woods?
I knew nothing could restrain my charm.
You...
I bet the saplings planted here
can't grow well due to failure
to absorb nutrition.
If they are moved elsewhere,
I am sure they will flourish
and bloom again.
I hope the Nine Cities
can grow prosperous and grand
like this sapling
to shelter the people.
Maybe one day,
I can also contribute to the Nine Cities.
What if every citizen
could take the official exams?
-What did you say?
-I was just kidding.
Look how shocked you are.
You were not kidding.
I heard what you said.
Did you mean it?
I'll make one more wish then.
I hope all the people in the Nine Cities
can realize their lofty ambitions.
[Huan'e House]
These are the recent accounts.
Yesterday's Seating Ceremony
is recorded as well.
Hu Die,
during all these years,
by trading information,
Huan'e House has not only
raked in big money,
but also collected
many secrets of the nobles.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm just doing my job.
To be honest,
I think only Your Excellency would inflate
your own value in your own establishment.
If I were truly greedy,
I could've earned much more than this.
Knowing when to stop
allows one to remain hidden.
Speaking of remaining hidden,
nobody can do it better
than Your Excellency, right?
Last night, Your Excellency slept
at Her Ladyship's place.
It was because of the note
I passed onto you,
the one about the Dark Wolf, wasn't it?
This was written
by the Dark Wolf leader 13 years ago.
Please take a look.
How did you get this letter?
By chance, from the Dark Wolf remnants.
But due to my incompetence,
the Dark Wolf leader
and the Dark Wolf Seal
are still unaccounted for.
The Dark Wolf organization was founded
by my late father.
It only answers to its real ruler,
namely the one holding the Dark Wolf Seal.
My late father used to keep this item.
But after the war for succession,
this seal disappeared.
Even if I am to take power,
I won't have a legitimate reason
to do so without this seal.
I understand. I'll try my best to find it.
Hold off on this for now.
It is no easy task.
But about Her Ladyship...
This woman...
It's not a bad idea to use her.
At first, I only thought
she had a complex background.
Lord Lyu picked her for me,
and the Three Excellencies gave her dowry.
I can't believe
she'd put on all that stuff.
It somehow confuses me
as to what she's truly up to.
By the way,
I asked you to shut down the shops
with a rogue mark.
Have you done it?
What's this about?
Who shut it down?
[Baiyu Hall]
What on earth is going on?
Is the governor
playing dumb with us?
You draw so beautifully, My Lady.
Good, isn't it?
This is
the pattern
of the Splendid Mountains and Rivers.
Suyin,
what are you drawing?
Take a guess.
I guess...
you're drawing a little lion.
It looks quite like it.
My Lady,
this is a sunflower.
A s-sunflower?
What a unique sunflower.
Keep working on it then.
Just go on.
It's good.
Your drawing is really lifelike, My Lady.
Is it a gift for His Excellency?
What a terrific painting it is.
I'm sure His Excellency will like it.
Now that I think of it,
it might not be necessarily true.
What do you mean by that, My Lady?
Anyway,
the governor is probably
not what he appears to be.
You should go to bed early, My Lady.
I don't think
His Excellency will come here tonight.
His Excellency has arrived!
W-Why would the governor
c-come here at this hour of the night?
Greetings, Your Excellency.
If you have nothing else to do here,
just leave.
It's already late at night.
Why are you still up, Governor?
These are...
roses?
I know your mother's name was Qiangwei,
which means roses.
I happened to see
these beautiful blossoms on my way here.
Come on, take them as a gift.
How thoughtful of you, Governor.
I'm afraid...
I don't deserve these.
Just take them as I told you.
Don't stand on ceremony.
Governor,
there is a scratch on your finger.
Please come in and let me bandage it.
This minor scratch is no big deal.
If there's nothing else,
I'd like to go back to my room.
Just come on in!
Sure.
Your hand is just like Gao Ran's.
Gao Ran?
You mean the one you see as your brother?
Has he been practicing sword skills
since childhood too?
Yes.
Anyway,
Gao Ran has exceptional martial skills.
Alright.
It's bandaged.
Governor, remember
not to get this finger wet.
It's just a minor cut.
Thank you.
By the way,
from now on, please
just call me by my name.
But...
wouldn't that be
inappropriate?
What's inappropriate about it?
You call Gao Ran by his name.
Why not call me by my name too?
What should I call you then?
"Qi Zheng."
"Qi Zheng"?
You'll call me Qi Zheng,
and I'll call you Fan Yun.
It feels closer this way.
Fine then.
You're the governor after all.
Qi Zheng.
Fan Yun.
Why are roses covered in thorns?
Governor, have you never heard
the story of Princess Rose?
Princess Rose?
I've never heard her story.
Tell me about it then.
When are you going to stop playing dumb?
What exactly are you up to?
Governor,
the night is growing late.
How about we continue tomorrow?
It doesn't matter.
I just love hearing stories.
I'll be gone after this one's told.
Fine.
I-I-I...
I put a pillow in the middle of the bed.
How did it end up being there?
I... This...
I haven't complained about you yet.
How could you fall asleep here
without cause last night?
-You...
-Fan Yun,
do you have a secret crush on me or what?
I... h-have a crush on...
How could you, Qi Zheng?
You slept in my bed,
yet you accuse me
of having a crush on you.
No, this won't do.
From today on,
you must take responsibility for me.
Qi Zheng...
You did that on purpose!
Get out!
Governor?
Look,
we fell asleep last night, right?
You didn't finish telling that story.
I have no story to tell.
Yes, yes, you do.
I'm so eager.
Let's pick up where we left off.
I-I don't have any stories to tell!
I swear I won't tell another story
in my lifetime.
Governor,
I really don't have a story to tell.
-Hurry.
-What are you doing?
-Quick!
-What's this for, Governor?
You...
Are you trying to pull stunts again?
What...
exactly are you doing?
Outside. Outside!
Someone is outside?
Yes.
Hurry.
Help me shake the bed.
[This marks the second time
Her Ladyship slept with His Excellency]
You're being followed again?
Please do me a favor.
[This marks the third time
Her Ladyship slept with His Excellency]
[This marks the fourth time
[This marks the... time
Her Ladyship slept with His Excellency]
[Huiyun Pavilion]
How come His Excellency is already
so drowsy just after the morning meeting?
His Excellency seems
to have been resting poorly lately.
T-Then...
-Your Excellency.
Your Excellency, do you know
the treasury is running low?
The treasury?
Did
the Commerce Ministry
not manage the budget well?
This has nothing to do
with the Commerce Ministry.
Since the beginning of this year,
all the Nine Cities
haven't been peaceful.
Multiple areas have been struck
by disasters.
People
failed to pay taxes on time.
This is what
caused the current predicament.
Then, Mr. Zheng,
do you have a solution?
After careful thinking,
I suppose the imminent concern
can only be addressed by higher taxes.
I have drafted a proposal
for raising taxes.
Read it, and Your Excellency will know.
Raising taxes, huh?
It's definitely not going to work.
People can't afford to pay taxes as it is.
Now, you're even proposing an increase.
People will struggle more, won't they?
What gives you that thought,
Your Excellency?
My wife.
Speaking of which,
I owe the three of you many thanks,
for bringing her to my life.
I'm grateful
that she took me out to see people's lives
and told me so much about their suffering.
I really cannot impose higher taxes
on the people.
In my opinion,
it's time to take reforms.
As for whether to raise the taxes or not,
we need further discussions.
I beg to differ, My Lord.
What do you think is wrong with it?
Is it wrong or not?
-Don't chime in.
Women can't participate in politics.
Doesn't
Her Ladyship know that?
I don't think
she's participating in politics.
Is she or is she not?
She's not.
Do you agree with the nonsense
that the governor said?
Of course I agree.
There's no need to hide things
between you and me.
The treasury is depleted.
What other solutions are there
apart from increasing taxes?
His Excellency is stalling.
And that talk about reforms!
Is he trying to turn the world
upside down?
That aside, look
what a woman you got him.
She has bewitched the governor.
And you are the one to blame!
Actually, I think
I picked the right woman.
Please stop looking, My Lady.
You would deem my embroidery terrible.
Who said that?
You're doing a great job at it.
Look at the duckling
you're working on this time.
Such a cute expression.
My Lady,
this is a mandarin duck.
A mandarin duck?
You mean...
this is a mandarin duck?
I guessed it wrong again.
Well, you're right.
This is exactly a mandarin duck.
How beautifully embroidered.
"The mandarin ducks fly together;
Catch them as a pair."
It's a lovely mandarin duck.
My Lady, I know
you're trying to comfort me.
I don't have much talent
in needlework.
Wait, Suyin.
You said...
this is a mandarin duck.
It's said
that words are to convey meaning.
Embroidery works in the same way.
Does it mean...
you're in love
with someone, Suyin?
No.
Don't talk nonsense, My Lady.
No wonder I've always seen you
writing letters in your room these days.
It turns out they're for someone you love.
I remember you are
from Jingcheng.
What about him?
Is he also from Jingcheng?
No, this is
not what you think it is, My Lady.
What's there to be shy about?
Throughout the ages,
nothing moves the heart more than love.
Women's passion is particularly powerful.
If you truly like someone,
then be brave and say it aloud.
My Lady, do you really think so?
Then don't just be a judge
on someone else's affairs.
It's time you directed your attention
to your own matters.
My own matters?
What matters?
Why does it seem like you don't care about
the governor's birthday at all?
Those in the Internal Affairs Department
told me
they've been waiting for your reply
about the menu
for this year's birthday banquet.
You mean...
the mayor's birthday is approaching?