[The Legend of Rosy Clouds]
[Episode 3]
Your Excellency.
You're back.
Fan Yun?
Why are you here?
I...
I came to apologize to you,
Your Excellency.
Hearing you say the word
makes me unhappy.
What word?
Do you mean the word
"apologize"?
We agreed you'd call me by my name.
Did you forget so quickly?
Yes,
Qi Zheng.
Since you're so uninterested in apologies,
I won't apologize then.
I'm leaving.
It's a rare opportunity.
Tell me your troubles
to make me happy.
You...
Never mind.
I wanted to say
that the memo
sent by the Internal Affairs Department
was buried under my books,
so I delayed the reply.
I was wondering
what I could do to make up for—
Just for such a small thing?
That's it?
That's it.
Could it be that you
want me to make a huge mistake,
so you can condemn me
to eternal ruin?
I have already replied
to the banquet menu issue for you.
You just need to manage it
and show your goodwill.
I believe they won't blame you.
Don't worry.
Really?
Thank you, Your Excellency.
You're so kind.
I wasn't helping you.
I was just helping myself.
You...
I...
Are you going back to the room with me?
I know. I know.
But I'm really tired today.
Take a rain check.
I'll definitely rekindle our romance
another day.
Alright?
What are you fantasizing about?
I...
I just wanted to ask
what gifts you want
for your birthday,
so I can make up for it.
I appreciate your thought,
but I just
don't like celebrating birthdays.
It's just that because of my position,
it's hard to decline.
As for gifts,
others can't skip them,
but Fan Yun,
you can.
Don't like celebrating birthdays?
How strange.
How can that be?
No matter what,
I am your wife.
Besides,
when I make a mistake,
if you don't let me make up for it,
I'll feel bad.
Tell me.
What do you want?
Haven't you always denied being my wife?
Why?
After we spent
these past few days together,
have you fallen in love with me?
In your dreams.
I'm going back to rest.
Why are you spacing out?
Escort her back.
Don't follow me.
I can go back by myself.
[Juyun Pavilion]
Have the identities of the two people
from the past 2 days been verified?
All the pawnshops have received the news.
But
we've asked everywhere
and haven't found
any information about them.
Go and tell all the silk shops
to keep an eye out for anyone
who has bought
similar silk threads recently.
They might want to imitate
the fabrics of Juyun Pavilion,
pass off inferior goods as high quality,
and make money from it.
What about Huan'e House?
Do we still take it?
The only thing worth mentioning about
Huan'e House is their tribute wine.
As for the other things...
I don't think much of them.
The first-grade tribute wine
from Huan'e House
is full-bodied with a deep red hue.
It's spicy but not hot.
It's the best of the best.
If we could see it with our own eyes,
maybe,
we could imitate 70 to 80 percent of it.
Tomorrow is His Excellency's birthday.
Could it be that you
want to give these wines to him?
These wines
have all been presented in previous years.
It's just that this year,
no particularly good wine
has been produced yet.
Why not let me choose this year?
My good grandson.
This is wheat liquor.
It was bought from the distillery
under Juyun Pavilion.
It's clean and sweet.
It's a top-quality product
in recent years.
Indeed, good liquor.
Look. Look.
We've taken advantage
of His Excellency's luck
to have a taste.
After entering Ling'an,
I have never entered
the Governor Residence.
Why not take this opportunity
to let me follow you
and broaden my horizons?
-You.
-Are a really good grandson.
-Come on.
It's said that
handsome men gather in Ling'an City.
Take the Governor as an example.
[Wei Ying,
the noble daughter of the Wei family]
He is a top handsome man in the main hall,
ranking second on the Guanyu List.
But doesn't he have a wife?
Wei Rong,
stop playing!
Fair faces end in bare bones.
Fine men soon fade with time.
The Governor Residence
is not a good place.
It's full of intrigue
in such a small space.
Such a simple person like you
can easily lose yourself if you go in.
What do you know?
Marrying the second-ranked man
on the Guanyu List
comes at a cost.
This time,
I want to live a different life!
[Wei Rong,
the noble son of the Wei family]
Lord Yan Jiang.
Don't run away.
You just came from over there.
Don't go back again.
My Lady.
Why is it you?
What a coincidence.
It's not a coincidence at all.
I've been waiting for you right here.
Waiting for me?
How did you know I would pass by here?
Because...
because ordinary people
wouldn't be able to walk here.
So I just waited here.
Only you would appear here.
I am speechless.
Lord Yan,
I have something to ask you.
It seems His Excellency
really doesn't want to celebrate
his birthday.
Why is that?
It is...
a long story.
It's hard to explain in a few words.
Let's get to work.
What time is it now?
Why hasn't breakfast been served?
Please wait a moment, Your Excellency.
Breakfast will be ready soon.
Forget it.
I'm not in a good mood today.
Just skip it.
How can that be?
Your Excellency.
How can you not have breakfast?
Fan Yun?
Why are you here?
I am, of course,
here to bring you breakfast.
You cooked...
cooked all morning
and only made one egg?
Your Excellency.
Don't underestimate this egg.
It has a great purpose.
Come on, sit nicely.
-What are you doing?
-Sit nicely.
Roll away the bad luck.
Roll in the good luck.
Roll away the villains.
Roll in the benefactors.
Roll away the diseases.
Roll in good health.
Roll...
No way.
This won't do.
This won't do?
-I mean…
-Alright.
What is this for?
Bad luck rolls away,
and a year of good times begins.
Once I peel this egg,
you can eat it.
I have to eat it?
It's like this now. Can it still be eaten?
Why can't it be eaten?
Only by eating it
will all your bad luck
for the year vanish.
Where did this custom come from?
I've never heard of it.
I'm not eating it.
But when I was sick as a child,
my mother used
to roll an egg on me like this.
Not long ago,
for his birthday,
my father boiled an egg for himself
and burned down the kitchen.
Since then, I've never
rolled eggs on anyone.
You should eat it.
It really works.
Then it's enough if I eat it, right?
I've finished it.
And...
Where are you going?
Well...
I...
Y-You haven't had the most important meal
of the morning today.
There's more?
Of course.
Listen, Your Excellency,
you have to finish every last bite
of this bowl of noodles.
It took me
a lot of effort to make it.
You can't leave a single bite.
Try it first, come on.
Qi Zheng.
Congratulations.
You're a year older.
Second Brother,
why do you always cook pig trotter noodles
for my birthday every year?
Mother said
pig trotter soup is the most nourishing.
You should eat more
to grow up fast
and stronger,
so no one will dare to bully you.
Slow down.
Be careful not to choke.
Eat slowly.
I want to be as strong as you,
so I won't be bullied,
and I can bully others.
We won't let others bully us,
but we can't bully others either.
Look at him, look.
So disgusting.
Does it hurt?
Did they bully you again?
It's fine, Second Brother.
It doesn't hurt anymore.
He's coming.
-Let's go.
-Come on.
It doesn't taste like that?
It shouldn't be.
I put so much effort into making it.
How could it be so hard to swallow?
Let me taste it.
Your Excellency,
how does it
taste?
The taste of this bowl of noodles
is very familiar.
I haven't eaten it in a long time.
The last time I ate it
was on my birthday.
My second brother made it for me.
I like this bowl of noodles very much.
That's great.
The bad luck is gone,
and the noodles are finished.
How did you know
about this bowl of noodles?
Well...
I asked Lord Yan Jiang about it.
Your Excellency,
anyway,
I think
time is fair.
The good and the bad will all pass.
So,
we should cherish the present,
live in the moment,
and live out
our true selves.
You know what?
Ever since my second brother left,
I've felt like
there's a huge gaping hole in my heart.
Somehow,
it seems to be filled up again today.
Thank you, Fan Yun.
But
you still haven't told me.
Whose side are you really on?
I...
You want to ask
about the 3 dresses with different colors,
right?
The Three Elders sent the dresses
presumably with good intentions.
So I took one color from each
to make a single dress.
This should
stand as my position, right?
Then I understand.
From now on,
you are my person.
Don't pull it apart with too much force
or make it too big.
-Each fits perfectly in one mouthful.
-Okay.
My Lady.
Suyin.
Lord Zheng Yuan is here.
Do you want to avoid him for now?
Lord Zheng?
Today is His Excellency's birthday.
No need to hide.
He is...
probably here
looking for me.
My Lady.
Greetings, Lord Zheng.
I was heading to the banquet.
I just happened to pass by
and wanted to see
how the preparations were going.
Since you are working hard here,
I came over to greet you.
Thank you, Lord Zheng.
It's all my duty.
Then you should also know
that there are some things
you shouldn't do, right?
As far as I know,
lately, you have had
your own opinions
on the residence's affairs,
or even, quite a few
complaints.
May I ask, Lord Zheng,
what exactly are you referring to?
No matter what,
no matter how noble your status is,
you are still a woman.
Women
should
mind their words and actions,
and do what they are supposed to do.
Keep to yourself,
and especially,
don't make wild comments
about the affairs of the residence.
Otherwise,
since what's said without intent
might be taken to heart by listeners,
I'm afraid
it will bring unnecessary trouble.
But...
listen.
Even the cicadas on this tree
have the right to make a sound,
so why can't I?
Besides, what I said
is all beneficial
to the residence.
I don't see anything wrong with it.
In that case,
I will take my leave.
Let me see you out.
No need.
My Lady.
I will see Lord Zheng Yuan out for you.
Go ahead.
The great affairs of the Nine Cities
are not for women to meddle.
A female ruling in man's stead
bodes chaos and ruin.
Beauty is a curse
and must not remain.
Take care, Lord Zheng Yuan.
Stop right there.
Release your grip.
Head up. Chest out.
A girl should act like a girl.
Continue.
Alright, alright.
Just walk normally.
Okay?
Is His Excellency really
the second most handsome in the world?
Well...
Second is nothing special.
The residence is full of old men
at the age of the Three Elders.
Qi Zheng is the only man
of marriageable age,
yet he can't even rank first.
You, Wei Rong!
When did you get here?
I've been here the whole time.
Is what he said true?
The lords in Ling'an
are indeed a bit on the older side.
-But—
-He can't even be number one?
Yet you said His Excellency
is the second most handsome in the world.
Weren't you two lying to me?
I'm not going.
I want to go home, back to Gao City.
No, no.
Even if you are as free as the wind,
you can't escape the shackles of the world
or the bonds of family.
Once you enter the residence,
you can't come and go as you please.
Shut up.
My good sister,
just treat it
as a visit to the Qi Residence,
right?
Just take a walk around.
His Excellency won't force you
into anything.
How can you guarantee for him?
Will a beautiful,
exquisite woman like me
be allowed to come and go freely?
Why do I feel like
you're quite proud of yourself?
Never mind.
I understand.
Shisan, you're tired
of being a bird flying freely in the sky
and want to be a canary
in a deep courtyard.
A song of "Caged Bird"
to bid you farewell.
Stop playing. I'm telling you.
Wei Rong.
If you keep playing...
I'll kill you if you keep playing!
You took my sword again!
Stop running!
I'm telling you,
if I catch you, I'll kill you!
Catch me if you have the guts!
Come here!
Both of you, stop!
Looks like there's a good show to watch.
Young Master Shi,
the Master wants you to go over quickly.
His Excellency is arriving soon.
I won't offer liquor today.
How can that be?
We came today to offer liquor.
If we don't offer it,
how do we explain it to the Master?
Get out of the way!
Come here!
Help!
Who are you?
How dare you commit a crime
with a sword here?
Capture her immediately!
A song of "Po Zhen Zi"
to embolden you warriors.
Shisan,
listen to my explanation.
What explanation?
I wouldn't deserve the surname Wei
if I don't beat you up today!
♪ Wind sheds rain like tears ♪
♪ Over the whole town ♪
♪ At the second our gazes meet ♪
♪ Past memories roar one louder beat ♪
This is a restricted area
of the Qi Residence.
You used weapons without permission.
Return with me to receive your punishment.
Good looking.
Are you going to arrest me?
How will you arrest me?
Will you tie my hands?
Do you like tying hands
or feet?
Tie me up.
Hurry up and tie me up.
Catch me.
Please behave yourself, Miss.
Misunderstanding! Misunderstanding!
Gao Ran, this is my younger sister.
She's a little mischievous.
Lord Wei,
your sister used a weapon
in the restricted area
and injured my people.
No matter who she is,
I must bring her back to the residence
to confess her crimes
and accept punishment.
Guard Gao.
My sister came today
for an audience.
So,
please be lenient, Guard Gao.
An audience?
It's fine if I don't see him.
Say less.
Lord Wei,
I'll leave you two to it.
I won't keep you company.
Thank you, Guard Gao.
Brother,
who is he?
Why do you care who he is?
You caused such a big mess today.
I haven't settled the score with you yet.
The birthday banquet is about to begin.
Hurry up and come with me.
I'm not going.
What?
I've found the one.
Found who?
The man I want to marry.
Don't tell me you've fallen for Gao Ran.
Gao Ran.
Even his name sounds nice.
I don't care who you fancy.
You still have to attend
His Excellency's birthday banquet.
Hurry up and come with me.
Let me tell you,
you only have 2 choices today.
First one, let me go.
Second, I'll die right in front of you.
I'm so beautiful
and good at martial arts.
What if His Excellency sees me
and won't let me leave?
Let's talk this out.
Put the sword down.
I won't.
My lovely sister,
it's good to be confident.
But what if...
what if His Excellency
doesn't even like you?
Right?
Fine, fine.
-Go. Go.
-Take it.
Let me tell you,
don't come back once you leave!
Wei Rong!
These two...
It's truly...
It's truly a misfortune
for our Wei family!
His Excellency has arrived!
-Greetings, Your Excellency.
You may rise.
-Thank you, Your Excellency.
Come on.
Careful.
Thank you, Your Excellency.
Don't let anything befall you.
Otherwise, I
won't know what to do.
Careful.
My Beloved,
here,
try this.
I know we are acting,
but act a little more naturally.
You're acting really weird.
The more exaggerated we are,
the more noticeable we become.
Hurry and try it.
Okay.
Is it good?
Yes.
Then eat more.
Your Excellency.
Look, who is the young man
sitting behind Lord Zheng?
Why does he look so familiar?
I'm right in front of you,
yet you are discussing another man.
Watch the performance.
You eat too, Your Excellency.
Great!
Well danced!
Great.
-Have some more.
-You too.
Happy birthday, Your Excellency.
Your Excellency,
may you live long and prosper.
-Happy birthday, Your Excellency.
-May you live long and prosper.
Your Excellency, you've had
a lot of good news lately.
Seeing how affectionate you two are,
I
can rest assured.
I hope you and your wife
will have a child soon
to continue the prosperity
of our Nine Cities.
Thank you for your kind words, Lord Zheng.
We...
will certainly live up to expectations.
That's you.
Don't drag me into this.
Since you took office,
there have been few heirs
in the residence.
But don't worry.
I have discussed it with everyone.
We should select noble women
to fill the inner quarters
and have more children,
to strengthen the bloodline
of the Qi family.
Well...
Today, there's a lady from the Wei family.
She is dignified
and gentle.
I am...
still young.
Filling the inner quarters
can wait.
Anything involving you
is a big deal.
Your heir involves Nine Cities.
It's not just a personal matter.
Among all the world's charms,
I desire but one.
Besides,
I already have my wife by my side.
I'm afraid my heart
has no room for anyone else.
Right, My Beloved?
You haven't even seen her yet.
How do you know there's no room for her?
Please invite Lady Wei in.
This... this is...
A man?
Hurry up and invite Lady Wei in.
On my sister's way here,
the horse pulling the carriage
was frightened.
The carriage overturned,
and she was unfortunately injured.
In my sister's heart,
Your Excellency, you're like the sun
high in the sky.
She felt inadequate
and unworthy of you.
She didn't deserve to see you.
Halfway here,
she left silently.
Did Wei Shisan
go home?
Fate is truly playing tricks on us.
I am deeply sympathetic
to your sister's misfortune.
Seems I have to disappoint you again.
Come on, give Lord Wei a seat!