[The Legend of Rosy Clouds]
[Episode 4]
Your Excellency.
Look.
Haven't my painting skills
improved quite a bit?
Even this bird can't bear to leave.
I wouldn't be so sure.
Don't go.
Your Excellency, the bee you drew
on the flower
is truly lifelike.
That's a real bee.
Is that so?
The carrying pole you drew under the tree
looks very realistic.
What carrying pole?
That's a door bolt.
I drew an erhu here.
No.
That's not why we're here.
Your Excellency.
What's wrong?
My two trusted generals,
do you like the iris flowers
I gave you?
If Your Excellency wished to
bestow flowers,
why give us dried ones?
Your Excellency always likes to tease us.
We're here today
to ask Your Excellency about this.
What's wrong with dried flowers?
They're still beautiful
even after being dried.
It'd be a shame not to give them away.
Wei Sui.
I've finished my drawing.
Take it and have it mounted.
Old fox.
The wine last night was poisoned.
-It was poisoned?
-What?
Someone is trying to harm Your Excellency?
The wine was offered to my wife,
but I didn't let her drink it.
But now I'm in the open,
and the enemy is lurking in the dark.
Every move we make from here on
will affect their next move.
So,
we must not alert them.
Then,
what does Your Excellency intend to do?
I need the two of you to help me
root out the treacherous person
targeting Fan Yun, along with the forces
behind them.
Here in the Qi Residence,
there are very few people I can trust.
But these iris flowers
represent my trust in you.
This is also a tradition of my family.
For generations, the rulers of
the Nine Cities have bestowed flowers.
This is the first time
I've ever done so myself.
Wei Ying, Yan Jiang, hear my command.
Yes, Your Excellency.
Though the flowers I bestow this time
are dried,
their significance is immeasurable.
By accepting them,
you pledge
lifelong loyalty to me.
Are you willing?
We're willing to follow Your Excellency
for the rest of our lives,
never wavering.
Good.
Rise.
Ever since Second Young Master Qi
was exiled,
the Nine Cities
have longed for a worthy ruler.
We have waited all this time.
Fan Yun?
Governor.
Perfect timing.
I was just about to look for you.
I have something to discuss with you.
I also have something to discuss with you.
Come on, let's go inside and talk.
There's no time.
Something has come up at my home.
I'd like permission to
leave the residence.
Leave the residence?
Your father holds a post
at the Qilin Pavilion,
and Gao Ran is with the Guardian Corps.
What could possibly be happening
at your home?
Well,
I just received a letter
saying the private school
was bought by someone else.
I want to go back and check.
No.
Right now, no matter what's happening,
you cannot leave.
Go back inside.
Why?
I...
I-I just...
don't feel like it.
I want to paint.
You need to stay by my side
and grind ink for me.
Hurry, go inside.
You don't understand.
I'll station the Guardian Corps
at the gates
so you can't set foot outside!
You...
Where are you going?
Qilin Pavilion!
I'm getting angry now!
Why are you still standing there?
Hurry up and follow her!
Yes.
[Juyun Pavilion]
Boss.
We've found something.
Go ahead.
Fan Yun was originally
the only daughter of the Fan family.
She loved reading
and worked as a teacher
at a private school in Ling'an.
She married
the Governor only recently.
Just an incompetent ruler.
Never mind him.
The walls of the Qi Residence
can't stop anything.
There have indeed been
quite a few scandalous rumors
about Qi Zheng before.
Even after their wedding,
they continued to sleep in separate rooms.
But word has it that they finally
consummated the marriage a few days ago.
So?
So...
I don't really understand these matters
between men and women.
Ling'an is full of beautiful women anyway.
Whatever type of girl you like, Boss,
we'll just find you another.
I just want to hear her play music again.
Do something for me.
Here to admit your mistake?
Wait until I finish
reviewing this memorial.
Then we'll discuss
whether you can leave or not.
What mistake...
does Your Excellency think
I should admit to?
Zheng...
Mr. Zheng.
Who's leaving where?
Me?
I was talking about...
relieving oneself.
Since it's not exactly a refined topic,
I won't elaborate.
Have you come to discuss something urgent?
It's about the matter of raising taxes.
Your Excellency once said
it required further deliberation.
Well, how is that going?
When will it be promulgated,
and when will it be implemented?
I simply found
your arguments
so profound and well-reasoned—
every word a gem, so eloquently put—
that I'm still savoring them.
Savoring them?
The treasury is running dry.
These days, we old officials
can barely get an audience
with Your Excellency.
We understand that Your Excellency
is deeply enamored with Her Ladyship
and has no time for us old folks.
That's only natural, I suppose.
Although
I don't expect
Your Excellency
to be as diligent and devoted as
Second Young Master Qi once was...
I still hope
Your Excellency can
exercise self-discipline
and maintain a proper balance.
Do not...
indulge in sensual pleasures.
I've indeed been neglecting my duties
lately.
Right.
Doesn't the Guardian Corps
hold a martial arts tournament
every two years?
That's right.
It's held to select talents,
and regular competitions
also help improve combat skills.
You... you mean...
That's exactly it.
Could we hold one again soon?
I'd also like to see if the Guardian Corps
has improved over the past two years.
Your Excellency,
the treasury is empty.
We just finished celebrating
Your Excellency's birthday,
and now you want a tournament?
This is hardly the conduct
of a wise ruler.
Well...
We can cover the expenses
by cutting back
on my personal expenditures.
In any case, keep everything
simple and quick.
Hold it immediately.
Yes, Your Excellency.
In the end, he didn't listen to
a word I said.
Mr. Zheng!
Make sure everyone participates.
Remember,
every single person.
Yes, Your Excellency.
Looks like we've had a thief in the house.
Brother.
Don't call me brother.
It makes my skin crawl.
I'm warning you—
if you lay a finger on
my access badge again,
I'll send you straight back to Gao City.
Okay, no problem.
Whatever you say goes, Brother.
I'm going to the Qi Residence today.
The Guardian Corps is holding
a martial arts tournament.
I can't be late.
Have fun by yourself.
Guardian Corps? Qi Residence?
Gao Ran?
Brother! Brother...
Stop right there.
I know what you're trying to do.
No way.
Brother...
I'm so bored
at home every day.
Our parents sent me here
for a marriage alliance,
yet I can't even see the person I love.
I'm so pitiful.
The person you are about to marry
and the one you love are
two different people, right?
Yes.
There is absolutely no way
I'm taking you into the residence.
Give it up.
Why?
That guy Gao Ran
is as thick as a brick
when it comes to romance.
He's completely clueless.
Why waste your time on him?
Because he's so handsome.
Even if he makes me angry in the future,
at least I'll enjoy looking at him.
Him?
Handsome?
Yes.
Is he as handsome as me?
He is more handsome than you.
You...
See? See?
I can tell from that alone
that your taste is terrible.
You should give up on him
as soon as possible.
Brother,
I was wrong. I was wrong.
You're the most handsome man.
If
Gao Ran is the most handsome in the world,
then you're second.
Get off me. Get off.
No.
Wei Rong, my brother! Do me a favor!
You...
The phoenix soars to the highest heavens,
resting only upon the parasol tree.
A worthy man may dwell in any land
but serves only the master
he deems worthy.
Today,
we convene this martial arts tournament
for two purposes:
first, to gather
heroes and talented warriors
from across the Nine Cities
so that all may showcase their skills
and exchange techniques;
second,
to further...
Slow down.
Block me better.
Select talents,
ensuring that no one
willing to serve the Nine Cities
goes unnoticed.
Where is Gao Ran?
Why don't I see him?
However,
a blade doesn't care who it cuts.
We hope you all
-That one, I think.
-can demonstrate your skills,
-but stop before any real harm is done.
-I see him. There he is.
Good thing I have you,
the Unrivaled Talent of the Nine Cities,
personally appointed by the Governor,
so I can enter the residence at will.
You're truly the pride of our family.
Even though his looks are only average,
everyone has the right to pursue beauty.
Moreover,
it's rare to see you pursue something
with such stubborn determination.
No need to thank me
for such a great favor.
Just remember you owe me one.
You're the one with average looks.
I want some water too.
I'm a little thirsty.
Suyin, pour some tea for His Excellency.
Yes.
This tournament
is being conducted under the principle
of simplicity and efficiency.
The prize is set as follows:
first place will receive 50 taels of gold.
Fifty taels?
You call that keeping it simple?
That's so much money.
I want it too.
It'd be great if I could have it.
Let the tournament begin!
Incompetent.
What a waste of time.
Fan Yun.
Do you want that prize money?
I'll win it for you.
Really?
Of course.
Actually,
I can give you as much money as you want.
Just...
could you stop being mad at me?
Don't ignore me, please?
I wasn't mad.
I was anxious.
I was just worried about
the private school.
Besides,
do I really seem that petty?
Really?
Really.
You're the dignified Governor, after all.
So just
sit here and enjoy the tournament.
How could I just sit here?
I have to win that prize money for you.
Keep the goodies within the family, right?
It won't.
Because...
Because I'm waiting for my Gao Ran to win.
Gao Ran?
Who else
dares challenge me?
Come on!
Move forward a bit. Move forward a bit.
Gao Ran is on the stage.
Since you've won,
why not have a match with me as well?
I wouldn't dare.
A true warrior
doesn't keep retreating
out of mere courtesy.
Now they're both on the stage.
For a moment,
I don't even know
who I should be cheering for.
But no matter what,
those 50 taels
should end up in my hands, right?
Qi Zheng,
in close combat,
your dodges must be quick.
But your attacks must be even quicker.
The moment your sword is
at your opponent's throat,
you win.
If anyone bullies you, Second Brother,
I'll use this move on them.
You're still young.
Focus on protecting yourself first.
Don't keep letting our brothers
push you around.
Come on, one more time.
Once you've mastered it,
I'll take you to see Father.
Okay!
I haven't seen Father in so long.
Thank you, Second Brother.
I lost.
Well done!
Gao Ran!
Gao Ran...
I...
I have something I want to tell you.
I have a second brother.
His name is Qingyuan.
When I was little...
he was the only one by my side.
He was also the only one
who always stood in front of me
and protected me.
When my second brother disappeared,
I cried.
I felt so heartbroken then.
The figure that had always protected me
was gone from my life.
So for all these years,
I've never given up searching for him,
just hoping to see him
with my own eyes again.
Then I could personally return
the position of Governor
that rightfully belongs to him.
But I never could have dreamed
that he'd been here all along,
so close.
I'm not your second brother.
And I don't belong here.
I know there are still many problems
in the Nine Cities.
I know I seem like an incompetent ruler
who neglects state affairs.
But actually, I...
I have my own plan.
I've been waiting for
the right opportunity all this time,
hoping that when he finally returns,
he'll find a better Nine Cities.
I know
your second brother
would definitely be happy to see you
become a true ruler.
But he no longer exists.
Stop looking for him.
You really are good at lying.
If my second brother's spirit
can hear this,
please tell him
that I, Qi Zheng, will definitely become
a worthy governor.
That push-pull tactic might backfire.
[Ningxiang Pavilion]
Look.
Just look at your brother.
-Good tea.
-I don't care.
Another cup.
Stop.
Where are you going?
I need to use the restroom.
Escort Miss Wei to the restroom.
Keep a close eye on her.
She's a grown woman.
Where could she possibly run off to?
Bad news! Miss Wei is gone!
What?
See?
Didn't I say so? Didn't I say so?
The second you take your eyes off her,
she's gone!
What are you yelling for?
I...
I'll help you find her.
Stop right there.
If you go look for her,
I'll have to go look for you later.
I...
Forget it.
I can't keep her under control.
Then let her learn her lesson
the hard way.
Yes.
Let her suffer a bit.
No, seriously, I've noticed...
What?
Governor, have a cup of tea first.
Governor?
Governor!
Have a cup of tea.
Governor,
I've noticed
that ever since you sparred with Gao Ran,
you haven't
quite been yourself.
No. I'm fine.
There's still something I'd like to ask.
You mentioned
Gao Ran used to work as a servant
in your household, right?
Then, when did he come to your family?
About...
13 years ago.
-There was a famine back then.
-Thirteen years ago...
Gao Ran was on the verge of
starving to death,
and my father brought him back.
Did your father ever mention
where he found him?
Did he go into any detail?
No.
We grew up together,
just like family.
So I never asked.
What's wrong?
Why are you suddenly so interested
in Gao Ran?
I'm just a bit envious of you—
having a family member like that
by your side
must make you very happy.
You and Mr. Fan Qi
have treated him well, right?
Of course.
I've treated Gao Ran
like my own brother since childhood.
I even
got angry at Father and him
because Father was always favoring him.
That's good.
Are you okay?
Have you...
caught a cold?
I'm not sure either.
I've just been feeling very tired
and weak lately.
You don't have a fever though.
Let me check.
What's wrong, Governor?
Nothing.
Let me have a look around here.
Governor...
what are you doing?
Where did you get this inkstone?
Oh, that?
This was a gift from the students
at the private school.
You like it?
But
I can't give it to you even if you do.
Since it's something you treasure...
I won't take it from you.
If you're not feeling well,
go to bed early.
I'll head out first.
Why did he act so weird?
The water is poisoned.
Your Excellency, well...
Just as I suspected.
This ring changes color
when exposed to poison.
The stain on it came from the ink
on the inkstone in Fan Yun's room.
It seems this matter isn't simple.
They failed to poison her at the banquet,
so they've turned to
the objects around her.
It seems someone
really wants Fan Yun dead.
That woman just now...
Wei Shisan?
That's my sister.
I see.
Let me go see what she's about.
Guardian Corps, listen to my command.
We're now entering the night patrol shift.
Squad on the right,
follow the garden path
through the Qi Residence
and proceed to Ling'an City's main gate.
This squad here,
remain in the garden on standby.
Remember not to let anyone in.
Squad on the left,
head to Ling'an City's east gate.
As for the last squad,
proceed to the west gate.
Is everyone clear?
During the night patrol,
stay alert at all times.
You must be starving.
A feast for the eyes
won't fill your stomach.
You've got a point.
Indeed...
Why are you staring at me?
I'm telling you,
I'm already taken.
Don't get any funny ideas about me.
I do have an idea,
and I want you to do me a favor.
I knew it.
There's no such thing as a free meal.
Go ahead. What is it?
I want you to...
Will you kill me if I refuse?
Of course not.
Then I won't do it.
I'll just make sure you can't get in here
and can't see Gao Ran ever again.
My Lady,
you have a visitor.
Who is it?
It's the eldest miss of the Wei family.
I'm here!
Miss Wei.
You...
Miss Wei,
what
brings you here?
I heard you were sick.
So...
So I'm moving in.
Such impeccable logic.
Did your house collapse?
Could you not curse me like that?
I'm here to save...
I'm here to be your friend.
B-Be my friend?
I have her covered. We don't need you.
You may leave now.
Go.
Fan Yun, sit.
Okay.
You...
Miss Wei,
why do you keep staring at me like that?
When someone's sick,
they need friends around.
And between friends,
we should have a heart-to-heart
and get to know each other.
Get to know each other?
Then, Miss Wei,
how would you like to get to know me?
What's your relationship with Gao Ran?
Why do they say
you're the closest person to him
in the residence?
Gao Ran?
That's because
we've known each other since childhood.
Since childhood?
I'm done for.
What kind of childhood sweethearts story
have I stumbled into?
What do you mean?
Wait, his surname is Gao,
and yours is Fan.
Why have you two known each other
since childhood?
Because when Gao Ran was young,
my father took him in.
But all these years,
I've always treated him
like an older brother.
So if you think about it,
we're basically like siblings.
Siblings?
But you're not related by blood.
What's with all this
"brother" and "sister" talk?
Miss Wei,
didn't you say
you wanted to get to know me?
Why do you keep asking about Gao Ran?
Because I'm not interested in you.
Then you...
You...
I-I get it now.
You like Gao Ran.
Obviously.
So that's it.
So you like Gao Ran.
Even though you're
a bit reckless
and impulsive,
I actually like that about you.
Let me put it this way.
Gao Ran and I have indeed
known each other since childhood,
but I've truly always
regarded him as my own brother.
And he has
always treated me like his own sister.
It's not what you're imagining.
Believe it or not,
that's the truth.
If
you want to be my sister-in-law...
the two of you
do seem like a good match.
Come here, future sister-in-law.
Scoot a little closer. Come on.
Tell me—
just how well-matched are we really,
and in what ways exactly?
Look,
both of you
have a dimple
on the same side.
And you're both
fair-skinned
and adorable.
Very nice. Very nice.
A perfect match.
Tell me more
about your interesting childhood stories.
Miss Wei,
I've been talking
for a whole day and night.
And I've already told you everything,
even what I shouldn't have.
I really have nothing left to tell.
Really?
Then think of more today
and tell me tomorrow.
I have to tell you more tomorrow?
My Lady,
I'm here to attend to you for the night.
-You're here, Suyin.
-I can take care of my friend.
You...
You may leave.
Miss Wei,
I've really told you everything.
What else do you want me to talk about?
Sometimes,
even the people closest to you
can't be trusted.
Nothing.