[The Legend of Rosy Clouds]
[Episode 5]
O-Oh, it's you!
Why are you here?
I...
Are you delivering cold medicine
to Her Ladyship?
Her Ladyship...
Her Ladyship hasn't fully recovered.
Please excuse me.
Where there is life, there is hope.
I guess the governor is right.
As long as I stay by Her Ladyship's side,
I can see you.
Bear with it.
Wait.
On your waist...
Do you and the governor
have some plan you didn't tell me about?
How do you know?
As perceptive as ever.
But
I can't tell you.
Why can't you tell me?
Actually, it's like this.
That's how it is.
I see.
So,
Her Ladyship's cold is fake,
but her chronic poisoning is real.
I got it. Thank you.
Leaving already?
Nothing else you want to know?
I know a lot!
I can tell you everything!
Nice.
There's another person protecting Fan Yun.
Fan Yun.
Miss Wei?
Miss Wei.
Where is Suyin?
Suyin?
Suyin said she wasn't feeling well
and went back
to rest.
She asked me to take her place.
Not feeling well?
She's sick?
What's wrong
with Suyin?
I don't know either.
Probably nothing serious.
But Suyin...
Suyin this; Suyin that.
Does the medicine I feed you not work?
Drink it now.
Why are you so fierce?
I'll drink it.
Yuck, it tastes awful.
Miss Wei.
You always
keep your access badge on you, right?
Yes.
Miss Wei,
could you do me a favor?
What favor?
I want to leave the premises.
No way.
You are still sick,
and the governor wouldn't agree.
Anyway, this time,
no one can stop me.
I must go out.
The private school matter
is urgent.
I beg you.
Please help me.
I can't help you with this.
Sister-in-Law.
What is that?
This is
Mr. Gao Ran's personal item.
I wonder if you're interested.
How can I help you?
I want the access badge
the governor gave you.
Here you go!
You're just...
just giving it to me?
Thank you, Miss Wei.
No, thank you.
You're welcome.
Your Excellency.
Why are you back?
I asked around.
The private school just changed owners.
It's nothing serious.
Did you find out
who bought the school?
The buyer is Juyun Pavilion.
We've sent people to buy the land back.
But they
don't seem to want to sell it.
Your Excellency,
there is another small matter.
Speak.
Her Ladyship borrowed
my sister's access badge
to slip out of the residence
despite the danger,
keeping it from all of us.
What did you say?
My Lady left the premises?
Where did she go?
Presumably,
she went to meet the teachers and students
of the private school.
Yan Jiang and I discussed it
and decided not to get in the way.
Where is Yan Jiang?
I came to report her safety first
to put your mind at ease.
Yan Jiang followed her.
That fellow who is bad with directions
is following her?
But Yan Jiang is good at
recognizing faces.
It'll be fine.
Your Excellency, where are you going?
Here you go.
Mother, I want this.
Where is she?
[Qingzhuang Academy]
You must be the teacher Fan Yun.
President Lou invites you.
Please come with us.
President Lou?
I knew it.
You were coming for me.
[Juyun Pavilion]
Young Master Qiyan.
You must have been
waiting for a long time.
May I ask why you
summoned me today?
Please speak your mind.
I'll listen.
Do you know
what kind of huqin this is
in my hands?
This is...
A masterpiece from the previous dynasty,
named the Ancient Moon.
A masterpiece for a beauty.
Please sit.
Young Master,
you didn't just invite me here
to look at an instrument, did you?
It seems you don't plan to
explain about
the incident at Huan'e House.
I offended you that day.
Please let me apologize to you.
I hope you can...
be magnanimous and forgive me.
Please don't take it out
on the private school.
Play a piece first,
and we'll talk about the school.
That's the tune.
The sound is engaging
and majestic.
It gets the blood pumping.
This must be "Absolute Loyalty."
Miss Fan Yun, why did you stop?
Young Master Qiyan.
The name of this piece is
"Listen to Rain on the Mountainside."
The tune is
tranquil, refreshing, and ethereal,
not the blood-pumping
battle song you spoke of.
It seems your ear for music is
really quite extraordinary.
This is our third meeting.
Gold is easy to get,
but a soulmate is hard to find.
I took the liberty of
inviting you here today.
Sorry for startling you.
This is my apology.
From now on, for every piece you play,
I'll grant you one favor in return;
anything at all.
You are
giving this deed to the private school
to me just like that?
Get your claws off her!
Your Excellency?
W-Why are you here?
Did he bully you?
No.
So the governor has arrived.
You sure are brazen, Young Master Lou.
Do you think you can
touch My Lady's hands as you please?
It's a pity I couldn't finish
listening to this piece.
Although we feel differently
about the piece,
your skills are indeed exquisite.
I really like them.
Thank you, Young Master Qiyan.
You even played a piece for him?
Look.
Good that you liked it.
But there won't be a next time.
Apologies for my poor hospitality,
Your Excellency.
Just as mountains and rivers
eventually cross,
may our paths cross again.
People who walk different paths
aren't a good fit.
See you never.
Miss Fan Yun.
We will meet again.
The students will thank you!
Your Excellency.
I only sneaked out
because I was worried
about the private school.
Hey, it hurts!
Your Excellency.
Do you want a snack?
It's delicious.
Try one.
Your Excellency, what are you doing?
Which hand did Lou Qiyan use
to hold yours?
I...
He schemed in every way
to get close to you;
even bought the private school for you.
He clearly has ulterior motives.
So, of course I have to wipe them clean.
Y-You know everything?
Of course I sent Wei and Yan out
to investigate.
You even used a honey trap!
I didn't!
Don't you
trust me to resolve the problem for you?
I...
I trust you.
Well, he gave me
the deed to the private school.
We aren't losing out,
are we?
Right?
I'll break his legs
if he dares to take advantage of you!
Speaking of Lou Qiyan makes my blood boil.
All merchants are dishonest.
He gave you this school,
so he must want something in return.
Don't tell me he's trading it for you!
Me?
How could I give myself to him?
B-Besides,
it's not like
he can do whatever he wants.
What are you thinking?
Your Excellency.
After all,
those are students
who have been seeking my guidance.
The private school is my life's work too.
Also,
if that Lou Qiyan
wanted to harm me,
he could've just found a random place
in the streets to bury me.
That would also reduce suspicion
against Juyun Pavilion.
Right?
I guess that makes sense.
All right then.
I'll believe you this once.
Now,
can you have the snack?
Try it.
It's really good.
Whatever!
Forget about him.
He's bad luck anyway.
I need to go home now
to sign the documents Lord Zheng left me
for raising taxes.
Raising taxes?
It's a stopgap measure.
But
is it right?
The most important thing in Nine Cities
is its people.
Blindly raising taxes
will only make the people suffer
and destabilize the Nine Cities.
Your Excellency,
let me take you somewhere.
Turn around!
To the Alley Literary Teahouse.
[Alley Literary Teahouse]
Have you heard?
They're raising taxes
in Nine Cities again.
How can small businesses
like ours keep running?
We have families to feed.
This literary teahouse
has been here since I was born.
I know it won't work!
Hidden talents abound here.
Everyone inside is very knowledgeable.
Do you still remember
the flood in Gao City 5 years ago?
Remember?
At that time,
many people
came here to ask them for advice.
Not to mention you lot...
The man on the left,
he sells silk.
That man in the middle
sells pork.
They are all very talented.
Don't underestimate them
because they are commoners;
each and every one of them
cares deeply about the Nine Cities
and its people.
There must be a limit
to taking the people's
wealth and hard work.
The imposition of taxes and labor
cannot be unbridled.
Otherwise,
we
and the entire Nine Cities
will be like a runaway carriage,
our fortunes taking a nosedive.
In my opinion, historically,
periods of prosperity are built on
minimal taxation and corvée labor.
There were no miscellaneous charges,
and the land tax was reasonable.
Nothing complicated;
the commoners only needed to hand over
a portion of their annual grain.
If such taxes
only account for 10%,
then such an excellent policy
of recuperation is
most beneficial to
improving people's livelihood.
Your Excellency,
will you still raise taxes?
Did you think I wanted to
raise the taxes of the people?
What do you
mean by that?
What do you think?
You said earlier
that it was a stopgap measure.
What about now?
What do you think?
What I think?
I think you
don't want to raise taxes,
and even have a desire for reform.
If you didn't
have the welfare of the people at heart,
you wouldn't have come with me
to that literary teahouse.
Your so-called incompetence
is just an act you put on, right?
Fan Yun.
The mind of a sovereign is inscrutable.
Is it?
Could it be
that this isn't the real you?
What about you?
Knowing all this,
you still cooperate with me
despite the danger.
Yes.
It's because I know everything
that I'm willing.
Because this is also what I want.
I've thought about it.
After we go back,
I'll keep doing my best
to cooperate with you.
I won't cause you trouble
and will let you
leverage my power steadily.
Wei Ying.
Why is my pay so much lower this month?
Shouldn't every official
know about the increased taxation?
Did I misunderstand it?
Weren't we raising taxes on the people?
Raising taxes is an incompetent move.
I was also worried
the governor was acting on a whim
without forethought.
But after
the tax adjustments were
announced to the public,
I realized I was overthinking it.
Look,
this tax increase only applies to
those with a monthly income
of over 5 tons of grain.
Other taxes remain unchanged.
There are even some
tax reductions and exemptions
for commoners.
Over 5 tons...
That's based on the salary
of a seventh-rank official.
And the agricultural income of the nobles
basically meets this standard.
I see.
The governor is trying to
take advantage of
the officials and nobles.
Such a tax reform is
going to... to be the death of me!
I... I...
I recognize that
the empty treasury this year
is a major issue.
But this year has been
a year of poor harvest!
That's right!
The commoners can't afford to pay taxes,
but we nobles don't have
any surplus grain either.
-Am I right?
-Totally!
-Exactly!
I used to enjoy
20 dishes for a meal.
Now,
I only have 12 dishes!
Lord Fan, look at me!
I'm wasting away!
-This tax increase...
-Yes.
Why is it targeting the nobles?
Were the commoners' taxes even raised?
Goodness...
[Duanyun Gate]
Last time Lord Zheng
suggested raising taxes
to fill the treasury,
I strongly agreed.
I didn't expect
the implemented draft
to cause such an uproar.
Your Excellency.
I believe
the tax regulations
currently implemented in Nine Cities
are different from what I presented.
-So...
-Lord Zheng.
Now you're aware that
raising taxes causes an uproar.
The current situation is
already so volatile.
Raising taxes on the commoners now
will surely provoke public outrage.
You...
Enough.
I'm also in a difficult position.
My dear lords, to be honest,
I've been tossing and turning
because of this matter these days.
But just last night,
I actually dreamed of the late governor.
So I asked the late governor, my father,
for advice on governance.
And guess what?
When the late governor heard
that I was actually
worrying about the people,
he was overjoyed!
So he proposed a strategy to me:
open up trade in Nine Cities.
Ji City is rich in steel.
Gao City is abound with fish and rice.
Wang City's porcelain is world-famous.
Every city has its own specialty.
With the treasury empty,
trade,
road repair,
and agricultural support
are all viable paths.
If trade routes are opened
and cities can trade freely,
then with the circulation
of money and daily necessities,
the people will naturally
become prosperous.
When we raise taxes then,
there wouldn't be any livelihood issues.
When I woke up,
I thought
it was brilliant; truly enlightening!
Lord Zheng,
what do you think?
A dream from the late governor;
this strategy
is good indeed.
But Your Excellency, have you considered
that a slow remedy
does not address the current emergency?
Besides,
it's just an armchair strategy!
Lord Zheng.
You certainly consider things
more thoroughly than the late governor.
But do you have
a better solution than the late governor?
I'm merely doing my best
for the Nine Cities.
Please make the decision, Your Excellency.
Invoking the late governor
to leave me speechless?
Qi Zheng has never dared to
defy me in political matters.
How did he come up with such an idea now?
The other day, the spy said
that he saw
the governor returning to his residence
with Fan Yun.
Could this be her doing again?
Qi Zheng is the governor,
but he is actually allowing himself
to be manipulated.
What utter foolishness and incompetence!
Please calm down, Master.
Who knew
that witch Fan Yun
would become so intimate
with the governor so quickly?
What's the use of blaming it
all on a woman?
The root of the problem
lies in that good-for-nothing man!
He is unfit for the position!
Master, be cautious with your words.
He's just lucky to be born
with the Qi family's blood in his veins.
Do you mean he is
Qingyuan, the Second Young Master Qi?
Qi Zheng had been
fooling around in the Nine Cities.
When the late governor was alive,
the favored heir
was not him.
So you're saying...
Knowing all this,
you still cooperate with me
despite the danger.
Yes.
It's because I know everything
that I'm willing.
Then cooperate with me on one thing first.
Poisoning?
Who would poison me in my bedchamber?
Fan Yun,
I just learned a makeup look
that is all the rage.
Let me try it on you.
Between close friends,
beauty secrets shouldn't be hidden.
Fan Yun?
Fan Yun!
What is it?
What's wrong with you?
Are you ready?
Then let's stick to the plan
and start the sick makeup.
I'm fine.
Time for the makeup.
Come on.
Everything's spinning.
Somebody help!
Her Ladyship has fainted! Come!
Hurry, hurry!
You're pretty quick.
I barely had to wait at all.
Suyin.
Look at me.
Did you poison her?
No one ordered me to do it.
I did it myself.
Don't be nervous.
Let me ask you again.
Fan Yun treats you so well.
Why did you repeatedly poison her?
My Lady... My Lady...
Is My Lady alright?
Since you did it yourself,
why do you care if she is alright or not?
I administered the poison,
but I didn't want her to die.
-Then why...
-Wei Ying.
Get up first.
Where is Her Ladyship?
Your Excellency.
Oh no.
Anything?
Your Excellency,
I have deployed men
to search for Her Ladyship.
Protect the governor!
A squad will stay with me
to protect the governor.
The rest, go after them!
-Let's go! After them!
-Get a move on! Let's go!
[If you wish to save her, come to
Linglong Tower alone. Fan Yun is here.]
To think they'd be so rampant.
Who knows what they want?
Her Ladyship...
might be in danger.
Linglong Tower...
Wei Ying, go find Gao Ran.
Tell him to notify Lord Fan Qi.
Lord Fan Qi.
Dark Wolf!
What are you doing?
Wolf! Wolf!
Wolf?
Your Excellency,
so you were just trying to scare me.
What wolf?
There are no wolves in this area.
Your Excellency, if you're here,
does it mean Yun is back too?
I came back specifically to see you,
Lord Fan Qi.
I'll prepare tea for you right away.
Hang on.
Lord Fan Qi.
Isn't your acting a bit over the top?
It's you, isn't it?
Me?
W-What... What do you mean?
You see, a perfectly good tree
that could have lived for a century
has now met with disaster.
Lord Fan Qi.
If the roots of this tree are withered,
how should it be saved?
Water it
and fertilize it.
If the roots are rotten,
what then?
Uproot it,
prune the rot, and rejuvenate the soil.
That's exactly what I wish to do.
Today's Nine Cities
is just like this withered phoenix tree,
decaying and conservative.
If we don't nourish it,
prune the rot, and rejuvenate the soil,
it won't be able to grow new buds
and bear fruit again.
I really don't want
this tree to die in my hands.
Do you understand?
I understand.
It's fine if you don't trust me
right now.
I'll pretend I bought
this paper knife at the market.
Although I like the look of it,
I don't want to take it by force.
Let's test its sharpness.
I'll take this paper with me;
I hope to have your help in the future.
Let's go.
Where am I?
Is anyone there?
Help!
You...
Who are you?