[The Legend of Rosy Clouds]
[Episode 6]
Master.
Go invite him in.
Yes.
[Linglong Tower]
Lord Zheng.
If that's the case,
there is no point
in continuing this conversation.
You've got the wrong person.
Second Young Master Qi.
I am not Second Young Master Qi.
My name is Gao Ran,
and I serve Qi Zheng.
The Governor of the Nine Cities
will only be him.
For a subject,
loyalty is enough.
For the people,
a wise governor is paramount.
A peach tree grows by the open well;
a plum tree stands beside it.
When insects come to bite the peach roots,
the plum tree dies in its place.
Trees sacrifice for each other,
yet brothers forget one another.
I once taught you this poem.
Do you still remember?
The plum tree used
to die for the peach tree.
But now,
what if the plum tree dies?
The peach tree
can live in its stead
and thrive for it.
Peach and plum trees share the same roots;
they live and die together.
Furthermore,
the fertile land of the Nine Cities
is enough to nourish thousands of trees.
How can such insignificant tricks
stop the vast power of heaven?
It seems you are prepared.
Lord Zheng,
Qi Zheng is actually
the wise governor.
Stop!
Put the blade down.
I told you to put the blade down!
Are you crazy?
Killing your own woman?
The footsteps sounded wrong.
Fan Yun isn't that heavy.
Speak!
Where is Fan Yun?
Fan Yun.
Fan Yun, are you okay?
Qi Zheng,
thank goodness you're finally here.
I thought I'd never see you again.
I'll get you out of here.
Okay.
Watch out, Qi Zheng!
Hang in there.
♪ Spring winds, autumn rain ♪
Fan Yun,
♪ Flowers bloom for a single season ♪
♪ Fallen petals turn into mud ♪
I'm a man of my word.
♪ It's never ♪
I will definitely take you back.
♪ The ending I crave ♪
♪ I'd be the wick lit up ♪
♪ For you each night ♪
♪ Burning myself bright ♪
♪ Beside you as you hold the brush ♪
♪ Till every streak of ink fades away ♪
♪ I search and search through all days ♪
♪ Lingering on with unwilling heart ♪
♪ What does a final choice matter? ♪
♪ In the moment of looking back ♪
♪ This life is worth it ♪
♪ When no dawn can be seen ahead ♪
♪ Who are the dream-walkers? ♪
♪ Facing the light ♪
♪ Singing a long song along the way ♪
Kill.
♪ Tear the dark night apart ♪
♪ Turn my whole heart ♪
♪ Into an ever-burning bright lamp light ♪
♪ Live up to every year ♪
♪ With fiery passion ♪
♪ Even if I merge into ♪
♪ The stream of stars in the end ♪
♪ With thousands of li between us ♪
♪ I never fade away within your eyes ♪
♪ Gaze at endless streams and peaks ♪
♪ Turn my whole heart ♪
♪ Into the glimmering sun and moon ♪
♪ Burn up every bit of time given ♪
♪ Seek no karma nor any fruit ♪
♪ Only one promise remains ♪
♪ No time can tear us far apart ♪
♪ It becomes an eternal old tale ♪
♪ As mountains and seas change over time ♪
♪ He keeps this memory close ♪
♪ As long as the heart's light remains ♪
♪ There won't be loneliness ♪
I'm sorry.
It's my fault for being so clumsy.
I didn't take good care of Fan Yun.
It's not your fault.
Your Excellency, Lord Jiang is here.
Send him in.
Lord Jiang?
The one who ranks first
on the Guanyu List
but always wears a mask
and never lets anyone
see his true face.
Since he is
such a mysterious person,
his medical skills must be extraordinary.
It's said that those
who saw Lord Jiang's true face
were almost scared to death by his beauty.
Later, Lord Jiang
didn't want to cause trouble,
nor did he want his beauty
to overshadow his talent.
So,
he decided to wear a mask.
I hope he can save Fan Yun.
I also heard
he's not only
first on the Guanyu List
but also first in the selection test
back then.
He also has the best medical skills
in the Nine Cities.
Lord Jiang Shu is exceptional
in both talent and looks.
He definitely has a way to save Fan Yun.
Your Excellency,
Fan Yun
will surely live a long life.
Greetings, Your Excellency.
[Jiang Shu, Manager
of the Commerce Ministry]
Jiang Shu,
what took you so long?
Come,
think of a way quickly.
I will do my best.
But...
you and everyone,
please step outside first.
I leave Fan Yun's life in your hands.
Please.
Your Excellency,
can you stop pacing around?
Didn't you say it yourself?
Jiang Shu
is the best doctor in the Nine Cities.
It will be fine.
Yes.
But Jiang Shu has been handling
Commerce Ministry affairs.
He hasn't practiced his medical skills.
I don't know if he can do it.
It'll be fine.
Just relax.
And you.
He's out.
Why isn't he out yet?
Lord Jiang.
Lord Jiang,
how is Fan Yun?
I can do nothing more.
Her Ladyship is severely injured.
I'm afraid...
we can only leave it to fate.
Lord Jiang,
is there really no other way?
Leave it to fate?
What do you mean by that?
There are no exceptions?
Unless...
Unless what?
Say something!
We finally managed to escape this time
and save our own lives.
I didn't expect this person
to be so powerful,
causing such heavy casualties
among our brothers.
Don't mention it.
Now we have meat and wine,
which is pretty good.
What exactly is the madam's background?
They said the governor's wife
was as beautiful as a fairy,
glamorous and charming.
But when I saw her last time,
she was just average.
She's not even as pretty as the girls
we find in the brothel.
-Exactly.
-Right.
-Come on.
-Drink up.
You are from the Shadow Slay League?
We
don't cross paths with you.
If you dare to touch us,
the people behind us
will never let you get away with it!
What you just said
made me very unhappy.
Spare... spare me!
Whenever we see you,
we'll walk the other way, okay?
Is Her Ladyship as beautiful as a fairy?
Yes. Her Ladyship...
Her Ladyship is as beautiful as a fairy!
Absolutely stunning!
A fairy from heaven!
Send the people who hurt Her Ladyship
in Linglong Tower that day here.
Yes.
Bring them up!
That day,
did you see Her Ladyship?
I-I didn't see her.
I didn't see her.
Did you?
I did! I did!
I did!
So it was you.
It was me!
It was me! It was me! It was me!
Which hand did you use
to touch Her Ladyship?
I... I...
I didn't!
I never touched her!
It wasn't me! I didn't touch her!
It wasn't me!
I asked you to think of a way.
Why did you give me a history book?
How do you explain this?
The solution
is in this history book.
Before the late governor passed away,
he used a specially provided
spiritual herb to prolong his life.
It is said that this herb
can repair muscles and bones,
and neutralize all poisons.
To save Her Ladyship,
we have to find it.
Then what are we waiting for?
Hurry up and find this Bailing Herb.
It's a pity.
What's a pity?
Can you finish your sentence?
This herb is rare.
After the late governor passed away,
it has never appeared
in the Nine Cities again.
Are you messing with me on purpose?
Don't wrong me.
I hate being wronged the most in my life.
Can you finish your words at once?
I can't stand you anymore!
Excuse me.
Have you seen the Bailing Herb like this?
No, I haven't.
How is it?
How about you?
Roll in the good luck.
♪ Watch how flowers bloom and wither ♪
Roll away the villains.
♪ Count how many springs
and autumns pass ♪
Roll in the beneficiaries.
♪ Why the sighs and regrets? ♪
Roll away the diseases.
Roll in good health.
♪ Lovers wait a lifetime ♪
I knew it.
♪ Love cannot be cut away ♪
How could such a silly method work?
♪ How to let go? ♪
If it were really good luck,
why couldn't I find the Bailing Herb?
Fan Yun,
it's all my fault.
♪ All our fates were long inscribed ♪
Although this trick successfully
lured out Zheng Yuan
♪ How to set free grief and joy? ♪
and helped find the Dark Wolf,
♪ Mortal life is but an ephemeral dream ♪
it caused you to be like this.
♪ No mortal soul may rule its life ♪
It was my negligence.
Bad luck, good luck,
diseases, or health?
♪ If women are akin to blossoms ♪
♪ Can they be cherished tenderly? ♪
Since my mother passed away
♪ For whom do they hide tears silently? ♪
and Second Brother went missing,
♪ How could one bear to lay blame? ♪
in this world,
♪ Time runs wild with reckless haste ♪
things I truly care about
♪ Never mind fate dyes white crimson red ♪
are very few indeed.
♪ For whom does ♪
♪ This phoenix blossom bloom? ♪
The world scolds me
and laughs at me,
♪ Love fills my years,
and my heart remains true ♪
so what?
I will just play the fool
♪ Let all worldly longing fade away ♪
in front of them.
♪ Fall deep within a single dream ♪
♪ Wait till a breath of wind arrives ♪
But Fan Yun, do you know?
I am
destined to walk this path alone.
But you appeared at this time
and gave so much for me.
Are you
going to leave me now?
♪ The wind arrives ♪
Your Excellency, Your Excellency.
Your Excellency,
Lord Fan Qi heard that Her Ladyship
was seriously ill,
so he specially sent this herb.
The old rule.
I eat the sesame,
and you eat the pancake.
Qiangwei,
your spirit in heaven
must bless our Yun.
May heaven guard her, for good souls
receive divine protection.
May she be blessed with peace
and happiness.
The Bailing Herb
was exclusively supplied
to the late governor.
Since the war 13 years ago,
no one has seen it.
You can give it a try, Your Excellency.
You only came back
when there's the Bailing Herb.
So should the credit go to you
or the Bailing Herb?
It is the will of Heaven.
After Her Ladyship takes this medicine,
she just needs to recuperate slowly.
With some days of rest,
her depleted vitality will be restored.
Well...
All right.
Come on.
Well...
Lord Jiang.
Lord Jiang told me to do this.
If it doesn't work,
I will hold you accountable.
Your Excellency,
this is...
I know. I know.
You may leave now.
Don't disturb her while she rests.
I shall take my leave.
Fan Yun.
Miss Wei.
Second Young Master Zheng.
Miss Wei,
are you heading
to Her Ladyship's chambers?
Yes, I am on my way there.
Why?
Has the Zheng family moved
the Directorate of Education's classes
to Her Ladyship's chambers?
Now I know how eloquent
and quick-witted you are.
Hearing that Her Ladyship
is seriously ill,
I gathered some medicinal herbs.
I hope they can be of help.
Please give them to her for me.
No need.
Fan Yun is fine now.
Has Her Ladyship recovered?
His Excellency found the Bailing Herb
for Fan Yun a few days ago.
She has already taken it
and is now recovering.
But thank you anyway.
Second Young Master Zheng,
if there's nothing else,
I will take my leave.
Your Excellency,
is Yun alright?
She's taken the Bailing Herb
and is getting better.
Lord Fan Qi.
No.
I should call you Dark Wolf now,
shouldn't I?
Do you still trust me now?
I,
naturally,
trust you.
Returning this to its rightful owner.
Your Excellency,
I
really want to see
our Nine Cities
thrive in full prosperity,
just like
these phoenix flowers!
Here.
Slowly, it's hot.
I heard
this herb is extremely hard to find.
Thank you for your trouble,
Your Excellency.
Actually, this time,
I wasn't the one who delivered
the medicine to save you.
It was Dark Wolf.
Well...
Dark Wolf?
Do you mean the one
hidden in the martial world,
the terrifying Dark Wolf?
Your Excellency,
you found him?
Oh, right.
This
was sent by Lord Fan Qi.
He said you've hated bitter medicine
since you were little,
so you must take it
with these candied fruits.
He also said he made them himself.
Have a taste.
Father said
he made these himself?
What's wrong? Why are you laughing?
He obviously bought these
at the corner shop.
My father
would blow up the kitchen
just trying to boil an egg.
How could he make these?
I didn't expect Dark...
Lord Fan Qi to be like this
behind the scenes.
How is it?
Do you feel better
after the candied fruit?
Fan Yun.
After going through this,
I know your feelings for me are true.
So from now on,
I will treat you well.
What's wrong? Choking?
I'm fine, Your Excellency.
Here.
Y-Your Excellency,
-Your Excellency, I can do it myself.
-It's fine.
You are injured now.
It is my duty to take care of you.
I... I...
Just give it to me.
Don't worry, Your Excellency.
I'm really fine now.
That's good.
Here.
Hurry and drink the medicine.
Don't let it get cold.
Here.
Careful, it's hot.
What's wrong?