♪I defy heaven, fate,
and so-called immortality♪
♪At last you say
we've been apart too long♪
♪Unwilling, unyielding, I won't let go♪
♪With you, even a dried sea
learns to embrace a stream♪
♪If heaven divides us, I'll reunite us,
with love as our vessel♪
♪If it forbids it, I'll shatter
the absurd Heavenly Dao♪
♪Even if countless stars
turn into my foes♪
♪To grow old with you, we burn
through the end of the long night♪
=Rise Again=
=Episode 19=
You're not Jiang Yao.
Who are you?
Forgot me already?
Senior?
Senior.
Senior, let's talk this out.
I heard Su Wubing
pulled the divine sword.
Yes. He's ruining everything.
So, he's the ancient Immortal King.
Immortal King?
Su Wubing is the Immortal King?
What else explains how strong he is?
Is there a woman
named Lin Ningxue with him?
Yes.
Ever since he showed up,
he's helped her every time.
Then her curse hasn't been lifted yet.
Senior.
This...
If Su Wubing is the Immortal King,
can you beat him?
No!
A mere mortal dares question me?
Senior, I'm just looking out for you.
Immortal King or not,
he's still in a mortal body.
Maybe this time
I can even take two immortal souls.
Senior.
As long as you eliminate him,
I will follow you to the end.
Before I came out of seclusion,
capture Lin Ningxue
to lure out the Immortal King.
Yes.
I'll do as you command.
Senior.
Mr. Gu.
You still have the nerve to speak?
Su Wubing.
Let's see how you get out of this one.
I'm finally going to win.
This aura...
It's the ancient Demon Clan.
Who are you?
Immortal King,
once I leave seclusion,
I'll settle the score with you myself
and take your soul
to fulfill the Demon Clan's plan.
Did Wubing turn you down?
W-W-Who got rejected?
I was just bored and stopped by.
Sure. Whatever you say.
And...
if you want to know
about the two of them,
I can tell you.
I've got nothing better to do anyway.
Fine.
So,
Wubing and the Holy Maiden
are made for each other.
Forget breaking them up...
Even a temporary separation
is out of the question.
Grandpa,
even if you're defending him,
you don't have to make up
something that outrageous.
Believe it or not,
everything I said is true.
Fine, fine.
Even if you told me
you've been alive since ancient times,
I'd believe that too, okay?
If you
truly admire Wubing,
staying by his side
isn't a bad choice.
Who knows... maybe one day
he'll change his mind.
(Oh, no. Grandpa's spent his whole life
healing people.)
(Don't tell me he's gone senile now.)
Still so reckless.
(Shan Martial Hall.
We need to talk. Come.)
(Shan Yingying?)
(Can't she just call?)
All of you, out.
Let's fight again.
Again?
You used spiritual power last time.
If you win this time,
the martial hall is yours.
If you lose, keep doing chores here.
Win or lose,
I'm still part of this place.
Suit yourself.
Bring it on.
Without spiritual power,
you're nothing special.
Why does this always happen?
Fine, I surrender.
This is our family heirloom
spirit stone.
Every head of the family
uses it to cultivate.
Ningxue told me about you.
I thought it might help you.
This is...
the stone used to forge
the Heavenly God Sword.
Thanks.
No need.
I just want to know
are you really the Immortal King?
Fine, keep your secrets.
I also want to ask you
do you remember
what you told me at the hotel that day?
You said if Ningxue were in danger
and saving her
meant sacrificing yourself,
you'd do it.
Is that true?
Yes.
You really are different
from any other man I've met.
I hope you mean what you say.
I don't understand
the Heavenly Dao's curse,
but Ningxue may look tough
on the outside,
but inside, she's barely holding on.
Don't let her down.
Thanks.
Wait.
One more thing.
How many wives can an immortal have?
W-W-Who's there?
Maybe I'm just too tense.
Guard the entrance.
No one gets in.
Yes.
Miss Lin,
let's make up for our wedding night.
What?
You have something to say?
Get lost.
Get lost?
Don't touch me.
Don't touch you?
You're like a lamb to the slaughter now.
If you touch me again,
Su Wubing won't let you off!
Su Wubing?
Even he couldn't find you.
Once I'm done with you,
I'll send you back.
Then you can
reunite with him underground.
Don't touch me!
Get off me!
♪I defy heaven, fate,
and so-called immortality♪
♪At last you say
we've been apart too long♪
♪Unwilling, unyielding, I won't let go♪
♪With you, even a dried sea
learns to embrace a stream♪
♪If heaven divides us, I'll reunite us,
with love as our vessel♪
♪If it forbids it, I'll shatter
the absurd Heavenly Dao♪
♪Even if countless stars
turn into my foes♪
♪To grow old with you, we burn
through the end of the long night♪