♪I defy heaven, fate,
and so-called immortality♪
♪At last you say
we've been apart too long♪
♪Unwilling, unyielding, I won't let go♪
♪With you, even a dried sea
learns to embrace a stream♪
♪If heaven divides us, I'll reunite us,
with love as our vessel♪
♪If it forbids it, I'll shatter
the absurd Heavenly Dao♪
♪Even if countless stars
turn into my foes♪
♪To grow old with you, we burn
through the end of the long night♪
=Rise Again=
=Episode 21=
Big talk.
You're asking for it.
Yingying!
You go first.
Wubing...
Su Wubing.
Ningxue.
What is this?
Ningxue!
Don't go!
That was
Ningxue's divine sense.
She's still trapped in the illusion.
Finally caught on?
You aren't that impressive, huh?
Her divine sense has been stuck
in ancient times.
You'll never break her curse.
Su Wubing,
you really think you can
change everything by yourself?
Now get down
on your knees for m-my Senior.
If he's pleased,
maybe you'll get a quick death.
You want to save her? No chance.
This ancient demonic power
was meant for you.
Even every god in heaven
couldn't last a minute in it.
Your soul is mine!
Sword, come!
You have reforged the sword?
Have you regained
the Immortal King's Heavenly God Realm?
Immortal King?
He really is the Immortal King.
Senior.
He can't be the Immortal King.
Otherwise, he wouldn't
need these mortals to save him.
Senior.
You promised me
you'd take his life.
Impossible.
Su Wubing is nothing to fear.
Just finish him!
A mere ant dares to make noise?
S-Senior, what are you doing?
Your job is done.
No use keeping you around.
Might as well use you
to boost my cultivation.
Consider it your contribution
to the Demon Clan.
Since you've reached
the Heavenly God Realm,
I'd be interested
to cross swords with you.
Since you insist,
I'll grant your wish.
Grant my wish?
They say an Immortal King's sword
can split the spirit mountains.
One strike can unleash
fifty years of power.
But you've spent a thousand years
as a mere mortal.
Even if you've awakened divine power,
you're not what you used to be.
You can't strike the way you once did.
Pity indeed.
You won't live to see that strike.
In that case,
I'll kill Lin Ningxue first.
Once you have a weakness,
you have an opening.
As long as
you can't let go your obsession,
no matter how many times you're reborn,
you're still nothing but an ant.
Let go now, and it's not too late.
Let go?
The Ancient God Sect
has waited all this time
for this very moment.
How is this possible?
This strike...
may not carry sixty years of power,
but it's more than enough to kill you.
Even if I die,
I'll drag Lin Ningxue down with me.
♪I defy heaven, fate,
and so-called immortality♪
♪At last you say
we've been apart too long♪
♪Unwilling, unyielding, I won't let go♪
♪With you, even a dried sea
learns to embrace a stream♪
♪If heaven divides us, I'll reunite us,
with love as our vessel♪
♪If it forbids it, I'll shatter
the absurd Heavenly Dao♪
♪Even if countless stars
turn into my foes♪
♪To grow old with you, we burn
through the end of the long night♪