♪I defy heaven, fate,
and so-called immortality♪
♪At last you say
we've been apart too long♪
♪Unwilling, unyielding, I won't let go♪
♪With you, even a dried sea
learns to embrace a stream♪
♪If heaven divides us, I'll reunite us,
with love as our vessel♪
♪If it forbids it, I'll shatter
the absurd Heavenly Dao♪
♪Even if countless stars
turn into my foes♪
♪To grow old with you, we burn
through the end of the long night♪
=Rise Again=
=Episode 20=
Once I'm done with you,
I'll send you back.
Then you can
reunite with him underground.
Don't touch me!
Who are you?
Guards!
Who the heck are you?
S-S-Senior.
I told you to bring her to me.
What's taking so long?
Senior.
I-I think
she and Su Wubing are going
to die anyway,
so it'd be a waste not to...
How dare you ruin my plan.
Please.
No...
Who are you?
With you, I can get his soul.
(I failed to beat the Heavenly Dao)
(because the sword wasn't fully forged.)
(With the spirit stone,
everything will be easy now.)
Sword, come!
Congratulations on reaching
the Heavenly God Realm.
With the sword as well,
we might just change the world.
I reached the Heavenly God realm
for Ningxue.
No time to waste.
Let's...
Break!
I set up a barrier here.
It couldn't be broken so easily.
Who is this?
Hello?
Su Wubing, Ningxue...
My Lord, look!
It's you.
Long time no see.
I told you at the teahouse.
the day I come out, I'll take your soul.
If you want to save Lin Ningxue,
come to the rooftop
of Gu Group tomorrow.
Remember,
come alone.
Otherwise,
I'll tear her soul apart first.
You!
My Lord.
Who is that?
A descendant of the Demon Clan.
What?
After ten thousand years,
the demons still won't quit.
I'll go with you.
You'll need backup.
No.
I have to go alone.
Ningxue is in his hands.
I need to do as he said.
Su Wubing.
You actually came alone.
Where's Ningxue?
I thought you were so capable.
Find her yourself.
Let Ningxue go
and I might spare you.
Even if you colluded
with the Ancient God Sect,
I could let that slide too.
You think you're in a position
to bargain with me?
You made me kneel last time.
We're not done with that.
Kneel. Now.
If you make me happy,
maybe I'll let you see her
one last time.
Senior.
Immortal King,
you never thought
you'd be trapped
in a mortal body again, did you?
Let Ningxue go.
Fine.
Then destroy your own spiritual core
and trade your soul.
This is between us.
Don't drag her into it.
You never change.
She's still your weakness.
Ten thousand years ago,
you defied the Heavenly Dao
just to break her curse.
You gave your life
and spent ten thousand years alone.
Yet her curse still remains.
Now you're pushing your limits again,
still trying to save her.
What...
How dare you!
Tianmiao!
That all you got, old man?
Tianmiao, you can't beat him.
My Lord.
Back when the Heavenly Dao descended,
I couldn't help you.
This time,
I will stand with you.
How touching.
Grandpa!
How did you get hurt so badly?
Senior, they're in the way.
Why not just wipe them all out?
Su Wubing,
I only came for you.
But if you let them
throw their lives away,
don't blame me.
Big talk.
You're asking for it.
♪I defy heaven, fate,
and so-called immortality♪
♪At last you say
we've been apart too long♪
♪Unwilling, unyielding, I won't let go♪
♪With you, even a dried sea
learns to embrace a stream♪
♪If heaven divides us, I'll reunite us,
with love as our vessel♪
♪If it forbids it, I'll shatter
the absurd Heavenly Dao♪
♪Even if countless stars
turn into my foes♪
♪To grow old with you, we burn
through the end of the long night♪