WELCOME TO HIKARI CITY!!
1.2 MILES TO TOWN
[Tetsuo] So it's been three years.
Takao, are you sure you want to do this?
Yeah.
You don't need to, you know.
-We can still--
-I'm all right.
At some point...
I'd have to face it, anyway.
[♪ opening theme music playing]
THE FLOWERS OF EVIL
EPISODE 11
[Takao's cousin] Grandpa!
[sobbing loudly]
Your sister...
-[Tetsuo] Big Sis...
-[Takao's cousin continues crying]
-[Shizue] Haruko...
-[Haruko continues crying]
I really appreciate you coming.
We'll see you again tomorrow.
Thank you for taking care of things.
[Haruko] Do you have a place to stay?
[Tetsuo] Yeah. Don't worry about us.
[Takao's cousin] Taka-chan.
You know...
There's one thing I have to say to you.
It's your fault, Taka-chan.
No one said it to your face,
but we were all amazed
you had the nerve to show your face.
[♪ somber music playing]
Do you have any idea
how difficult you made our lives?
I bet you didn't get to see
Grandpa at the end
because he rejected you, Taka-chan.
I'm sorry.
I sincerely apologize!
If you're actually sorry,
spend the rest of your life
making things right.
[Takao] You're born in this town
and you die in this town.
We're sorry for your loss.
STYLE
::cue()
[Takao] That was supposed
to be my life, too.
KASUGA FUNERAL
But I got out of this town
and continued to live on.
GUEST SIGN IN
Then, what is this town?
What does it mean to me?
MIZUKOSHI INC.
NEIGHBORS
After what he did three years ago...
-I'm shocked they showed up.
-Yeah.
-[male mourner] It is him.
-My goodness. They've got some nerve, no?
After causing that much trouble...
[whispering continues indistinctly]
Takao, are you doing all right?
Yeah.
Dad,
Mom,
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Takao...
We're very sorry for your loss.
It's been a while.
Kinoshita...
[indistinct chatter]
I'm sorry...
about back then.
[Ai] Right after,
Nanako moved away without even telling me.
I don't know her address.
I guess I could've
tracked her down if I tried.
But, I just...
Have you seen her since then?
Yeah.
What, really? When? Where?
Last year, in Omiya.
-[♪ somber music playing]
-She was with her boyfriend.
Apparently, she lives in Utsunomiya now.
Is she doing all right?
Yeah.
She said she's "happy and stuff."
Right.
[inhales]
I see... [whimpers]
Funny... I've just been left behind.
I drove you guys out of town.
And I couldn't stop Nanako
from leaving, either.
Back then...
what should I have done?
I'm the only one
that's been trapped in this town.
Forever and ever... [sobbing]
I don't want that...
What about Nakamura?
What happened between you two after that?
I haven't seen her.
Not since the moment
she pushed me off the stage.
I don't know... where she is now.
Whether she's alive,
or if she's dead.
Don't you want to see her again?
I hope I can see her again, someday.
[♪ music fades]
Do you want to know?
Do you want to know where she is now?
What?
STYLE
::cue()
-[Aya] You're lying.
-[Kotegawa] It's crazy.
[Aya] You have to be lying.
That can't be true.
Oh... Mornin'.
Morning.
How was Gunma?
Got any souvenirs for us?
Who comes back from a funeral
with souvenirs, idiot?
You know, Tokiwa was feeling lonely
with you absent for two days.
She wouldn't shut up about you.
Hey, that wasn't all I talked about!
[both laughing]
Hey, Kasuga?
Yeah?
If you're free today,
why don't you come over to my place?
-Sorry.
-Hmm?
I should've told you my parents were out.
No, don't worry about it.
The thing is...
I've finished...
my novel.
What?
Seriously? When?
Last night.
Please read it.
Tokiwa...
Congratulations.
But...
I can't read it right now.
There's something...
I need to tell you.
You see,
when I was in junior high,
I made a contract with someone.
[♪ instrumental music playing]
[Takao] That town,
the town I was born and raised in,
is a depressing town
surrounded by mountains.
In my second year of junior high,
I stole the gym clothes
of the girl I had a crush on.
I didn't mean to, though.
I just...
found it on the classroom floor,
and I took it home with me.
This classmate named Nakamura saw me...
SAEKI
...and I ended up
making a contract with Nakamura.
One day, the two of us
destroyed our classroom.
We snuck into the school at night,
used the calligraphy ink and paint,
and turned the place upside down,
changing the classroom
into a chaotic mess,
like no one had ever seen before.
Then, during swimming class,
I snuck into the girls' changing room,
and I stole the panties
of every girl in my class.
It's not like I wanted them or anything.
All I wanted was...
I wanted to make Nakamura...
I just wanted
to see Nakamura laugh.
But, after all,
I never succeeded
in making her truly laugh.
In the end,
I decided
to leave this world with her.
But...
even that was beyond my reach.
STYLE
::cue()
That's the reason I moved here.
[♪ music fades]
Sorry.
You need to leave.
I have to think about this alone.
Please.
I can't leave.
Why?
You're done with your story, right?
[angrily] What do you want from me?
I don't want anything from you.
I just felt like I should tell you.
Don't you think you're being selfish?
All I asked was for you to read my novel.
Did you just want to get this
off your chest?
-No, it's not like that.
-What is it, then?
I...
I don't want to run from it anymore.
Honestly, I thought I'd keep it to myself.
That it'd be selfish
to make you deal with this.
But...
[♪ somber music playing]
the past won't go away.
I realized
I still can't let go of Nakamura.
It's not about liking her or not.
I can't tell if I want to hold her
or be killed by her.
I just...
I just want to see Nakamura again.
So that I can find a life with you.
Nakamura's whereabouts are in this note.
I got it the other day
from a classmate in Gunma.
After I see Nakamura one more time,
if you'd still forgive me...
then...
I'd like to read your novel.
The answer is no.
I can't let you read this.
This seems so silly now, all of a sudden.
Tokiwa!
-[sobbing, panting]
-Wait!
Stop it!
[Takao grunting] Wait!
[Aya] Let go of me!
I said, let go!
[Takao] I won't let go of you, ever!
[Aya grunts]
[panting]
Then...
can you kiss me?
[♪ gentle music playing]
I'll go with you.
What?
I'll go with you to see Nakamura.
[♪ music fades]
STYLE
::cue()
NAKAMURA IS WITH HER MOTHER NOW,
HELPING OUT AT HER DINER IN TOKAWA, CHIBA.
TOKAWA STATION
[sighs]
Let's go.
Okay.
[♪ melancholy music playing]
GUEST HOUSE CHONAN-SO
[Aya] Excuse me.
Yes?
Is there a diner around here?
Sure, there are a few.
One that's run by a mother and daughter?
Ah. You must be looking
for the Mizukoshi's, then.
Mizukoshi Diner.
It's at the end of this road,
but they close at 3:00 p.m.
[Aya] I see.
Thank you very much.
Ah.
MIZUKOSHI DINER
[♪ music fades]
OPENING HOURS 11:00 A.M. - 3:00 P.M.
4:30 P.M. - 8:00 P.M.
Hey, you've got customers.
[owner] Coming!
Hello there, welcome.
A table for two?
-Yes, please.
-[Shino] Right over here.
-[customer] Thanks for lunch!
-[Shino] Thank you.
You must be busy
without your girl helping out.
-[chuckles] Come again soon.
-Will do.
Hmm?
[chuckles] Please sit.
Is that... her mom?
Have you decided on your order?
I'll have the fried mackerel set meal.
All right.
And you?
I'll have... the same thing.
STYLE
::cue()
Sure. I'll have those out in a bit.
[door slides open dramatically]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[Takao] It smells like...
[Sawa] I'm back.
[Shino] Welcome back.
[Sawa] They only had
small bottles of soy sauce.
[Shino] I see. Thanks for getting these.
-Take this to that table, would you?
-[Sawa] Sure.
Here's the fried mackerel set meal.
I'll be back with another.
Hey!
[♪ music fades]
Nakamura...
Do you remember me?
It's me, Kasuga.
Takao Kasuga.
I came to see you.
[♪ gripping music playing]
TO BE CONTINUED
[♪ closing theme music playing]
ON THE NEXT EPISODE
[narrator] Kasuga and Nakamura
are reunited.
Tokiwa quietly watches over them.
Next, on the final episode,
see the other side of The Flowers of Evil.
Translated by Yuka Kristi