=Wonder Wall=
=Episode 17=
What happened?
What's wrong?
I will get a doctor.
Stay calm.
Doctor!
Relax, relax.
Where's her family?
She only has one family member with her.
We don't know where he went just now.
Get in touch with him right away.
Okay.
Ma'am, tell me,
what are you trying to do?
You want to make a call, right?
♪Work hard and make money♪
♪I want to get rich♪
Wenwen, Wenwen.
What are you saying, Mom?
What's wrong, Mom?
Wenwen, Wenwen.
Don't get worked up. Calm down.
Calm down. Stay calm.
Don't move around,
or the blood will flow back.
Calm down.
What's wrong?
Relax, relax.
Look at her, quickly.
She's really agitated right now.
She's awake?
Lanying!
Lanying, it's me. It's me.
Stay calm, don't get worked up.
You mustn't get worked up.
Wenwen, Wenwen.
Okay, okay, alright.
Don't worry, don't worry.
Wenwen will be fine.
Captain Guo, someone's here to see you.
Bigfoot.
What's wrong, Yitong?
Here's the thing.
My mom and Wenwen
have been kidnapped.
This is the kidnapper's number.
The call came from this number.
This is the video he sent.
This is my mom.
Wenwen is next to her.
Please, help us find them.
The four of us
have been searching all afternoon.
Yu Ming's mom
has been admitted to the hospital.
This is the number.
Call him right now.
You... The police...
Calm down. Calm down.
Tell me,
when were this video
and the photo taken?
They were sent this afternoon.
Dad.
You're here.
Yeah.
Mom.
Wenwen... Wenwen has been found.
She's fine.
Not even a scratch on her.
She's all good.
She's exhausted
after everything tonight,
so I sent her home to rest first.
You can rest easy.
I want to go home.
No, you shouldn't go home.
You need to recover your strength
right now.
And if you go home now,
Wenwen will get very anxious.
Let her be alone
at home for a bit.
Let her process it first.
I want Wenwen.
You shouldn't... You shouldn't go home.
Don't worry, she's fine.
Wenwen... You're lying.
I'm not lying to you.
I'm not.
It's true, Wenwen was found.
Mom.
Wenwen.
Don't get worked up.
Lanying, don't get worked up.
You're lying.
Don't get worked up, Lanying.
Lanying, calm down.
Lanying, stay calm. Stay calm.
The patient must control her emotions.
Look at her blood pressure right now.
See how high it is?
Please step outside for now.
Don't worry, Ming. Let's wait outside.
Give me Wenwen.
Interesting.
In my darkest hour,
so much money just fell from the sky.
I know
it was my brother watching over me
and helping me.
I thought
he really gave me
this huge sum of money
to hold this family together
and to win back Yitong.
My brother was so kind.
I haven't spent
a single cent of this money.
But he made me realize
what true wealth really is.
♪That cup of tea on the table♪
Only the family and loved ones
around you
being safe, sound, and healthy
is what matters most.
Mom being able to recover,
Wenwen and her grandma
coming back safe,
that's far more important than money.
Who is this?
You.
♪Let's wait for the rain to stop♪
Why, in your eyes,
am I like this?
♪If the umbrella's downstairs♪
♪We'll just get♪
♪A little wet♪
♪Let's wait for the rain to stop♪
♪Instead of worrying so much♪
♪Maybe this time♪
♪I'll learn to let go♪
♪The clock has stopped ticking♪
♪The light has started to fade♪
♪The dripping pipes♪
♪Keep the beat of a sleepless night♪
♪I pull out an old shirt♪
♪Its creases make me smile♪
Don't worry, Ming.
They'll all be fine.
♪The world keeps turning all the while♪
♪Let's wait for the rain to stop♪
♪Then we'll be on our way♪
♪If the umbrella's downstairs♪
♪We'll just get♪
♪A little wet♪
♪Let's wait for the rain to stop♪
♪Instead of worrying so much♪
♪Maybe this time♪
Ouyang.
Pang Jiajia just called me.
She and Yitong are truly out of options.
They called the police.
The house is full of cops now.
We might not be able
to keep the money under wraps.
Got it.
How's the check on the entire
compound's surveillance going?
Almost done, just a little bit left.
About 30 percent to go.
What about the ones
outside the compound?
We've finished all the outside ones.
But for now,
we still haven't spotted the suspect.
Assign these tasks.
Okay.
Go on.
Alright.
We've started setting up surveillance.
Try to get some sleep.
The kidnappers could contact us
at any moment.
I'm not sleeping.
Every time I fall asleep,
I keep dreaming.
I keep dreaming of my mom and Wenwen
lying on
a big stainless steel slab.
Both of them were covered
with white cloth.
I'm standing at the door, can't move,
can't get in.
I call Yu Ming, but Yu Ming won't speak.
I...
I'm afraid of having that dream.
I totally understand
what you're going through now.
But the most important thing right now
is to keep your emotions in check.
Okay. I can. I can do it.
Leave the rest to us police.
- Okay?
- Okay.
After you left,
the kidnapper called Yitong.
(Pang Jiajia)
They want 30 million in ransom.
Said to pay it tomorrow.
But all the money we've scraped together
is only about 100,000.
We had no choice but to go see Guo Li.
We told her everything.
About the 60 million,
we still haven't told the police.
You decide for yourselves
whether we tell them.
I understand.
Once everyone comes back safely,
I'll go and confess everything
to the police.
I'll shoulder
all the responsibility myself.
We'll make preparations on two fronts.
After you drop me off later,
go find Chen Zinuo.
Ask Chen Zinuo to tell her mother
that this money is to save lives.
I only need 30 million.
Just give me the 30 million.
The rest is all hers.
If Wenwen
or my mother-in-law
suffers any mishap,
I'll confess everything to the police.
We'll all be finished.
It's already been 24 hours
since they were kidnapped.
We're running out of time.
Now, Xiao,
take a team to Forest Island.
Sweep all the surveillance
within a five-kilometer radius.
Also, Hui,
the convenience stores
near Yu Ming's place,
security booths, all these blind spots,
don't let a single one slip by.
Check them all.
And focus on
investigating license plates
that are deliberately covered
and out-of-town vehicles
and individuals.
Get photos printed ASAP.
Where the vehicle disappeared...
Where did it go?
Do you know?
Songshan District.
At the intersection
of Forest Island Street,
we'll put
heavy surveillance on this area.
At the same time, south Anshun Road
needs increased police presence
for a thorough sweep.
- Yes, sir.
Something this big happened,
and you didn't call the police? Why?
If Yitong hadn't
come to me today,
how long were you planning
to drag this out?
The longer you drag, the worse it gets.
Don't you even understand that?
If something had happened to
her mom and your child,
have you thought about the consequences?
Now, answer me this.
How did you get targeted?
When did they start targeting you?
I haven't even thought about it.
When... I don't know when.
If I had to guess,
they must have thought
we won that 130 million.
Then they just
wanted to take advantage of us.
Take advantage? Is that all?
Yu Ming, you think I don't know
what kind of person you are?
You're the type who's afraid
a falling leaf might
cut your head open.
Something this huge happened,
and you didn't tell me?
Does that make any sense?
And Yitong, you're suspicious too.
You two must be
hiding something from me.
Right here.
Xiao.
We found the info
on the incoming call number.
The original owner's ID was lost once.
Afterwards, this ID was used
to get seven phone cards.
Seven phone cards?
Yes.
Think hard.
Have you two offended anyone recently?
Or had any financial disputes
with anyone?
Or do you yourselves
have any suspects in mind?
Anything at all.
Think hard, try to remember.
Jiang Juan.
Jiang Juan?
After Wenwen and her grandma
were kidnapped,
she vanished as well.
Time to eat, come on.
Eat.
I'll go feed her.
Come on.
Ma'am.
Smells pretty good, huh?
Here, let me feed you.
Come on.
Eat up.
What are you whimpering for?
You want to starve?
Forget about it.
Come on, eat.
My grandma is sick.
Then she certainly needs to eat.
Come on now.
Open up.
Hurry.
Don't test me.
I'm warning you.
What's wrong with you?
Let me check.
She's burning up.
She has a fever.
Go get medicine.
A fever? It can't be that serious.
Just go.
She's a hostage,
not your grandma.
Cut the crap.
Here.
Drink some warm water.
Careful.
Ms. Jiang,
can you face your own child?
If you get arrested,
she'll never see you again.
I know I'm doing the wrong thing.
Honestly, I envy you so much.
Every time I see Wenwen,
it's like seeing my own little girl.
I haven't seen her for so many years.
The last time I saw her,
she had just gotten her hair braided.
Back then,
I braided her hair every day.
A different style each day.
I just have to get the money.
I need to bring her out here.
Her dad did beat me.
I remember
the last time he beat me,
he kicked my spleen until it ruptured.
If I hadn't run away, I would've died.
With my little girl living with him,
there's no way she's had a good life.
Later on,
I did some things.
There's no going back now.
For so many years,
it's been a living hell for me.
No matter what you say, it's useless.
You're a horrible person.
A kidnapper.
Wenwen.
Ms. Jiang,
this is a gift for you.
Put it on.
You'll look like a fairy from heaven.
Grandma says
kids turning twelve face bad luck.
Didn't you say your daughter
is about my age?
I got her a pair of socks
and a charm bracelet.
These things really work.
Wenwen bought
these two.
She usually spends
all her pocket money on snacks.
Guess she's growing up.
She learned to be thoughtful.
My dear daughter,
I can't turn back now.
Zinuo.
How is it?
There are some things
I must tell you face to face.
Your mom isn't the one
who kidnapped them.
After Ming gave her the money,
he got a call from the real kidnapper.
So your mom used this situation
to swindle the money away.
Now, we have no way
to save the hostages.
Your mom's now holding
two lives in her hands.
So you absolutely must
talk to your mom.
Make her give the money back.
Even just 30 million is fine.
We must save those two first.
She can take all the rest.
Once she got the money,
she won't return it.
She can't do it.
Unless we
have something she wants.
What thing?
Zinuo.
Li Jin swindled Yu Ming
out of the money they needed
to save lives.
You were involved in this too,
weren't you?
Lei,
do you even know
what you're doing?
Why are you helping her?
She's doing this
for you.
This money that your dad left behind
is your future security.
How many times
have I said I don't need it?
She keeps saying it's for me.
Has she ever considered my feelings?
I'm just an excuse for her evil.
Think about it carefully.
Who really needs this money?
Is it me,
or is it her?
Zinuo,
you've misunderstood her.
She's changed.
If she had truly changed,
she wouldn't be scheming
to steal
other people's life-saving money.
If because of this money,
Yu Wenwen and Fan Meijuan
end up like Chen Liyang,
end up like your sister,
I'll never
forgive myself for the rest of my life.
Then tell me,
how do you want me to help you?
The thing inside the cuckoo clock,
what exactly is it?
It's a flash drive.
You must have made a backup,
right?
Give it to me.
I don't have a backup.
Buddy.
What time is it?
My phone died.
It's 10:30.
10:30.
You're still delivering goods this late?
Go back to Chen City.
The client there needs it urgently.
Driving at night isn't easy.
For me?
Thank you, thank you.
Take care.
It's a bit hot.
Thanks.
(Unknown Number)
Hello?
Zinuo, it's me.
Lei?
This is my other number.
That phone from before,
Li Jin tampered with it.
Since you know she doesn't trust you,
why are you still helping her?
I'm not helping her.
I'm protecting you.
What's inside the cuckoo clock
can destroy all of us.
It will only bring you trouble.
You absolutely must stay out of this.
You do have a backup,
don't you?
I do have a backup.
But I can't give it to you right now.
I called to tell you
that you must
keep your distance
from this whole thing.
Remember that.
Everyone says it's to protect me.
For my own good.
And what did they do?
She lied to me.
I accept that.
But I won't let her hurt anyone else.
(Nuo)
Return the money to Yu Ming.
That money isn't his.
And it isn't yours either.
That money was left for me
by Chen Liyang.
Consider this me begging you.
I'm begging you, give the money back.
This money is to save lives.
I'm your mother.
We are family.
Why are you always better to outsiders
than you are to me?
Give him the money first.
We can talk about the rest later.
Nuo,
I spent
five years of my life
getting this money.
This money was paid for
by Chen Liyang with her life.
You have no right to touch it.
If you have a shred of humanity left,
give the money back.
My child,
can you even tell what's good
and what's evil?
Yu Ming's family was kidnapped
because of his own greed.
I paid the price
for my own greed.
Shouldn't he?
That's still not for you to judge.
If you don't return the money,
then I'll take
what's inside the cuckoo clock
and hand it to the police.
Do things really have to be
this absolute?
Let's both calm down.
Let's meet face to face.
Her fever still isn't going down.
The medicine isn't working.
This won't do.
We have to go to the hospital.
Are you insane?
That's suicidal.
Go to the hospital?
Might as well just turn ourselves in.
What the hell do you know?
She's weak to begin with,
and her heart is bad.
If you let her die on us,
who are we gonna ask for the money?
Try giving her more medicine.
We really have to hurry this up.
Don't let her drag on until she's dead.
Ma'am, we're from
the Municipal Criminal
Investigation Unit.
Have you seen this person before?
Yeah, I've seen her.
She lives right across the corridor.
There's a man
living here with her.
Always wears a hat when he goes out.
That man's got a bad temper.
Once I even overheard them
arguing about
getting money.
Did you hear them say
what kind of money?
Couldn't make that out clearly.
The soundproofing here in our building
is terrible.
You can hear voices
but can't make out
exactly what they're saying.
Actually,
that guy
used to have a job.
But lately,
I haven't seen him go to work.
He stays inside all day
and never comes out.
When were they talking about money?
Probably...
About a week ago.
Find them.
Keep looking for them.
Captain Guo.
Yitong, Yu Ming, come here.
Let me brief you both.
Right now, we've already alerted
the city's public security system
about your family.
You can rest assured about that.
We'll definitely do
our utmost to find them.
Yu Ming,
as your friend
and as a police officer,
I've done everything I should.
You two
still won't tell me the truth?
The very first time
I came to this villa,
I knew something was off.
Why were the windows sealed?
And the drag marks in the basement?
You two never won the lottery at all.
I know that.
Still, a while back,
your spending habits
had such a huge change.
You think I don't know
what your family's
financial situation is?
And Hong Jinkui.
Hong Jinkui
sold this villa to you, right?
Before he died,
he was in contact
with you most frequently.
Why?
♪Work hard and make money♪
♪I want to get rich♪
Unknown number.
It might be the kidnapper.
It could be the kidnapper calling.
Prepare to trace it.
You have to stall them.
Can you stall them?
I can try.
Hello?
Got the money ready?
Yes.
But we're in the middle of packing it
into cases.
Because the amount is so huge,
it's going to take a long time
to pack it all up.
It'll take quite a while.
But we're going as fast as we can.
We bought eight big suitcases.
And while buying the cases,
we even had to consider the color
to pick and choose.
There's red, blue, black,
green, brown, burgundy...
Which color do you like?
Black. Black is low-key.
Okay.
There's also half-pink, half-white.
Black. I want black ones.
Right now, we've packed four cases.
- It's tiring.
- They've done four.
But we haven't rested.
We'll keep packing the other four cases.
They're probably stalling for time.
Now we gotta keep packing.
Cut the crap.
Tell me,
are you stalling for time with me?
I'll give the location at 1 PM.
If you don't
have the money ready by then,
you can collect their bodies.
I did my best.
Is that alright?
Can we now...?
Check the situation.
Those two are way too cunning.
Put the fake bills at the bottom,
don't let them show.
This whole affair
is going to be exposed sooner or later.
So we need
to figure out a plan first.
Here's what I think.
Between the two of us,
we should try to let only one person
be jailed.
The other person stays out here
to take care of the family.
I've thought about it.
Your personality is too fiery,
and you have no special skills.
In prison,
you'd be easy to bully.
But I'm different.
I'm gentle-natured
and fairly quick-witted.
The main thing is, my Mandarin
isn't very good.
Once I'm in jail,
they won't understand me,
which will cut down on opportunities
for conflict.
That will reduce
my chances of getting bullied.
Are you going to talk to me properly
or not?
Yitong,
all these years,
you've been so good to me.
I've caused you so much grief
and given you so much trouble.
Give me a chance to atone.
As for you,
just pretend you know nothing.
If things go wrong, just expose me.
Yu Ming, you're a good man.
Your...
Your biggest problem is
that you always think of others first.
No matter what, you put others first.
You do that with Wenwen,
and with your brother,
and with your mom.
That's the reason why I've been
staying with you until now.
But right now,
we have to
think about this rationally.
We need to pick the person whose absence
will cause the least damage
to our family.
If I'm jailed, the damage is smaller.
Why?
Because you have to
support two families.
Sun Lanying
and Wenwen.
I can't handle Sun Lanying.
If you're jailed,
Sun Lanying won't be able to take it.
She'll collapse.
And your family will collapse too.
You can do it.
You can take care of my mom.
I'm serious. Listen.
Listen to me.
I can't take care of her.
Sun Lanying and I don't get along.
There's no such thing
as a selfless person in this world.
The reason I'm doing this
is that because I know deep down,
with our personalities and our bond,
the one who stays free
will have it much harder
than the imprisoned one.
The money's packed. Let's head out.
I'll go too.
No, you stay.
Wait here for news.
Ouyang, you're with me.
Okay.
Be careful.
Don't worry, Yitong.
Our people
will be following the whole way.
Okay.
I'm fine. I am.
Dad, I'm heading out.
Take good care of Mom.
♪Work hard and make money♪
Hello?
In half an hour,
get to Chenchunmen Interchange.
The kidnapper called.
Trace it now.
The command center
is already tracking it.
Contact all stations near Chenchunmen.
Notify the SWAT team. Prepare to deploy.
Team One, Team Two,
follow to Chenchunmen Interchange.
Switch to Team Three for tailing.
Team Three, go to
Chenchunmen Interchange and stand by.
Copy that.
The van has arrived
near Chenchunmen Interchange.
Team Three, prepare to take over.
Team One, Team Two,
don't follow too closely.
Be careful not to alert the kidnappers.
Copy.
(Unknown Number)
♪Work hard and make money♪
Hello.
I'm here.
How do I give you the money?
Go to Gaoshi Street.
I'll send you the location.
The kidnapper changed locations.
Gaoshi Street, old town.
Team Three, tail the van.
Copy.
Team One, Team Two,
head to Gaoshi Street and set up now.
Copy.
Got it.
Pull up the Gaoshi Street surveillance.
Okay.
Too many interfering factors
in the old town.
The surveillance cameras
haven't been upgraded.
This whole area
is a blind spot right now.
Li,
contact the local police station.
Notify all units along the route.
We need strict surveillance.
The van has entered the old town.
The old town
has complex road conditions.
Team Three, stay tight.
Understood.
The van has entered Gaoshi Street.
Team One, Team Two, move in.
Copy.
The van has stopped
in the middle section of Gaoshi Street.
Watch the surroundings.
Don't blow your cover.
♪Work hard and make money♪
Hello?
I arrived.
How do I give you the money?
Leave the keys in the van and get out.
Then leave.
Isn't it money
for the people?
Where are they?
Where are my child and my mother-in-law?
Do as I say. Now.
I'll send you a location.
Get out and leave.
Where are they?
Let's get out first.
Yu Ming and his friend
got out of the van.
All units, stay sharp.
Move in as soon as the suspect
gets in the vehicle.
All possible escape routes
for the vehicle
are blocked with roadblocks.
Xiao,
your team follows Yu Ming.
Zhou, your team stands by.
We're tracking the vehicle,
not the people.
Leave them alone.
Track the vehicle, not the people.
Copy.
I...
I think he can see us.
Once I got here,
he called me right away.
So what do we do now?
We wait.
Wait for him to take the money.
The police will catch him.
Ming.
Li Jin asked to
meet me at Du Lei's company.
I'll make her give the money back.
What the hell?
Zinuo wants to help you
get the money back.
Is her mom still here?
If she got the money...
Her mom is still in Luzhou.
After taking your money, she never left.
She's incredibly bold.
She didn't leave?
Why?
She wants to negotiate?
She says she has
dirt on her mom.
Her mom is truly
a terrifying person.
Now, I'm really afraid
she might do something to Zinuo.
You know?
Then should you go check on her?
What about you?
I'll wait. Wait for the police.
Having you here won't change anything.
You're just here to keep me company.
I'll send you
Du Lei's company address.
Okay, I got it.
Be careful.
Take care of yourself, then.
(Your daughter's here.)
Guo Li,
the kidnapper sent me Wenwen's location.
I'm forwarding it to you.
I'm heading there first.
(If I get the money, they stay safe.
Anything happens to me, and they die.)
(Die)
What is Yu Ming doing?
Team One, follow.
Team Two,
cut through the alley on the left.
Get in front of him.
Understood.
(Guo Bigfoot)
♪Work hard and make money♪
Yu Ming, where are you going?
Hey, just now he sent me
a location.
I thought it was
the place where Wenwen was.
When I got there,
I found
a black box.
Inside the black box,
there was
a dead chicken
wearing one of Wenwen's socks.
In the dead chicken's beak
was a note.
I opened it, and it read,
if he can't
get the money smoothly,
he'll kill Wenwen
and my mother-in-law.
I'm driving the van away now
because my van is full of fake bills.
If he finds that out,
Wenwen and my mother-in-law
are dead for sure.
I'm driving off now
to stall him.
He'll contact me again.
When that happens,
you guys grab him fast.
And first, find Wenwen
and my mother-in-law.
You don't teach me how to do my job.
Get back here right now.
Listen...
What happened?
What happened to Yu Ming?
What is it?
It's nothing. Nothing.
Sit back down.
Execute the backup plan. Now.
Understood.
Zhou, head to the east gate.
I sent you the location.
Copy.
He called the cops.
Pack up. We're leaving.
These two can't be left alive.
Why did they have to call the police?
Calling the police leaves no way out.
Ma'am,
you want your life,
and I want the money.
That was the deal, right?
I don't want to hurt you two.
Ma'am,
nobody has ever
treated me as well as you have.
I don't want to hurt you.
Now, he wants to kill.
He wants to kill.
He's going to kill.
What do we do?
What do we do? He's going to kill.
He's going to kill.
I know, Ms. Jiang.
Ms. Jiang, listen,
calm down.
Listen to me.
My old bones don't matter.
I'm begging you,
let Wenwen go.
Please.
No!
I want to stay with you, Grandma!
Silly child,
don't talk!
I'm begging you.
Please, let Wenwen go.
She's my only grandchild.
I know
you're afraid she'll recognize you.
That if she gets out,
she'll give you away.
She won't.
She's not a little kid.
She's a big girl now.
She understands things.
Jiang has had it hard.
You know that, right?
So hard.
She knows you have your reasons.
We all know you have your reasons.
We won't.
You have a child too.
Please, let Wenwen go.
I'm begging you.
I'll repay you in my next life.
I'm begging you, Ms. Jiang.
One day, I'll repay your kindness.
Ms. Jiang, you...
Ms. Jiang.
Untie her. Untie the child.
Untie her.
Ms. Jiang.
You're still a good person.
Thank you.
I owe you this.
- I owe you, Ms. Jiang.
- Grandma.
Ms. Jiang.
This is my daughter's hairpin.
I'll let you have it.
Okay.
And this.
You made it for her.
You said it brings good luck.
Say thank you.
- Thank her now.
- Put it on.
Thank her now.
It's wild outside.
Be careful when you go out.
Okay.
Go now.
Be careful.
Okay, okay.
I'll do everything you say.
Go.
Alright.
That scum, Zhan Chun.
(Next Episode)
(Actress, Ren Suxi)
I'm Ren Suxi.
I invite you to watch Wonder Wall.
Found it.
We found his motorcycle.
Where did he go?
Headed toward Binjia Town.
Wenwen, run!
Grandma!
Back off!
Scumbag.
I see your face.
Don't ask for it, you old fool.
Ma'am!
Don't you have something to give me?
The money and the USB drive are hers.
None of your business.
Sun Leping.
It's been a long time since anyone
called you by that name, hasn't it?
♪The road ahead is still so long
Where have you gone?♪
♪Under the blazing sun
I keep heading north♪
♪To those who pass me by
You don't have to look at me♪
♪Just keep walking your own way
I'll manage on my own♪
♪Is the rain falling hard?♪
♪Is there someone
to hold an umbrella for you?♪
♪The wind has blown
the numbers off the signs♪
♪Where am I supposed to go?♪
♪Can I change my mind?♪
♪How do I go on without you?♪
♪When will this
endless rain finally stop?♪
♪Then I'll wait for you♪
♪Please don't leave me waiting♪
♪Is the rain falling hard?♪
♪Is there someone
to hold an umbrella for you?♪
♪The wind has blown
the numbers off the signs♪
♪Where am I supposed to go?♪
♪Can I change my mind?♪
♪How do I go on without you?♪
♪When will this
endless rain finally stop?♪
♪Then I'll wait for you♪
♪Please don't leave me waiting♪