=Wonder Wall=
=Episode 18=
Found it.
Evidence bag.
Got it.
Go check for any cameras.
These are all old alleys.
No cameras.
Now, we have one.
Captain Guo.
The suspect is not on site.
The phone was left in the trash can.
But there's a camera here.
It should have filmed everything.
Captain Guo.
Yu Ming parked the Jinbei van
by the road.
He's waiting for the kidnapper's call.
Keep a close watch.
Yes.
Get out.
(Match)
Captain Guo.
The matching results are in.
Zhan Chun lost the phone
on Gaoshi Street.
Where is he now?
He went into Jiujing Street.
The fork is easy to spot.
Two roads have cameras.
Rewind, and we'll locate him.
But the roundabout
has four or five turnoffs
and no cameras. Hard to find him.
Found it.
We found his motorcycle.
Where did he go?
Headed toward Binjia Town.
Contact Binjia Town.
Comb every street, one by one.
He entered Binjia Town and headed west.
Now he's in a camera blind spot.
That is an industrial zone.
There are many abandoned factories
and warehouses.
Set up a checkpoint
in the southern area.
Launch a grid search.
We must find him
before he reaches the hostage.
Yes.
Let me tell you about domestic violence.
It's never just once.
If he ever beats you again,
what will you do?
If it really comes down to it,
I'll stay at my relative's place
in Binjia Town.
I can hide in their scrapyard.
Guo Li.
What's wrong, Yitong?
I just remembered something.
Jiang Juan mentioned before
that she has a relative
at a scrapyard in Binjia Town.
This is a key clue.
We'll look into it.
Don't worry, Yitong.
Okay, okay.
Relax, take it easy.
The police will handle it.
They'll find her.
Give me the money.
Or I'll give this
to the police.
You know what's inside.
Du Lei gave you that?
Du Lei is Chen Liyang's eyes.
He watched me go to prison
and watched me get out.
He watched over my apartment,
how many cups of coffee
I drink every day,
what kind of wine I drink
what time I go to sleep,
even who I meet.
It's annoying.
That just means you feel guilty.
Have some decency.
Don't burn all your bridges.
Even if it's a dead end, I'll take it.
Then you'll just have to
walk into prison
and keep saying "reporting in."
I sent you in once.
I can do it again.
Once, twice.
So what?
Even if you wanted my life,
I'd give it to you.
Because you are my daughter.
Now, you have the USB drive.
My life
is your call.
Those years in prison,
every time
family visitation came around,
the night before,
I was too excited to fall asleep.
I was hoping
to see you.
Five years.
You never came to see me.
Not once.
After I got out,
I could only drink, nonstop.
I drink every single day.
Only when I was numb with drink,
in my dreams,
could I see
you smiling at me,
could I see your face clearly.
Nuo,
I'm your mother,
and I only want you to be happy.
Where is the money?
It's in the garage.
Do whatever you want with it.
Today is my birthday.
Would you have a drink with me?
Happy birthday.
Can you go faster, please?
Any faster and we'll be speeding.
Zoom in on this and let me see.
Captain Guo.
This is Chief Xiang
from the Binjia police station.
- Hello, Chief Xiang.
- Captain Guo.
I've reviewed the footage.
The road he took
gets more deserted as it heads west.
Ahead, there are two villages,
but they've been completely demolished.
The only possible hiding place
is a scrapyard.
We call it the "car graveyard" here.
To the right is a forested area.
Go past the forest,
and you will see an old railway.
Captain.
The kidnapper's phone.
Everyone, be quiet.
Pick it up. On speaker.
Listen to me.
I... I saw
that black case you gave me.
I opened it.
You achieved your goal.
I'm really scared.
Trust me, I didn't call the police.
As for me taking the van,
it's because...
Yu Ming!
Now what?
Bigfoot?
How did you get
the kidnapper's phone?
You caught him?
Hang it up!
It'll be fine.
Xiao,
the kidnapper is already contained
in Binjia Town.
Pull your team back now
to assist with the arrest.
Yes.
Everyone into the vehicles.
Back to the command center.
(This folder is empty)
Du lei,
you've crossed the line.
You can stick your nose in some things,
but other things,
you shouldn't meddle with.
Anything that concerns Zinuo,
I have to get involved.
Zinuo dared to come
with an empty USB drive
and deceive me
just because you told her
that you had a backup, right?
You ruined her.
She is your daughter.
You don't deserve to be a mother.
Chen Liyang spared your life back then,
and this is how you treat me?
Mr. Chen spared my life
to take care of Zinuo.
Zinuo.
Don't you have something to give me?
The money and the USB drive are hers.
None of your business.
Sun Leping.
It's been a long time since anyone
called you by that name, hasn't it?
You think that after all these years,
changing your identity
can erase your past?
I can turn myself in,
but you can't get away.
Only when you're dead
can I be completely clean.
Lei.
What do you want?
I spent five years in prison.
I paid my debt a long time ago.
Why are you still pushing me?
So...
So you have to die.
No.
This is murder.
You're killing!
Do you realize what you're doing?
They pushed me to this!
What did I do?
Do you know
what he backed up
means I'll never see you again
for the rest of my life?
Everything I've done
is for you!
Get out of the way. He must die.
You're the murderer.
You...
Nuo,
you're pointing a knife at me.
In your heart,
I always come second to an outsider.
Is that it?
What am I to you, inside your heart?
Everything I did
was for you!
You don't know. You don't understand!
Everything I've done,
I just wanted to go back
to how things were.
I wanted you to come back to me.
You can't go back.
You can't.
Lei!
It's already gotten out of hand.
(2018)
Neither Li Jin nor I can get away.
I can't stop worrying about Zinuo.
I'll take the fall for this.
Li Jin will be out in a few years.
She loses control easily.
After she gets out, if she
treats Zinuo well,
then you serve her.
Whatever you do for me, you do for her.
But if she tries to control
or hurt Zinuo,
take her out.
I won't be able to
watch over Zinuo anymore.
You need to be my eyes.
Leave, now.
Lei.
Only when he's dead
will we have peace.
You're the one who destroys all peace!
You destroy everyone's peace!
You're the devil!
You're a demon!
Nuo.
(Bridgeway Financial)
Zinuo!
How did you discover
this case?
I came for my friend.
After I went in,
I found someone lying on the ground.
I know who the murderer is.
It's Li Jin.
Steady.
Be careful.
Run! Run!
Grandma, I'm scared.
Don't be afraid. Run!
Run out and get someone to save me.
Running again? Get down here.
Grandma!
Don't you...
Wenwen, run!
Jump! Run, Wenwen!
Back off!
Traitor.
Scumbag.
I see your face.
You...
Back off!
Don't ask for it, you old fool.
Ma'am!
Wake up!
You killed her.
So what if I killed her?
You never killed anyone?
Who killed Hu Deshuai?
You know better than I do.
Are you threatening me now?
Who did I do it for?
Who, really?
Who did you do it for?
You did it for money.
You did it for that 30 million.
You were not in it for the money?
Stop acting all righteous!
I did it for my daughter.
Your daughter?
Your daughter is dead.
Let me tell you the truth today,
Jiang Juan.
It took three water pumps
to pull her out.
Half her body was in the mud.
She was all swollen from the water.
Her face was twice its normal size.
Now you get it.
This isn't true.
Where is she?
Tell me where she is.
Give me your phone!
Stop it.
She's in the underworld now!
Now you hear me,
the underworld!
Once you're dead, you'll see her.
Then you can give her
the hairpin and red socks!
Go die. Then, meet her.
This isn't true.
You're lying.
Me, lie to you?
Here, here.
Look. Who is this?
Do you recognize her?
You know her?
You see the round birthmark?
Is this your daughter?
See for yourself.
Give it to me!
There's nothing to give you.
- Give it to me.
- There's nothing.
Listen,
her father didn't care about her.
Three years ago,
she was playing in a pond
and drowned.
Jiang Juan,
sometimes when you act tough
in front of me,
when you go too far,
it's a joke to me.
I just ignored you.
You went too far? Fine.
You've got no hope now.
In this world,
only I can walk with you to the end.
You got that?
Get away.
Old lady,
I'm sorry about this.
You saw my face,
so I have to kill you.
No one else is to blame.
It's Yu Ming's fault.
He didn't give me the money.
He fooled me.
Your daughter's another ungrateful one.
I'll try to make it quick.
So you don't suffer.
You scared me.
Through our investigation, we discovered
that outside the guardhouse
in the middle of the scrapyard,
there's a motorcycle
and a van.
The two vehicles
are highly similar
to the suspect's vehicles.
So I suspect that the hostages
and the suspects
are in that guardhouse.
We have to move fast on this operation.
The kidnapper
hasn't received the ransom.
He could harm the hostages
at any moment.
Yes,
on it.
Captain Guo.
You're back.
Zhou,
take a team and coordinate with SWAT.
Secure the west exit.
Yes.
Xiao,
you back up from the outside.
Yes.
Keep away.
I... I'm family.
You can't go in.
Bigfoot!
Guo Li!
I know, I know.
I won't go in. I won't go in.
Why are you here?
Do you know where you are?
I... Well...
Because the kidnapper
never contacted me.
I'm worried that something might happen
to my family.
Yu Ming,
do you have any idea
how many officers we've deployed
for this operation?
You have messed everything up.
Sorry.
I... I'm just worried...
Enough. Cut it.
Zhou,
take him to the tent in the back.
Keep him out of the way.
Understood.
Stay put.
Let's go.
Trust us.
Okay.
Report to the command center.
Team one is in position
at the guardhouse.
Team two, converge on the guardhouse.
Team one, continue standing by.
Copy.
Captain Guo.
Dispatch says
the suspect, Jiang Juan,
called to turn herself in.
Turned herself in?
Yes.
Report to the command center.
Team two has arrived at the scrapyard,
near the guardhouse.
Awaiting instructions.
Team two, move in.
Quick.
Yes.
Police! Freeze!
Hands on your head!
Secure them.
One hostage is at the scene.
The hostage is injured.
One suspect is dead.
Rescue now! Hurry!
Let's move.
Mom.
Don't worry,
her life is not in danger.
Guo Li, thank goodness you are here.
Excuse me, where's my kid?
Where's Wenwen?
Yu Ming, listen to me.
Jiang Juan said the child
escaped on her own.
‌Rest assured‌,
we are the police, and we will find her.
Take your mother to the hospital now,
okay?
I want to find my daughter
with you.
No,
we have our procedures.
Listen to me.
She is my daughter.
I know her.
I can provide help.
I won't cause you any trouble.
Let him come along.
Absolutely no acting on your own.
Understood?
No, I won't.
Captain Guo,
The suspect is in there.
Okay.
Stay here. Don't move.
I want to make a call.
Hello.
Mom is safe now.
She was only slightly injured.
What about Wenwen?
Wenwen escaped on her own first.
Go find Wenwen! Go find Wenwen!
Yu Ming!
I...
We will go find her.
I will search with the police.
We will find her.
Don't worry.
Now, you go to the hospital
to check on your mom.
You take care of her.
I'll go find Wenwen.
Officer.
Where's my mom?
She's being treated right now.
Where? Where is she?
Inside.
Where? This one?
Yes.
(In Operation)
How long has she been in surgery?
You'll have to ask the doctors.
She'll be fine.
What's wrong?
The search dog lost her scent.
This should be the last place
where it picked up Wenwen's scent.
The last place?
Don't get nervous.
Not the "last" you're thinking of.
It's just that Wenwen's scent
disappears here,
so the dog can't track any further.
How can it be?
How can a scent just disappear?
But I read online that
search dogs can smell
a person who's been missing for 14 days.
Wenwen's only been missing one day!
Could you sniff again?
Many factors could affect
a search dog's performance.
How can I explain it to you?
The tide is going out now.
If it comes in,
the water will be very deep.
What if...
You are talking nonsense.
Don't say that.
The dog can't find her, but we will.
- We must keep searching.
- Yu Ming.
Stay calm.
Remember what you promised me?
You guys search over there,
Yu Ming, come with me.
Wenwen!
Yu Wenwen!
- Yu Wenwen!
- Wenwen!
Wenwen!
Yu Wenwen!
- Wenwen.
Wenwen!
- Wenwen!
Yu Ming!
Slowly, slowly.
Check this.
When you play hide-and-seek
in such a big place,
you need to give me some clues.
Smart as I am, I still can't find you.
Just admit you are bad at it.
Next time,
I'll leave you a marker.
I'll go easy on you, okay?
You know about markers?
What is it?
Dad is a big tree.
Mom is a big umbrella.
Boys on the left, girls on the right.
Get it?
Follow me.
This way.
Dad.
Wenwen.
Mom,
trust me.
Grandma will be fine.
I have a secret with her.
I promised her
that when I earn my first pot of money,
I'll take her to Beijing.
We'll get a fancy haircut
and a photo at Tian'anmen Square.
To get that photo,
she'll definitely live to 99.
Mom,
don't worry.
People of their generation have faith.
You can believe in faith.
I believe in you, not faith.
Your grandma's fine.
When you're feeling better,
come to see me.
♪You said, don't rush♪
♪Take life one day at a time♪
Bye-bye.
♪That cup of tea on the table♪
♪Has sat there cold for two days♪
Wenwen said
she's going to Beijing with my mom,
and get a fancy haircut.
♪Nothing much has happened
Nothing earth-shattering at all♪
Such a good girl.
♪Half the words we meant to say♪
My mom is over 70.
Who would have imagined she'd
come across something so absurd?
♪Let's wait for the rain to stop♪
♪Then we'll be on our way♪
She is blessed with great fortune.
She'll be fine.
♪If the umbrella's downstairs♪
♪We'll just♪
♪Get a little wet♪
♪Let's wait for the rain to stop♪
♪Instead of worrying so much♪
♪Maybe this time♪
♪I'll learn to let go♪
I'm going back to the station now.
When you're done here,
we need to talk.
Come find me yourself.
Careful, take my arm. Easy.
Ms. Guo,
Ms. Jiang helped me.
She's a good person.
Thanks for the tip, Wenwen.
I'll keep it in mind.
Now go on.
Dad,
can I go see
my grandmas first?
Let's do your checkup first.
Ming.
Weren't you looking for Chen Zinuo?
Don't mention it.
I did go look for Zinuo.
You know what I saw?
Du Lei got stabbed.
When I went in, it was all blood.
What about Chen Zinuo?
I don't know.
The police keep telling me to wait
for news.
How can I just wait?
So I followed Du Lei's ambulance
here.
I'll talk to him when he wakes up.
Does everyone who gets involved
with this money all go crazy?
Ming, seriously,
it's a good thing you held on.
That was ten years ago.
Back then, my daughter was still young.
I didn't want her to have a hard life,
so I came to Luzhou alone to find work.
At first,
I worked as a caregiver at the hospital.
They all said I did good work.
Someday, Hu Deshuai found me
and asked me to take care of
his paralyzed father.
The pay was great,
so I took the job.
That's also when I met Zhan Chun.
He drove for Hu Deshuai then.
As time went on,
they teamed up for no good.
That scumbag Hu Deshuai
tricked us, saying
we could invest
our wages with them.
The interest was high,
and it could make money grow.
We thought that he was
such a big shot,
so we believed him.
For over a year,
he didn't pay us wages.
Later, he got into trouble.
(2012)
From our station,
today at approximately 4:37 PM,
a serious collapse occurred
at the Wanjiahui Overpass
in Songshan District, Luzhou City.
Multiple sections
of the bridge deck fractured,
causing several moving vehicles
to plunge from a height.
According to preliminary statistics,
the accident has caused eight deaths
and thirteen serious injuries.
Rescue teams are searching
at full capacity.
Turn off the TV.
For further details,
we'll go to our correspondents
on the scene
for specific updates.
Zhan Chun told me
that when that overpass was being built,
Hu Deshuai was also involved.
When the accident happened,
Hu Deshuai wouldn't let Zhan Chun
drive anymore.
He fired him.
What are you doing here?
- Well...
Hu.
Just a little...
Just a little thing.
About our wages,
would you mind settling them?
Well, you don't have to pay all of it.
Just part of it will be fine.
Because
Ms. Jiang has to give her child
monthly living expenses
and tuition.
So if you could just pay this part...
Didn't I tell you
a few days ago?
Your wages
and the interest
will all go into your accounts.
But the process has to be followed.
The accounting has to be done.
Boss,
but the accounting has been going on
for ages.
Can we do it this way?
Now, we give up
the interest.
You just pay our base wages,
and we'll leave tomorrow.
What's that supposed to mean?
You think I'm going to short you?
No, no.
Get back to your work.
Bother me with this again,
and you'll get nothing.
By then, we both knew
we were never getting that money.
Without money, how could I bring my girl
over here?
I tossed and turned all night.
In the middle of the night,
I heard a noise in the room.
We only wanted to get back
our wages,
but after seeing that,
we wanted way more.
Stop right there!
After we killed Hu Deshuai,
we went back to his place
and found all that money was gone.
Where's the money?
Talk! Where's the money?
Hu Deshuai had seven villas
in Ziyu Garden,
and we believed that the money
must be in one of them.
However,
before we could even start searching,
the police had already found
Hu Deshuai's body.
Zhan Chun and I ran off in a panic.
Later,
after many years,
we thought the heat
had all died down,
so we came back to Luzhou
to keep looking for the money.
As for what happened after that,
you've already asked about it.
Print it out.
Take a look at the statement.
If there are no issues,
put your fingerprint on your name.
No need to read that.
I know how serious
my crime is.
Officer,
may I
make a request?
Go ahead.
I have a daughter.
She's twelve years old.
Her name is Xie Yuyao.
She's with her father,
who's working in Guizhou.
She...
Right here,
there's a large red birthmark.
Can you check for me
whether she...
Whether she's really gone?
I'll remember that.
Thank you.
Thank you all.
(Next Episode)
(Actor, Guo Jingfei)
Hi, I'm Guo Jingfei.
I invite you to watch Wonder Wall.
I don't know
where Chen Zinuo's mom went.
It was my fault.
I shouldn't have let Zinuo
go find her mom alone.
Chen Zinuo's mother.
She appeared
at suspicious times
and locations in these two cases.
And both victims
had frequent contact
with Li Jin.
This is no coincidence.
Mr. Yu,
We brought some local specialties.
Chicken, ducks, fish,
and all kinds of vegetables,
which we grew ourselves.
You're too kind.
Look.
No need to do this for me.
♪The road ahead is still so long
Where have you gone?♪
♪Under the blazing sun
I keep heading north♪
♪To those who pass me by
You don't have to look at me♪
♪Just keep walking your own way
I'll manage on my own♪
♪Is the rain falling hard?♪
♪Is there someone
to hold an umbrella for you?♪
♪The wind has blown
the numbers off the signs♪
♪Where am I supposed to go?♪
♪Can I change my mind?♪
♪How do I go on without you?♪
♪When will this
endless rain finally stop?♪
♪Then I'll wait for you♪
♪Please don't leave me waiting♪
♪Is the rain falling hard?♪
♪Is there someone
to hold an umbrella for you?♪
♪The wind has blown
the numbers off the signs♪
♪Where am I supposed to go?♪
♪Can I change my mind?♪
♪How do I go on without you?♪
♪When will this
endless rain finally stop?♪
♪Then I'll wait for you♪
♪Please don't leave me waiting♪