Are you scared?
No, honey, it's 10,000 times bigger than an earthworm.
My brother put it in.
I?
Okay, I'm just going to put it in, baby, throw it, okay?
One, two, three, the end.
Yeah, nothing much, right?
Is this the end?
Hey, you're good.
So now all that's left to do is wait.
Why are you like this? I must be crazy.
I'm crazy, what should I do?
what?
I think the battery went out?
I'll go
Baby, put some beer on your doorstep
Eoktti, Eoktti.
Thank you for
that you watched.
Zinc, Zinc, Zinc.
Take care of yourself, why are you doing this, Ah-yeon?
Brother.
What are you doing there?
Brother, brother diabetes
Don't hit me!
Brother!
Suyun?
Suyun
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm
sorry, I'm sorry.
Yes, sir.
We are looking at it now and looking at it.
What is this?
We are looking into it now.
I took the photo down.
yes yes what is this
What's strange about this?
They said it wasn't an error and they said the local government filed a complaint so they should replace it right away.
It's not as simple as just taking down the photo.
I guess it was because all the team leaders gathered together this weekend?
There are originals and GPS records for other routes, but this route does not.
So, a photo that was never taken in the first place.
They say it was uploaded.
Didn’t team leader Woo Gyo-sik say he came and went?
uh.
Team leader Woo, he is.
I haven't been receiving any calls since I took sick leave. Has anyone contacted me?
Well, anyway, I don’t even know how this road has changed in the meantime.
Anyone go back here
I have to take a picture.
Updates must be made by evening.
Who wants to go?
I'll go.
Oh, are you okay, PD Han?
You couldn't even rest.
it's okay.
Because it's our team's job.
Still can't contact the school meal team leader?
Oh, but why are you so worried that you took sick leave?
There's an uproar, but I'm not the kind of person who can ride for a while.
Are you going?
Is it that embroidery?
uh.
No, there are other team leaders too.
why?
I haven't been able to contact you since my senior went there.
I need to find out what's going on.
No, anyway, what are you going to do?
You don't even go near the water.
He says he's very interested. Let's live like strangers.
No, we have already become worse than others, so how can we live like others?
Oh wait a minute.
I'll open the trunk for you.
Please give it to me.
yes.
I'll put it in.
hello.
Ah, I got a new one from Team 1.
You know?
Mr. Sejeong.
PD Jang said he was going to see a ghost today?
No no no
When did I do that?
No, the car stopped running just a little while ago.
Thank you for your day off.
Both.
no.
We're on the same team, so of course we should go.
I'm actually looking forward to it, right?
hello.
Ah, hello.
He and the two road cams also picked me up on the way.
Ah, yes.
My name is Song Gyeong-tae.
Oh, I really heard a lot from Manager Lee Jong-won.
Hey, this is my younger brother, producer Song Gyeong-jun.
Ah, hello.
I made an urgent request, but thank you for coming.
Oh, no, no, I was a bit in a hurry.
I need to make money, money.
I will work hard.
Yes, let's get in.
Let's go.
Eat your life, road view ghost
That's all they talk about these days.
It's awesome
Ah now we
I'm going to take pictures there again.
Oh, that's right. I heard that two more people went missing there recently.
We need to come to our senses again
Water ghosts are more dangerous than other ghosts
They say they raise a lot of people.
I'm a better swimmer than a water ghost.
It's a leaked SS scene.
It's different there
It's been there since ancient times
It was famous as a place where you could meet dead people.
The name Salmok
Some say that the scale of production was cheaper.
From what I looked into, I heard it was originally a cemetery?
They built a reservoir without even relocating the place.
There are so many ghosts
I wondered why I didn’t mention this cemetery.
It's just a reservoir created during the Saemaeul Movement.
After hearing some strange stories, come and take it.
How about PD?
PD, do you believe in ghosts?
I only believe in what I see
Didn't everyone forget that we were haunted?
Hey, that must have been a reflection or there was some crazy person there.
It's all here now, so you can check it out for yourself.
This is bigger than I thought
Why are you doing that?
I need to take some out now.
what
What are you talking about?
Sounds stupid?
It's a stone tower.
Didn't you see this?
I couldn't see anything behind me, just now.
Brother really...
The car seems to be fine.
yes.
Take out the carbonation.
You can't touch this.
How hard was it to build it?
Why destroy something that is fine?
Writing is.
The child is following me.
Sorry, old man, we stopped while parking.
I'm glad I came here. I almost died in the water.
People.
thank you
yes?
There's a face I'm looking for
Ssa-eul-ra-go-yo?
Let’s pile it up quickly.
Stack it up?
Let's do it quickly.
Uh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
no!
You have to make a wish first.
Ah, yes, yes, Songwon.
Letter, Songwon.
It's a letter.
Songwon.
I'm in.
Yes.
Let’s finish stacking up and let’s go quickly.
PD, what should I do?
Shall we stack more?
Ah, how far are you going to build it up?
Well, it's almost the same.
It's harsh.
Somehow, there is a smell of the truth.
First of all, the luggage
I'll get off.
Let's film everything and then pack it up and go.
Bro, where do I put this?
here?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Oh, I'm sorry. Are you surprised?
No, I think the road view filming will end soon anyway.
It's rice cake, rice cake rice cake
But PD, do you like fishing?
missing
Isn't it?
Why can't I grow old?
It's pretty full
What is it?
Ah that
I'm going to use this when filming.
A boat?
why?
Oh that that
Anyway, I was going to tell you.
Here's how it happened
Well, I run a horror channel.
A little kitchen feel?
I'll show you
There aren't many items like this one these days, so I'm using it as a double duty.
to?
Are you going to film this today?
I won't disturb you.
I came on the weekend without any extra pay.
What am I? I don’t even answer.
Oh, I don't know, I'm going to take a picture.
Not everyone came to have fun.
I won't worry about what I do as long as the filming is over, so just concentrate.
increasingly.
Is this the way?
Is this a road that needs to be taken anew?
yes
How far is it?
It will be about 3km.
I'll take it in about 2 hours.
Didn't you see the signal?
Oh really
Can't you catch this?
Ah, once you catch this, it keeps happening.
uh?
senior
Were you originally coming today?
no
I also lost a few hours because of this the other day.
I need to move this controller location
Not here
ah
mister!
Are you caught?
Done
I'm connected?
No, why are you suddenly going into the water?
Strangely, I had to go exactly there to get GPS.
Ah, that's still true.
please.
Hey, that's enough.
Do your thing.
Today you are the team leader.
Hey, why haven't I been able to contact you?
Were you worried?
Well, of course.
A person who only knew about work suddenly started diving.
So you came to help.
What happened?
What are you so curious about?
Let’s finish filming first.
I'll explain later.
senior.
great job.
Thank you for your hard work.
Please clean this.
PD.
If the team leader helps with the setup,
How can we
Should we take pictures of the place separately?
uh..
huh!
okay!
yes!
brother
huh
Oh, team leader?
Is this your first time here since you got sick?
Yeah, right?
The atmosphere is a bit...
What happened?
Oh, that's...
Last year, Team Leader Oh’s wife passed away in a car accident.
Things have gotten a little worse since then.
But whatever.
Who doesn't know this?
hmm...
Energy faucet?
Oh, I'm surprised.
Oh, what if someone sees it?
Ah, who is watching?
Are you so stubborn that you want to suddenly start working?
Can I do it?
What I do is fast.
Hey, look at you.
I'm reinstalling one of my fishing rods.
Do you think he'll make a fuss again?
At that time, my brother stayed still.
No, I'm giving attention to something that doesn't matter.
People are really annoying.
CEO, if you press the lag button, photos will be taken automatically at a certain distance.
Please press it before entering.
Oh, you can't stand it?
Press quickly.
Yes, confirmed.
Yes, I'm going.
goodbye.
Come back.
Yes, you can go like this.
Oh, should I come?
President, just a moment.
please go back a little bit
back
Go?
I have something to check.
sorry.
Please leave.
It's really annoying
It's not right
President, is there really no one there?
That's because I said there isn't one.
PD, come and see for yourself.
It would be best for you to get out of there first.
Why do I go out?
Why are you doing that, it's really annoying.
What are you doing?
Is there anyone here?
Huh?
Thanks for watching!
I don't know.
Sous
-titration
Company
Radio
-Canada
Eh?
Huh?
Why why why what
Representative, Representative
older brother!
Why why why what why!
to?
What's going on again?
uh?
Where have you gone?
brother!
ah
Where are you?
Do you know?
Why are you so surprised?
Didn't you just see this?
There is nothing, what are you talking about?
Find me quickly with my brother.
brother!
What did you just do?
What did you just say!
What is this?
this?
Put it down.
why?
Put it down!
What is this
rice bowl
I brought it
I brought this
It's a rice bowl. It's a rice bowl.
It was clearly a woman's head.
Because I saw it wrong
Did you see the prank I just played?
I really saw it
Okay, okay, I really saw it. It really was there.
What are these guys talking about?
You left it.
Does this seem like a magic trick?
yes?
What is it, why?
Oh, that's what shamans do when they pull souls out of the water?
No, why would you hang something like this on a tree?
I can't believe you saw it
and
oh my god
Roadview: Are you saying you saw a ghost?
Why are you smiling now?
Do you think it's a joke?
What time is it now?
sorry.
For now, I will withdraw today
I'll come back down tomorrow and take pictures.
I have to finish it by today.
You know that a lot of people went missing there, right?
Because of that, the local people there are very sensitive.
They said they were pouring oil on a fire and that one o'clock was urgent.
If you say we should just delete this road for the time being, no, it won't be mosaiced or anything.
They just say they don't like it, so they hide it for no reason and then it comes out.
I definitely want to change it by today.
Well then now
Please send the equipment immediately.
Yes, thank you, PD.
Manager, PD Han said something happened?
the equipment now
I decided to send it again
Oh, but won’t the sun set when we arrive?
I'll be waiting nearby and take pictures as soon as the sun rises tomorrow morning.
Did you talk to Manager Lee on the phone?
No, I'm wondering if I've explained the situation here correctly.
Yes, I said it.
Instead, they said they would give me more daily wages for the second day.
No, PD.
They say I can't take money or anything.
Do I really have to take a picture of a road that doesn’t even look like that road?
I'll talk to Manager Lee on the phone.
Dear Representative,
I heard you are close to the manager.
But?
Please help me properly.
This is also the cost of repairing the camera.
The manager said he would take responsibility for everything.
Oh, really.
It has to be uploaded by 8 a.m. tomorrow morning, so it has to be ready by 6 a.m.
The city is just 30 minutes away, so let’s go out now.
Rest well all night
there before that
Do you think I should go again?
There is no controller.
I think you dropped it when the CEO missed it earlier.
Do you remember where it was?
I don't know
I'll come back and pick you up tomorrow when I'm filming.
Oh, let’s leave it here all night?
Where were you?
Just tell me the location.
I'll go and come back.
Anyone who has been there should go
Let's go together
go
Let's go
Let's come and visit us soon
Yes, let's go
I'm getting my equipment and going.
Please tell me where to stay.
Are you coming?
No, the company tells me to go, but I can't not go because of you.
I'm still alive.
The controller is gone and I need to find it.
Then I'll go to Salmeokji.
Gyo-sik senior has come.
Kyosik team leader?
You came there?
He said he would help.
I don't know.
It's a little strange.
People have changed.
He seems quieter than usual and in a worse mood.
Ask me separately later.
Yes, come carefully.
Is this right here?
Ah, but this is what I'm talking about here.
It should be posted here, but why isn’t it there?
what
look?
This is where the Road View ghost was filmed, right?
That's right, that's about it
I guess it worked, right?
where?
excuse me?
Uh, over there.
Did you find it?
no.
Senior like that
Is this something difficult to talk about?
People at the company were also very worried.
I'll tell you later.
if
What happened here?
Did you build a stone tower too?
yes?
They say that if you build a stone tower here, your wish will come true.
Oh yes what
I made a wish, it's just mine
Because my wish came true
What?
Sir.
There's another place around here that looks a bit similar to this one.
Because there is?
Maybe you're confused with that?
IC.
These all look similar.
Then how can you two come back with me?
Are you going now?
I'm going to stay here and watch
Do you know this place?
You're doing well
Wow, it looks like a human head (Watch on www,kisskh,id to support Admin)
ruler
The night of survival has finally arrived.
From now on, using this motion detector
I'm going to try catching a ghost.
How much is it really like in this place?
Will many ghosts be caught?
What, they said there were a lot of ghosts and nothing happened.
Where is everyone?
Please say hello.
Hyejin, if you think about it rationally, you would understand.
There are no such things as ghosts.
now!
uh!
oh my god!
Oh, that's strange.
Even in quite deserted areas, you can still get a signal.
A ghost caught in Road View
I can't even get the Sim type equipment, huh?
AC
Thank you so much
Oh, the ghosts don't come because the PD keeps teasing them.
No, they say there is no such thing as a ghost.
Ah, why doesn’t it work like this today?
Ah, voice actor, what are you doing so quickly?
But I think the teaching team leader is too late.
Thanks for watching.
Oh, this happens, it’s a lot.
Mr. Sejong
If you found the video editing and subtitles helpful, please subscribe and like.
yes?
Is there anything I can insert a memory card into?
Oh, sure.
Is there anything to see?
huh.
Isn't this a Sunteam memory card?
Aren’t you the teacher’s team leader?
Eat well
But where is this?
Team leader, you also built a stone tower?
As for building up...
wait for a sec
hello?
You said the team leader was here, right?
uh
Why are you still together now?
No, he went to look for the controller now.
Han Soo-in
What's wrong with you?
What are the two, bro?
You have to throw this much.
To this extent.
One two three four five six nice.
damage damage damage.
Look carefully. Look carefully.
No, we can't meet.
I'm not the only one who can hear right now, right?
uh
Teaching team leader
He passed away in the hospital last night.
what?
I was surprised too, so I checked it several times.
I think it's true that he passed away
hospital?
why?
you really
Look what the teaching team leader saw.
hello
here
Daejeong, are you okay?
are you okay?
It looks like something flew in from the direction of the reservoir.
Over there?
Didn't the fire just go out?
Apparently something like a stone flew by
No, it's a bird.
huh?
Bird?
uh
How could a stone fly at this hour?
What?
what?
Why is this suddenly turned on alone?
What is that again?
By continuously changing the radio frequency, the ghost picks out what it wants to say.
To put it simply, equipment that allows you to communicate with ghosts?
Hey, the world has gotten so much better.
Do you talk to ghosts?
If you go somewhere, give it a try and give it a listen.
Is that so?
I can't connect
IC
Did everyone hear it?
I told you you just arrived.
today
6 people?
It's never happened like this before
How can I talk about it?
I'm here, just say it.
Are there ghosts here?
me...
Feel free to take a picture of me
Does it come out well?
You can do it.
Okay who are you?
Cucumber, yeah, you dude, you’re out of here
Are you a dead ghost?
Hey, then did you throw a bird at us earlier, you bastard?
Please answer me
This guy scared me
What's wrong with everyone?
Why are you so surprised?
Loddenmunderul
He's dead
Are you okay?
Why are you like that?
Gyo-shik senior said where he was going.
Oh, I'll call you.
First of all, stop everything you are doing and start with number two.
Look for it.
I'm going further in, so go back the way Songjin came and look for her.
all right.
Oh what.
Why are you so surprised?
no
How far do I have to go?
yes?
I have to go further.
No, they said it was close.
Even if I tried, I lost
I have to go further
What are we going to do?
Team leader?
Why is the team leader doing that?
Who is it?
Huh?
Oh, my God.
Oh,
my
God.
Oppa, the ghost box you mentioned earlier is amazing, right?
I got goosebumps
Brother!
are you okay?
Ah, yes.
What did you say?
Oh, that's right.
Bosto Box.
So, it's very strange.
Oh, it's never been like that before.
So.
I guess it really feels like a ghost.
Ah, I wish I could figure out something about this too.
Let’s start by looking for the team leader.
uh?
brother
There's someone over there
Team leader Woo?
Woo, team leader!
What is that grandson doing?
What are you doing there?
brother
That stone tower
Isn’t that the one from earlier during the day?
why is it here
It's probably just similar
no.
That's right.
Team leader Woo?
Where is your representative?
Team leader.
Meanwhile, are you okay?
What's going on?
no.
It's not like that.
Have you seen a ghost?
today.
What is there here?
uh,
Team leader.
Hey, let’s go back first.
Oh, my God.
What's going on?
It's a waste.
get out!
How are you, CEO?
My brother was up in the tree
My brother is on the tree
The fucking foot was on the line!!!
path
Search again
This is the end of the video.
Thank you for your viewing.
Please subscribe to the channel if you
like.
Thank you for your viewing.
Thanks for watching!
Hey, are you there?
Excuse me.
Excuse me
Are you okay?
my
This is my daughter
When you fall into the trap of living, you never thought you would see each other for the rest of your life.
I thought.
Even though it is a temple, here
It's better to leave it alone.
Why did you come here?
Ah, I wanted to ask you about the way.
Who is there in Salmokji?
How do you do that...
Our team leader was building a stone tower?
where are you?
Let's just go
Mr. Lee
where are you?
speak quickly
First, let's report it to the police.
Don't report it
Because I'm going to kill that bastard with my own hands.
We still don't know who did this
So does it make sense to throw down a stone tower when a person is dead?
I can't find my senior right now.
Why can't I find it?
Why can't I find it!
already, already
How do you find a dead person?
asleep?
Dead?
To Ki-tae
I got a call
Senior teacher
Are you kidding?
We were with that bastard all day.
You took road views all day long.
You bastard, you believe that everyone is a ghost now?
Then call me a ghost!
Then why are you killing my brother?
Why are you killing my brother whom you have never seen before?
Falling into the water...
what?
It's like a local spirit that bites you.
The person among us who entered that space was the representative.
outside...
Someone is already dead
Come out and say that my brother is dead!
You can't follow that crazy bastard.
Me first.
this
Where did the bastard go?
Where is this bastard?
sir!
Soviet Army!
this...
You crazy bastard...
This fucking psycho bastard...
hey...
Hey illuwa
Me and this bastard.
Hey you fucking bastard, come here.
Bidi, Bidi.
Wait a minute you idiot.
You can't go.
Hey fucker, come out.
Calm down.
Me?
Why don't you know?
They're luring you towards the skinny side now.
Entice it, yes.
why.
You bastard.
I don't know, man.
I can't sit here.
Oh, my
God.
I have to get out of here.
stuffy
doesn't exist.
I don't have it anyway
let's go
Go straight. This is the way out.
I took a picture, but it came in the wrong place, right?
Let's go out again
Oh, come to your senses again.
Let’s make it!
Just turn it off!
It's not that complicated!
There is a U-turn 20 meters ahead.
Ah, sir...
...
We'll be right
back.
What, this is where I came from earlier?
That was the crossroads just now, right?
Let's turn left this time.
Yoongi Tae?
Hey, what are you doing now?
Han So-hee!
Now look in front!
Hey, you almost got in big trouble!
No, can’t you see it?
uh?
There's a fire in front of me right now!
Hajin!
What are you all doing without coming to your senses?
What the heck...
My car is stuck and I can't move at all.
So we can't get out of here anymore?
All of those grandmothers
We met, right?
You can't get out of there alive.
So how did your daughter come to be here?
If you want something, go for Holtop.
pile up
So I have to pray
I want to build a stone tower and ask for help.
I know how it sounds, but there is no other way.
Why don’t you say Ganggangsullae then?
Yes, then why not walk?
Let's go out together
You won't know if you're in your room. No, you can't even get out by car, so walking will make a difference.
No, if you try to do something, if a forest fire breaks out, you won't be able to come.
What did everyone wish for?
yes?
You tried to make a wish earlier.
I just prayed to make you rich, okay?
I didn't pray
Why? Oh, what is my wish?
Why are you putting it off when it has come true?
Ask me to meet my senior
I wanted to know what happened here.
My senior was like that too.
He said his wish came true.
What do you think it was?
Oh, team leader and wife?
He passed away last year.
No other wishes were granted.
They only listen when calling on the dead.
The old lady said that too.
They say you can’t come out alive.
that's right.
That's why they said they built a stone tower
then
He must have died
He tried to build us a stone tower to look after his daughter.
The problem was that they built that damn stone tower.
So?
Let's tear that down.
For some reason, it was too rough to build it up.
Team leader too
Did you build a stone tower?
As for building up...
Are we going to destroy it again?
I heard he died in the hospital?
So that means you got away with it.
The senior also destroyed it.
Where is that stone tower now?
What we saw is already gone.
Seongbin, where was the stone tower built by Gyo-sik?
No way.
what?
no.
If you take it for no reason and spill it again.
Then it's just us who become X again.
Then stay here.
I'll go.
Don't miss out!
stop!
What if we fight among ourselves?
Do you have anything to drink?
It's in the car.
I'll get it.
You can't go alone.
Let's go together.
Oppa fact
I just lied.
I wish too
I prayed.
That's why everyone died.
I'm going to blow away ghosts.
Hyejeong, you can go out.
Are you going?
you
If you go alone again and get possessed.
Still, I have to do it somehow.
What's the point if I ask you to come with me at least once?
What about the two people?
I have to throw it away
That's how we live
what does that mean
you are good
Think about it
Who first brought us here?
It was Han Soo-in.
Right now, a PD is saying that he is a ghost...
Whether it's a ghost or possessed, that thing
This is not the Hansuin we know.
Who stopped us when we tried to withdraw because of the cameras?
It was Han Soo-in.
That's boss...
So how can you believe that?
Did I see you talking on the phone?
I need to find the school leader.
It was Han Soo-in who got us scattered.
It was Han Soo-in who discovered the CEO’s body first.
And now look at it
Keep talking about stone towers
They're pulling us in
no
Let's just wait until the sun rises
Sejeong, look at the time now
It’s been 1:30 since a while ago
Time doesn't pass
I have to go out
then
Gitan PD...
You'll notice.
Let’s go out, Sejeong.
It will be dangerous.
That means we're going together.
Sejeong, take a picture of the navigation again.
it's okay!
I'm on my way
If you leave, they'll call the police and come straight to the living quarters.
Then we can save both of them.
Be careful, be careful.
I don't
know.
Bowl!
I came out, I came out
brother
I lived, I lived
Are you okay?
Soohyun, calm down.
No, where are you going?
no, please say something
What is this person
first
Let's go back
I found it.
Suin.
Anyway, I need to hurry as quickly as possible now.
I also want to hurry as much as possible.
Do you have a jump ship?
Jump ship...
ah!
Yes there is!
Jump ship!
wait a minute!
Let me ask you something.
I'll be there as soon as the car starts, so don't worry too much.
thank you
But when did you come?
Today.
today.
How many people are here?
ah..
Six people?
What is it?
Why are you here?
caught.
What is this? It’s a Sejong City pad. There’s memory here.
What kind of memory do you have?
Why is the road view taken by 3 vehicles?
There's a boat, but I don't think it's here.
Isn't this where we are now?
Is it really over there?
Where are you, Sejeong?
Why do I keep coming back here?
Don't do that.
Where is the assessment room?
Assessment room!
What's there?
Sejeong, it’s okay, we’re here, so get out of there.
Sejeong
are you okay
This way Mr. Sejeong.
No
I'll chase you back
Chased
Oh, my God.
Now this is the only way
Let's do it.
We'll be right back.
Don't look down.
Just look ahead.
thank you.
You just came to the stars.
How did you know Hotz was here?
Is it Ki-tae?
Was it about that time?
The place where I died.
Yong-tae.
Sunbae?
Yeah, over there.
5 minutes?
No, 10 minutes.
I think it was a good 10 minutes.
How I was struggling alone.
I got a call early that morning.
My office is in charge
It has been turned into a pasture land.
however
Originally in charge of grazing land
It was you.
You changed it, right?
sorry.
I didn't know it would happen like that
lie
you
You've been here
But I haven’t even started filming.
I ran away
Is that why you sent me?
I am
It would have ended if I died, but even now
It's not too late.
Ah, let’s call Gi-tae too.
Just like you've been doing
Let's take him
Seniors don’t say things like that.
Don't pretend to be a senior
Come
Who?
peace of mind
Trina!
I don't know.
Thank you
for
watching.
To be continued...
I don't know.
We'll be right
back.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my
God.
I don't know.
Oh, my God.
Thank you.
Oh,
my
God.
I don't
know.
I don't know.
Subina!
Soyoon, it’s okay.
Oh, I'm here.
Oh, sit down, sit down.
you.
are you okay?
yes
But what
For work?
The team leader
They said the body was in the flesh.
to?
that day
After being admitted to the hospital, they contacted us.
They said they came.
Then, Team Leader Woo gets angry.
Are you saying you couldn't do it?
It means he didn't come out alive.
Anyway, I thought the producer who mentioned this should know, so I called him.
No contact after payment?
You know
why?
What were you doing here?
I just got to work and wanted to get some coffee.
No, why did you come out already?
Why don't you rest some more?
Since I was home alone, I kept thinking about it more.
What's going on?
no
Would you like one too?
however...
What if the teaching team leader was trying to destroy the stone tower?
Why did he die?
well.
I don't know.
Now let's just forget everything.
I shouldn't have gone in the first place.
Swea
Thank you.
I don't know.
Don't believe anything.
Never.
To be
continued...
We'll be right back.
Thank you for watching.
I don't know.
you're a trouble and a threat
but a beautiful addiction
you're a meaningful regret
this is all a science
fiction my heart skips beats i need a
doctor my blood i'm
scared
I feel stalker, but do
it all over again.
breath makes fun there's
a tension in the air can't you
see i'm suffocating so choke me i
Your neglect feels so rewarding
I misbehave so you can scold me
I crave attention with each step
Infatuation makes me feisty
Falling for the
touch
So let me dive into that love in your
devil eyes