This series is crafted for the purpose of entertainment.
All characters, behaviours, settings, and events depicted in this drama are entirely fictitious.
They are not designed to allude to any particular entity, occupation, or group of people.
Viewer discretion is advised.
[North Star Entertainment]
[IQIYI]
[Present]
♫Never met anyone who could make me understand this word♫
♫But when I met you, my heart started beating fast♫
♫You’re the only one in my heart who could make me feel this way♫
♫This long-awaitied moment is now over♫
♫From now on, my heart and soul will be yours for the rest of my life♫
♫Always have each other, never let go♫
♫Trust in me ‘cause I’ll be by your side♫
♫Hold my hand, Baby♫
[Desires in the Wind]
[Previously]
Does Wind have a girlfriend or anyone she likes yet? If so, I’ll back off.
Traitors! I’ll have you all executed!
Last night, I just got drunk and fell asleep…
and didn’t do anything weird, did I?
You fell asleep right away.
Don't you go sweet talking like this to anyone.
They might misunderstand and get the wrong idea.
Do you really not know who it is that Wind likes?
The person Wind likes is you.
If you don’t believe me, just go ask Wind yourself.
Everything will be over soon.
And I’ll take you back to Madelin myself.
Do you need anything?
Ask Bua too. Does she need anything?
She’ll give me an earful if I forget to buy it for her. That rascal.
Just call me if you need anything.
Okay, sure.
Bua will take you out today.
I can’t go with you.
I have to look after the house for Uncle Boonsong.
Mhm.
What are you writing?
Isn’t this the Madelin language?
If you ever see this message, run away immediately.
I have a boat ready at the back of the bay.
You want me to run? What about you?
I’ll be right after.
I won’t let you go alone.
Why mention this all of a sudden?
It’s just in case.
Hey, just want to let you know I caught lots of fish last night.
Get ready for a feast, honey.
What do you want?
I don’t have anything valuable on me.
Shut up. Take me to your boat.
Move!
Take me to the princess and I’ll spare your life.
I’m just an old fisherman.
I have no idea what princess you’re looking for–
If I dump your body in the sea, I doubt anyone would find it.
See you on the island.
I already got someone to take me there.
Geez, Miss Phat.
I still haven’t caught much.
Why do we have to go back now?
I’m not feeling quite well.
Oh, you’re not feeling well?
How are you feeling now?
A bit exhausted from the sun.
I’ll get you some pills then.
Hurry up! Hurry up!
Move!
Lead the way.
Show us the way, you old coot!
Where is she?
Hang on.
Hurry up.
You guys get ready.
Split up and seach!
Hey, found anyone?
No, not a soul here.
Where has everyone gone?
Are you f***ing with me?
No…No, sir.
There. That’s Vayo–the girl you’re looking for.
Go get her and the princess! Go!
Quick!
Go, go , go!
Comb the place!
Split up! Now!
Over there. That way. There too!
If you ever see this message, run away immediately.
I have a boat ready at the back of the bay.
Found them?
No, Boss.
It’s a trap!
Shit, the cops! Run! Take cover!
Turn yourself in!
F***ing bitch! Just you wait! Cover me, quick!
Miss Blew!
Miss Fai! How did you get here?
Lom sent me to get you. We have to go now.
What’s going on? Where’s Miss Vayo?
Don’t worry about her. We have to take you to a safer place.
They’ll be coming this way soon.
But isn’t Miss Vayo in danger right now? We have to help her.
Please trust my sister. Let’s get on a boat.
It’s for your own safety. We have to get out of here as fast as we can.
Let’s go!
Hurry up, Miss Blew!
She’s over there!
Find a boat and go after them! Go!
There! Go faster!
They’re here.
Miss Blew!
F*** it!
Uncle!
Hey, go closer!
Lom!
Are you all right, Miss Blew?
Look out, Vayo!
Lom!
Miss Blew!
She’s wearing a ballistic vest.
Lom.
Miss Vayo, wake up.
Lom!
Miss Vayo.
Miss Vayo, Miss Vayo.
Lom!
Miss Vayo.
Don’t put yourself in danger like that,
or conceal anything from me ever again.
If anything happens to you, I’d blame myself for the rest of my life.
I’m all right.
[Boonwech Hospital]
Hello, Uncle Wathit.
Are you all right, Your Highness?
I’m fine. Are Uncle Boonsong and everyone on the island all right?
Yes, Your Highness.
How is Lom, Your Highness?
The doctor said she’s safe now. Nothing to worry about.
Then, would you kindly grant me a private audience with you, Your Highness?
I’ll look after Lom for you.
Please, Your Highness.
I must apologize for causing your daughter to be in great danger.
It’s not your fault, Your Highness.
It’s those traitors who are to be blamed.
As for those attackers, they’re all taken care of, Your Highness.
But I’m afraid…
there might still be more of them.
So, I’d like you to be more cautious, Your Highness.
I’m well aware of the situation.
But I’m afraid those traitors will never let me return to Madelin alive.
Please don’t worry, Your Highness.
Fah will soon be able to contact your people in Madelin.
I awfully hope our plan will succeed before my imposter will conclude her visit and return to Madelin.
I’m going to request for the list of individuals who are entering Thailand.
Should any of them are from Madelin, I will inform you immediately, Your Highness.
I want it to be over as soon as possible.
I don’t want Miss Vayo to risk her life for me any further.
Aww, looking for your girl first thing when you’re awake, huh?
Are you disappointed to see your little sister instead?
Where’s Miss Blew?
Outside, talking to Uncle Thit.
Dad’s here?
Yeah. But he’ll probably leave soon. He said he has a lot to take care of.
How long do I have to stay here?
No idea. But isn't it better to stay longer?
So that you can act all clingy to Miss Blew.
Watch it, give her some respect.
Aww, acting all protective, huh, Lieutenant?
There she is.
Miss Vayo, how are you feeling?
I’m good now. Thank you for saving me, Miss Blew.
I was so scared when you got shot. Please don’t risk yourself like that again.
Oh, Nam is here.
Are you all right? I was shocked when I heard it.
I’m okay, Sis. Not a big deal at all.
Not a big deal, my foot! You guys almost got yourself killed!
And you even hid it from me and Din.
Would you let me do it if I told you so?
Lom!
What is this about?
I want to know too.
Well, Dad and I set up a plan to lure those thugs out.
I could sense I was being followed for quite a while back.
We believe they’d soon find out about the island and come after us.
So, we came up with a plan to get them.
Your Stir-fried Squid with Basil, Miss.
Your green tea is here, Young Master.
Looks like you’re being followed.
Yeah, for a while now.
Tell our men to find out who they are.
And tell Uncle Boon not to leave the island during this time. Not until I say anything.
So, I had someone look into them.
Yes, Uncle Yod?
It’s as you thought, Young Master.
They’re not from around here.
They have a picture of Miss Lom and keep asking every villager if they’ve seen her.
They’ve discovered our track.
It won’t be long until they’ll find the island.
Definitely the hitmen from Madelin.
They’ve found us faster than I thought.
What are you going to do then?
Do you want to move somewhere else?
No, I’ll come up with a plan to trap them.
Can you contact Dad for me?
Anyway, when are you leaving?
Tomorrow morning, I guess.
That’s your coffee. I ordered it for you.
Thanks, dear.
Drink something first, to freshen up.
Yeah, it’s so hot today.
How is it?
Did they put galangal in there too?
What galangal? Not a drop of sugar here–so strong I could stay up all night!
Yes, Boss. I think I’ve found him.
What a foul luck, he’s barking up the wrong tree. Wait till Young Master gets him.
Yes, I’ll keep an eye on him.
They’ve followed us here like you said, Uncle Thit.
What now?
I’ll send some men to standby on the island.
Those thugs will definitely show up there tomorrow.
I’ll go help Lom there too.
Take care of yourself too, Fai.
Can you put my team on the line?
Hang on.
Yes, sir.
Hey, I caught lots of fish last night.
Get ready for a feast, honey.
Thank you, Uncle. Please be careful too.
They’re coming. Let’s stick to our plan.
What about Miss Blew?
I already told Bua to keep watch.
If Miss Blew hears the gunshot, she’ll probably run back to the cottage.
Don’t worry, I already wrote a secret sign for her to run away.
Please make sure you take her to the boat I’ve prepared.
Just leave the rest to me.
Okay, don’t worry. But please be careful.
This is something serious.
Shouldn’t any of you at least tell me about it?
Fai?
It’s not like I didn’t want to tell you.
But it was quite a last-minute decision.
I was the one who came up with the idea.
Please don’t blame her.
I told her not to tell anyone.
My apologies, Miss Nam.
It’s not your fault, Miss Blew.
This is a matter of life and death, don’t you think you should at least let me know?
I think there’s no use finding who’s at fault right now.
Aren’t we lucky enough that everyone is safe?
Yes, so lucky, right?
Absolutely.
We’re good now. Safe and sound.
You brat.
So, how are you feeling? Better?
I’m good.
Were you really going to keep quiet about it?
She said ‘don’t tell anyone’.
Please drink some water.
Okay, Din.
See you later.
Din and Boss Rose are at the airport now.
They’ll probably arrive here late at night.
They’ll come visit you tomorrow.
What’s with all the fuss?
It’s nothing serious.
I’ll be out of here soon.
Be nice, Lom. They care about you.
It’s been quite a day, isn’t it?
Let’s go back and get some rest.
Lom needs to rest too.
You and Lada can stay at my place.
I already told them to prepare a room for you.
What about you, Miss Blew?
I think I’m going to stay here with Miss Vayo.
Why don’t you go back and get some rest first?
There are cops guarding this room and keeping watch here anyway.
She risked her life for me.
If there’s anything I can do to repay her, I’m willing to do it.
Please go home and get some rest first, Miss Blew.
You’ll be more comfortable there.
Don’t worry about me.
Are you declining my offer to stay and trying to get rid of me?
No, it’s not like that.
I want you to stay.
I’m just afraid you might feel uncomfortable.
It doesn’t matter. I’ll never leave you.
All right then. That’s settled.
Come, let’s go home.
We’re leaving, Sis.
Get lots of rest.
Please get well soon.
Thank you.
Get well soon.
Thanks.
Babe.
Yes?
About Miss Blew and Lom, do you also think the same as I do?
What are you thinking?
Well, something between them has changed.
The way they look at each other is like when you look at someone you love.
You probably imagined it.
Lom should know best what is what.
Haven’t you heard of a saying–‘nothing is impossible’?
What do you mean?
It’s better if you hear it from her yourself.
The lift is here.
Oh, come on.
What have you got?
Nothing.
Spit it out right now.
Give me 500 first.
- Fai, tell me now.
- Really, you two.
1,000 if you drag it longer.
What did you say?
Those you sent to kill Blew are all dead?
All shot dead by the police.
It’s definitely that cop and her father’s doing.
Now what? We have to go back to Madelin soon.
If that annoying princess is still alive, all of our efforts would be in vain.
The nerve to ask me that.
If you hadn’t hired those muppets and just taken care of this matter yourself,
she would have been dead long ago!
It’s you who must be responsible for this!
Can’t sleep?
Why are you still awake?
I already slept a lot today. Don’t need any of it now.
But you’re sick. You should sleep a lot so that you’ll recover soon.
Why are you looking at me?
I’m just glad.
I’m glad you’re here.
I need to get some sleep.
Let’s talk tomorrow.
I’ll never forget what you’ve kindly given me.
I owe you my life, Miss blew.
I don’t want anything in return for helping you.
Get some sleep, Miss Vayo.
I can’t. How can I sleep when my life savior is having a hard time sleeping on a sofa?
I’m good here. I even slept on a fruit truck before, remember?
I still don’t feel good about it.
What should I do then, to make you sleep?
Morn–
–ning.
- What’s wrong?
Lom’s sleeping.
Let’s not wake her up.
Why don’t we come back later?
Let’s go. Come on.
Hold on, shouldn’t we wake her up?
No, leave her.
Let’s go. Come on.
Let’s go, Sis.
Is it the princess or Lom who forgot where her bed is?
Geez, Fai. What?
Just get out first.
Listen, why is the princess sleeping on that bed with Lom?
Yeah, isn’t that brat afraid she’ll get her head chopped off?
I don’t get it.
Maybe I should go wake her up.
Calm down, Sis! Easy there.
There are some things you don't need to understand.
Fai, that’s the princess of Madelin we’re talking about.
Look, if you don’t say it, and I don’t say it–then who’d know?
Even the nurses don’t know who Miss Blew is.
But I don’t want Lom to regret it later.
Leave that for the future to decide.
For now, let’s go ask the doctor how long Lom has to stay here.
Come on. Let’s go.
But that’s the princess! I’m worried for Lom.
Yeah, so what?
Your food and medicine are ready.
My heart skipped a beat there.
Your food and medicine are here.
Sorry for interrupting.
Please excuse me.
Let me help you with it.
I’m sorry.
It’s okay. I can do it.
But I want to. Just think of me as Phatpha then.
We’re not on an island anymore. There’s no more Wind and Phatpha.
I miss those times together.
Me too.
Hello, children. Let’s learn some English today.
This is called ‘Laughing’.
Everything will be over soon.
When that time comes, I’ll be the one to take you back to Madelin myself.
Let’s eat, Wind, so you can take the medicine.
Want some more?
It’s delicious.
Then, eat up.
Have some more.
You got something on your face.
Good morn–
Lom. Miss Blew. Are you two all right?
Miss Vayo and I are fine.
I’d better leave then so that you siblings can talk.
Does anyone want to feed her for me?
I do!
No need. I can do it myself.
But I want to do it.
She’s all yours then, Miss Fai.
No problem.
Aww, don’t look so sad.
Here, let me do the honour.
It’s just plain rice.
Open your mouth.
Good girl.
It’s horrible.
Not as sweet as those bites you took earlier, huh?
I’d rather help myself.
So, you can use your hands now?
Come, Lil Sis.
What?
Let me feed you.
It’s okay. I’m good.
Come on.
No, I’m good here.
- No.
- Come on. Be a good boy.
No good boy.
- Come on, good boy. Eat it.
- No.
[Vayo]: We’re not on an island anymore. There’s no more Wind and Phatpha.
[Blew]: I miss those times together.
[Vayo]: Me too.
Miss Blew.
Have you just arrived, Miss Lada, Miss Rose?
Yes, Lada and I went to get some snacks first.
Miss Din and Miss Nam are talking to Lom inside.
Then, let the siblings have some alone time together.
Looks like something is bothering your mind, Miss Blew.
Lada and I are always here if you need someone to talk to.
We’re more than happy to help.
Don’t worry if it’s something private. Your secret will be safe with us.
We promise we’ll keep our lips sealed.
In your opinion, what do you think love is?
Love, for me, is staying by each other’s side–complimenting each other,
protecting and caring for each other–
and be each other’s happiness on a simply ordinary day.
For me, that person is Din.
As for me, a good love is something that makes you love yourself.
I used to think I could live alone and be on my own.
But after I met Nam, I’ve realised that we don’t always need to be strong or good at everything.
If there are times when I want to cry or don’t want to act strong,
Nam will always be there to support me.
What about you, Miss Blew?
I don’t know.
I’ve never been in love before.
The only love I’ve experienced is one that I have for my people in Madelin.
All this time, I’ve only focused on my duty as a princess.
So, I have no idea how it feels when you’re in love.
Please don’t worry. When love comes to you, you’ll just know it.
Excuse me, are you Miss Fah?
Hello. Have a seat, please.
I’m Sebastian, Prince Karel’s friend.
I heard Princess Blew has sent you.
I’m Fah, a reporter from Thailand.
The princess wants me to hand deliver a confidential letter to the prince.
How should I trust you?
Is this enough for a proof?
Hello, Sebastian. It’s Princess Blew here.
Fah is our person, and I need you to trust everything that she has to say.
I have a favour to ask you.
Please contact Karel secretly.
Thank you very much.
The prince is on his way to France.
Really?
I’ll let you know when he arrives.
Thank you so much.
I’ll report this back to Thailand.
The princess will be so happy to hear it.
I’d appreciate it if you'd only keep this to yourself.
Is it far?
Just cross this mountain and we’ll reach the border of Thailand.
I didn’t expect you to come by yourself, sir.
If it weren’t because of those muppets, I wouldn’t have had to be here myself.
The weapons I’ve asked you to prepare, have you got all of them?
Yes, sir.
Dad.
How are you feeling?
Much better now.
The doctor will let know when to be discharged.
Where’s the princess?
In a shower.
What’s the matter, Dad?
Those thugs we executed on the island are all Thai.
They were probably hired.
I already have my team look into it if there are any more of them.
That’s why I want to–
Have you ever wondered why they were so quick to track down Miss Blew and my whereabouts?
What do you mean?
Hold on.
Nothing. Thank you.
It’s me. Just hide in here first. I’ll take care of the rest.
Chief!
Don’t worry about me.
He went that way.
Go after him!
Quick!
Go!
It’s all clear.
How did the cops know I’ll be here?
No idea.
But right now, you have to get out of here before Wathit will send his men to secure all the exits.
Let me make this clear.
If I don’t make it out of here, you won’t either.
Have you ever wondered why they were so quick to track down Miss Blew and my whereabouts?
What do you mean?
Is Chief Santi on your team too, Dad?
Are you saying Santi is working with them?
We can’t trust anyone right now.
The traitors have some of their men disguised among us cops.
I got summoned to the hotel immediately.
Take care of the princess for me.
No one told me anything.
Did Chief tell you to go?
Nothing. I’m hanging up.
It’s not that I don’t trust Dad, Din.
But it’s those around him–whether the cops or his men–I don’t trust any of them.
We got ambushed, sir!
They’ve followed us here like you said, Uncle Thit.
I’ll send my team to standby on the island.
Those thugs will definitely show up there tomorrow.
Can you put my team on the line?
Hang on.
Yes, sir.
Just as I thought, it’s really you, Chief. You only have two choices.
Help us or walk straight to jail.
Nam, is everything okay?
Lucky we’ve moved Miss Blew out in time.
Did they catch the suspect?
No, he got away.
But Uncle Thit already has his men check the security footage from every road leaving Surat Thani.
Nothing. Thank you.
Just a moment, Your Highness.
The car is coming to take you to the safehouse in Khao Yai.
Thank you.
Here, Fai packed these clothes for you.
I’ll keep you posted on any update.
That’s your car.
This one?
Yes, Your Highness–to avoid getting attention from the suspects.
A rescue wagon, huh?
At least, there’s no dead body in there.
Does that mean there was earlier?
I’m not sure.
Let’s hurry. Please, Your Highness.
Let's go.
We’re here.
Can’t believe there’s a house hidden deep in the forest.
We have no phone signal here. If there’s anything, the staff at the resort will light the SOS flare to let us know immediately.
Let’s go in.
Any news about that cop?
We’re working on it but General Wathit is watching our every move.
It’ll probably take a while.
I don’t want to risk it.
It’s double the amount you got last time.
Just give me Vayo’s whereabouts.
You have three days.
I’ll be in touch.
Is it okay?
Of course, no problem.
Then, please get some rest.
I’ll go fix something for you to eat. I’ll let you know when it’s done.
Miss Vayo.
Yes?
I have a question.
Okay.
Promise me first that you won’t lie.
Okay, I promise.
Bua told me that the woman you like is me.
Well…
But I’ll never believe it until I’d hear it from you.
Why are you asking me all of a sudden?
How do you feel about me?
I…
If you think my question is inappropriate, please forget it.
That’s not what I think, Miss Blew.
It’s because I don’t just ‘like’ you.
What do you mean?
It might seem too soon for me to say it since we just got to know each other.
But I have absolutely no doubt about how I feel.
And how do you feel?
Please forgive me for not knowing my own place.
All this time, I keep telling myself how I don’t deserve to be with you.
But whenever you’re near, I just can’t help falling deeper and deeper.
I love you, Miss Blew.
How many loves have you had before?
Yes?
You have dated many girls in the past.
All these situations might have brought us to get close to each other.
So, I just want you to be sure…
whether this is love…or just a crush.
I am sure.
I am sure that this is love.
I genuinely appreciate how you feel about me.
But I’m afraid I can’t return the feelings.
Knowing what I just said didn’t make you feel upset or disdain, I’m already content enough.
To me, you’ll always be my last love–
whether it’ll come true or not.
Are we going back to Madelin after we finish here?
Not yet. We’ll go back to Thailand to get rid of the real princess.
Hasn’t Henri already taken care of that? Why do we have to go?
I don’t trust him.
He has no resentment towards the royal family.
If he changes his mind to be on the princess’s side, my plan to take revenge will just go down the drain.
What grudges are you holding against the royal family?
It’s none of your business.
Just do your best as a fake princess.
[Next Episode]
Dad will lure Henri here and arrest all of them.
Miss Vayo!
Is Miss Blew okay?
They’ve taken Miss Blew.
- Uncle Thit and his team are–
- I’ll go help her.
You and Karel will come to Thailand, Father?
We should be able to get some family time together before you’ll come back to take your throne as the Queen.
This is not what we’ve planned, Grace.
What if my father and King Arther already find out?
Wouldn’t we all get a death sentence?
You look exactly like me.
♫ I wonder which star it is that guided me to meet you ♫
♫Or is it destiny that has brought us together♫
♫You’re like the wind, carrying me to the sky♫
♫No matter how high, I won’t be afraid♫
♫ Only you is enough, I don’t need anything else ♫
♫ust us together is enough, you’re the meaning in my life♫
♫Every day from now, please stay by my side♫
[Desires in the Wind]
♫and we’ll always have each other♫
[North Star Entertainment]