"The Edge of Horizon"
(Episode 1)
[1902]
Thank you, Phob.
(In unison) Let's go.
Go straight.
[1914]
Definite rules for
spacing are not successful,
it is a matter of a draftsman's judgement
and sense of design.
I'd like to present cotton
rose to you, Your Highness.
Sure, you can.
I should tuck it behind your ear.
- No!
- Why not?
It doesn't suit me, it suits you.
It looks better on you.
Come on.
So adorable.
- I don't think so.
- Of course, it is.
Stop touching it already. Stop, okay?
Stop fidgeting already.
Stay still like this.
- I can't take it out?
- No, you can't. Just keep it like that.
[Varakulvatin Palace]
Hey! All of you!
Stop running around like monkeys!
He will have gifts for eveyone.
Euam, well…
why are they giving us gifts?
It's not even Songkran.
Well, Prince Vasin just got promoted
so they're kind enough
to give something to us.
We're so lucky
to have kind masters like them.
Sathu.
What are you waiting for? Come on.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Nual, where is your son?
Call him for me.
I have something for him.
Phob is hanging out with
Prince Tinnakorn for sure.
When you see Prince Tinnakorn,
you will see Phob there.
Just like me, waiting to
serve you, Your Highness.
Stop it.
Why don't you call him for me?
Yes, Your Highness.
- Watch out!
- I'm okay.
Please be careful, Your Highness.
I think I should get it for you.
Why are you yelling?
Be careful. There are many flowers,
why do you want that one?
I like this one.
Watch out!
Phob!
Stay still, I will clean it for you.
Can you wipe it off?
Sure, I can.
I was so worried about you
and you made fun of my face.
You're so mean.
You looked funny when you fell.
Stop sulking already.
Smile.
Stop making a grumpy face already.
Smile, come on. Wider.
- You still got some dirt on you.
- Phob.
The Princess is calling for you.
Okay, Mom.
I met Khun Luang Prat yesterday.
Your teacher said that
you're a bright student.
You're a fast learner.
You've done so well in school.
Thank you, Your Highness,
for allowing my son to study.
Your son is a bright student.
My son and I talked
and we decided to pay for his
tuition fee as long as he wants.
We wish that he won't
have to serve us in the future.
Instead, he should serve the nation.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Phob is doing so well in
school, Dad and Grandma.
He always helped me with the lessons.
No matter how good
he is, he still is a servant.
He was born in a lower class of society
so he still needs to crawl.
You can give him more pens
but you can't change his servant blood.
Tin, you should know about this.
Don't praise him too
much or he would get cocky.
I'm just telling the truth.
Actually, you should let him
tutor you sometimes
- so you'd do better in school.
- Tin!
If you don't have nice things to say,
then keep your mouth shut.
You're doing nothing but getting off track.
You're bringing shame to the family.
You won't study, you don't
care about reading books.
Since you were young until now,
can you be as good as the servant's son?
Phob,
don't mind Chat.
But what he said was true.
Who cares if I'm doing great in school?
I can only be a servant,
a lower class of society.
Phob,
look at this.
Cotton rose
is white in the morning,
then it changes to pink at noon.
And in the evening, it
won't be the same anymore.
In the future, your status can be different
based on your potential.
Nothing can stop you.
You're determined and focused.
I believe in you.
Thank you, Your Highness.
You've been so good to me
since we were young.
You've never once seen me
as a servant.
You've never disdained me.
Therefore,
I don't care what the future holds,
I will be your Phob
forever and ever.
Now you're saying nice things to me.
But I will study in the UK in two months.
By then you might be happy
that you don't have to
follow me around anymore.
- Your Highness.
- Phob.
- Stop it!
- Stay away.
- Your Highness!
- Come here.
My dad scolded me because of you,
you stupid servant!
He sent you to school
so you could serve me.
Instead, you chose to be a star.
You didn't know your place,
you're just dust under my feet.
You hear me! Get out!
You stupid servant!
You hurt me? I'm going to kill you.
What is going on? What is this?
- What?
- Grandma!
He hurt me! Look at this! He hurt me!
He hurt me!
How did you raise him to be like this?
I'm hurt! This is so painful.
Grandma!
Look at me! Why don't you look at me now?
You have to look at me!
Prince Wasin and Princess
Pattamapreeya were kind to you
and I still need to punish
you so you will remember this.
But Prince Chatthorn
hurt Prince Tinnakorn first.
I just protected my prince.
Prince Chatthorn
started the whole thing.
Are you talking back to me?
Why don't you know your place?
We're just servants.
Why did you become so full of yourself?
Your grandma
was a servant in the palace.
And I was born here.
We can live like this
because our masters are so kind to us.
But there is no more slavery.
I am grateful for them.
But what he did was
wrong and it was different.
You wanted me to be
responsible for what I didn't do?
Only the masters can do no wrong?
Phob!
You can't say that or
you will go straight to hell.
He is the master so he can't be guilty.
We are the servants and
we need to accept that.
You need to promise me
that you won't do
something like this ever again.
You need to praise him far above
our own heads, your hear me?
My dad scolded me because
of you, you stupid servant!
He sent you to school
so you could serve me.
Instead, you chose to be a star.
He is the master so he can't be guilty.
We are the servants and
we need to accept that.
Sir?
I heard from Euam that
your mom flogged you.
I'm worried about you.
I'm fine.
But…
You have a wound?
It's just this and it's far
from my heart. I'm fine.
It's big.
I'm totally fine.
If you don't believe me, just touch it.
See? I'm fine.
Ow!
I…
Are you hurt? I'm sorry.
I'm just teasing you.
Come on.
This is fun.
I brought some salve to put on your wounds.
I…
Come on, let me put it on for you.
I…wait.
I can put it on myself.
I can do it for you.
It's okay, Your Highness.
- I can do it.
- Phob!
Don't move.
I'll take off your top.
It stings a little.
I can put it on for you.
It will sting a little.
Does it hurt?
I can take it.
Does it hurt here?
Phob, honey.
What did you say?
You want me to punish your son?
Yes, Your Highness. He was guilty
for hurting the master.
Nual, it's water under the bridge.
Why are you bringing it up?
Also, Phob didn't mean to hurt him.
But my son was really guilty.
He didn't know his place.
And he became this way
because he was arrogant.
He thought that he's
Prince Tinnakorn's favorite.
I think you should refrain him
from taking care of Prince Tinnakorn.
So he'd stop acting like this.
They grew up together
and your son always helps my son.
We should let him do his job.
But…
You want us to be cruel masters
who bullied the servants?
Mom!
Why did you ask Prince Vasin
that I should stop taking care of his son?
Did you eavesdrop earlier?
I did't mean to hear it.
You're getting too close to him.
He is a prince.
- And you're just a servant.
- If he wasn't a prince,
if he had no title,
if we were equal, only then
could we get close to each other?
Shut up.
You will go to hell for this.
Don't say the impossible.
You're a servant
and you should know your place.
From now on,
you can't get any closer
to Prince Tinnakorn, okay?
I'm sorry, Mom.
As long as he needs me close,
I will stay with him like this.
Fine.
He will study abroad soon.
When it happens, even if
he doesn't tell you to go,
you can't follow him there anymore.
My dad came back from
his business trip to France
so he told me to give you this.
You're so kind, honey.
- Make yourself at home.
- Yes, ma'am.
The westerners
make such a remarkable perfume.
A beautiful gift from beautiful lady.
But the recipient…
is even more beautiful.
Look at you,
you've always made jokes
right in front of the guests
since you were young until now.
Siri, don't go home just yet.
You should wait to meet Tinnakorn.
Tinnakorn and Phob should be back soon.
You should wait to meet him.
That's right, you should stay.
Would you like to walk in the garden with me?
The roses have just bloomed.
So pretty.
Chatthorn, if you're free, then
you should to back to study.
I met your teachers,
and they said that your
grades weren't very good.
But I...
Siri? When did you get here?
Saranrom Club will organize a
music event next week.
I heard that there are bands from
overseas, do you want to come?
Do you normally go to the music events?
I shall go, if it is my father’s command.
If my father so commands,
I suppose I shall go.
Why is it up to your dad?
If you want to, you can ask him.
My dad doesn't let me go anywhere.
I only can go places
when he tells me to.
What about this?
If you want to go, I can ask him for you.
You can meet with your
friends and join the society.
- Sounds good?
- Yeah.
In the next few days,
the Thai Red Cross
will organize a big fair.
I think you should visit the fair.
I went there last year
and it was so much fun.
Right, Phob?
Yes, sir.
Let's eat.
Dad?
Why did you stop me
from hanging out with Siri?
Instead, you let Tin hang out with her.
When did you get close to her?
Tinnakorn is closer to Siri than you are.
You will make them feel awkward.
How could it be awkward?
It is obvious that I like her.
I don't like her as a sister
but I see her as a woman.
And I think that
Siri likes me too.
I will talk to you frankly
so you will stop with this nonsense.
Siri's dad and I made an agreement
for Tinnakorn to be engaged to Siri.
What?
Why would you do that?
You know well that I like Siri,
why didn't you let me?
Because I don't want to be mortified.
Look at you.
You're doing so bad in school
and you are not a decent human being.
The whole city knows about
you getting into fights with people.
What kind of parents would want you to
marry their daughters?
This is not fair.
You've never given me anything good.
You've always given Tin something good.
- England and Siri. What about me?
- Chatthorn!
Stop thinking about your love life already
and focus on your studies.
And don't compare yourself to your brother,
you can't even compare yourself to Phob.
Go back to study.
Phob!
Why are you here?
Princess Siri is gone?
Yeah, I just sent her off.
I see.
So now you have time for me.
What is wrong with you? Phob?
Are you sick?
I saw you enjoying yourself talking to her.
Do you like her?
I feel bad for her.
She needs to follow her dad's orders,
she can't do anything on her own.
I adore her...
but as a sister.
So what is wrong with you?
What's with the grumpy face?
Tin! Are you happy now?
Move, you filthy servant!
Both of you must be laughing at me, right?
You know well that I like Siri.
What are you talking about?
Why did you bring Siri into this?
Stop acting so innocent already.
Dad wants you to be engaged to Siri.
What?
What he said is true.
What is your problem?
I…
I don't love her like that.
We're like brother and sister.
It's not always about love.
It's about suitability.
- But I don't love Ruethaisiri.
- Or you love someone else?
Who's the girl?
It's okay.
I don't care who she is.
You can just marry
Ruethaisiri as your first wife.
So she can help take care of the palace.
You're a great man,
you can have 4-5 wives
and I think you can take care of them all.
Soon,
our palace will hear good news
from Prince Tinnakorn
and Princess Ruethaisiri.
You knew about this?
Prince Chat yelled so loud like that,
everyone heard about it.
But Prince Tin doesn't love her like that.
He just adores her as a sister.
His relationship is none of your business.
He is a master,
servants like us can't be involved.
But he shouldn't be forced to be into this.
He should be the one
who decides on his relationship.
That's none of your business.
He is a master
and he has his duties to fulfill.
Our duties
are to take care of him and to be grateful.
Don't you see?
This is me trying to give back to him.
I want to help him and make him happy.
I don't want him to marry
someone he doesn't love.
Are you sure about that?
You're not thinking of him as
more than just a master, are you?
- Mom! I..
- Listen to me carefully.
No matter what your thoughts are,
they have to stop now.
Don't drag him to your level.
He is a master
and we are only servants.
We can only respect him as
one of the royal family members.
If one day,
you think of him more
than a master and servant,
you will be the one
who will taint his reputation.
♪ A mischievious ♪
♪ and hard-working ♪
♪ man named Ngoh ♪
♪ He saw a daughter ♪
♪ of a ruler. ♪
♪ Her skin is glowing ♪
♪ like the moon. ♪
Prince Yai's live performance is so great.
His group is the most popular in the city.
My grandma has booked the group for months.
Scoot over.
Move your leg.
One leg at a time.
- Move my leg?
- Follow me. Watch me.
One at a time like this, follow my lead.
Now speed up! Speed up!
Look at me!
- Do you know what it is?
- What?
Like Ngoh!
Smile.
You saw me as an ugly and
dirty-looking guy, didn't you?
If that's the case,
from now on,
I won't help you study anymore.
Stop sulking already.
I mean you look like Ngoh
when he shows his real self.
Ngoh's skin is covered with gold.
But I'm just a servant,
I am nothing like him.
Nobody would toss me a
garland like she did to him.
It's no garland,
but you can have this cotton rose.
Does this mean that
you tossed me the garland?
Is that right?
I'm hungry.
Let's find something to eat in the kitchen.
Don't drag him to your level.
He is a master
and we are only servants.
We can only respect him as
one of the royal family members.
If one day,
you think of him more
than a master and servant,
you will be the one who
will taint his reputation.
Nual.
Where is Phob? It's
about time to go to school.
Well, he left early this morning.
He said that he'd study before class first.
What? He normally waits for me.
Why did he leave first?
I don't know, Your Highness.
But it is better this way.
He is a servant, you should
let him go to school by himself.
[Royal Pages School]
Kamol?
Have you seen Phobthee?
I haven't. He's normally
around you all the time.
Let's go, we don't want to be late.
- Let's go.
- Come on.
I want to play soccer next week.
Sure, you want to join?
- Sure.
- You're joining us?
- We need Weerapon to join the team.
- He needs to come.
He's so good at blocking.
- So great.
- Phob.
There you are.
Let's get back home.
The driver is waiting.
I have to run some errands.
I think I will go home by myself.
You can go home, Your Highness.
What's wrong?
I'm not mad at you.
I'm just a servant.
- How could I be mad at the master?
- Enough with the master and servant.
I know!
You're still thinking about
Chat's insults, don't you?
It has nothing to do with him.
Then what is it about?
I..
Have I offended you?
Can you tell me?
I could have done something
and I didn't know it, so tell me.
If I know, I won't do it again.
But you refuse to tell me anything.
I don't know what to do.
Phob! Phob!
Hey, what is the name of the female vendor
in front of the school?
The one that you helped her the other day.
(In unison) Saijai.
Here, she wanted me
to give you some snacks.
You're quite something.
That Saijai who is pretty
with nice skin, right?
Whoa! Aren't you a charmer?
Our friend is quite something, isn't he?
Hey! There is a new bar at Charoen Krung.
Should we give it a try?
- Let's go.
- I'll buy Phob some drinks.
He tutored us until we passed the test.
- You should come, Your Highness.
- Please come.
Come on. Let's go.
Don't be late.
I think you should go home first.
Cheers!
You shouldn't be drinking too much.
We're at the bar so we
need to drink some liquor.
You expected me to have some desserts?
That's right. Having
some desserts? Cheers!
You're right, Your Highness.
We're not at Saijai's
stall selling desserts.
Among all of us, I think Phob
will be the first with a girlfriend.
Of course, Saiji has such beautiful eyes.
And she flirted with you.
As a real man, you should reciprocate.
Shut up!
Hey! I lost the bet and I
still need to buy you drinks?
You can have another
round to make it up next time.
I told you that you shouldn't
be drinking too much.
Did you watch me?
How could you ask me that?
You should know it well that
I care for you every day.
Well, that was before.
Now you could care more about that Saijai.
Your Highness.
You should care for her.
And you can forget what you said about...
being my Phob.
Enough with your sarcasm already.
You should know well that
I meant what I said.
I will be your loyal servant,
always have and always will.
Why did you avoid me?
You've been avoiding
me all day. What did I do?
It's not your fault.
So you accepted the fact
that you avoided seeing me.
Why didn't you tell me?
We've talked about
everything since we were young.
Did you know that you hurt my feeling
when you acted like that?
You know?
Something
can't be said.
Because I'm worried that
you wouldn't understand
and you could hate me.
Just try to say it.
Actually…
I..
I…
I think we should go home
so you can rest.
You should have let me fall.
So I'll get used to it
when you're not around.
Your Highness,
it's not like I wanted to give you
the cold shoulder or ignore you.
I was just worried that if I said it,
you would hate me.
Why don't you try to say it?
I promise you that no
matter what you say or do,
I will not hate or be mad at you.
I promise.
Who are they?
What are they doing in the back?
(Next Episode)
I saw what you two were doing
behind the bar that night.
There you are, Your Highness.
Just now, I saw Phob and Tin
heading towards the servants' quarters.
No matter what, I want to be
Your Highness's Phob... forever.