I'm talking to you, Wu Wei.
Did a year out there make you dumb?
Thank you, Mr. Gu. Thank you, Mr. Qin.
Don't rush to thank us two.
Do you know who transferred you back?
China Aerospace.
Xu Xu.
Because the current rendezvous and docking plan
adopted your previous idea.
Because of this,
Xu Xu spent a lot of time persuading the leaders.
You'd better not thank me.
Let's be practical.
Buy me a meal.
Today
is already our seventh test.
Still not good enough.
Everyone, we need to hurry up.
I think
although we cannot capture
the signal in the blackout zone,
we can have the ocean-going flight control team
use their shipborne monopulse radar
and photoelectric theodolite for capture and tracking.
Then sync the position and data of the reentry module
to all flight control stations.
This way,
as soon as the reentry module passes through the blackout zone,
we can capture it.
The method is fine.
But
the window for tracking and capture is only three minutes.
The flight control difficulty is very high.
But using monopulse radar,
the search beam is quite narrow.
Plus, the reentry module
has no ground-to-space response signal.
It can only be tracked by the reflection signal
from the plasma shell.
The surface of the plasma shell is very irregular,
and the reflection signal fluctuates greatly,
so stable tracking is impossible.
It can only serve as an auxiliary method.
Using photoelectric tracking equipment to track
is like using the naked eye
through a telescope
to find a high-speed meteor in the sky.
The reentry module's speed is so fast,
capture is extremely difficult.
With such a short time of three minutes,
how can it be captured?
The points you mentioned,
I have considered them all.
It's just...
Go on.
Hello?
So we need an extra layer of guarantee.
Okay, I understand.
I just received a notice from the Space Monitoring and Early Warning Center.
They predict solar flare activity
with a high probability of periodic outbreaks.
Ground signals will be interfered with by electromagnetic storms.
Everyone, we need a contingency plan
and to be fully prepared.
The mission might be delayed.
If it gets delayed,
we will miss another window.
The data inside the blackout zone,
we admittedly don't have.
But the data before entering the blackout zone,
we have it very completely.
What we need to do is actually very simple.
Have every flight control station use their data
to estimate the returner's trajectory.
They should notify each other and compare results
to minimize the error.
You mean
we should compare with each other
to calculate the trajectory and landing site?
This way, even if the optical-electronic theodolite loses it,
we can recapture it
the moment it breaks out of the blackout zone.
That's right.
Our spacecraft has a certain degree of protection against electromagnetic waves.
We can also prepare contingency plans for autonomous docking.
Mr. Gu.
Do you think it's feasible?
Very good.
Please continue.
I
will go send a message to Mr. Qin.
Did you write it all down just now?
Everyone, listen up.
I announce that from now on,
we are entering joint combat mode.
Old Qin and I will stay with you
until we crack this hard nut.
Yes.
Uh, Old Qin.
Uh.
Keep it up.
Qin,
you seem off today.
What's wrong?
No. I asked you
to encourage everyone,
and say a few words.
Why are you being so quiet?
What for?
Look at everyone's mood.
Did your words encourage them?
Do you know that?
Anxiety is actually a kind of pulse wave.
It can interfere with signals
and cause an emotional blackout zone, understand?
Then I'd rather have more anxiety
to strengthen the photoelectric signals
and penetrate the blackout zone.
It's better than scratching our heads and working hard here.
Photoelectric.
Theodolite.
That's one way to do it.
But I still don't want to see you scratching your head all day.
Even if you scratch, you should scratch happily.
These two are bickering again.
I'm used to it.
How do you scratch? Let me see.
Can scratching your head
be done in a fancy way?
You can scratch like this.
Bah! That's a monkey.
You old thing,
always finding ways to insult me.
Your skills are inferior to a monkey's.
Wu Wei, what are you doing?
Wu Wei, what are you laughing at?
Why are you scratching your head?
Hurry up.
Mr. Gu, Mr. Qin.
I have an idea.
Regarding the signal problem of the return capsule,
can we use an optoelectronic theodolite
to capture and track it?
This would solve
the signal capture problem of the return capsule.
He's right.
And paired with a monopulse radar.
This method works.
Come up with a plan tonight,
and conduct joint testing based on the parameters.
No problem.
Well then.
What your Mr. Qin means is that
he will go out now
to buy you milk tea and coffee
and treat you all. Sound good?
Okay.
When did I say it was my treat?
Okay, my treat.
My treat.
Come on, let's give him a round of applause.
Thank you, Mr. Qin.
I'll treat everyone.
How is his condition?
Judging from the test results,
Mr. Qin's cancer has relapsed.
Moreover,
it has spread to his liver and lymph nodes.
Surgery is no longer an option.
How much time does Qin have left?
A few months.
Or it could
worsen at any time.
During this time,
try to keep him comfortable.
Do you still remember
the question Qin brought up?
I think I figured it out,
but I'm not sure.
Qin asked us before too.
Do you have an answer now?
Perhaps.
But this answer
is different for everyone.
I only know that meaningful things
are never easy.
I don't know about the answer,
but it reminds me of a quote
by my idol, Carl Sagan.
Looking back from the eternal,
all-encompassing dark universe.
You will see an
unremarkable pale blue dot.
That's here.
Earth.
Everything we are.
Everyone you love,
everyone you know,
everyone you ever heard of,
lived out their lives on it.
All our joy and suffering,
love, hate, and parting,
every young couple in love,
parents and teachers,
hopeful children,
scientists, and explorers,
are all here.
Go on.
This is Wenchang Space Launch Site.
The Zhengtu-5 Y5 carrier rocket
and the Haoyue-5 lunar probe
have been vertically transported to the launch area.
It is scheduled between 4:00 a.m. and 5:00 a.m. on the 24th
to carry out the launch mission at an opportune time.
Aerospace Flight Control Center,
Wenchang Space Launch Site,
Xi'an Flight Control,
Yuanwang tracking fleet,
and various flight control stations for the mission.
We have fully completed
all mission preparations before the launch.
Attention, all stations.
Two minutes to launch.
Ten-second countdown.
Nine.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Ignition.
Liftoff.
Liftoff time,
04:30
and 21.806 seconds.
Wenchang optical radar tracking is normal.
Telemetry signals are normal.
Wenchang flight is normal.
Programmed turn.
Wenchang optical radar tracking is normal.
Telemetry signals are normal.
Wenchang flight is normal.
Booster shutdown.
Booster separation.
Fairing jettison.
First and second stage separation.
Second stage, secondary shutdown.
Spacecraft and rocket separation.
Solar panel deployed.
Wenchang announces successful launch.
Great.
We made it.
Good.
Then launch it.
I watched it from beginning to end.
Good job.
Rest assured.
The orbit entry went smoothly.
Now we're just waiting for the next phase.
Next, we will enter
the closed period for the lunar landing mission.
We came specifically to let you know.
Rest assured.
We will definitely complete the mission well.
Good job.
I have a better eye
than Mr. Gu.
You look more energetic with short hair.
Ziqi.
You must
bring the lunar soil back.
Rest assured.
I'll be waiting
to drink the celebration wine.
Oh, you.
I prepared grape juice for you.
No drinking.
Why? As long as we're celebrating,
anything we drink is wine.
What? Are you afraid I can't hold on?
I still want to dance in space.
You had a piece of your intestines cut out,
and you're still bragging.
Then I'll dance for you now.
Okay, you're not bragging.
That's enough.
I can dance.
You must come back
and see the lunar soil yourself.
I'll be waiting.
It's a promise.
Head back.
You still have a mission to do.
All right then.
Go back and get some rest.
Wait for our good news.
I'm leaving.
What are you doing? Are you leaving too?
What else should I do?
Look at that sour face of yours.
I've looked at it my whole life.
I'm sick of looking at it.
Can't you change it?
Can't I?
Fine. What else do you want me to do?
I'm bored.
I'll give you one last chance.
Tell me a joke.
Look at you.
How could I possibly tell a joke?
What am I?
Look.
There was a doctor.
A doctor again? Why?
Well, it's a joke about a doctor.
Okay, okay.
There is this doctor.
What about the doctor?
He says to his patient,
'I have to tell you
two pieces of very bad news.'
'The first piece of bad news
is that you have cancer.'
Then the patient says,
'My God.
I have cancer.
Doctor, am I going to die?'
Then the doctor says to him,
'Well, look.
Your second piece of bad news is...'
And also found out you have Alzheimer's,
which is dementia.
The patient said,
"Oh my God, doctor.
I thought I had cancer."
W-What do you mean?
What do you mean?
Th-That is the worst joke
I've heard in my life.
What is this? It's so lame.
W-What are you doing?
Isn't it a bit early?
What are you doing?
Listen to me, old man.
The best thing in my life
was being able
to be partners with you.
In the next life,
if you don't mind,
I'll still come find you.
I'm leaving.
I'll wait for you on the other side.
Prepare for four-module separation.
Powered descent.
Yes.
Lander-ascender combination separates from orbiter-returner combination.
Subsequent actions to be carried out as planned.
Yes.
7,500-Newton engine on.
Powered descent begins.
Switch to rapid adjustment mode.
Switch to slow descent mode.
30-meter slow descent mode.
30 meters.
20 meters.
10 meters.
7,500-Newton engine off.
According to the Aerospace Flight Control Center,
I'll just hold it for you.
The Haoyue-5 probe
successfully landed on the near side of the moon
at 51.8 degrees west longitude
and 43.1 degrees north latitude
in the pre-selected landing area,
and successfully transmitted back landing images.
It will subsequently conduct a two-day lunar surface operation
to collect lunar samples.
Attention all stations.
Lunar surface operations are about to begin.
Ready to drill for lunar soil.
Start the drill.
The drill is approaching the lunar surface.
Almost at 300.
Reached 300.
Almost at 400.
Reached the rocky zone beneath the lunar surface.
Analyzing data.
We have enough deep lunar soil.
Drilling completed.
Begin encapsulation.
Attention all stations.
This is Beijing.
Encapsulation is complete.
Lunar soil sampling finished successfully.
What's wrong, Chao?
What's wrong?
Nothing. I'm happy.
I've worked on this robotic arm for five years.
It's finally finished.
Mr. Qin.
The orbiter-returner combination is operating normally.
The ascender and orbiter-returner combination
working status check is complete.
Haoyue 5 ascender,
lunar surface ignition,
liftoff.
The ascender is operating normally.
Preparing for rendezvous and docking.
The ascender GNC subsystem is operating normally.
Roger.
Where is your backup?
Mr. Gu,
the Monitoring Center reports that
a solar flare erupted 8 minutes ago.
The lunar orbit is affected by electromagnetic waves.
Although this rendezvous and docking is autonomous,
we must also ensure
that we can constantly monitor
the real-time data of the ascender and orbiter-returner combination.
Prepare the emergency plan and continue docking.
Copy that.
Autonomous attitude control started.
Ready to dock.
Report.
Telemetry communication anomaly in the orbiter-returner combination.
Telemetry communication anomaly in the ascender.
Report.
Anomaly detected in ascender telemetry data.
Communication signal lost.
The ascender and the orbiter-returner combination
have temporarily lost contact.
Requesting emergency protocol.
Approved.
Activate global tracking stations
to search for telemetry signals on all bands.
Signal restored.
All stations, report status.
Orbiter-returner combination navigation is nominal.
Ascender attitude is nominal.
Orbiter-returner combination attitude is nominal.
Based on the data from both spacecraft,
we can continue with rendezvous and docking.
Prepare the orbiter-returner combination
for rendezvous and docking with the ascender.
The orbiter-returner combination is leaving the parking point.
Docking flight begins.
Final 100 meters.
Translation and approaching phase.
About to dock.
Report.
Autonomous docking complete.
Docking precise.
Mechanism locked.
Sample transfer started.
Sample transfer complete.
Beijing copies.
Docking mechanism separated normally.
Lao Qin,
you do it.
Attention all stations,
this is Beijing.
Rendezvous and docking completed normally.
The orbiter-returner combination has entered the lunar orbit waiting phase,
and will return to Earth at an appropriate time.
We made it! Finally!
Baozi.
Chao.
We have lunar soil.
Chao! Chao!
Baozi.
Congratulations.
We succeeded.
We did it.
Twenty years.
We finally did it.
You are nervous again.
I know you are nervous again.
Right?
I am not nervous.
I am happy.
I am sorry, but from now on,
I can't let you spread anxiety to me anymore.
However,
my good luck,
I will always leave it to you.
Leave it to you.
Old Qin,
are you okay?
Thanks to Team Muxing.
Thanks to all the aerospace workers.
Thank you.
For making this old dreamer's
dream come true.
The return capsule successfully passed through the blackout zone.
Do you need me to help you clean up?
No need, no need.
I have a lot of things to arrange,
so I'll leave first.
Tomorrow I'll have them come over
and change the sign at your door.
No need.
Let it hang there.
You old geezer.
Old man.
I want to see
what treasures you have hidden here.
I'm talking to you.
What are you doing?
Rummaging through my things.
You old geezer.
Gu Lifeng.
I'm talking to you.
Don't always think about stealing my treasure.
Put it back where it belongs.
Put it back. Put it back.
Don't think I can't see you.
I am in another parallel universe right now,
watching you.
I'm watching you too.
This is my turf.
I call the shots.
You are my lackey.
Tell him for me,
to listen to you over there,
and not make you mad.
You know, old friend.
In this life, if you aren't after this thing of mine,
you're after that thing of mine.
How about this?
I'll leave them all to you.
But you must promise me
to take good care of them.
Otherwise, I'll take them back.
By the way,
it's about time I get some good rest.
Time to sleep.
Goodbye.
Goodbye, old friend.
Old man.
Rest well.
Professor Qin, we've come to see you.
We brought back the lunar soil.
Nearly two kilograms.
Professor Qin.
Our Chinese scientists
finally don't have to rely on 0.5 grams of lunar soil
to write papers anymore.
The things you couldn't let go of,
we have accomplished for you.
Mr. Qin.
I have nothing to report regarding work.
Because I know
I can never surpass you in my lifetime.
But I will keep working hard.
However, in life, I will definitely surpass you.
Today, I'll set a goal right in front of you.
I, Caibao,
will definitely stop being single and find a girlfriend this year.
Mr. Qin.
Today happens to be my birthday.
By the time I reach your age,
perhaps the technological development of China's aerospace
will be completely different.
But I believe
no matter how far it develops,
our purpose and meaning
should remain the same as in the beginning.
I hope that by then,
I will still be fighting on the front lines of aerospace.
You will always be my role model.
That's right.
No matter where we are,
the brightest star in the sky will always be you.
Mr. Qin.
I know
you've always been here.
Mr. Qin.
Rest assured.
We've taken the baton.
We will continue to move forward step by step.
Now it's the moon,
and next it's Mars.
There will be even more distant places
where we leave our footprints.
Along with our Five-Starred Red Flag.
We will keep working hard.
That's enough.
Let's go.
Mr. Qin.
I understand your question.
Now,
I have the answer.
In the vast universe,
I feel we are all just tiny grains of dust.
Whether meeting or flying apart,
it is an entanglement of gravitational orbits.
Earth
is the cradle of human civilization.
But humanity is unwilling to live in the cradle forever.
Exploring space and embracing the universe.
In the unknown deep space,
lies the future of humanity.
Chinese civilization,
as one of the oldest
civilizations on this planet,
is radiating new vitality.
A generation of young Chinese astronauts
are full of ambition
and ready to set sail.
This will be a long journey across hundreds of millions,
or even billions of light-years in distance,
spanning thousands
or tens of thousands of years.
A human's life,
in comparison,
is merely a brief moment.
Our journey
is the sea of stars.
But life
is endless.
Towards the sea of stars,
let's set off.
The names of spacecraft and related missions in this drama have been fictionalized.
Xu Xu
Ying Deqian, He Qiang
Chen Bing
Zhao Qiangjun
Wu Jianguo
Xiaobai
Wang Yiqi, Feng Shuaige, Tang Zixuan, Fu Jingyun, Wang Zhenglin, Qin Dehang, Zhang Haoming, Wang Zihan
Zhu Zimo, Liu Hao, Wang Jinxi, Bao Chuhan, Wu Yuze, Wang Xiu, Duan Yakun, Wang Zhenggang
Production Team
Daily Life Producer Zhao Xuguang
Lighting Team
Lighting Technician
Sound Recordist
Painter
Maker
Makeup and Hair Team
Data Management Li Peiyuan, Tong Zhenzhong
Legal Team
Equipment Support
Beijing Liushun Huihuang Film & Television Media Co., Ltd.
Beijing Chuangxiang Xinshijie Film & Television Culture Co., Ltd.
Colorist
Visual Effects Production Company
Beijing Free Loop Digital Technology Co., Ltd.
VFX Supervisor Zhang Zheng
Modeler
Beijing Moying Dongli Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Packaging Artist
Compositor
Dubbing Production Team
Bianjiang Studio
Music Production Team
Theme Song 'Muxing'
Singer
Lyricist
Poster Design Team
Acknowledgements
Tianjin Xingye Real Estate Group Co., Ltd.
Tianjin Jingmao Metal Products Co., Ltd.
Publicity Department of Nankai District Committee of Tianjin
Publicity Department of Jinghai District Committee of Tianjin
Jingwumen Zhonghua Wulin Park
Jizhou Cheshenjia Scenic Area
Guiding Unit
News and Publicity Center of China National Space Administration
Zhengzhou New Power Film Co., Ltd.
Horgos New Power Film & Television Culture Co., Ltd.