I'll do whatever it takes
to win your heart.
And I've already started.
Does that make me special enough?
Could you stay with me for a while?
Withdraw from this project.
How do you think people
in this company will see Piang,
when the chairwoman's granddaughter
is chasing after
a food researcher like this?
I owe everyone an apology.
I won't be able to present this project.
What happened? Why all of a sudden--
Just leave me alone.
Song, wait.
-What happened? Why all of a sudden--
-Just leave me alone.
Hey, Sis.
-Stop--
-What happened, Song?
Before the meeting,
Ploy already had you recheck the data.
If the formula was really wrong
like you said, you would've told us.
Sis, calm down.
How can I calm down?
-I'm sorry--
-I don't want an apology.
I want the truth.
I won't calm down.
The reason I'm so angry,
is not because you ruined it.
It's because you always
keep everything to yourself.
We're on the same team.
We're practically family already.
So why don't you trust us even now?
Sarut told me
to withdraw from this project.
If I don't, Piang will get dragged
into this mess.
What does Piang have to do with it?
He found out about me and Piang.
He even threatened to tell everyone.
If it were just me, I wouldn't be afraid.
But Piang is involved.
I'm worried about her.
He actually went that far?
He said he has evidence.
He's probably
been collecting it for a while.
Both photos and videos.
Honestly,
I always knew that bastard
would try to get back at you.
You took the Best Researcher
title from him.
But honestly,
I didn't think he'd stoop this low.
He's capable of anything, Sis.
I used to work under him.
I know exactly what he's capable of.
That's why I said
I'm so lucky to be with all of you.
I owe you both an apology,
Nampraw and Ploy.
I'm sorry things turned out like this.
It's okay.
We understand now.
Just stay strong.
We're on the same team.
Were you eavesdropping on us?
Yes.
And I heard everything.
Song, I'll handle this myself.
How are you going to do that?
I'll tell everyone myself
that I'm the one chasing you.
There will be nothing
for anyone to expose.
But you're the chairwoman's granddaughter.
-Don't you feel ashamed--
-No.
What's truly pathetic
is letting someone you love suffer
and doing nothing about it.
Piang, don't.
That'll only make things worse.
Then how do we fix this?
It's not fair that your team
has to lose because of his dirty tricks.
Like I said,
the best solution
is for you to stay away from me.
-But that's not--
-It's not that hard.
Just stop pursuing me
and spend your time
with someone more suitable.
Who do you mean by that?
The one your grandmother picked for you.
Trust me.
It's the only way to end this.
If you really like me,
then consider this my request.
Please do this for me.
Excuse me.
Mudmee asked me to invite
both of you to her office.
Yes.
I have an announcement.
Since you two are currently tied
and have the highest scores,
management and I have agreed
to hold an official competition
to determine this year's
Mega Excellent winner.
I'll announce the challenge
and rules as soon as possible.
I have a question.
If one team is unable to participate,
does the other team automatically win?
No.
For this competition,
withdrawal will not be allowed,
regardless of the reason.
Your grandmother is sitting right here.
Don't you see her?
Come talk to me first.
Yes, Grandma.
How did your date with Dr. Namking go?
Why are you back so early?
I waited there for an hour,
but she never showed up.
Is this really the person you said
was perfect for me?
I'll excuse myself.
I'd like to thank everyone
for supporting our foundation.
Now, please excuse me
while I call the director.
Please enjoy yourselves.
Please do.
Ms. Pannee’s foundation
that tackles violence
has received tremendous support.
I hope that
the stray dog and cat rescue foundation
I'm working on
will receive the same support.
I'll have to think carefully
about whether I'll support it.
I've already apologized
on my granddaughter's behalf
for making Piang wait.
And not showing up as promised.
For a doctor,
a patient's life comes first.
That proves if they get married someday,
she'll take excellent care of her partner.
You do have a point.
Fine.
I'll give her one more chance.
I figure no one suits Piang better
than your granddaughter.
But don't let her mess up again.
Otherwise,
I won't help your foundation.
Excuse me.
Are you laughing at me?
Sorry to say, but yes, I am.
What's so funny?
What you were just talking about.
Honestly,
I wasn't trying
to pry into anyone's business.
But you were speaking so loudly
that I couldn't help but overhear.
And the reason I laughed
is because of the way you think.
You see your granddaughter
as a business tool.
You set her up for your own benefit.
I honestly didn't realize
people still think like that these days.
So when I heard it,
it was just ridiculous.
I couldn't help laughing.
I'll get going now.
Hey, who is that woman?
How dare she talk to me like that?
Why wouldn't she?
She's M.R. Salika Warakijaruwongs.
Rich, and of royal descent.
She's sharp-tongued.
She's usually very private.
She rarely attends events like this.
This is probably her first one in years.
MON
Hello. Are you free?
Come see me at the office.
I am. But I'm not coming.
My heart is broken.
I don't have the energy to go anywhere.
What? Did you and Song have a fight?
Then I guess you don't want to see
Song's feature that airs tomorrow.
What a shame.
I wanted you to be the first to see it.
Wait.
I'm on my way.
Someone mature.
Age doesn't matter.
It's about their mindset and character.
They should be well-presented
in both appearance and personality.
Someone who gets it right away,
isn't childish…
Piang.
How much longer are you
going to keep quiet?
I don't know how I'm supposed to feel.
Part of me is happy seeing her shine,
but another part is sad
that I'm not there with her.
Looking into her eyes, holding her hand,
and admiring her.
Piangrawin.
Why is your life so tragic?
Hey.
You don't need to comfort me.
I'm not comforting you.
I'm telling you to move
your face away from my screen.
This screen is expensive. You'll break it.
Thanks a lot, friend.
Honestly,
if Song wasn't being threatened,
would she really want you out of her life?
No. I'm sure of it.
I believe Song feels something for me too.
There have been so many times
when she let it show.
Especially,
when we slept together.
Slept together?
Then if you want to see her,
there is a way.
How so?
Friends with benefits.
A relationship where two people meet
just to sleep together.
So why don't you suggest that to her?
But you'll have to make her believe
that's all you really want from her.
No strings attached.
But friends with benefits
isn't supposed to involve feelings, right?
Yes.
But you said it yourself.
You're sure she already
has feelings for you.
And if that's true,
asking her to be friends with benefits
will only make her fall for you even more.
You're a genius, my friend.
Obviously.
Then why did you try to stop me from
having a one-night stand with Song?
What happened?
Did your nun spirit leave your body?
No.
I just didn't want to see you like this.
You looked like a dying puppy.
Aw.
-So pitiful.
-Hey.
Am I a dog again?
Let me see your paw.
Come here.
Leave me alone.
-Come here.
-No.
It's perfect.
1. USE FOOD TECH OR CHEMISTRY.
2. CONNECT TASTE, AROMA,
AND TEXTURE TO LOVE.
3. MAIN INGREDIENT
MUST FIT THE THEME'S STORY.
4. NO WITHDRAWAL ALLOWED.
TO COMPETE FOR THE MEGA EXCELLENT AWARD.
You've seen the competition brief, right?
"A dish that tastes like love."
You must be thinking of Piang.
You can stop using Piang to threaten me.
It won't work anymore.
Can't you see?
The rules require both of us to compete.
And neither of us can withdraw.
True.
I'm starting to wonder
what the boss is really after.
Why is she so determined
to make us compete?
Honestly, if she wanted you to win,
she could just do that.
After all, she…
seems crazy about you.
Or maybe…
before you went after Piang,
-you went after the boss first.
-Sarut.
You're actually a very capable person.
And you've got decades
more experience than I do.
If you truly competed against me on merit,
I'm sure beating me would be easy.
You don't need dirty tricks
or a dirty mind like this.
Well, maybe it's because
I've seen so much in life.
That's why I know
being the bad guy makes life easier.
Then can I borrow that idea too?
I know as well.
The reason you like playing golf
isn't because you enjoy the game.
It's because you've got
your eye on someone there.
And if you don't want your wife
to hear about this,
then stop being a jerk.
And play by the rules.
Understood, Sarut?
Yes.
Why didn't you tell me?
If I hadn't overheard it myself.
I would have never known about this?
Anyway.
You don't have to worry about
the competition anymore.
Or about Piang.
I'll take care of everything myself.
Thank you so much, Boss.
But, Piang and I already agreed
not to get involved anymore.
That's good.
If the two of you can really do that.
Moo Grob.
Come let Mommy hold you.
Moo Grob, you didn't see it, did you?
There, there.
SONG
Why did you send me these photos?
I sent them
because I wanted you to see them.
Why?
To get your attention.
And it seems to have worked.
That's why you're calling me now.
Didn't anyone ever teach you
how dangerous this is?
What if these photos got leaked
and someone saw them?
Do you know what could happen?
Not only did I get your attention,
I got your concern too.
Totally worth it.
If you're messing with me, I'm hanging up.
Wait.
You don't have to worry
that I'm after something from you.
I just want to be
friends with benefits with you.
Huh? What did you say?
I think
I'm not actually serious about you either.
I guess I'm just
hooked on what we have in bed.
And I know you are too.
So full of yourself.
You told me yourself
that you'd never sleep with
the same person twice.
But you've already broken that rule.
And if you don't want
to be serious with me
and want to stop me
from meddling in your life,
then don't turn me down.
Please, Song.
If you agree,
I promise I'll stop chasing after you.
But it's okay
if you don't want to do this.
I might find someone else instead.
I'm sure there are hotter people
than you on the app.
But if not,
I'll just look around at clubs and bars.
Don't.
Friday nights only.
What?
We'll be friends with benefits.
But only on Friday nights.
If you're okay with that.
Okay.
Okay, pan in a little more.
Okay, that's enough. Yes.
Okay, we've got it.
-Thank you.
-Please go over there.
Alright.
You did great today.
-Thank you.
-I'll send you the retouched photos later.
Sure. Thank you.
See you. Thank you.
Thank you.
We're done for today, so I'll get going.
-Thank you so much. Thank you.
-Sure. Thank you.
Shit.
Why is he here?
Don't forget.
If anything happens, tell me.
I know.
What's up?
Song, where's your junior?
What?
Nothing.
Are you free tonight? Let's grab a drink.
It's Friday. I can't.
I already have plans.
Some other time then.
Who are you meeting, and do we know them?
Could it be Piang?
How could it be?
I already told her
we'd stop seeing each other.
Then what is…
What's this?
Don't you have work to do?
And how's that research
I asked for coming along?
Honestly, I still don't trust Sarut.
I think he might have
something else up his sleeve.
Nampraw.
Forget about him.
Things have already come this far.
Whatever happens, happens.
Let's just do our best
and focus on our work.
At least,
hard work never hurt anyone.
Let's do this.
Let's do it.
Let's go.
Sure. Let's go.
That's right.
-Let's go.
-Yes.
Great job, everyone.
-Bravo, seriously.
-Exactly.
Come on, let's get back
to the work we love.
Bravo. Fighting, unnie.
Hey.
Why does Song seem unusually fired up?
Just the other day, she looked so down.
Why are you asking so many questions?
Isn't this a good thing?
It is, but it's weird.
It's weird, and weird is not good.
It's like she's bipolar.
So what did you tell your grandma?
Don't tell me you said
you were staying at my place.
Well, I am. Who else could I use
as an excuse besides you?
Talk later. Song is here.
Song.
Before we go up to the room,
can we stop and buy a bottle of wine?
You could just order it.
But I want to get some snacks too.
Do you think we're going on a picnic?
Do you understand
what friends with benefits means?
I do.
If you do, then why--
Friends with benefits get hungry too.
Come on, it won't take long.
Wait.
What are you doing?
I was watching a series,
and I saw them do this.
They poured wine over their body
and tasted it.
I think it's pretty sexy.
It looked romantic.
That's only in TV dramas.
Do you know what it's called in real life?
What?
A waste.
Song. You're such a mood killer.
So that's why you bought the wine.
Next time,
if you want something romantic,
just tell me.
You don't have to go this far.
Song.
Can it be my turn to please you?
Normally, I don't like
being on the receiving end.
I prefer being the one giving pleasure.
I don't know
what the women you've been with were like.
But for me,
I don't want to be selfish.
I want you to be happy too.
Please.
I'm only allowing this once.
And…
don't do anything weird.
I'm here. Where are you?
Hi, I'm Fern.
I'm Ple.
Hey.
Get out of my head already.
What is this?
Why are you so drunk?
And you drove here yourself?
Hey.
Oh.
Did you just make me fall?
I didn't do anything.
You did this on your own.
-Come on, let me help you up.
-No.
Don't be stubborn. Get up.
Why are you being so fussy?
I called you today,
but I couldn't get through.
My phone broke.
Then why did you come here?
Because my phone broke,
so I came to check on you.
Actually, I've been coming every night.
But I saw you were doing fine
and I didn't want to bother you.
You might be uncomfortable.
By the way,
was there a reason you called me?
Wait, did that jerk come after you again?
Are you hurt anywhere?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Luckily, I got away in time.
But I was still panicking.
That's why I went out drinking.
I'm sorry.
If we'd been able to reach each other,
you wouldn't have had
to go through that alone.
You're not thinking straight.
So what?
Are you going to say no?
You're awake.
I was just making breakfast for you.
Where did you get all this?
You didn't buy it when we went
to the supermarket last night.
I got up early and went to buy it.
You can wake up early?
It's not easy,
but I'm trying to train myself.
Just in case one day
we end up getting married.
Then I can be a good wife.
Or…
maybe a good husband?
You're talking nonsense.
Since when do friends
with benefits get married?
You're not even a little swept away?
Hurry up and finish. I'm hungry.
Yes, my temporary wife.
Oops.
It's all over the place.
This brand of mayonnaise
has terrible packaging.
I told you, don't play with food.
It's wasteful.
Song, you keep ruining the mood.
Come here you.
Don't.
Stay right there.
-No way.
-Stay right there.
Don't. Don't come any closer.
Song.
I've never seen
you laugh like that before.
You're happy right now, aren't you?
I guess so.
See you next Friday.
Song,
my matcha café is having its
soft opening next Friday morning.
I'd like you to come.
Just think of it
as a product developer role.
I think I'd better not.
Let's stick to our agreement. That's best.
Okay.
Come on, I'll walk you out.
The setup looks amazing, Mudmee.
Do you like it?
I love it.
-Mon, can you get some shots of the DJ?
-Sure.
The DJ has good taste, too.
-I'll be right back.
-Okay.
-Keep an eye on things, Mon.
You got shots of the DJ already, right?
-Hello.
-I thought you weren't coming.
Congratulations, Mudmee. Here.
Thank you.
And thank you on behalf of my sister, too.
For making her dream come true.
My pleasure.
I should be thanking you
for giving me the opportunity.
Actually, this was
my first project at 124 as well.
At first, I wasn't sure
I could pull it off.
But seeing it all come together…
Makes you proud, huh?
Yes.
You should be proud.
Because honestly,
you're far more capable than you think.
By the way, Mudmee,
are you doing better now?
Well, I'm doing better.
But where I am in life,
there's always something
to deal with every day.
Then next time you're not feeling okay,
why don't you try visiting
an art exhibition?
It helps you relax and enjoy yourself too.
I do it all the time.
I think it's better
than going out drinking.
In that case, would you take me?
Well, if I'm not busy, sure.
-Come on, let's go inside.
-Okay.
This is our signature drink.
Make sure to get some shots.
Sure.
Will this drink make me float?
Right up on a cloud.
Totally.
And this area is our workshop section…
Dr. Namking.
Congratulations, Piang.
The bouquet is a bit large.
I wanted to congratulate you,
and use it as an apology too.
I'm sorry I missed
our first date that day.
Congratulations, Piang.
Are you okay?
I've been feeling a little drained today.
Then, why don't you get some rest?
If you're tired,
we don't have to do anything tonight.
Just relax.
Or go to sleep if you want.
I'll stay right here with you.
Song.
I'm sorry.
I really can't go on anymore.
No, Neung. Don't do this.
And don't forget to keep your promise.
No!
Did you have a nightmare?
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Go back to sleep.
Come on.
Bad dreams, be gone.
What are you doing?
Calling your spirit back.
When I had nightmares as a kid,
Mudmee always did this.
Then I'd sleep through the night
without bad dreams.
You don't have to be scared.
It was just a dream.
It's not real.
What if it really happened before?
Well, just think of it as
something that's already passed.
And don't let it hurt you again.
Song, don't be afraid.
I'll be your dreamcatcher.
Then stop pushing me away.
Didn't we agree not to do this?
I was just making desserts for the café
and wanted you to try them.
How about we date?
Usually, you don't talk
to many people, do you?
Maybe when I warned you
to stay away from Piang,
it wasn't enough.
At Dr. Namking's birthday party,
I'm sure you saw
that where you stand
and where Piang stands are worlds apart.
I'll disappear from Piang's life.