Why are you in such a hurry?
Why don't you wait for Jamie
so you can go to school together?
I still have a lot to do.
I need to go ahead.
Please, come in.
And introduce yourself.
Al?
Good morning, everyone.
I'm Alistair Ravena.
The Q.E.D. Club members are here.
Alright, hold on.
Welcome.
I've been expecting you.
Actually, I'm pleased to finally meet you
face-to-face, Ms. Lorelei.
Something strange is happening.
The situation is weird.
Even if she doesn’t show herself to us,
she still finds ways
to submit poems for our portfolio.
Me and you, everything is tragedy.
What makes you think it's an SOS message?
At first glance,
it looks like an ordinary poem.
And it could've looked like
your writer sent it by mistake.
But the truth is, she didn't.
Actually, I feel like
I was really with Loki earlier
with how quick you were able
to decipher that code.
The only difference
is you genuinely care about the victim.
Are you really going to pick that lock?
Yes.
Lori, are we about to do
something illegal? Huh?
What if someone sees us?
Then we'll be accused of trespassing.
You just threw it away, huh?
If you won’t let me go, just kill me!
- Help!
- There, there.
Whatever!
I don't want this anymore!
- You shameless bastards!
- Tie him, tie him!
Just wait!
- I’m reporting you to the police!
- Tie him tight!
You should be the one preparing for us!
After what you did to Camille.
I kicked like that.
- I don’t know about you.
- You really are something.
Anytime.
Actually, he helped me solve
a case earlier,
so that’s where we came from.
Interesting!
Care to update me
before the rest of our blog readers?
Welcome to the Q.E.D. Club.
Moria...
Can you describe his voice?
Cold and deep.
- You’ll get goosebumps when you hear it.
- Moriarty.
I think the person
they were talking to was a man.
There was something off about him.
He had a lollipop in his mouth that time.
A big sin...
a wrong committed against him.
I’m just a pawn on his chessboard.
All of their requests...
we'll pass to Moriarty.
What would an officer be doing
in the place where you supposedly
kidnapped yourself?
It’s a pleasure
to finally meet you in person.
I am Moriarty.
Is that for your Humanities class?
This is Moriarty's spider web
of conspiracy.
So you're saying,
Stein a.k.a. Moriarty,
is a spider?
"A spider that sits motionless
at the center of this bloody web."
If I were to borrow
Sir Arthur Conan Doyle's words.
You're so serious.
Just kidding.
But all jokes aside,
what Stein’s doing isn’t funny.
But this one...
we have no proof
that Stein is connected
to the murders plotted by Moriarty.
But we can get that
from the people connected to him.
May I?
Be my guest.
If three of them are dead,
and one’s a convict,
and we still don’t know
who Lollipop Guy is,
that means our closest link to Moriarty
is Officer Montreal.
Because he’s the one
I saw calling Moriarty’s number.
My guess is,
he’s the one who can give us
the evidence we need to convict Stein.
Precisely.
So, should we start an operation
to gather evidence?
Or do we just leave it to chance
and wait until we encounter him on a case?
My concern is…
is this the right thread to follow?
Is it really this simple?
Because what if Stein
is not the real Moriarty?
♪ Shadows. ♪
♪ In the dark are crawling. ♪
♪ Keeping watch and barring your way. ♪
♪ As if the line could not be crossed. ♪
♪ To every scream and every tremor. ♪
♪ These walls remain the only witness. ♪
♪ Every noise is etched in here. ♪
♪ Like fire and ammunition
for your memory. ♪
♪ Heed the warnings. ♪
♪ The threats poised to strike. ♪
♪ For this world ♪
♪ is not what you imagined. ♪
♪ Heed the warnings. ♪
♪ Open up your eyes. ♪
♪ For this world ♪
♪ is not what you imagined. ♪
♪ Heed the warnings. ♪
But he admitted it, didn’t he?
That’s why you got mad.
It was wrong of me
to let myself go like that.
But the point is…
what if he's just like that officer?
What if he's only a proxy
sent by the real one
to play mind games with us?
That's possible.
But as long as there is no new evidence
to prove otherwise,
I'm gonna take his word for it,
that he really is Moriarty.
Do you want more coffee?
I can make you another cup.
I don’t think we have time
for a second cup.
You need to dress up, don’t you?
Dress up?
For what exactly?
You’ve forgotten about our date.
Date?
Wait, Lorelei, are you free this weekend?
I don’t have anything planned
this weekend yet.
Why?
I’d like to invite you on a date.
Huh?
Wait. Wait.
I thought that was a joke.
And why would you even
go out with me?
Jamie’s there, or whoever. Why me...
It’s not a romantic date.
- Oh...
- It’s more like a…
Sorry.
It’s more of a case consultation.
But you’re still suspended, right?
But in a different school.
Ah… I see.
Okay. Well, in that case…
count me in!
Are we including Jamie or Al?
Since he's a new member of Q.E.D. Club.
She’s unavailable.
But you can ask your childhood friend
to tag along.
Okay. I’ll do that.
Lori, is everything okay?
Of course!
Loki just wants to know
if you want to tag along with us
to a school we’re going to today.
Someone requested
his assistance on a case,
and we’re about to investigate it.
I would love to,
but I’m heading back to Manila now.
I’ll make it up to you and Loki.
I see.
That’s unfortunate.
It was only confirmed now.
You know…
if I can help you with anything,
just call me right away, okay?
Honestly…
I’d rather be solving cases with you.
But I can’t.
I don’t really want to do
what they’re making me do in Manila.
Okay. I’ll tell Loki you’ll be in touch.
Take care on your trip, okay?
Okay.
Take care too. Just call me
if you need anything, Lori, okay?
Bye.
Looks like it’s just the two of us again.
I was never fond of anything
that defies logic.
But I need to read it
so I can understand
the other elements of this case.
Are you familiar with chain messages?
Those stupid messages that say
you'll be hit with bad luck
if you won't forward it
to a certain number of people?
Yeah.
I remember, that used to be
popular in my school back then.
What’s the connection to Wizardly?
Well, at the school we’re going to,
there’s a fan group dedicated to the lore
of this young adult fiction work.
And recently,
two members of the club were found dead
after receiving a mysterious text message.
Message? What message?
Havre k'davra.
Huh?
That spell was part of the chain message
received by the two victims
before their death.
Died because of a chain message?
Wait, what’s the meaning of "havre..."
Havre k'davra!
According to the book,
that spell causes an instantaneous
painless death to the target.
Well, I can’t read all of this right now.
Too bad Jamie’s not here.
Her photographic memory would’ve helped.
And the other day...
you were surprised to hear
that Jamie slept in my room.
In my bed.
Did that bother you?
Loki!
- Stop it!
- Jamie!
Come on.
No!
Why would that bother me?
Well, you’ve got nothing to worry about.
Nothing happened between me and Jamie.
I’ve built a wall of pillows
between us when we slept.
My acquaintance is a tech genius
and a brilliant inventor.
He could’ve made money
from his inventions,
but he chose not to sell his patents.
What are his inventions?
Remember that stun pen I gave you?
He made that one.
Well, I can’t wait to finally meet him.
What’s your business here, ma’am? Sir?
Offices are closed today. It's Saturday.
Sir! They’re with me! Let them in!
Hi! Hi! Thanks for coming today, Loki.
So you must be Lorelei?
I'm Herschel Aguirre.
It's nice to finally meet
the creator of the stun pen!
I had someone I know who
is good at inventions do it.
It's a stunning device disguised as a pen
that you can bring anywhere.
Stun pen? Ah...
I hope you’re not using it for pranks.
Seems you’re like the boss
around here, huh, Hershey?
He can never remember my name.
I gave up on that.
So, shall we?
Let's go.
Come on, guys. This is our playground.
It's exactly where we do everything.
This is our lab, as you can see.
Sorry! Sorry!
I forgot the oven’s voltage
isn’t compatible with our outlet.
I was just about to heat up
the pizza I bought for our guest.
Leona! Did you forget that...
Help me out here!
Move!
Did you forget it's not an ordinary oven?
Did you forget?
Safety is priority number one.
Second, wear your gloves and your gown.
Everyone, meet my assistant, Leona Divino.
She helped me develop the stun pen.
Hi! Nice to meet you.
Hi. Nice to meet you!
Come on. Come on.
Leona is a member of the Wizardly Club
that... What was it again?
Fellowship of the Wand.
Fellowship of the Wand!
My precious club.
Herschel, wrong reference.
Tomato, tomato.
Two members were found unalive,
but Leona can tell you more about it.
Yeah! Come with us!
Come.
Herschel! Hey! Come here!
The member who were found dead
are Godfrey Griffin and Sylvester Salazar.
Both are founding members
of Fellowship of the Wand.
This is Godfrey,
the one with the red scarf.
This happened after the general assembly,
around 6:00 p.m.
I was there when it happened to Sylvester.
The meeting
for the club acquaintance party
that will be held
later this afternoon just ended.
Oh, here. Hold on. Let me show you, guys.
I’m also with Syvester,
the one wearing a green scarf at the back.
Some members of the Fellowship think that
the message the contains the Havre K’davra
killed two founders.
But that’s… that’s impossible, right?
There’s no way a message can kill.
Huh? How did that happen? Magic?
There’s no such thing as magic.
There may be a logical explanation
for the deaths of the two founders.
And we will get to the bottom of this.
Lorelei and I would be glad
to take on this case.
Look.
- You can see Sylvester there...
- I see.
Pressure.
Click.
Okay.
It's been weeks
since I personally solved a case.
Solving cases really makes
my overall wellness better.
I'm more excited to know
who's the real killer.
Hey! Coffee! Here.
Hold on.
Here. Coffee.
Thanks!
Do you think Loki will be stuck
in the security office for long?
I'm not sure, but I think
they're reviewing a lot of footage.
Why? Do you still need anything?
So far, nothing yet.
I’ll study this autopsy report first.
Okay.
Well, is it okay
if I leave you again for a bit?
I have to go 'cause I have to pick up
some things
for the acquaintance party later.
Yeah, sure. No worries.
Okay! Enjoy your coffee.
Hello, Al!
Is the signal okay now?
Can you hear me, Al?
Yes. Loud and clear, Lori.
I got your message about the case.
I can’t reply right away
’cause I’m driving.
Are you busy?
I can call later
if now is not a good time.
No. It’s fine. I don’t mind.
It’s better to have someone with you
while you’re driving.
What’s the cause of death?
Well, according to the report...
the cause of death is asphyxia
due to neuromuscular blockade
caused by the poison curare.
It says here that curare
is a type of poison that causes paralysis,
which then leads to asphyxiation
due to the victim’s inability
to contract the respiratory muscles.
According to the autopsy,
a puncture wound was found
in the victim’s nape.
Curare...
So someone injected curare
into the victim?
Or maybe someone stabbed them
with a needle laced with curare?
That’s possible too.
But we already saw
some of the CCTV footage.
The victim was alone before he collapsed.
No one even approached him.
Lori, I’m about to lose signal,
but just message me.
I’ll call right after this, okay?
Yeah, of course!
No problem, Al. Drive safe, okay?
Hey! You’re already here.
How’s it going?
Did you find anything on the CCTV footage?
Nothing.
Even the phone number used
in the chain message can’t be tracked.
What does the autopsy say?
Well, it says here,
the cause of death is asphyxia
caused by neuromuscular blockade
caused by the poison curare.
What I still can’t figure out, though,
is how it was injected into the victims
when no one even came near them?
Have a look?
This reminds me of a similar case.
Do you remember the culprit
in Chemistry Lab Case?
Yes, of course! Genesis Cabangon.
Genesis Cabangon.
He too was poisoned,
just like what happened here.
He was also pricked in the nape.
According to the autopsy report,
a broken needle tip
was found lodged in his nape.
A fast-acting paralytic
was detected in this area.
Poison.
John, John.
John! John!
We both know someone
who employs a similar modus.
Moriarty?
But Stein is still unconscious.
Are you saying that Chivalry College
has their very own Moriarty?
It’s too early to tell.
We need more information.
There are no students
we can ask right now.
But the Fellowship of the Wand
is having a grand acquaintance party
for the new members.
Here you go!
It’s a members-only event later,
and members need to get dressed to fit in.
- There you go.
- Here.
Thanks.
Are these hand-me-downs?
Is this a scarf or a dish towel?
Loki!
Don’t worry, Loki. It’s all brand-new.
But that’s how it is.
They bought it from a supplier.
It’s strange...
their membership fees
and miscellaneous expenses are so high.
But look at the items.
They’re not worth the price.
Substandard.
Maybe that’s why
some Wiz-heads don’t join.
Maybe the officers are getting kickbacks
from the membership fees?
So that’s why
they’re using cheap suppliers?
Maybe we should ask the members?
Don’t look at me!
I’m not a fan of fantasy series.
But they needed my services, so I obliged.
Wait, let me demonstrate! Come here!
Follow.
Found it!
Leona, my dear,
can you kindly close off the lights?
Of course. Hold on.
Ilumino!
So gorgeous.
So you pretty much created
a flashlight that looks like a...
a wand?
Not ordinary wand.
It has a voice recognition system
installed.
You don’t need to press a button
or flip a switch.
Just say the magic word.
Like this!
It only has five spells available, look...
Can we now focus on the case?
Lights on, please.
I'm just gonna tinker off with my wand.
Leonora!
- Leona!
- Yes?
When you went
near the second victim's body,
did you notice anyone
pricking him on the nape?
Or did you see a needle-like object?
No.
We didn’t have time to check the body.
Well, my team immediately carried him
to the clinic.
So if someone pricked him,
we didn’t notice it.
Who else was with you in the video?
Oh, Rowen Ravino and Helios Hontiveros.
They’re also the founders
of the Fellowship.
Okay.
What was their relationship
with the victim?
Sorry, I know this might sound
like a stretch,
but it seems like they weren’t that close.
Usually, if people are friends,
they are all together side by side.
But judging by their body language,
Sylvester was trailing behind.
He isn’t walking ahead. No urgency.
Spot on observation!
Is it possible those two
had a motive against Sylvester?
Well, you’re right!
The four founders have always
had disagreements.
So, they’re not that close.
Well, Sylvester wanted stricter selection
for members entering the Fellowship.
Meanwhile, the other three founders
are fine with anyone who’s willing
to pay the membership fee.
Some of our applicants
aren’t really fans or readers.
They’re just following the trend
because our club is popular.
In short,
the remaining two founders
will somehow benefit
from their colleague's death.
No more opposition for them.
Is there anyone else who will benefit?
I think the one who will replace
Sylvester as Mage of Earth.
Do you know him?
Yes. Lucius Malvar.
Actually, his appointment will be
announced later at the acquaintance party.
He can be a suspect,
an accomplice,
or a target.
What do you think?
Well...
what we do know is that two
of the four founders are now dead.
And there’s still the possibility
that the killer
is targeting their leaders.
If the culprit is someone who has
a grudge against the founders,
they may need to vet
for more replacements.
If both or either of the founders
drop dead later,
this becomes a serial killing.
What? We're wizards.
Hello, Al?
How are you?
Are you done with your errands?
Yeah, I just finished.
And actually, it was a lunch meeting
with your dad.
What? You had lunch with Papa?
Why didn’t you tell me right away?
Because I knew you’d react like that.
But you don’t have to worry about it,
he was just asking about you.
- Good thing you told me.
- Who are you with? Lorelei?
- Yeah, over there.
- Anyway, Loki and I have figured out.
- How about you?
- That the two murders
are likely connected to a killing spree
targeting the club’s founders.
Many lives are at risk.
That’s why we’re here
at their acquaintance party now.
To investigate and hopefully, to prevent
the killer from striking again.
Okay. Observe those who come into contact
with the potential targets.
And also take note of who shakes hands
with them and who approaches them.
And also those who aren’t too far.
People within about five to ten meters,
something like that.
Five to ten meters? Why?
I did some research about curare.
Indigenous people in South America
dip their arrows or blowgun darts
in curare before hunting their prey.
Are you saying there’s a possibility
the killer didn’t need
to get close to the victims?
Like, the killer used blowgun?
Possible, because even after reviewing
the video you sent,
there’s no sign of any student
carrying that kind of weapon.
It’s either the culprit
isn’t visible in the frame,
or they found a clever way
to conceal the weapon.
But there’s a flaw in that reasoning.
If it really was a blowgun used,
how did it manage to penetrate
the victim’s scarf?
You said in the autopsy report,
there were puncture marks
on their napes, right?
I just realized something.
The scarf he was wearing is thin.
A needle can easily pass through it.
Lori! Hey! Come!
Loki and Herschel are looking for you.
Sorry, Al. I have to go.
Okay. Alright.
You and Loki take care, okay?
- Hey, what's up?
- What's up?
Oh, here she is!
Guys, guys. I'm gonna show you, guys.
This is Lorelei Rios.
She’s also the vice president
of the FOTW at Clark U.
She’s also a House of Life
like you, Helios.
- Come on, come on.
- I'm Helios Hontiveros, by the way.
Always pleased
to meet a fellow House of Life.
Yeah.
And I am Rowen Ravino.
House of Sky.
What an honor to make your acquaintance.
- It's nice to meet you both.
- Just enjoy the party.
You guys wanna go with us?
- Sure.
- Oh, okay.
- Yeah.
- See you. Bye, bestie.
Miss you!
So, what did your childhood friend say
during your phone call outside?
Wait. How did you know Alistair
was the one I was talking to?
Well, it could be your aunt,
but she'll message you first
before calling.
Unless it's urgent.
It could be your father,
but you're not fond of him.
So, your conversation won't probably last
for more than 30 seconds.
It could be any of your classmates,
but today's a weekend,
so, you're not required
to take their call.
So, that leaves, Alistair,
the only one who can make you stay
on the line for five minutes.
Sssh!
Sorry.
Well, I’m impressed.
But anyway, speaking of Alistair,
he told me he thinks
the culprit probably used a blowgun
or something to that effect
to shoot a poison-laced needle
at the victims.
So, basically, the suspect didn’t need
to get close to the victims
to prick them with a needle.
I've arrived at the same theory.
And this case reminds me
of the Sherlock Holmes Novel,
The Sign of Four.
Where the murderer used a blow pipe
to shoot at the victim
with a poisoned dart.
Dear, Fellows of the Wands!
Please rise and prepare your wands!
The program is about to begin!
Look...
she's gonna ask us to do something stupid.
In three,
two,
one…
Raise your wands and illuminate
the hall with your magic.
On the count of three!
One, two, three!
Ilumino Magna!
- Welcome to the grand acquiantance party.
- Ilumino Magna.
Today is a special day.
Hey!
Is there a problem?
I think something’s
just wrong with the wire.
Probably about the voice
recognition something.
But, don’t worry. I’ll fix it later.
It’s alright!
Their wands…
is this related
to the wands that they have?
To the new members
of the Fellowship, welcome!
To the old members, welcome back!
Before we officially begin
our acquaintance party,
let us offer a moment of silence
for the two fallen founders
of the Fellowship.
In light of the untimely passing
of our colleagues,
we, the remaining founders,
have chosen the right person
to lead the House of Earth.
Wizards, a round of applause
for Lucius Malvar, the new Mage of Earth.
Lucius! Lucius!
Lucius! Lucius! Lucius!
In the name of the Houses...
He's looking at his phone.
And that’s the Havre K'davra message.
- Rowen! Rowen!
- Hey!
- Rowen!
- Call the police!
Hershey! Lock the venue!
- No one gets out! Lock the door!
- No one gets out!
Rowen, are you okay?
Rowen, come on! Rowen!
- Hey! Don’t touch him!
- Rowen!
Is there a pulse?
He's gone.
Who are you two, really?
Why won’t you let us
get close to Rowen’s body?
And now you’re right beside him?
Okay.
We lied.
We’re not Wizardly fans.
We're detectives hired to investigate
the murders of your two founders.
And now, three.
Hershey, did you bring your thing?
Gotcha!
No one gets out, everyone!
Please stay calm until the police arrive.
I’ll call the cops.
- How? We never even got close to him.
- How did this happen?
You saw the distance
between us and him, right?
There's no need
for any close physical contact.
All you need
is a cleverly disguised contraption
that can shoot this needle.
Something that won’t raise suspicion.
Like this wand…
it could also be hiding a blowgun.
No one would suspect
that this fake wand can kill.
Correct!
Now it's the part where we apply
the process of elimination.
You were on the stage with Rowen,
a few steps away from him.
He's an easy target.
But the puncture mark
is on the right side of his neck.
Helios is on his left side
while Lucius is kneeling.
So if he’s the one who did it,
we’ll know immediately.
Maybe it's someone from the crowd,
someone who's a meter
or two away from Rowen,
standing within the range
needed to shoot
the poison-laced needle at the victim.
And among them,
who is smart enough to modify the wand
into a murder weapon?
Who among them
appeared in the CCTV footage?
Leona?
Hey! Is there a problem?
I think something’s wrong with the wire.
Don’t worry, I’ll fix it later.
You.
You're in the perfect position…
to shoot at the victim.
Do you mind if Hershey
inspects your wand?
This will instantly prove your innocence.
You shouldn’t have gotten
involved in this.
But I couldn’t have done this
without them!
Those four...
are the reason Emma died!
They were the first to kill!
Those four...
the idea to start the Wizardly fan club
didn’t come from them.
It came from Emma.
They stole her idea,
made it look like it was theirs,
and then banned her from joining.
They were just going to use Emma's idea
to scam money from membership fees
and Wizardly item sales.
She tried to defend herself.
She insisted they stole her idea,
but those four made her look like a liar.
And then she was bullied
by the Fellowship’s die-hard members
like a cult!
Emma’s mental health deteriorated
until she finally ended her own life.
I transferred to Chivalry
just to join the Fellowship.
I promised I would get revenge
on those guys.
I won’t stop until the same thing
that happened to Emma happens to them.
I’d rather be gone than end up in prison!
I’ve avenged my friend…
My only friend!
Leona, don't!
Stupere!
Oh, my gosh.
Don't worry,
"Stupere" is just a voice command
that can generate high power voltage
with low amperage charge.
Let's go, man.
Come on. Move.
It was her!
She’s the one who killed!
Guys, thank you for your help.
It’s sad, that all this time,
the person closest to me at school
was the killer.
What a waste of genius.
But Helios and some Fellowship officers
are still being investigated
for corruption on high registration fees
and overpricing substandard items.
If they hadn’t deceived Emma,
this wouldn’t have happened.
Loki, Lori,
I hope to see you again.
But under better circumstances, I hope.
- Be careful, Herschel.
- Thank you.
Thank you, Hershey.
The founders were wrong
in what they did to Leona’s friend.
But killing is even more wrong.
Stealing ideas and deceiving others
brings nothing good.
But revenge brings even less good.
Right?
Yeah.
When did you find out
Leona was the culprit?
Was it at the party?
In their lab,
right after I realized that the killer
had concealed the murder weapon
into an object that would not raise
any suspicions.
Only her and Herschel
could make a weapon like that.
And Herschel isn’t in the footage,
and he has a strong alibi.
So, it only leaves to...
Leona.
But why didn’t you tell me right away?
If we were to accuse an innocent
looking girl who was kind to us...
surely, you would be affected.
And I needed you to act naturally,
or she would suspect
that we were on to something.
I still can’t believe it.
It’s such a shame.
Is there a problem?
Somebody broke into our unit.
What?
Before leaving, I put this
between the door and its frame.
If anyone opened the door,
this piece of paper
would have fallen to the floor.
Which means...
someone was inside before us.
Were we robbed?
Shit!
Where is it?
Shit.
It doesn’t look like
any of my things were touched.
My laptop is gone.
The one containing Pandora’s box.
Did someone break into your apartment?
Do you have any clues about who did it?
Tita Martha said she didn’t notice
anyone suspicious entering the apartment.
We also asked the tenants
in the other units,
but they didn’t notice
anything unusual either.
There are no CCTV cameras
on each floor either.
So until now,
we still don’t have a clue on who did this
and what they looked like.
And only Loki’s laptop was taken?
The one who took it
definitely knew its contents.
Wait, what was in it?
Well, let’s just say,
that the laptop contains files
that Loki could use in the future
to turn the situation in his favor.
But anyway,
I think Loki already has a plan for that.
Lori, on a different note,
Saint Barths’ cultural fest is coming up.
And I talked to Lionel before I left.
He said we’re welcome to go if we want.
Do you want?
Lori, look...
if you don't like, you don’t have to go.
There’s still a long week
before the event.
Think about it.
Okay. I'll let you know.
If there’s anything I can do
to ease your negative feelings
about our school,
I’ll do it.
If only I had a magic wand
and could cast a spell,
I’d do it.
“Quod Erat Demonstrandum.”
"Which was to be demonstrated."
You can Google what that means.
Because it’s in Latin,
it sounds like an ancient spell.
It feels like there’s something magical
whenever a case gets solved.
Loki?
Is your suspension lifted now?
I wouldn't be here
if it wasn't the case.
Oh, Jamie, meet our newest member,
Lorelei's childhood friend..
Al...
Alexander.
Alistair!
Nice meeting you!
OMG!
This is so exciting, there are four
of us in the Q.E.D. Club now!
You know what,
we should hold a party
to celebrate Loki’s return.
And it’s also a welcome party
for Alistair.
Right?
Instead of holding a party,
we must focus on solving cases.
Once the students find out
the Q.E.D. Club is back,
our clients will come rushing in.
And we should be ready.
Come on, Loki! It’s just this once, please?
You know what,
let’s just enjoy your return.
We should have some fun!
- Loki, please.
- Careful.
Her facial expression changed
when we entered the room.
She gave me a nasty look,
but when she introduced herself,
she was all smiles.
You know, we’re complete.
We’re only complete now.
There's more to her than meets the eye.
Just be careful, okay?
Let's also welcome Alistair.
Please.
Okay. Fine!
Let’s have it your way.
Just don't ask me to buy
you food and drinks,
since it’s your idea to have the party.
No problem! We got that.
What should we order?
And just when we though that finally
we had a reason to celebrate
our small wins...
we suddenly found out that the mystery
still hadn't been solved.
That man…
whatever his real name is...
he’s the one behind.
Why is M doing this?
This Moriarty likes to play games.
He’s everywhere.
He's got eyes and ears, everywhere.
You don’t know
what the Q.E.D. Club means to me.
I’m able to help people
by bringing bad people to justice.
Even if it’s hard,
I’ll fight for this club.
We need to stand together
and fight for this.
And strive to uncover the truth.
I’m Stein Alberts.
I am Moriarty.
No one can stop us.
The game has just begun.
Moriarty is back.