[Never-Ending Summer]
[Episode 24]
What kind of medicine are you taking?
Is this why you asked me to come?
What else?
It couldn't be because I love you.
♪ People ask me how to heal ♪
♪ But what's the point
of questioning the leaving? ♪
♪ Naiveness is always used
in the wrong place ♪
♪ Sadly, I didn't notice anything ♪
♪ The panic in your steps ♪
♪ Is the symphony named betrayal ♪
♪ Your silent answer ♪
♪ Is the confusion
that pushed me to the valley bottom ♪
Do you think
this makes us even?
♪ Me and myself ♪
♪ The unsettled self ♪
♪ Dancing at night ♪
♪ I want to calm my broken heart ♪
♪ Looking at myself ♪
♪ With those traces of being teased ♪
♪ I want to show my love
but I always step on the glass ♪
♪ If promises can't be broken ♪
♪ If true love can't be abandoned ♪
♪ I'm the only one left to heal myself ♪
♪ People ask me how to heal ♪
♪ But what's the use of waking up the one
who pretends to be drunk? ♪
♪ Expectation are always used
on the wrong occasions ♪
♪ Sadly, I didn't reject anything ♪
♪ The panic in your steps ♪
♪ Is the symphony named betrayal ♪
♪ Your silent answer ♪
♪ Is the confusion
that pushed me to the valley bottom ♪
♪ Me and myself ♪
♪ The unsettled self ♪
♪ Dancing at night ♪
♪ I want to calm my broken heart ♪
♪ Looking at myself ♪
♪ With those traces of being teased ♪
♪ I want to show my love
but I always step on the glass ♪
♪ If promises can't be broken ♪
♪ If true love can't be abandoned ♪
♪ I'm the only one left to heal myself ♪
Breakfast is ready.
Today is the kickoff meeting
for the Lan Yue Phase II project.
It is also your first official day
as the director's special assistant.
There's about...
30 minutes to go.
I'll go change.
Today
marks the official launch
of Phase II of the Lan Yue Resort,
Lan Yue Cloud Dwelling Secret Realm.
For the company, this project
is a vital step in our strategic layout
and a benchmark key project.
I know that
over the past few months,
from planning to bidding,
you have all overcome many challenges.
On behalf of Lan Yue,
I extend my sincere gratitude
to everyone involved in the project,
Hello, miss.
How can I help you?
It's my first day here.
I haven't got my badge yet.
Then please register first.
[Lan Yue Group]
I'll look up your name.
What's your name?
Zhou Wan.
Which Zhou?
The Zhou as in Zhou, Wu, Zheng, Wang.
And Wan?
Jun, why isn't the search working?
I don't know either.
I just started too.
Please wait a moment.
In the future,
we will be driven by innovation
and guided by customer needs.
Let's move forward hand in hand
and step into this journey full of
opportunities and challenges together.
Great, great, great.
[Cloud Dwelling Secret Realm]
[Phase II Resort of Lan Yue Group]
Next, please allow me
to introduce to you
the core members of
our Phase II project team.
Sorry, sorry.
I'm so sorry I'm late.
Come.
First up
is someone we are all very familiar with,
[Cloud Dwelling Secret Realm]
[Phase II Resort of Lan Yue Group]
our Project Director,
Lu Xixiao, Mr. Lu Jr.
Deputy Project Director
and Special Assistant to the Director,
Zhou Wan.
[Cloud Dwelling Secret Realm]
[Phase II Resort of Lan Yue Group]
Hello everyone, I am Zhou Wan.
Project engineering manager, Cheng Feng.
Sorry to interrupt.
Ms. Qilan.
To facilitate communication
between the Phase II project team
and headquarters,
the board of directors has decided,
and in accordance
with company regulations,
to appoint
Strategic Director, Mr. Jiang Yan,
to join the Phase II project.
Let's hear it!
Director Jiang
graduated from the Architecture Department
of Huaqing University.
He has worked at
several well-known
real estate groups in the industry.
I believe his addition
will definitely make our Phase II project
even stronger.
Great!
Looking forward to working with you.
Likewise.
Great!
Please come in.
I'm glad to be colleagues with you.
I had no idea
you'd join the Phase II project team.
You...
Mr. Lu made a last-minute decision.
I'm just following orders.
Then I'll rely on
your guidance from now on,
Director Jiang.
Want to go home together after work?
I still have a lot to do.
You go ahead when you get off work.
It's fine. I'll wait for you.
Riding with me
is better than taking a cab.
Jiang Yan.
Lately,
I'm not going home.
Not going home? What do you mean?
Zhou Wan.
Excuse me.
What's wrong, Director Lu?
Are you that free?
If you're that free,
go make me a cup of coffee.
Yes, Director Lu.
What's the background
of this Director Jiang?
He was handpicked by Mr. Lu
to join Lan Yue.
Don't you get the connection?
I don't get it.
Mr. Lu Jr.
is Mr. Lu's son.
And Ms. Qilan trusts Mr. Lu Jr.
But Director Jiang is on Mr. Lu's side.
What kind of complex
family business drama is this?
It's normal you don't get it.
It's very complicated.
Let me tell you.
That Zhou Wan is a tough one.
She used to be
the top star at Boxing Construction.
She competed fiercely
with Dingshang.
Now she's at Dingshang,
clinging to the person in charge,
and even became the deputy director.
Her tricks are really something.
Oh my.
Are you going to work or not?
What are you talking about?
Do you all have nothing to do?
Come on, you.
They were chatting in here,
and you just stood there listening?
After so many years in the workplace,
I stopped caring a long time ago.
They don't pay my salary.
Why bother with them?
Director Lu, your coffee.
What do you want to eat?
I'll cook for you.
Anything.
I don't know how to cook "anything".
Will you cook
whatever I want to eat?
All right then.
I want Buddha Jumps Over the Wall,
Dongpo pork,
Wellington steak,
Spanish paella,
and beef bourguignon.
Just make any of them for me to try.
I'm sorry.
I'm out of groceries.
You can only have noodles today.
Next time I go to the supermarket
and buy some ingredients,
I'll make you a big meal.
Wellington steak,
Buddha Jumps Over the Wall, whatever.
It's all in here.
Eat up.
Where are the chopsticks?
Unwashed chopsticks.
Wait.
Let me add some spoiled scallions for you.
I guarantee it tastes awful.
You think I don't dare to eat it?
Then eat it.
I will.
It doesn't taste good.
I told you it would taste awful.
What happened to your hand?
From cooking for you.
It burned me.
When I was working part-time in college,
I never got burned.
But I ended up getting hurt here.
You worked part-time?
Who would support me if I didn't?
Eat it.
Who did you learn this from?
I told you, at a noodle shop.
I just help out at the noodle shop,
cleaning up and stuff.
I also tutor occasionally.
Move over.
Move over, I'll do it.
Go eat.
I'll do it.
-I can’t choke you if you don’t eat.
-That's nowhere near enough noodles.
And it tastes terrible.
Move over.
Fine, wash them if you want.
You can wash the dishes from now on.
You worked part-time
with these cooking skills?
How was that place
supposed to stay in business?
The restaurant I worked at in college
was the most popular noodle shop.
Before you went there, right?
Sit.
♪ I'mma take a frozen heart ♪
♪ Someone's gonna make it ♪
♪ In the building of my broken part ♪
♪ Someone's gonna fix it ♪
♪ I'm the only one guy
with the ten things crime ♪
♪ I deserve a sanction in my mind ♪
♪ Nescience doesn't mean ♪
♪ That I can fly ♪
♪ But I never seem to close ♪
♪ The dormer lock ♪
♪ Tell you starts were above the floor ♪
Wan, I have an emergency.
Wan.
What's wrong, Meng?
Your house suddenly lost all power.
I am currently experiencing
primitive candlelight nightlife.
That building is too old.
Don't worry.
Check and see if it's
an issue with the circuit breaker.
No, the power switch hasn't tripped.
Maybe the wiring is aging.
In that case, Meng,
you can't use electricity anymore.
It's too dangerous.
Then how long will it take to fix?
We'll have to inspect everything first,
then reinstall it.
I don't think it can be solved
anytime soon.
How about this?
I'll let you use my employee discount
at our group's hotels.
No.
Your employee discount
only has a quota of a few thousand.
I won't use it.
Keep it for yourself.
I have a place to stay.
Well...
Um, do you have
any extra candles?
I can't find any.
I'm out of candles too.
I have to go buy some.
It's fine. Forget it.
I'll figure something out.
Then WeChat me anytime.
Bye.
Okay, bye.
Meng.
Lu Xixiao?
He's asleep.
Who is it?
What time is it?
Look at the time when you call.
Calling at this hour.
So noisy.
How can I sleep?
You touched my hand
while I was asleep.
How did...
-You pretended to be asleep.
Why?
You called me here
just to make me a maid?
You owe me. You deserve it.
Apply the medicine yourself next time.
I'm going to walk the dog.
Are you coming?
Suit yourself.
I've been walking him myself for years.
Let's go, Xiaoliu.
I'll just keep walking him myself.
I walk him in the morning,
in the afternoon,
and at midnight. Let's go.
Wait for me.
How can a puppy walk a puppy?
Xiaoliu.
Do you have something to say?
Stop.
It said stop.
Xiaoliu.
Sit.
Bark.
It doesn't listen to you at all.
It has something to say.
It's just too shy to say it now.
What?
It says it's thirsty
and wants some milk.
Yes, sir.
Good dog, Xiaoliu.
It can't walk anymore.
I can't walk anymore either.
Wait.
Is this how you take care of Xiaoliu?
What do you mean by that?
What if it falls off later?
Do you see it falling off?
Are you really going to ride home?
Yeah.
Who let you work here?
Working is not allowed at home.
Go warm up some milk.
Okay.
Drink less, Xiaoliu.
You can only drink a little.
Where's mine?
You can drink with it.
Go to sleep.
I want to work here.
I want to sleep here.
Then I'll go somewhere else.
No.
Stay here.
Time to sleep.
You're impossible.
Didn't I tell you
when you agents come to see the house,
you have to let me know?
And you didn't even close the door.
Why are you here?
This is my house.
Why do you think I'm here?
How is it your house again?
I paid half of the down payment.
By the way.
Aren't you at your boss's beck and call?
Is there no signal at home?
How did you get kicked out?
Didn't you say you'd sell the house
and never see me again?
Why did you come back?
None of your business.
I want to stay in the bedroom.
Go ahead.
If you don't mind
the hard tiles, go ahead.
What are you mumbling about?
I don't understand.
If you take the blanket inside,
where will I sleep?
Sleep wherever you want.
Can you be reasonable,
Gu Meng?
Wan.
Here is the compiled list
of all the qualified
enterprises.
Including culture and tourism groups,
commercial groups,
and IP operation groups
we can work with.
Have you done the background checks?
Yes.
All enterprises on the list
have no issues with their qualifications
or public reputation.
And there are no
commercial disputes or legal issues.
It seems that
only Xinghai Entertainment
is more suitable.
And they seem to have
cooperated with Lan Yue before.
Mind if I join you?
Of course not.
You are the Strategic Director
sent by the headquarters.
We also need
your professional advice.
Cooperating with comprehensive IP
operation enterprises
is indeed the safest model.
They have strong
brand premium capabilities.
Their IPs each
come with their own traffic.
I participated in
the Sky Isle Lake Resort project before.
Because it introduced
the Dream Star Domain IP,
the annual foot traffic
increased by 23%.
But have you thought about
how difficult it is to negotiate
a partnership with them?
If we try to
negotiate a partnership now,
we'd have to haggle
for a very, very long time.
Not to mention we have to pay
the royalty fees.
The bulk of the profits
will be taken by them.
How are they
supposed to make a living?
Director Jiang, you only know how to
use past cases
that cannot be 100% replicated
as examples.
How about this?
Let's prepare both plans.
If cooperation with large
comprehensive operation enterprises
fails,
we can also choose
multiple professional
intellectual property enterprises
for sub-item cooperation.
Exactly.
We can target different business formats,
choose the best partners,
and bid by sub-item.
Let's take a break first.
I'll go make some coffee for everyone.
-Okay. Thank you, Wan.
-Thank you.
Good job.
Take a break.
Why are you speaking up for him?
What do you mean?
We're at the company.
I was just talking about the matter.
What did I do wrong?
I was also just talking about the matter.
I came to remind you.
You'd better clearly remember
your job responsibilities.
Don't do this at the office.
What did I do?
Clumsy.
-Wait.
-Did you burn yourself?
It's hot.
-Stop wiping me.
-Are you okay?
-Did you burn your hand?
-Wait.
Your clothes are wet.
What are you going to do?
It's fine. I have a spare.
Excuse me.
Director Lu.
Go wash your hands if they are dirty.
Don't bother yourself.
My special assistant wiped them for me.
Zhou Wan.
Are you free this afternoon?
What is it?
My mom talks about you a lot.
Would you like to go
see her with me?
It has indeed been many years
since I saw your mom.
-But I still have some...
-You haven’t seen each other for years.
My mom misses you very much.
And today is her birthday.
How about we get off work early
and go see her together?
See you
in the underground garage after work!
Did you hear me?
What's wrong?
Who is he yelling at?
I don't know.
I have plans tonight.
I won't go back with you.
Don't forget what you are supposed to do.
Don't forget.
What are you two looking at?
What's so interesting?
Haven't you seen someone on the phone?
I'm going with Jiang Yan...
I'll be back early.
What about my dinner?
Am I not going to have dinner?
Where should I have dinner?
Before I moved in,
did you starve?
Wait for me to get home and cook.
All right.
I'll wait for you at home then.
You have the address, right?
Don't go to the wrong place.
All right.
[Wellness Center]
Hello, visitors.
Please register here.
I'm at the supermarket.
What should I buy?
Sorry, sorry.
It's fine.
Mom.
Yan.
Is this your classmate?
Yes.
You could've told me
your classmate was coming.
Hello.
Hello, Ms. Jiang.
You even brought me a gift.
Ms. Jiang, please sit.
Yan doesn't have many friends.
I'm busy with work.
Please spend more time
with him when you're free.
He is a very
filial and sensible child.
Every time he visits me,
he brings me a lot of delicious food.
When he's busy with his studies,
he lets Hei keep me company.
We are good friends now.
When did Ms. Jiang
get diagnosed with
Alzheimer's?
Just in the past two years,
she suddenly became forgetful
and sometimes gets her memories mixed up.
I took her to many hospitals,
but nothing helped.
However,
at least she's happy now.
Compared to when she was younger,
she is much more relaxed.
So is this the reason
you decided to return to Pingchuan?
That's part of the reason.
My mom doesn't want to leave Pingchuan.
I can spend more time
with her now that I'm back.
-Ms. Jiang, you want the cake?
-Be careful.
Mom, be careful.
My son bought this cake.
Here, have some.
Thank you so much. Happy birthday.
Come, have a seat.
Happy birthday.
Thank you. Please take a seat.
Be happy, sis.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
Which light soy sauce should I buy?
The one with zero additives.
This cake has zero additives.
It's really delicious.
We haven't lit the candles yet.
Such a filial and good son.
I'm jealous.
[Organic green vegetables]
[Prepped Vegetables] [Sprouts]
What vegetables should I buy?
Buy whatever you want to eat.
Organic vegetables will do.
Let me help.
Okay.
Let's sing...
-"Happy Birthday" together.
-Come on.
-Okay.
What's the difference
between free-range eggs
and battery eggs?
Happy birthday to you.
How are things
with Lu Xixiao?
Same as always.
Did Lu Xixiao help you get into Lan Yue?
Is it Lu Xixiao?
Is he trying to reach you
about something urgent?
It's nothing important.
Why did you join Lan Yue?
I have my own reasons.
If you don't want to say,
I won't force you.
But I hope
when you run into difficulties,
you can think of me.
Whatever Lu Xixiao can do for you,
I can do too.
Jiang Yan.
I am very grateful to you.
But some things
aren't meant to be
shared or faced together,
even between friends.
What about Lu Xixiao?
He's no exception.
Zhou Wan.