(Respect copyright)
ظآزMemories hold you back
from fulfilling your dreamsظآز
ظآزOnly by moving forward
can you find reunionظآز
ظآزEndings only mark new routesظآز
ظآزIt's all part of the sceneryظآز
ظآزTo the horizon's callظآز
ظآزYour journey hasn't startedظآز
ظآزTowards mountains,
chase the stars brightظآز
ظآزLet time embrace you
and wash away the pastظآز
ظآزPut every twist behind youظآز
ظآزDrift leisurely through timeظآز
ظآزMake headway against the windظآز
ظآزLet mountains bow to your paceظآز
ظآزRush towards a life without regretظآز
ظآزLet your nature burst freeظآز
=The First Jasmine=
=Episode 30=
Prince Ding, I wish
to make a deal with you.
A deal?
Yes.
But I need you to swear an oath
that as long as you live,
you must ensure
my son Tianyang's safety.
The Empress Dowager did not implicate
your family out of regard for old ties.
I was in power for many years,
and countless were defeated by me.
Do you think my signed confession
will settle this for good?
No.
The great calamity of my Zhou family
of Huaixi has just begun.
So my son Tianyang cannot die.
Why should I help you?
Because I have a huge secret
to tell you.
Back then, your elder brother
and the Heiyun Cavalry were convicted
of treason for entering
the capital without an edict.
But it has been proven
that the edict did exist.
And you indeed used
that edict to bring me down.
Aren't you curious
exactly who
tricked the late emperor's edict
from your brother?
Of course it was you
who instigated Dowager Consort Qin
to trick away the edict.
Your brother was no ordinary man.
He knew it was his lifeline.
Why would he just hand it
to me or Qin Zheng?
Someone else tricked the edict from him.
That person gained
your brother's complete trust.
They took the edict
and hid it immediately.
Then they watched as your brother
was framed and executed
and as Heiyun Cavalry crumbled
and suffered heavy casualties.
So?
Don't you want to know
who that person was?
(Vast as the Earth)
Empress Dowager,
Zhou Jing has confessed.
He met with Prince Ding today
and then signed
and marked his confession.
What did he say?
He asked to clear the room.
No one else was present
but a confidant of Prince Ding.
There is one more thing.
Zhou Tianyang is still kneeling
outside the palace.
It has been two days already.
Father.
Tianyang,
why are you here?
I... I came to see you, Father.
How are you?
Have they treated you badly? Have you...
Didn't I tell you to go back to Lingnan?
Why are you still in the capital?
You're in danger. How can I just leave?
Staying here won't help.
Who says? Look.
I knelt outside the palace for two days,
begging for the Empress Dowager's mercy.
Today, Eunuch Shunxi
personally gave me this.
I've checked. Inside are fine wine
and delicious food.
Father, the Empress Dowager
still cares about you deep down.
At the next interrogation,
be sure to be honest
and confess voluntarily.
Don't resist.
Perhaps out of old sentiment
and your merits, the Empress Dowager
will be pleased and pardon you.
Father, what's wrong?
Are you feeling unwell?
No.
That's good.
Tianyang, listen to me.
My affairs involve many people.
There won't be a quick resolution.
Your mom is in poor health.
If she knows this,
she might not survive it.
Hurry back to Lingnan
and take good care of her.
It's more useful than staying
in the capital, understand?
Father, what about you then?
Tianyang,
you've been spoiled by your mom
since childhood.
Your nature is simple.
It's my fault for not teaching you well.
That's not true.
In the past, I always thought
that with me protecting you,
it wouldn't matter
even if you were unruly all your life.
But from now on...
Let's not talk about this, Father.
We haven't reached
the end of our rope yet.
I... I wrote to Qin Zheng.
The Empress Dowager trusts her most.
She can surely save you once she's back.
Enough.
Time's up. You should leave.
Listen to me.
I will definitely get you out of here.
When you get out,
let's go back to Lingnan
and live together, alright?
I've grown up.
I can take good care of you and Mom.
Then our family of three
will be happy together, alright?
- Go!
- Alright.
- Father.
- Hurry!
Father! Father!
Wait for me. Just wait!
Let's go.
- I will.
- Wait for me!
Your Majesty, Marquis Muyang has died.
Your Highness, did you make
this straw doll?
It's getting late.
Why not rest early?
Don't wait any longer.
What time is it now?
A quarter past the Zi hour.
- Li!
- Ms. Wen.
Li!
What's the rush? What happened?
Yao... Yao sent word that...
He said... He said...
Zhou Jing is dead!
He's dead.
Li, our revenge is fulfilled.
Li, he's dead. He's dead.
It's over!
Yes, it's over.
It's over.
Your Highness hasn't returned yet?
Your Highness,
now that Marquis Muyang is dead,
your household, the Heiyun Cavalry,
and the late Prince Ding's injustice
will soon be revealed to the world.
The wrongs will be righted,
and evil will be purged.
Congratulations, Your Highness.
Your Highness bore it for eight years.
I know best the bitterness of it all.
From now on, you and we can all
truly live for ourselves.
On this joyous day,
I originally wished
to have a good drink with you.
But it's getting late.
Your Highness should go home now.
After all, Her Highness
has suffered a lot this time,
enduring so much fear and worry.
It hasn't been easy.
Now that the matter has settled...
Revenue Clerk Gu.
You and Her Highness will surely
live in harmony from now on
and enjoy a peaceful and stable life.
Revenue Clerk Gu!
Revenue Clerk Gu,
it's getting late.
Why don't you go back first?
Although Marquis Muyang has fallen,
Imperial Court of Judicial Review
isn't clean yet.
Tomorrow will be a busy day.
You have a fair point.
Then, Your Highness,
I must have a good drink with you
some other day.
You mustn't refuse me then.
I take my leave.
Your Highness,
shall we return?
I'll go get the carriage.
Your Highness, the carriage is ready.
Your Highness?
Your Highness!
Physician, how is he?
Let's talk outside.
(If it weren't for her,)
your brother could have stalled
until Duke Hua's return.
Who?
Xu Wanzhou of Lishan Academy.
Say that again.
The one who tricked the edict
from your brother Mo Xiuwen,
causing his tragic death
and bringing unjust blame upon
the Heiyun Cavalry and your household,
was none other than your wife's mother,
Xu Wanzhou.
Just ramblings of a dying man.
You know well whether
it's ramblings or not.
In such a critical situation back then,
aside from a Lishan Academy member,
who else could have made him willingly
hand over that life-saving edict?
Your brother
probably even regarded her
as a great savior.
But that's understandable.
After all, Lishan Academy
is a top institution of letters
and has always stayed
out of factional strife.
Its status is transcendent.
If it'd been me,
I would've probably
been fooled by her as well.
What?
Has your wife
never told you
a single one of these things?
I originally thought
you were magnanimous.
It turns out you had no idea at all.
Ever since your wife married
into your household,
you must have been
living quite comfortably.
Newly wed and deeply in love.
Even your crippled legs
of many years were healed.
Have you never thought?
Did she truly want to marry you?
Or was it out of guilt,
wanting to compensate you?
Prince Ding, you are so astute.
Have you never taken a good look
at your other half?
Is the look in her eyes
genuine love or guilt?
Shut up!
After all, her mother
owes your family a life.
- Shut up!
- And 30,000 lives of Heiyun Cavalry!
Just wait for your doom.
(Yao, have I ever told you?)
This time down the mountain,
I have so many things to do.
What things?
I want to eat lots of good food.
I want to take back my mom's shop.
I also want to find my seniors.
And...
And help that senior chop down the tree.
Already done.
And help you stand up
and make you live happily.
ظآزWhy do you panicظآز
ظآزFor no reason,
you pushed me away and left meظآز
ظآزAfraid we might start againظآز
ظآزChanging many things, right or wrongظآز
ظآزFate is blurred and bewilderingظآز
They stole a very important item
from my mom.
Have you found the item now?
I have some leads.
ظآزAmidst life's ups and downs,
turns and twistsظآز
ظآزLove has never strayed awayظآز
ظآزThroughout this lifetimeظآز
ظآزIn the end, we're together againظآز
ظآزCountless trials and pleadings,
right or wrongظآز
ظآزTry to make this love quietظآز
ظآزBut we fight backظآز
Your Highness,
you haven't slept all night?
His Highness hasn't returned?
Not yet.
Didn't they say Marquis Muyang
committed suicide in prison?
With such a big event,
he must have been busy.
Even when he was busy before,
he would send someone to inform me.
Well, maybe he was just too busy
and never got to it.
Is that so?
It must be.
That makes sense.
Jin, you're back.
ظآزThe eyes are still clearظآز
ظآزNone better than you,
and none better than meظآز
His Highness hasn't come back?
No, His Highness
has official business to attend to.
He sent me back for some things.
Why do you smell
so strongly of medicine?
Do I? I don't smell it.
Did His Highness say
when he would return?
No.
Then I'll go find him.
Your Highness,
you'd better wait in the mansion.
When His Highness is due back,
he will come back.
You...
(If you are around, I can be braver.)
Then I'll accompany you.
It's a deal then.
No matter what path you take,
smooth or thorny,
(I'll be with you.)
(You won't be alone anymore.)
(I'll always be with you.)
ظآزAmidst life's ups and downs,
turns and twistsظآز
ظآزLove has never strayed awayظآز
ظآزThroughout this lifetimeظآز
ظآزIn the end, we're together againظآز
ظآزCountless trials and pleadings,
right or wrongظآز
ظآزTry to make this love quietظآز
ظآزBut we fight backظآز
(But Qingshuang
has always been with me.)
I will always be with you, alright?
Alright.
ظآزSilently, we turn pain into joyظآز
ظآزYou reach out and pull meظآز
ظآزAnd I gently touchظآز
ظآزSmooth out the creasesظآز
ظآزSo we can tightly fit togetherظآز
ظآزWithout you, there's no meظآز
ظآزPassing by the worldظآز
ظآزPart of my broken selfظآز
ظآزFinds our places in an embraceظآز
ظآزFulfilling our wishesظآز
ظآزLovers remain calm and composedظآز
ظآزNone better than you,
and none better than meظآز
ظآزLove blooms at every spring and sunsetظآز
(To the Chancellery:
By Heaven's Mandate for the sovereign.)
(Marquis Muyang Zhou Jing
formed cliques for personal gain,)
(stole military weapons,
colluded with Cangbei,)
(betrayed the country,)
(and even concealed
the late emperor's edict,)
(causing loyalists to be wronged
and the nation to be in turmoil.)
(His crimes are heinous
and too numerous to record.)
(He committed suicide out of fear,
bringing his own ruin.)
(Considering that he had
some minor merits carried on,)
(all those who were unaware,
not involved, and not accomplices)
(are exempt from collective punishment.)
Their estates shall be seized,
(Changxing Gate)
titles revoked, and stripped of rank.
They shall be reduced to commoners,
forever disgraced
and barred from office.
(The Heiyun Cavalry served
with loyalty and valor,)
(earning great battle honors.)
(They're now fully restored
in reputation.)
The late Prince Ding, Mo Xiuwen,
diligently performed
his duties with utmost loyalty.
(Jingzhao Prefecture)
His title's restored to honor his valor.
Your Highness.
What is it?
Ms. Wen says
it will be the death anniversary
of Master Xiuwen in two days.
She wants to visit the grave
and asks if you'd like to go too.
The day after tomorrow?
Yes.
Tell her that I will go.
Also, Ms. Wen asks
when Your Highness will return home.
No matter how busy
the official duties are,
you can't just not come home.
Her Highness has been waiting
for you for days
and has lost her appetite.
She has lost much weight.
Tell Ms. Wen not to worry.
I'll come back once I'm done.
Yes.
(Tomb of Lord Mo Xiuwen)
Xiuwen,
we've come to see you.
And we've brought you good news.
That edict has been found.
Our household and the Heiyun Cavalry
have been cleared in reputation.
And Zhou Jing is dead.
Good and evil always meet their due.
But it took too long for that to happen.
You've been down there
for so many years.
You must have been waiting anxiously.
The soldiers of the Heiyun Cavalry
have also been cleared of their charges.
Those still in the army
have been restored to their posts.
Those who lost their positions
have received silver as compensation.
For the deceased, their families
can report to the authorities.
The court will distribute compensation
to their parents, wives, and children.
Mom,
Father has been exonerated.
Why are you still unhappy?
I'm not unhappy.
But you keep shedding tears.
One can cry even when they're happy.
I just feel that
eight years is too long,
and things have changed so much.
Some people can wait and see it.
And some
will never be able to see it.
Wuyou, go with Jin and Steward Cui
to fetch some water
from the nearby stream.
- Yes.
Let's go.
This matter can be
considered settled, right?
Yao?
Did you have a fight with Li?
She has been looking
very unwell these past few days.
She eats very little
and has lost a lot of weight.
She has no close family
of her own by her side.
She's been through so much pain
and suffering lately.
Please don't mistreat her.
I understand.
When I first married your brother,
I was still young.
He was always away with the army.
We hardly saw each other
a few times a year.
He was dull and didn't like to talk.
At that time, I really didn't like him.
And I was certain
he didn't care about me either.
Several times I went home
and cried to my mother,
wanting to divorce.
Then later, he got into trouble.
From imprisonment to execution,
it was only a short two months.
It felt like a dream.
Before I could realize, he was gone.
After he died,
I received a letter from him.
When I opened it,
I found a letter of divorce.
The last thing that clumsy-tongued man
wanted to say to me
was to divorce me.
Xiuwen didn't want to implicate you.
Yes, and that's when I realized
that he truly cared for me.
Unfortunately,
it was too late.
Yao,
this is all there is
for your brother and me.
But you and Li are still young.
Don't be like us.
Whatever you have to say, say it.
Don't wait until she is gone
to cherish her.
(Fine Wine)
My lady, you're here.
Yes.
Your requested seat
from last time is ready for you.
You're here for the story too?
Yes.
You're here. Hurry.
My lady, your food.
Just in time.
Feel free to call me.
Your Highness, please eat something.
You haven't been
eating properly these days.
Your Highness, why exactly
did we come here today?
To listen to a story.
Coming!
You are seriously carefree.
His Highness hasn't returned
for several days.
You're still in the mood for a story?
Last time we left off,
Madam Liu forced Liu Sanlang
to divorce Lady Meng.
A loving young couple
was forced to part.
It was heart-wrenching.
Lady Meng returned to her maiden home.
But her snobbish elder brother
forced her to remarry a wealthy man
from the neighboring village.
With no way out, Lady Meng
asked a neighbor
to send a letter to Liu Sanlang.
Hearing the news,
Liu Sanlang couldn't stand it
and went to rescue her at once.
Just then,
Madam Liu stopped him
and told him
the cause of his father's death.
Only then did Liu Sanlang learn
that his beloved wife,
whom he cherished like a treasure,
was actually the younger sister
of his father's murderer.
He stood frozen on the spot,
and his feet could no longer
step out of the gate.
(Liu Sanlang's father died
in corv├رe labor,)
and Lady Meng's brother
was the overseer at that time.
That was the root of it.
And Liu Sanlang is a filial son,
unable to defy his mother.
There was no chance.
On the day of the wedding,
Lady Meng waited in vain
for Liu Sanlang.
She only saw the golden carriage
and jade wheels,
a bridal procession
with red silk and brocade,
coming in a grand display.
Lady Meng's heart was broken.
She knew their vows had come to nothing.
So she removed her hairpin,
gathered her skirt,
and jumped into the river.
Alas, what a tragedy.
She died?
When the news of Lady Meng's death came,
Liu Sanlang felt
as if struck by lightning
and vomited blood.
He stumbled to the pavilion
where they had parted
and shouted at the sky.
He cursed fate for toying with them,
preventing lovers from staying together,
and hated himself
for breaking their vows,
causing his wife's death.
So he hung a white silk cloth
from the pavilion
and ended his life.
Truly a pair of ill-fated lovers.
As the saying goes,
the underworld forbids
branches to entwine;
the heavens find no trace
of paired wings' sound.
The cruelest is the heartless sky,
as two lonely graves
share the same moonlight.
(Prince Ding's Mansion)
Your Highness, you're back.
His Highness is back. He's in your room.
You all go ahead.
Yes.
Haven't you been sleeping well?
You've got dark circles.
Busy with official duties,
but it's fine.
Marquis Muyang is dead.
I know.
Before he died,
he told me some things about your mom.
I want to know if they're true.
What things?
If I ask you,
will you tell me the truth?
I will.
Back then,
was it your mom who tricked the edict
from my brother?
Yes.
But she didn't do it intentionally.
Back then, the late emperor passed away.
The Eastern Palace was burned down.
And your brother was in prison.
The one presiding over his case
was Marquis Muyang.
Your brother claimed he entered
the capital by an edict,
but he refused to produce the edict.
He was determined to wait for Duke Hua.
My mom was deceived.
She got the location
of the edict from your brother.
She wanted to save him
but ended up causing his death.
So regarding this matter,
your mom never hid it from you?
You've known all along, haven't you?
Haven't you?
Yes, I have.
Then why didn't you tell me earlier?
I was afraid you would
drive me away if I told you.
Before your brother was executed,
I went to see him on behalf of my mom.
I promised him
that Lishan Academy would clear
his, his family's,
and Heiyun Cavalry's names
and that I would heal your legs
to repay my mom's debt
and compensate you.
Repay a debt?
Compensate?
My brother was wronged for eight years.
My sister-in-law
became a widow overnight.
Wuyou lost his father at a young age.
Thirty thousand Heiyun Cavalry soldiers
followed my brother to death.
Tens of thousands of soldiers
suffered unjust accusations.
How many families were torn apart?
And how many parents
had to bury their own children?
I can't appreciate
your mother's struggles
on behalf of those people.
As for myself,
I am very grateful to you.
I thank you for healing my legs
and for giving a cripple
like me a chance to live.
You came to my side
to compensate and pay a debt.
I should be grateful to you.
That's not true.
(Preview)
Only a crazy person can see herself.
You are just too lonely.
You should let Qingshuang stay with you.
Quiet!
All of you, get to work!
Your Highness,
are you going out without breakfast?
Did you drive her away?
Did she go back to Lishan?
Prince Ding is now
the Pacification Commissioner
and granted a banner of authority.
He shall bring 50 bolts of silk,
100 taels of gold,
and a box of century-old ginseng
(Lishan Academy)
to visit Lishan on behalf of His Majesty
to demonstrate the imperial grace.
ظآزMemories hold you back
from fulfilling your dreamsظآز
ظآزOnly by moving forward
can you find reunionظآز
ظآزEndings only mark new routesظآز
ظآزIt's all part of the sceneryظآز
ظآزTo the horizon's callظآز
ظآزYour journey hasn't startedظآز
ظآزTowards mountains,
chase the stars brightظآز
ظآزBoth joy and grief
make the trip worthwhileظآز
ظآزTrying to catch up
to your own lost shadowظآز
ظآزWithin the wilds, echoes thriveظآز
ظآزClear mind leads to a clear pathظآز
ظآزBe grateful to your lossesظآز
ظآزMake your steps weightlessظآز
ظآزTowards mountains,
chase the stars brightظآز
ظآزLet time embrace you
and wash away the pastظآز
ظآزPut every twist behind you,
drift leisurely through timeظآز
ظآزMake headway against the wind,
let mountains bow to your paceظآز
ظآزRush towards a life without regretظآز
ظآزLet your nature burst freeظآز
ظآزUnbound by formظآز