In South Korea, there are undoubtedly many great chefs.
But in reality, who truly runs a business better than I do?
(The ultimate business survival show)
(The greatest restaurateurs of Korea)
(Those who prove their business skills with number)
(Those who prove their business skills with flavor)
We take reservations for 30 days in advance.
(Those who prove their business skills through customers)
(Those who prove their business skills through time)
The best restaurateurs from each field gather...
for Street Restaurant Fighter.
- I've never heard of this.
- This is amazing.
They compete through sales...
and prove their skills through business performance.
(Street Restaurant Fighter)
I cook to remember the taste of the four seasons.
I'm chef Jo Seo Hyung.
(Hipjiro Joan of Arc)
I own a restaurant called Euljiro Boseok.
There has never been a time when it wasn't fully booked.
Reservations sell out in 15 seconds.
Even the waitlist notification requests are fully booked.
It's reached a point where you can't even make a reservation.
Someone who is good at cooking can't be good at business.
Someone who's good at business can't be good at cooking.
I believe I'm in between those two extremes.
I might be good at handling...
that tightrope area.
(Jo Seo Hyung, Hipjiro Joan of Arc)
(Each participant stands in a spot...)
(marked with their keyword and signature dish.)
"Sales Gangster?"
"In 10 countries, 450 locations?"
Is it important to have many stores?
Anyone, come in quickly.
(Top-tier Japanese Cuisine)
"Top-tier Japanese Cuisine?" Who could it be?
Gosh, it's overwhelming. What's all this?
- Welcome.
- What?
I run an izakaya specializing in udon.
I'm Jung Ho Young.
If I were the customer, would I be satisfied paying this price?
I always think from this perspective.
I'll show you what it looks like when a chef goes...
beyond cooking and becomes a true business owner.
Are there just the two of us?
We're the only ones who entered so far.
(30 Million Dollars Galbi King)
"30 Million Dollars Galbi King?"
Galbi?
I'm Yang Ji Sam, working in the food service industry.
I run a galbi brand called Cheonggiwa Town.
I believe its average sales are probably number one...
among franchise brands by a significant margin.
When you ask brands about their sales,
they often include what franchise stores sell.
But I only talk about what I personally sell,
which is about 35 million dollars.
(Yang Ji Sam, 30 Million Dollars Galbi King)
(Top-tier Japanese Cuisine, 30 Million Dollars Galbi King)
(Top-tier Japanese Cuisine)
Do you make 30 million dollars in a year?
Yes.
That's very impressive.
"Gyeongsang Province Business Monster."
Gyeongsang Province Business Monster?
(Gyeongsang Province Business Monster)
I run various restaurants in Busan.
I'm Kwak Dong Hoon.
I try to develop menu items that can make...
an ordinary Korean BBQ restaurant become very popular.
I once created honeycomb pork skin,
which became a huge hit.
We became one of Busan's signature pork barbecue restaurants.
I also run a Mexican restaurant called Taco Sounds Club.
I created an izakaya called Chohissatsu,
and I still run it.
(Gwangalli, Busan)
A lot of people travel to Gwangalli.
There's a high chance that more than half...
of the itineraries include one of his restaurants.
I make sure my business concepts don't overlap.
You could call it my hobby.
I enjoy my work.
(Kwak Dong Hoon, Gyeongsang Province Business Monster)
(Busan insider)
I was hoping you wouldn't be here.
This is how I want to sell hangover soup.
This is how I want to run a meat restaurant.
As I'm blocked by a mental barrier, I can't open a restaurant.
Then I go to a restaurant for the first time,
and it's exactly what I dreamed of.
All such restaurants belong to one owner.
CEO Kwak Dong Hoon.
I don't like him.
All the successful restaurateurs are here.
Who's next?
(Michelin Couple)
No way.
Michelin one-star.
(Kim Hee Eun, Michelin Couple)
I'm Chef Kim Hee Eun, and I run Soul and Egg and Flour.
It's him.
Isn't it the Dragon King?
Yeouido Sashimi Chairman, Kim Min Seong.
(Kim Min Seong, Yeouido Sashimi Chairman)
Seoul Top Three Pasta, Shin Ga Young.
(Shin Ga Young, Seoul Top 3 Pasta)
It's a couple that makes excellent fresh pasta.
She was right next to me.
I felt a subtle sense of rivalry.
Brand Predator, Kim Ho Yoon.
(Kim Ho Yoon, Brand Predator)
(The Italian Club, Hoshiwoobo, Ice Cream Society...)
The one I'm most worried about is Chef Kim Ho Yoon.
Among chefs, he combines cooking skills...
with a strong business mindset.
How many brands does he have?
I thought that I was doomed.
Is this the right spot?
Yongridan-gil Hot Spot Maker, Kim Hoon.
(Kim Hoon, Yongridan-gil Hot Spot Maker)
He's the best at running restaurants.
I know.
Oh, my.
Annual sales of 10 million dollars, Go Seok Hyun.
(Go Seok Hyun, Sales Gangster)
Seochon's Icon, Lee Jae Hoon.
(Lee Jae Hoon, Seochon's Icon)
Global Cuisine Master, Choi Sang Hyun.
(Choi Sang Hyun, Global Cuisine Master)
Isn't he the chef at Deepin?
She makes 150,000 dollars a month with noodles.
Kim Mi Ryeong.
(Kim Mi Ryeong, 150,000 Dollars With Noodles A Month)
A legend from Yeonnnam-dong who captures the MZ generation.
Lee Sung Hoon.
(Lee Sung Hoon, Yeonnam-dong Legend)
This will be fun.
I didn't expect to see so many familiar faces.
Everyone I expected is here.
So many famous people are here.
I feel like the remaining ones are...
really strong.
Itaewon Prince bothers me. That nickname is mine.
That's mine.
"Itaewon Prince?"
(Itaewon Prince)
If he's a prince, he must be very handsome.
Who is it?
(Itaewon Prince)
Itaewon Prince?
Hello.
It's Hong Seok Cheon.
What? Seriously?
What?
The original Itaewon business legend.
Hong Seok Cheon.
It's nice to meet you.
Comparing a chef...
with a celebrity is...
Is he a chef? A CEO? What should I call him?
TV personality, Hong Seok Cheon?
Hong Seok Cheon is probably the easiest...
to compete with.
He was definitely good at running restaurants in Itaewon,
but is he still good?
I should at least defeat Hong Seok Cheon.
I'm sorry for saying this.
I've been running restaurants in Itaewon for the last 20 years.
I'm Hong Seok Cheon. It's good to see you.
I've learned how to succeed,
and I understand why people fail.
When it comes to business,
I can talk about it for a long time.
I'm good at reading trends,
and I tend to stay ahead of them.
I'm doing a lot of thinking right now.
Fifteen? We still have five more to go.
I'm most curious about Chinese cuisine.
Business skills for Chinese cuisine are on another level.
Who's Top Four Legendary Chinese Chef?
Chinese cuisine is already intense, and he's 1 of the top 4?
(Top 4 Legendary Chinese Chef)
Who is it?
Fifty-six years of cooking experience.
Fifty-six years.
We're dead meat.
Top Four Legendary Chinese Chef, Yoo Bang Nyeong.
Mr. Yoo Bang Nyeong?
In 1972, I started as a delivery boy.
I was beaten for forgetting to bring chili powder.
I even got a bloody nose. Things were like that back then.
I joined Plaza Hotel in 1983...
and worked there for nearly 30 years.
I cooked for presidential events at the Blue House.
I even served meals to Chairman Jung Ju Yung.
I don't have much formal education.
I spent all my time in the kitchen...
to learn and experience.
Now, I've become Chef Yoo Bang Nyeong.
As far as I know, "chef" is a French word.
It sounds too sophisticated.
I just want to be a regular cook.
I still have to learn.
The feeling will come.
(Yoo Bang Nyeong, Top Four Legendary Chinese Chef)
His presence is making me feel humble.
Seriously.
(French Culinary Master)
"French Culinary Master."
Who will be French Culinary Master?
There are only a few.
- There's onion soup.
- Right, there's onion soup.
No way.
It can't be him.
Who is it?
It's him.
It's really Ki Hak.
The first generation of French cuisine chefs in Korea.
Lim Ki Hak.
Oh, no.
My gosh. Finally...
- This is incredible.
- Chef Lim Ki Hak? Unbelievable.
Chef Lim Ki Hak is the first generation of French chefs in Korea.
Most people who studied western food would know him.
He's rarely on TV, and he's here?
I'm Chef Lim Ki Hak, and I run a French restaurant.
I gained experience at Chef Daniel Boulud's DB Bistro...
in New York and Chef Gray Kunz's Cafe Gray.
In Korea, I worked in Grand Hyatt...
as well as Park Hyatt.
The most unexpected chef is...
myself.
Here's what made me want to participate.
I want to create an awareness of the possibilities...
of the French cuisine.
(Lim Ki Hak, French Culinary Master)
I got goosebumps. This is no joke.
It's very competitive.
- There's no one easy.
- Absolutely no one.
Who's the one with 450 restaurants in 10 countries?
(10 countries, 450 restaurants)
Gosh, who is it?
The legend of Dookki Tteokbokki.
- It's really him.
- It's Dookki Tteokbokki.
Annual sales of 270 million dollars.
Four hundred and fifty restaurants in ten countries.
Kim Kwan Hoon.
(450 Chains in 10 Countries, the CEO of a global franchise)
One person that made me shocked...
about him joining is the Dookki CEO.
Diversifying a brand...
isn't easy,
but taking a brand all the way to its peak...
is very difficult.
I'm very curious about the net income.
Why would someone like him come here?
Darn it.
There are a lot of strong participants.
One, two... Two more left.
(Seven-star Chef)
"Seven-star Chef."
What?
What do they mean by seven-star?
How did they get seven stars?
(Seven-star Chef)
Don't tell me...
It is him.
Head chef of the hotel in Dubai.
Seven-star Chef.
(Brand Predator)
This is crazy. Really?
Edward Kwon.
Seeing Chef Edward Kwon was unexpected.
He doesn't suit a competition show like this.
He's like the chef of all chefs.
I nurtured my dream of becoming a chef...
by reading his book in university.
Is he actually here? It feels like a dream.
I was shocked.
Nice to meet you. I'm Edward Kwon.
Actually, a seven-star doesn't exist,
but many say the hotel is on another level,
so they call it a seven-star hotel.
I worked at Dubai's Burj Al Arab...
as the head chef.
If I remember correctly, I was 32.
I was very lucky at a young age.
I thought this was the chance...
to go back to the basics.
I'm here to learn too.
(Seven-star Chef, Edward Kwon)
(Fine dining restaurant, Lab XXIV by KUMUDA)
This is no joke.
Edward Kwon was my ex-judge...
- Exactly.
- in the previous show.
I didn't expect the lineup to be this strong.
There's one person left.
(Chinese Cuisine Master)
The last person...
I hope it isn't who I think it is.
Chinese Cuisine Master can't be...
Someone incredible would come out.
It is him.
Seriously?
No way.
No!
(Kim Hee Eun, Michelin Couple, Lim Ki Hak, French Culinary Master)
It is Lee Yeon Bok.
(Kim Ho Yoon, Brand Predator)
The dignity of Chinese cuisine in Korea.
Lee Yeon Bok.
I'm Chef Lee Yeon Bok.
I cooked Chinese cuisine for 53 years.
It's been a long time...
since I last went on a survival show.
But I heard this was a business showdown.
It sounded so fun,
so I gladly accepted it.
"Lee Yeon Bok is still alive and kicking."
I want to show everyone this.
(Lee Yeon Bok, Chinese Cuisine Master)
The best food businesspeople of each field have gathered...
for the business survival show.
Welcome to...
Street Restaurant Fighter.
(Street Restaurant Fighter)
This is insane.
The lineup is too strong.
This won't be easy.
This is bad.
Amazing.
From now on,
you will go to various commercial districts in Korea...
for business showdowns.
Your judges...
(Your judges...)
are the customers.
That's even better.
So it's real business.
Yes, being judged by the customers.
That's the scariest.
They're the scariest.
The winner will be decided by the sales.
Various factors will be reflected,
such as the ingredient cost and customer ratings.
The winner's prize money...
is infinite.
- What?
Infinite?
What do they mean by infinite?
The last person standing on Street Restaurant Fighter...
will win the base prize of 100,000 dollars...
and...
the full amount of the revenue earned on the show.
(You'll get full amount of the revenue earned on the show.)
They take everyone's revenue?
If you get eliminated, you leave your revenue behind?
I guess so.
You can't overlook the average order value.
You need to manage the costs right.
This changes things.
The first task you'll do...
is launching a new brand.
Launch a new brand?
Throw away the name you've been using.
The new signboard will become your name.
(Gyeongsang Province Business Monster)
(Brand Predator, Seochon's Icon)
I opened my brand four days ago.
(Kim Ho Yoon, Brand Predator)
You're confident.
That's practically what I do every day.
It's what I do all the time.
Let's just do as usual.
There's the energy you get...
when you first open a restaurant, the resolution to make it work.
You get very excited and nervous.
And when you succeed, you get the thrill.
The street restaurant...
will be revealed right now.
It will be revealed right now.
- Right now?
- With no delay?
(Michelin Couple, French Culinary Master)
I...
Gosh, what's this?
- Oh, my.
- Goodness.
It's going up.
It opens.
This is our restaurant?
Amazing.
- I didn't expect this kind of vibe.
- It's a booth.
They really made it like a restaurant.
This must be the restaurant.
It looked like there were 20 restaurants.
All of these shops will do business at the same time?
- I'm excited.
- I can't wait.
Get a grip.
From the name of the brand...
to the signboard, the interior design, and the menu.
Plan it with your own hands.
Make your own brand...
and sell the food here?
I need to renovate this?
Put up the signboard and everything.
It's big enough to do everything.
I could even butcher a cow here. This is fine.
It's my new restaurant.
(Street Restaurants revealed)
- They have all the basic stuff.
- This...
(Street Restaurant provides only the discussed basic equipment.)
Long time no see.
(Chinese wok range)
This is nice.
The gas stoves.
Three, okay.
This is pretty good.
(Multi-fuel range)
I'll change this...
and put a countertop.
Place a deep fryer and a fridge.
My brain in my head...
kept running.
"Right, I was this excited and had so much fun..."
"when I first created Dookki."
I'm so excited.
I'd have so much fun.
Street Restaurant Fighter.
I'll reveal the first mission.
(I'll reveal the first mission.)
- Already.
- Finally revealing the mission.
My heart is racing.
Round One...
(Round One...)
is a 1,000 dollar sales race.
What?
Sales race?
A 1,000 dollar sales race.
You need to hit 1,000 dollars as fast as you can?
If you achieve the 1,000 dollar sales first,
you automatically advance to the next round.
It's all about average order value, really.
You're given 300 dollars for the ingredients.
Make 1,000 dollars out of 300 dollars?
With 300 dollars? How?
When I heard I needed to do business with 300 dollars,
I thought, "What can I buy and what can I sell?"
That 300 dollars weighed on my mind.
What kind of menus...
can I come up with?
If you spend more than 300 dollars on your ingredients,
your sales will start from a negative amount...
which corresponds to the excessive amount you've spent.
(A 1,000 dollar sales race ingredient cost)
(Ingredient cost, 300 dollars, starting sales, 0 dollars)
(Ingredient cost, 470 dollars, starting sales, minus 170 dollars)
Even if you don't spend over 300 dollars,
the leftover cost will vanish.
The sales race is first-come, first-served survival basis.
(They survive based on the order of reaching the goal.)
The business will run for one full day.
After the lunch business, there will be a break...
before the dinner business.
(If they fail to hit the target during the lunch business,)
(they'll continue with the dinner business.)
It's the same.
It's the same as running an actual restaurant.
The two with the lowest sales...
in Round One...
will be eliminated.
They'll shut down the business immediately.
(The two with the lowest sales will shut down their business.)
Eliminated as soon as they start?
That's harsh.
Shut down.
"Shut down." That's so scary.
And this business...
is a blind business.
Blind?
Your faces won't be revealed...
to the customers.
Yes, that's how it should be.
- They should.
- They should be for this.
There are a lot of famous people here.
I cheered internally.
It's worth a shot. I could do it if I worked hard.
That's exactly what people like us wanted.
- Those who aren't known to public.
- It's worth a shot.
A new face.
A new face which the people want.
(Laughing)
Where and how many customers are have become very important now.
- That's right.
- Right.
I'm more curious about the location.
Now,
I'll announce the commercial district of the race.
Where is it?
Where is it? A popular spot?
What's that?
The commercial district?
From the above?
- Where is this?
- Oh, this.
Where is it?
- Where's that?
- Where is it?
- "Ministry of Education?"
"Ministry of Culture, Sports and Tourism, National Library."
"Ministry of Patriots and Veterans Affairs."
- "Government Complex." - "Government Complex."
- "Government Complex." - It's near that area.
Gwacheon or... Oh, Sejong.
- Isn't it Sejong?
- Is it Sejong-si?
- I think it's Sejong.
- It's Sejong.
Where the government agencies are gathered.
The customers are mainly public officials.
About 12,000 public officials work in this area.
It's a commercial district for office workers.
Okay.
The most important thing about that commercial district...
is that it shouldn't be expensive.
The food needs to be filling.
They have limited time...
to eat.
They need to be able...
to finish their lunch and grab a coffee...
within that one hour.
The estimated number of customers...
is 1,000 for lunch and dinner combined.
(Estimated number: 1,000 customers for lunch and dinner combined)
The unit price can't be high, can it?
The price can't be high since they're public officials.
That's right.
There would be price resistance, no doubt.
When I asked the Sejong public officials...
which restaurant was good around that area,
they said the chicken katsu place was the best.
- Chicken katsu?
- Which was a first.
Should I sell chicken katsu?
Not many commercial district favors that kind of menu.
Rather than a new experience...
- A safe menu.
- Something safe,
and they'd come for the menu...
which looks delicious at a glance.
You need to get them to come in.
Like spicy stir-fried pork.
- My goodness.
- That startled me.
- What is it?
- What's this?
Like spicy stir-fried pork.
- My goodness.
- That startled me.
Is a judge going to come up from here?
What's this?
What is it?
That scared me.
- An outdoor restaurant... What?
- What?
Outdoor...
It's an outdoor booth.
And this is...
where you'll compete fiercely.
It's the Street Arena.
(Street Arena)
These are the locations of the stalls.
Like a food court.
Those look like tables.
There must be outdoor tables.
Is that me?
(Twenty miniatures with their names)
That's amazing.
Looks like you need to place your name on the slot.
You can choose the location...
of your Street Restaurant yourself.
(They can choose the location themselves.)
We need to choose the location.
- The location is important.
The location is important.
The experienced call it "the right spot."
Getting the right spot...
contributes to 70 to 80 percent of a successful business.
The order to choose the location...
will be decided by drawing balls.
Kim Hee Eun, choose your slot.
(Number 1, Kim Hee Eun)
Where will she choose?
If they've come all the way here,
the spirit is more important than the location.
I was going to choose that spot.
(Kim Hee Eun)
Jo Seo Hyung, choose your slot.
I'll choose this.
I didn't choose the slot at the end.
Customers would go to the end...
and then always come back.
So I chose the spot they'd come back to...
in about five footsteps.
Everyone thinks alike.
That spot looks good too.
Go Seok Hyun,
choose your slot.
Right next to the entrance.
I wanted to leave a strong impact at the entrance.
The spot with the most exposure has the highest sales.
The spot Go Seok Hyun took is the best spot in my opinion.
(Exit, Entrance, Go Seok Hyun)
Lee Yeon Bok,
choose your slot.
You'll give up the good spots for your juniors, won't you?
- No.
- The good spots.
Why are you coming here?
- He won't.
- I'm taking a slot over there.
They'll make a round to scan the booths...
and then decide on mine.
Jung Ho Young.
I'll go far away from Lee Yeon Bok.
Chinese cuisine is a strong opponent...
because the food has strong flavors.
Lim Ki Hak.
(Number 9, Lim Ki Hak)
You left the middle spot empty.
I want to avoid being next to the Chinese cuisine chefs.
Their food is bound to be tasty.
Edward Kwon,
- choose your slot.
- Chef.
Hong Seok Cheon.
(Number 18, Hong Seok Cheon)
I used to like Edward Kwon.
In the past, that is.
Kim Hoon.
They could buy mine on their way out.
- Is that your slot, Hoon?
- Yes.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
The slots have been decided...
for Round 1, a 1,000 dollar sales race.
Now, I'll reveal the opening crews...
whom you'll run the Street Restaurant with.
It's impossible to do this alone.
Opening crews.
I'm ready to be shocked by the lineup.
(Street Restaurants will be accompanied by a teammate each.)
I think they're famous chefs.
Definitely.
It's cool.
(Opening crews)
I have a good feeling.
Are those legs?
It looks cooler.
Their legs look cooler.
Did they invite all the famous chefs?
Exactly. My gosh.
Isn't that cheating?
Why do they get to make such a cool entrance?
- I know, right?
- This is so interesting.
This is insane.
Nice.
(The opening crew who will run Street Restaurant together)
Are you going to shut down your restaurant?
Why is your husband here?
That's cheating.
It says "Michelin Couple."
How can we beat the teamwork of a married couple?
They're a couple too. Kim Hee Eun and her husband.
(Husband, Kim Min Seong, Wife, Park Min)
- Let's do this.
- We're a married couple.
(Wife, Shin Ga Young, Husband, Lim Hong Geun)
(Master, Lee Yeon Bok, Apprentice, Wang Byeong Ho)
- I'll be in your care.
- Is that Yoo Bang Nyeong's son?
Yes, his son Sang Min.
You can check inside.
(Son, Yoo Sang Min, Father, Yoo Bang Nyeong)
- They're all formidable opponents.
- Yes.
Imokase brought her son too.
(Friend, Hong Seok Cheon, Friend, Park Min Hyuk)
They're doing this on purpose.
(Friend, Jeon Seok Su, Friend, Edward Kwon)
Hello. Chef, whose crew are you?
This is cheating.
- Hello.
- What's happening?
Is he the MC?
This is crazy.
He shouldn't be here.
Isn't this cheating?
- What?
- Hello.
Song Hoon, you shouldn't be here!
Hello.
(Opening crew, Song Hoon)
I'm curious.
Who is Chef Song Hoon going to?
- Whose team is he...
- Song Hoon...
- Come on.
- No way.
Why are you here? You should've stayed in Jeju Island.
- It's you two?
- Yes.
You're out of your mind.
- You're crazy.
- We're friends.
(Friend, Jung Ho Young, Friend, Song Hoon)
- For real?
- He's with Chef Ho Young.
For real?
- Isn't that too much?
- Exactly.
The 20 teams of Street Restaurant Fighter...
are complete now.
Gosh, only the strongest are here.
The legends.
Little did I think they'd be this strong.
- There are too many tough chefs.
- Exactly.
The CEOs of big brands and chefs.
They must be the hidden masters.
I better pack up.
Compete through sales, and prove yourselves...
with your business skills.
(The first business showdown venue)
(Ministry of Health and Welfare)
(Ministry of Education)
(Government Complex Sejong)
(Government Complex Sejong: The center of Sejong)
(Home to 22 government agencies with over 12,000 workers)
(At the heart of the government complex)
(20 restaurants were transferred as-is.)
(Street Arena)
(Transformed into a food court with 600 seats)
(An area bustling with office workers)
(1,000 customers)
(20 teams of business experts)
(Street Arena)
Everyone on Street Restaurant Fighter,
this is the Street Arena.
(Opening day, 6 hours before business)
It's as grand as BTS's stage.
For real.
- Goodness.
- Gosh.
- Oh, my.
- Welcome...
to Round One of Street Restaurant Fighter.
Now, the new restaurants...
you designed yourself will be revealed.
We'll get to see them.
- Three, two, one.
- One.
- Let's see.
- Open.
- Gosh, this is...
- My goodness.
- Oh, dear.
- Gosh.
It's going up.
This is a huge food court.
Look at that. The shutter doors are going up.
Wait, the doors are opening.
- Cool.
- Goodness.
Gosh, all of them are pretty.
Imagine we're unable to see the customers' faces.
This is a battle of the menu and the exterior design.
Our key point is vibrant colors.
The first thing customers notice is the store's image.
We could hang up a signboard that would help us stand out.
(20 teams with 20 new restaurants)
- It draws attention.
- Whose is it?
Extraordinary Couple did a great job.
Yes, keep giving us a shout out.
- The signboard is so cool.
- Right?
Extraordinary Couple. Look at Extraordinary Couple.
The signboard...
- has its own character.
- For real.
- That one's great.
- What a nice theme.
Goal!
- Is Gotgan Imokase's?
- Yes.
Gotgan is no joke.
A straightforward name that just makes you...
walk in and order.
Oh, gosh. Everything About Tteokbokki.
He's going with one menu.
Everything About Tteokbokki? He's selling tteokbokki.
That place even has a cauldron.
Agungi.
(Sales Gangster Go Seok Hyun, Cauldrons as a design focal point)
There's an aquarium.
- You're right.
- Is that an aquarium on the side?
(Seochon's Icon Lee Jae Hoon, An aquarium as a design focal point)
(Yeonnam-dong Legend Lee Sung Hoon, Blue color as a design focal point)
(Global Cuisine Master Choi Sang Hyun, Red color as a design point)
- Nicely done.
- Gosh.
Now then, here are the new restaurants...
and the menus being sold.
Here's the menu.
Arirang House, Yang Ji Sam.
- Spring cabbage cockle bibimbap...
- That meal...
- and bossam.
- with bossam? And just 13 dollars?
Ingredient cost, 393.22 dollars.
- The sales race begins...
- What?
at minus 93.22 dollars.
Yoo Bang Nyeong. Five-color bibim jjajang.
Kim Hee Eun. Charcoal-grilled tteokgalbi rice plate.
Chimichanga and chili cheese stick combo.
- Signature black ramen.
- Gosh.
Beef noodle soup.
XO shrimp fresh pasta.
(Choi Sang Hyun, Ingredient cost: 299.48 dollars)
- Everything About Tteokbokki.
Kim Kwan Hoon.
I wonder how much the tteokbokki is.
- Let's see.
Tteokbokki, five dollars.
(Ingredient cost: 290.62 dollars)
- Wait, five dollars? Gosh.
- Five dollars?
- My gosh.
- Oh, my.
A clear win.
Amazing. Tteokbokki will get first place.
If the other chefs are providing main menu items,
our team will serve a side menu that can be shared at every table.
Let's become the perfect supporting dish!
Becoming the perfect complementary dish is my strategy.
That's the plan.
(A shareable-menu strategy)
He has to sell 200 dishes.
- But the thing is...
- Serve big portions?
- No. Everyone...
- Yes?
will order it.
- All customers might order it.
- Exactly.
- As a side dish.
- Right?
That's a good idea.
Sell it all out, or just go home.
I've chosen 1 of those 2 options.
The Star In My Heart, Jo Seo Hyung.
(Laughing)
(The Star In My Heart, Jo Seo Hyung)
The chicken with glutinous rice nurungji and Korean calcot.
(Ingredient cost: 404.47 dollars)
It's 28 dollars.
I bet it's the priciest menu.
Twenty-eight dollars?
That's tough.
She's an elimination candidate.
She's standing on a cliff.
The chicken with nurungji and Korean calcot?
In 28 dollars?
It's not a dish you can sell with half-hearted confidence.
- That's an incredible challenge.
- Let's go.
Goodness.
HunGry, Kim Hoon.
Kim Hoon!
(Yongridan-gil Hot Spot Maker Kim Hoon, Teammate Kim Jong In)
We have a pro here.
Tenderloin steak rice.
(Ingredient cost: 572.46 dollars)
(270 dollars over the base ingredient budget)
- As expected.
- Hoon!
(Starting in minus by the amount he overspent)
Nice one.
As expected.
(Everyone is happy for him.)
- Let's do it with spirit!
- We'll sell a lot!
(Kim Hoon, Initial revenue: minus 270 dollars, last place)
- We'll make sure to sell a lot.
- We're going for buzz.
I've already beaten you!
(Go Seok Hyun, Initial revenue: 0 dollars)
- Let's do this.
- I'll see you at dinner.
(Song Hoon, Initial revenue: minus 170 dollars)
If you don't sell out during lunch, you need to do dinner business.
Start preparing...
- for the lunch rush.
- Let's go.
(The 1,000-dollar sales race begins.)
- I'm in your care.
- Good luck.
Please attract many customers.
(5 hours before opening)
First place. We're here to come in first place.
It does feel like foul play...
for Chef Lee Yeon Bok to participate.
He has over 50 years of experience.
His dish gives off that energy, you know?
Chef Lee Yeon Bok. I'm happy to see him,
and yet, I'm quite scared of him.
The 1st team to reach 1,000 dollars in sales is the winner.
What should we sell, and will it work in this market?
In my experience,
business was bad when I sold a dish that came out of nowhere...
and was hard to understand.
Since our customers are office workers,
one menu item should be jjamppong.
Familiar flavors sell.
The dish is easy for anyone to approach.
People know what they're getting.
They already recognize the menu.
(Lee Yeon Bok's strategy: Familiar flavors)
Jjajangmyeon...
is commonly made with pork or shrimp,
but not with freshwater snails.
Freshwater snails have great texture. They're chewy.
Hence, we made freshwater snail jjajangmyeon.
(Menu 1: Freshwater snail jjajangmyeon, 7 dollars)
The jjamppong is topped with well-cooked meat.
Beef loin jjamppong.
(Menu 2: Shrimp and beef loin jjamppong, 12 dollars)
Mianbao xia is our restaurant's signature menu.
It was added to the menu...
to boost sales.
Jjajangmyeon, jjamppong, and mianbao xia.
It's not an exaggeration to say that we're the best at them.
That's why they're our menu items.
(Freshwater snail jjajangmyeon, beef loin and shrimp jjamppong...)
Put your cooking shoes on. We need to get ready.
Let's put them in the freezer first.
- Okay.
- Open the noodles.
As we had a lot to prep in the morning,
- we were in a rush.
- Yes.
(Pressed for time, ripping the packaging open with a knife)
The noodles are still frozen. Interesting.
They were in the freezer.
Oh, dear.
Are you okay?
I was being hasty,
trying to prep quickly.
We should've used scissors or a cutting board and a knife...
to cut the packaging,
but we were on the floor, using a knife while chatting.
That's when I cut my finger.
He asked what was wrong. I told him I cut myself...
and to be careful with his fingers.
Just when we got started.
We're doomed.
Come on.
But he was also in a rush...
- and cut his finger.
- Today will be...
- Back then...
- It was unbelievable.
We're off on a bad start.
In the beginning.
My mind went blank.
"Did this really happen?"
I couldn't believe it.
His cut was bad.
It was a mess. He was bleeding a lot.
We would've just worked if possible.
You should go now.
- Go now.
- You should get it sutured.
The amount of bleeding wasn't something I could put up with.
If things went wrong because of my cut,
I would get us eliminated.
My mind was racing.
I was in full panic mode back then.
(BokBok)
(Lee Yeon Bok is alone in the kitchen.)
I was a bit worried.
I was too busy and swamped.
Other restaurants...
had two people prepping,
but one of us went to the hospital.
I had to prep everything alone.
(BokBok)
Time was ticking. I was really all over the place.
Back then,
I had a small mental breakdown.
Today is going to be chaotic.
(Leaving Yeon Bok, who is struggling alone)
(Another store with 3 Chinese wok ranges)
(Sunlin)
(A Chinese-style orange-colored exterior and signboard)
Dad, I'm leaving this here.
Yes, okay.
(Top 4 Legendary Chinese Chef, Yoo Bang Nyeong of Sunlin)
I personally know Lee Yeon Bok.
We worked together when we were young.
Was it 1978 or 1979?
We worked together at the same hotel.
I was in my 20s...
when I went to clubs every night.
I can't talk about it. Even my wife doesn't know about it.
Who's that? Isn't it Yoo Bang Nyeong?
Yes, hi.
Hey, friend.
We met again after 20 to 30 years.
We were coworkers back then. Now, we're competing with each other.
We're rivals.
When the time comes, you might see blood.
They'll scan the booths...
- and then decide on mine.
- You'll succeed no matter where.
The spot that...
Lee Yeon Bok chose was the one I had in mind.
Yoo Bang Nyeong needs to stay away since we both cook Chinese.
(Lee Yeon Bok)
- I was going to put mine here.
- Next to mine?
- Kind of like Chinatown.
- Chinatown?
- Chinatown.
Chinatown.
Lee Yeon Bok took that spot.
Yoo Bang Nyeong,
choose your slot.
I'm going over there.
On the opposite side of Chef Yeon Bok.
- They're facing each other.
- Interesting.
Nice.
Head-to-head.
Chinese Cuisine Master.
- My gosh.
- Oh, my.
A battle between the two.
I chose the spot right across from Lee Yeon Bok's.
(Yoo Bang Nyeong, Lee Yeon Bok)
(BokBok)
Sunlin.
(Sunlin)
It's right across from us.
What dishes was Lee Yeon Bok selling again?
- Mianbao xia.
- Right.
Beef brisket jjamppong.
Beef brisket jjamppong?
(BokBok prepared classic Chinese dishes.)
I was worried Yoo Bang Nyeong's menu...
would overlap with ours.
Yoo Bang Nyeong is the only other chef...
serving traditional Chinese cuisine like us.
(Sunlin)
They're getting on our nerves the most.
I wonder what Yoo Bang Nyeong will serve.
The customers are office workers. Lunch should be tasty...
while being cheap.
What's more, it shouldn't take long.
Jjajangmyeon.
I...
have been cooking jjajang...
since the moment I learned how to use a wok.
The number of jjajangmyeon dishes I have made is countless.
I can tell if it's bland or salty...
just by its smell.
Okay.
(He cooked jjajang in no time.)
Fill it with cold water.
(Yoo Bang Nyeong)
(Bang Nyeong is cooling down the freshly made jjajang.)
Put in some ice.
Every jjajangmyeon dish can have its own unique taste.
(Sunlin)
Five-color bibim jjajang.
(Five-color bibim jjajang, 9.50 dollars)
I may be old, but I'm trying to stay young.
Cooking also changes with time.
You hit a wall if you only cook plain jjajangmyeon every day.
You must come up with new dishes.
Okay.
Our jjajang is enjoyed cold.
(Cooling the jjajang sauce for about 2 hours)
(The freshly cooked noodles are immediately rinsed in cold water.)
(Topping it off with some jjajang sauce)
The garnishes are in four colors. With the color of the jjajang,
it has five colors in total.
(5 colors complete with 4 garnishes and jjajang)
Pickled onion gives it that tanginess.
Together with the jjajang sauce, it creates a novel taste.
I do feel the pressure.
But trying something new is necessary.
Only then will the customers think,
"This jjajangmyeon is different from the one..."
"at Yoo Bang Nyeong's Chinatown restaurant."
With a new brand,
we can introduce a new dish.
It's a type of mianbao xia.
(Shrimp mix)
I made it with Chinese twisted donuts.
Youtiao xia.
(Youtiao xia, a new type of mianbao xia)
They are yellow jalapenos.
I haven't seen a Chinese restaurant in Korea use one.
Yellow jalapeno peppers are spicier and tastier than normal ones.
(Yellow chili meat rice bowl, a new type of beef rice bowl)
Beef rice bowl.
Oh, my gosh.
I've lost.
How much will it appeal to customers?
It's a challenge.
(BokBok)
(Sunlin)
A part of me is filled with worries.
But you never know what'll happen until it actually does.
(A Chinese cuisine showdown across the street)
Is BokBok's jjajangmyeon better than ours?
That's for the customer to judge.
A flavor you've never tasted before.
The stove works.
I want the customers to look forward to that.
Next...
The chefs who could possibly have a tough time are...
those in fine dining.
I don't think Chef Lim Ki Hak will win.
Those who actually do business...
should win this survival show.
We're technically in a battlefield.
A sense of crisis? None.
No matter how much I thought about it,
it came across as interesting.
Something that lived only in my imagination.
"Will the customers come to like this?"
It's something worth trying.
First off, our theme should be...
French cuisine, no question asked. But a more approachable one.
(The popularization of French cuisine)
If there's one thing that's different,
it's that we won't change...
our concept even if we get a mission.
Regardless of the kind of mission,
we plan to serve French cuisine on a single plate.
The name is Bol A Bol.
One plate.
The dish we prepared...
is a simple lunch...
featuring a condensed three-course French meal.
Poulet basquaise.
In Korean, it would be spicy stir-fried chicken rice bowl.
If the meat is served over rice in a bowl,
it could easily appeal to the public.
I also wanted to serve some sausages.
Rice with sausages on top. It's hearty, isn't it?
I handmade the sausages.
There's also dessert. Creme caramel.
(Creme caramel, 4.50 dollars)
We practiced the same dishes twice.
I was confident.
I will start cooking the poulet basquaise.
Searing the chicken well on high heat...
was the most important first task.
Chicken drumsticks.
I was in full concentration mode...
to cook the chicken well.
How well the chicken sears...
accounts for half of how good the dish will taste.
(Stir-frying onions in the leftover chicken fat)
As stir-frying the onions,
I started to see the next steps.
Where is our canned tomato?
- What did you say? Can?
- Canned tomato.
Canned tomato...
This is bad.
Gosh, this is serious.
I was the one in charge of packing the ingredients.
The moment I heard the word "tomato,"
I realized I forgot to pack it.
Tomatoes are one of the core ingredients...
for poulet basquaise.
This is an absolute emergency.
I couldn't find it anywhere. I saw the can opener, but...
Why did we even bring the can opener?
What should I do if there are no tomatoes?
But I couldn't just stop there.
The show must go on.
Will they have it at the grocery store?
I don't know. I'll go check.
I'll go to the grocery store now.
- I'm done with this. I'll go now.
- Okay.
Make it quick.
I'll be right back.
I'll buy anything that's related to tomatoes.
(Grocery store)
(The cost of additional ingredients is deducted...)
(from the revenue at retail price.)
Please.
I have a bad feeling that they don't have it.
Since I couldn't move on to the next step,
I turned off the stove.
It wasn't a situation where I could blame anyone.
It was a situation where I just had to find a solution.
Do you have tomatoes here? Oh, there.
(He found fresh tomatoes.)
(45 tomatoes: 36 dollars)
- Please wait. I'll be right back.
- Okay.
Chef, they only have ripe tomatoes.
There are 45 of them.
- Price?
- It's over 30 dollars.
- Ripe tomatoes?
- Yes.
Buy all the tomatoes there.
Okay.
I'll buy all of these.
Yes. I'll have these.
- All of them?
- How do I pay?
It will be deducted from the revenue later.
Okay. I get it.
(The initial revenue of Bol A Bol: minus 77.87 dollars)
(Returning with a box of tomatoes)
- How many do we have?
- There are 45 tomatoes.
- We have 45 tomatoes?
- Yes.
Hoon, slice them first.
- These?
- Yes.
Okay. I'll slice them first.
I'm not sure if we can get the right flavor with these.
The amount is about right, but...
I think the taste will be completely different.
The richness and sweetness...
of Italian tomatoes and domestic tomatoes...
are completely different.
I worried a lot about how to bring out a rich flavor...
when the core ingredients were missing.
(Thinking)
- We can make it work.
- Okay.
- We can do this.
- Yes.
Then, what we need right now is...
What we need now is...
Chicken powder.
An ingredient I have never used before.
Just in case the flavor doesn't come through properly,
I did prepare those seasonings as a backup.
Should we add a bit of a familiar taste?
(Picking up pure black pepper)
(Familiar taste)
I can't believe I'm even using pure black pepper.
This is my first time using pure black pepper on my own dish.
I'm adding 30g of doubanjiang.
(Doubanjiang with a spicy umami flavor)
Did we add Cheongyang chili peppers in the middle of it?
We have to bring out the flavor from here somehow.
We used a lot of spices...
that are familiar to Koreans...
and even chili peppers.
I'm so worried about how it will taste.
I'll taste it.
It's good.
The flavor actually turned out much better than I expected.
I think using the doubanjiang was a stroke of genius.
How much were the tomatoes?
- They were 36 dollars.
- Great.
We just need to sell two more servings.
Okay.
I'm sorry that I forgot to bring them.
Don't be.
I'm just afraid we won't get the result we wanted.
- That's not true.
- Okay.
I didn't double-check either.
We can't say it's entirely your fault.
I was afraid...
Hoon would think it was his fault that he forgot it.
I just wanted to make sure...
he wouldn't feel that way after it happened.
Everything is perfect, except for the canned tomatoes.
No. They say every cloud has a silver lining. It's okay.
- No problem.
- Okay.
(Min's)
This is the problem.
- This isn't working.
- It will work. It's working.
- No, it's not.
- I'm sure it will work.
(Kim Min Seong, the husband, Park Min, the wife)
No, Min Seong. It's not working.
(A team with a lot of bickering)
You always say that.
I run a Japanese restaurant called Kuma in Yeouido.
My name is Kim Min Seong. Nice to meet you.
(Yeouido Sashimi Chairman, Kim Min Seong)
I've been cooking for about 30 years now.
And I've been a fixture in Yeouido for the past 20 years.
Our restaurant is a place where you can find a list of fish...
that people are curious about.
Such as 100kg jewfish,
200kg or 300kg tuna,
giant grouper over 20kg,
large sharks, and so on.
We handle fish that ordinary seafood restaurants can't.
Our restaurant is practically an all-you-can-eat place.
If customers ask for more, we give them as much as they want.
Since Kuma has the concept where they serve...
extremely high-quality fish...
I'm sorry to say this,
but it doesn't seem like they're trying to make money.
I wonder if they can even make...
any profit by selling it at that price.
It says "Yeouido Sashimi Chairman."
(The self-proclaimed and publicly recognized sashimi expert)
You're given 300 dollars for the ingredients.
A budget of 300 dollars?
Are you going to serve sashimi?
No. We don't have any good fish for sashimi in March.
There's only spring ridged-eye flounder.
Other than that, there aren't many types of fish available.
And we can't stay within budget with just 300 dollars.
I see.
There's no way we can serve sashimi.
A 300 dollar ingredient budget is way too low.
Our food costs have always exceeded 40 to 50 percent of the prime cost.
People call my husband a man obsessed with ingredients.
He's someone who handles high-quality ingredients...
without even thinking about the price.
With only 300 dollars, I can't think of any sashimi menu...
that I can serve.
("Sashimi Chairman" can't serve "sashimi" here.)
(What is the alternative menu of the sashimi expert?)
This is the highest-grade Korean beef.
(Top secret curry)
I'll start making curry then.
There's something called Korean beef scrapes.
It's meat cut off from different parts.
(Leftover meat trimmed from various cuts during butchering)
Because the shapes are irregular, it's on the cheaper side.
Still, they are the highest grade, so the quality is excellent.
It's a curry made by boiling beef and vegetables thoroughly...
in a pressure cooker, and then blending them together.
Even if we give it out generously, we can have over 100 servings.
(100 servings of the top secret curry are done.)
It's better to have too much than not enough.
(A hot spring egg)
It has to taste good.
(Top secret curry, 12 dollars)
But how did everyone else...
buy all their ingredients within 300 dollars?
The one I understand the least is the raw fish guksu.
Will they be able to manage the cost?
How much is the price? Is it 15 dollars?
I guess it's 13 dollars.
Is it 13 dollars?
I could never sell it at that price.
I can't even source raw fish at that price.
It's impossible.
(Gotgan)
(Jeju raw fish guksu set)
Hello.
I run a noodle place in Gyeongdong Market.
I also run Jeulgeoun Soolsang in Chang-dong...
and Bada Soolsang on Jeju Island.
My name is Kim Mi Ryeong.
(Kim Mi Ryeong with 30 years of experience in Korean cuisine)
It's sold at a traditional market, so the price is cheap.
A bowl of noodles is only 10 dollars,
but I pulled up our monthly sales to 150,000 dollars.
It's not easy. It's a low-margin, high-volume business.
This isn't a cooking survival show, after all.
This is a business survival show.
I have total confidence when it comes to business.
I can make and serve food right away,
keep up the speed, and handle a large number of customers at once.
I believe that's my strength.
(30 years proven in the market)
Turn down the heat just a little.
Am I your assistant or something?
I gave birth to him.
I created him.
She did.
(Her teammate and her son, Lee Jun Seong)
Since elementary school, he's come to the kitchen...
to wash dishes, pick up trash, and serve food.
He is highly experienced.
He's young in age, but heavy on experience.
So, I think we will have great chemistry.
(The raw fish in question)
We're going to serve raw fish guksu.
We predicted that...
no one would be serving raw fish here.
(Jeju raw fish guksu set, Ingredient cost: 249.23 dollars)
- Unbelievable.
- For raw fish?
What kind of fish did they use to only spend 249 dollars?
What kind of fish did they use?
What kind of fish do they serve?
No matter how much I thought, I couldn't figure it out.
- What are they using?
- What is it?
(Everyone was curious about the raw fish.)
There are specific types of fish for this.
We can't make raw fish guksu with red seabream.
- Yellowtail amberjack is in season.
- It's called yellowtail amberjack.
The price is very cheap.
We slice up the fish and serve it.
(Similar to Japanese amberjack, it's in the carangidae family.)
They are caught in large numbers,
so the price is very low now.
(It inhabits the warm waters of the Jeju region.)
Consumers would probably be shocked to hear this,
but the price is incredibly cheap.
(The overwhelming cost advantage of a business on Jeju Island)
We thought about all that before starting this, of course.
Without the option,
a budget of 300 dollars would be impossible.
It'd easily cost 1,000 dollars.
Jun Seong, the important thing is that we're in Chungnam Province now.
- This is Chungnam Province, right?
- Yes.
You know what it is famous for here. It's kalguksu.
(The region with the highest number of kalguksu restaurants per capita)
Apparently, people here have a huge preference for noodle dishes.
I have absolute confidence when it comes to noodle dishes.
We will serve Jeju-style raw fish guksu.
And it would be a bit disappointing just to have noodles.
So I prepared pork suyuk.
And it will be served with laver that I roast myself.
You might not know it, but eating noodles...
wrapped in laver is incredibly good.
(Roasted laver to accompany the noodles)
Add the bean sprouts, Jun Seong.
It's a set meal. I like serving a set meal.
It feels a bit lacking if there's only a single menu item.
(Jeju raw fish guksu set: 17.9 dollars)
And Jun Seong knows a recipe...
that can make marinated shrimp within ten minutes.
Is that right? Is it ten minutes?
It's a bit pressuring when you put it that way.
When we have...
leftover shrimp at our restaurant...
and want to eat it for lunch, we can't marinate it right away.
And we have a vacuum sealer at our restaurant.
If you use it to suck the air out,
the shrimp gets marinated in just five minutes.
But we couldn't bring the commercial vacuum sealer here.
So we decided to use...
a vacuum airtight container sold at a dollar shop.
(A vacuum airtight container)
The sauce is forced into the shrimp without any separate aging time,
so the texture of shrimp doesn't break down from aging.
- That's true. It's not mushy.
- It just absorbs the flavor...
while keeping the firm texture.
(Gotgan)
I make good perilla oil guksu. For the clean taste.
So we prepared perilla oil guksu with marinated shrimp.
(Jeju marinated shrimp guksu set: 17.9 dollars)
There is one hour left before the business starts.
(The participants must decorate the exterior themselves.)
(There's one restaurant that catches everyone's eye.)
He really knows how to utilize props. He's so good.
Chef Kim Hoon is amazing at designing the exterior.
(The LA food truck concept)
He is someone who can lead the trend.
He is extremely talented and has great ideas.
When it comes to running a business, Chef Kim Hoon is the best.
He is someone who caters perfectly to modern tastes.
Hello, I'm Chef Kim Hoon who is running restaurants...
in Yongridan-gil.
I run Sam Sam Sam, an American-style comfort food restaurant,
Teddy Beurre House, and Namdo Dwaejichon.
The genre I'm handling has now become...
a hot spot brand that targets Gen Z.
In this specific genre, I believe I have the strongest momentum now.
I honestly wonder, "Who here is actually better..."
"at business than I am?"
There aren't many people who have actually run businesses...
in many different commercial districts.
But I do have that experience.
I've been in office districts like Yeouido and Gwanghwamun,
and I've even done it in specialized commercial zones and food courts.
I think this could be my stage.
How many kilograms of meat do we have?
We have 16kg.
- I'll marinate the beef first.
- Okay.
The menu item we prepared is...
tenderloin steak rice, loaded with tenderloin.
(Tenderloin steak rice: 13 dollars)
Office districts are areas...
where a high volume of repeat purchases occurs.
I currently run restaurants in office districts...
like Gwanghwamun, Yeouido, and Jamsil.
Since those areas trap customers like a pot,
the same office workers end up eating the same things repeatedly.
So the food which can be eaten in daily life is successful there.
(Budae jjigae, spicy stir-fried pork rice)
(Homemade tonkatsu)
However, this is a restaurant that only operates for a single day.
Still, we should make this place a hot spot.
It could be a big event for the office workers here.
Since we have to take both factors into account,
we can't simply judge this place as a typical office district.
So I thought about a place that targets office workers...
but is still considered trendy.
There is actually one such place in Korea.
It's The Hyundai Seoul in Yeouido.
(A specialized commercial area...)
(where an office district and hot spots coexist)
I believe data never lies.
If we move according to that data, we won't get eliminated.
That's how we will survive. I have total confidence in that.
It's an office district, but we're not just targeting office workers.
We need to do something trendy, but it shouldn't be too trendy...
because there are many office workers.
Let's just make it simple.
What's the number one item in sales at The Hyundai Seoul?
Once we find out what it is, it's game over.
We did some research.
When I looked into the best-selling items...
during lunchtime at places like department stores,
it turned out to be the steak rice. So I chose it.
If you can have a hearty steak rice for 13 dollars during lunchtime,
you will absolutely buy it. I'd even eat it five times a week.
What is the menu item that you think will do the best?
The steak rice.
I think the steak rice is selling well.
They're ordering the tenderloin steak rice.
I knew it would be popular.
First of all, a meat rice bowl is one of those items that never fails.
And on top of that, it's a steak.
Beef tenderloin? They're using beef tenderloin?
That means they're not going to skimp on costs.
(Tenderloin steak rice, Ingredient cost: 572.46 dollars)
It's 572 dollars!
(The number 1 restaurant in negative ingredient cost)
This is all about momentum.
I thought that if we embrace the negative budget...
and serve a generous amount of meat as a steak rice,
it would show our sincerity to the customers.
The fact that you can have...
a tenderloin steak rice for just 13 dollars is a huge merit.
If you pay just 0.1 dollars more than our hamburger steak,
you can eat real beef.
(Black bean rice with hamburger steak: 12.9 dollars)
You get a whole chunk of beef.
I thought it would be tough.
The person I'm keeping an eye on...
is Kwak Dong Hoon.
While Seoul has Kim Hoon, Busan has Kwak Dong Hoon.
I thought it would be fun.
I have a desire for people to notice me.
Since we've often sold over 1,000 dollars per hour,
I think we can finish it within lunchtime for sure.
(Number One)
Let's have confidence.
We have our years of hard-earned experience.
I think the government institutions probably have their own cafeterias.
We can't sell something that you would find in a cafeteria.
Wouldn't they want to try something new and trendy?
The other chefs tend to do what they are best at.
French cuisine, no question asked.
I think it's better to include jjamppong on the menu.
We're chefs, so the food has to be good.
Of course, it has to be good.
They seem to be serving the food that they can make best,
but I look at the customers' needs.
What customers want to eat.
We are the type who make food that consumers desire.
That's why I'm planning to set up what is needed in Gwangalli.
I think it's best to make food that doesn't exist in Sejong.
That is my strategy.
(The needs hunter)
What we are making is...
chimichanga, which is our specialty.
(Jumbo chimichanga: 12.8 dollars)
And a chili cheese stick.
(Chili cheese stick: 6.8 dollars)
These are the items that are trending on social media now.
The jumbo chimichanga is a dish...
that went viral on social media...
and created explosive waiting lines.
That's how I'd describe the item.
Earlier, some of the participants looked at our menu...
and asked what a chimichanga was.
Jumbo chimichanga and chili cheese stick combo.
What is chimichanga?
Is it something like dim sum?
That means there are people who don't know it.
Wouldn't it be even more so in Sejong?
A chimichanga is a dish made of a deep-fried burrito...
generously covered with sauce.
First, we prepared the fillings that go inside the chimichanga.
We cooked rice...
to mix it with Mexican sauce.
This is the exact moment where my experience...
as a military cook shines through.
(Mexican sauce rice, the base of chimichanga's taste)
Then we stir-fried and seasoned...
chicken and pork.
We also deep-fried french fries.
(Fries to add the crispy texture)
(Chicken sauce, pork sauce, fries)
I made unique pickles using the red onions.
That evens out the greasiness of the chimichanga.
As much as we're proud of this dish,
we're desperate to present it.
It's delicious.
The current time is 10:50am.
Ten minutes before the business begins.
Oh, I'm tight on schedule.
I'm pressed for time more than I thought.
Okay. Done.
(Gyeol, BokBok, Gotgan)
Round One.
A 1,000 dollar sales race begins.
The blinds will come down now.
(Out of 20 restaurants here,)
(2 will close.)
- We'll now begin.
- Oh, no.
- It's starting.
- I'm nervous.
Here we go.
No matter how many restaurants I opened before,
it's always nervous to open a new one.
Will people choose my restaurant?
Will they be happy with it?
It's time for the cold evaluation.
- One, two, three, go.
- Go.
It was pretty tense.
Good luck.
- We can do it.
(Government Complex Sejong)
(Time to open a new restaurant regardless of their titles)
The Street Arena door opens.
- Cool.
- Can we go?
(The mics are worn on only those who want to.)
- There are so many.
- It's crazy.
It's pretty. There are so many restaurants.
How are we going to order everything here?
Where do you want to go first?
- Check it out.
- What do you want to eat?
- It's opening.
- People are coming.
I wonder what the first customer is getting.
(Get out of my way.)
- It's going to get crowded.
- Something smells delicious.
(The customers scatter toward the restaurants.)
Handmade ice cream?
Then...
The customers are here. Hey, they're here.
They're coming this way.
Hey, Hoon. They're coming. They're coming this way.
They're looking at us. They're coming.
- But the food...
- Everything sounds delicious.
There's so much to choose from.
I've always wanted to try that. The chili cheese stick.
- That's trendy now.
- What?
- The chili cheese stick.
- Really?
(Immediately reacting to Kwak Dong Hoon's trendy item)
Sunlin.
I want to eat everything. There are also dumplings.
- Do you want to go around first?
- Yes.
- Wolfie's?
- That sounds delicious.
Black bean rice.
Hamburger steak.
They went halfway around.
Did they linger and leave?
Yes. I think they're checking out all the items.
When the customers come, they'll go around at least once...
before choosing the food.
(The customer's route)
After going around,
where would they go first?
Let's go.
There's something I want to try. Is there raw fish?
- Let's go around then.
- Sure.
(Vermicelli tteokbokki, spring cabbage bibimbap)
Oh, tteokbokki.
Spring cabbage is really popular these days.
Oh, curry.
Karaage.
That looks delicious too.
(Passing for now)
Puffer fish soup.
- Mianbao xia.
I want to eat it all.
Oh, marinated shrimp.
- We can't see the chefs?
- Nice.
What?
There's also glutinous rice nurungji.
- I'm having that for now.
- What?
- I want to eat that.
- Go get it.
(What does the first customer choose?)
Mom.
(Gotgan)
- No customers?
- They're ordering.
- We order here.
- Marinated shrimp.
(Jeju marinated shrimp noodle combo for 17.90 dollars)
One marinated shrimp.
(The first order goes to Kim Mi Ryeong.)
Office workers want to eat quickly...
and get some rest during lunch.
I prepared everything, so I could serve it right away.
(1. Vegetables and sauce prepared)
(2. Roasted laver prepared)
(3. Boil noodles and rinse them in cold water.)
I'll prepare the cutting board.
- Just rinse the noodles for me.
- Okay.
(Everything is prepared in advance to reduce the wait time.)
(When the order comes in,)
(it's quickly prepared for office workers.)
I need more black pepper.
- Is this okay?
- Yes.
Let's go.
(It took a minute and half to be served.)
(Exclaiming)
For the first round,
we decided to sell everything quickly during lunch.
We plan to rest during dinner.
Yes.
(Gotgan plans to emphasize on the speed.)
One is ready.
Why do we need to talk when we're here to work?
Everything is prepared in order.
Thank you. Enjoy.
I think we have to order a lot.
(Jeju marinated shrimp noodle combo for 17.90 dollars)
When I was first told about the mission,
I was told it'd be a blind test.
And that we couldn't talk to the customers that much.
If we can't explain the dish,
and if it's a blind test,
we might as well write it nicely and serve it with the food.
So, tips like...
how it tastes better with laver.
We wrote those tips on paper.
We should try it with laver.
- Really?
- Yes.
It's written here.
Wrap the raw fish and noodles with laver.
(The customers try the food as Gotgan intends.)
It's the best bibim guksu I've ever had.
- I know. I agree.
- So good.
How come we're not getting any orders?
No one...
- Ramyeon sounds good.
- That looks good.
- Let's get ramyeon too.
- Yes.
We saw everything.
What should we eat?
Gosh. What should we get first?
Do you want to check it out again?
- Oh, it's steak rice.
- Oh, steak rice sounds good.
I want to have steak rice.
Oh, what? This is crazy.
Is it two?
- Two?
- One?
- One. Oh, it's one.
- One.
(Immediately followed by more customers)
Okay. We're getting more.
Two steak rice.
What? Why are you getting so many?
Let's go. Oh, hot.
See you later.
See you up there.
I should roast the meat, right?
Place onions.
Add the tare sauce.
(Stir-fried onion on a bowl of rice, tare sauce)
- The meat is ready.
- Okay.
For one serving, right?
Is it a little too much?
It's a little too much, but it's good.
Since it's for our first customer.
(Tenderloin steak rice for 13 dollars)
You can take this.
Enjoy.
- Enjoy. Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Thank you for the food.
- Hurry up and try it.
Okay.
(Exclaiming)
- Good?
- Yes.
The steak is really good.
Yes. They did a good job of grilling.
It's not chewy at all.
This meat is different. I can't stop eating it.
- I know. It's not dry at all.
- No.
- I'd totally pay for this price.
- Me too.
If we could get it for this price in Sejong,
- we'd totally line up for it.
- Yes.
- They're checking it out first.
- Did they go to the next door?
Come on. Come to this side.
How come no one's coming to this side?
- They're here.
(Gyeol, BokBok, Gotgan)
- They left.
- Did they leave?
I was begging for them to stop, but they kept leaving.
It's been a while since I waited for customers to come.
It's the first time...
I've ever waited for customers to come this desperately.
Gosh.
There's no room to eat in Mokran.
Try it here.
That's what I mean.
(Tiptoeing desperately)
Well...
We have one person coming.
I think she's ordering.
We got it.
- What is it?
- One jjamppong.
One best mianbao xia.
One mianbao xia, one jjamppong.
I'll make it delicious.
I can't stop laughing even making jjamppong.
I can't believe how happy I am...
to get an order of 1 jjamppong and 1 mianbao xia.
In my restaurant...
(Laughing)
If we make it look delicious, other people will see it and go,
"Where did you get that from?"
"Where's that from?"
(Current sales: 27 dollars)
Done.
(Another restaurant at the same time)
It's the spring cabbage.
(Turning away)
(Customers keep passing.)
(Arirang House)
It seems...
there's no rush.
Is everyone else the same?
It's hard to sell 1,000 dollars during lunch.
We have to work to death to make that happen.
Business is tough.
(Go Min Seong, teammate)
Let's face it. Office workers...
don't grab something fancy for lunch.
So I picked the menu you'd find easily.
The bibimbap with spring cabbage and cockle...
and bossam combo.
We need to sell something appropriate for the business area.
So I thought a lot about...
what they'd want for lunch.
It's mostly men.
There are women, but a lot more men.
(There are more men than women.)
And they don't like to share.
(They don't share the food.)
I thought they'd have...
soup in the end.
Something that can be boiled and served right away.
And something that can be sliced and served right away.
I think that's the best. The meat soup...
- with meat and kimchi.
- Yes.
That's the best. Let's make it a combo.
You're good.
I focused...
on a combo for one person...
instead of something to share.
(Quiet)
I think it was a mistake.
I guess my strategy was wrong.
No.
(On the other hand)
Enough for 2 to 3 persons.
Do you want to get this? Should I order it?
There are more people coming anyway.
- Then we can share it.
- Yes.
We can tell them to come.
It's for 2 to 3 persons. Should I get it?
- What?
- This is for 2 to 3 persons.
(Order)
It's all Korean calcot. This is crazy.
Wait. There are too many.
This is crazy.
What? Awesome.
The Korean calcot is our good kid.
It's our good kid.
Our item is...
the chicken with Korean calcot and glutinous rice nurungji.
(The chicken with Korean calcot...)
(and glutinous rice nurungji for 28 dollars)
I knew it. I told you...
people share food in this town.
They're sharing.
It was my strategy.
We knew other places would come up with a combo,
so we planned a dish to share on purpose.
- Yes.
- Right.
(During the opening ceremony)
(No one paid attention to the tables.)
This must be big. It's for four people.
Then they'll share.
So they'd prefer...
something like a platter...
to share.
And the public officials...
I noticed the tables were for four people.
I knew people were going to share for sure.
So in the brackets,
I wrote it's enough to share.
(For 2 to 3 persons)
(She prepared a dish which is enough for 2 to 3 people.)
(Groups of customers start ordering something to share.)
What are you getting?
- I don't know.
- For 2 to 3 persons?
Sounds good to me.
- Is that the item...
- This is nice.
- which is available in 20 per day?
- Yes.
- The Korean calcot.
- Okay. Pay now.
(Only 20 available)
We decided to make it limited,
so people can't help but order it.
That was our plan.
So we added that it was a limited menu for 20 people.
These onions are available...
only for a month.
(Seasonal onions only cultivated in Hamyang)
(Limited availability using the limited seasonal ingredient)
- Only 20 supplies.
- Only 20?
- There's a limit.
- Then we should order it now.
The glutinous rice nurungji with Korean calcot.
Only 20. Order it now.
- Only 20 supplies.
- What?
- Do you want to eat this?
- Yes.
- Shall we get that?
- Sure then.
- Are we getting this?
- Then we can all share.
- The seat...
- I'll pay for everything.
- Let's all share.
Yes.
This is insane.
(When she finishes serving one,)
(another order comes in.)
One Korean calcot ready.
Okay.
What happened?
Don't worry about it.
It fell on the floor.
No way.
This is crazy.
The bills were...
There were so many bills printing...
- that they fell on the floor.
- There were just too many.
They dripped down to the floor.
Like a sagging tongue.
"What am I going to do?"
It was a perfect strategy.
Chef Jo Seo Hyung.
She's a business genius.
I offered her to work together,
but she rejected me.
She's that good.
Gosh, this is insane.
We have so many.
This is unbelievable.
(Another bill dripping down)
I've always wanted to try this.
- American girls on YouTube...
- Really?
Oh, I know that. It's very popular these days.
The chimichanga full of cheese.
- I know this.
- Yes.
- It's famous in the US army camp.
Yes. This one.
- Do you want to try that?
- Yes.
- The chili cheese stick.
- Right.
(The trending video is already playing outside.)
I know what to do at gigs.
And how to approach people...
on the spot.
We prepared a large TV...
and played videos of people eating our food.
(The eating shows to draw people's attention)
When we play that video,
I'm sure people will feel like to eat it.
When will we get to try this again?
One chimichanga and one chili cheese stick.
- We have to eat this.
- Right?
- We should eat it.
- Chimichanga?
It's trendy these days.
- It's trendy?
- The cheese stick. Yes.
Are you ready to order?
(The trendy item continues to draw customers.)
Ji Beom, let's get started.
Finally, it's showtime.
- Oh, thank you.
- Thank you.
I'd better serve the customers fast.
So I served the food quietly and quickly.
I'm going smart. I'm serving two at a time.
Yes. That's a good idea.
Oh, I haven't seen bills like these in a long time.
How many cheese sticks do you need?
Cheese sticks? Three in total.
To make a cheese stick, I cut mozzarella in whole,
coat it with flour, egg, and breadcrumbs,
and fry it for 2 to 3 minutes.
And dip it...
in the Nashville sauce...
which tastes sweet and salty like chips.
(The Nashville sauce enhances the cheese stick flavor.)
- Is it another combo?
- Yes.
Okay.
Enjoy.
(2nd combo)
(3rd combo)
(4th combo)
(5th combo)
How far does it stretch?
Awesome.
I can eat three with no problem.
(Gone in no time)
What is that?
- It's chimichanga.
- Over there.
- Number 1.
- Number 1? Thank you.
(The reason it's more favorable for the food that's sold first)
(Glancing)
What's best?
- The steak rice.
- I'd say this.
- Where is it?
- The steak rice...
- You can get it from HunGry.
- HunGry.
- HunGry?
- It's delicious.
(It automatically promotes the food.)
What about steak rice?
Look at this.
Tenderloin steak rice for 13 dollars?
Not bad.
I think the steak rice is selling well.
They're ordering the tenderloin steak rice.
I knew it would be popular.
We plan to sell one every minute for lunch.
Since we spent a lot on the ingredients, we'll sell a lot.
We're confident.
I told you.
I don't feel confident about losing.
I'm going to sell 130 servings during lunch, Jong In.
What? Okay. Good attitude.
Two tenderloin rice.
One is ready.
We have so many orders.
- Just keep going, okay?
- Yes.
(The current sales: minus 142.46 dollars)
(Minus 67.46 dollars)
There's a line.
This place is crowded.
(The current sales: 390.54 dollars)
Jong In, make 20 servings of steak rice. Okay?
Yes.
(One more wok at work)
(Despite the gush of orders,)
Your food is ready.
(their speed is stable.)
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
Here you are. Enjoy.
I think we sold like 5,000 dollars.
Is it...
- Keep up the good work.
- okay for me to rest now?
- It's so hectic.
- Nice.
My arms are killing me.
- Done.
- Let's hurry up.
I won't be able to sleep if I lose.
(Number One)
We have the first survivor...
of the 1,000 dollar sales race.
We have the first survivor.
(Exclaiming)
Oh, I'm so jealous.
- Already?
- Oh, my.
- Who is it?
Who is it?
I don't think it's been one hour yet.
Already?
(Current time)
(It hasn't been an hour since the opening.)
(Reaching 1,000 dollars in sales)
(Which restaurant is the first to survive?)
It's stir-fried.
(HunGry, Kim Hoon)
(Bol A Bol, Lim Ki Hak)
(Gotgan, Kim Mi Ryeong)
(Number One, Kwak Dong Hoon)
(Round 1, a district dominated by office workers)
(A 1,000 dollar sales race)
The first restaurant to survive is...
The Star In My Heart.
(Jo Seo Hyung, current sales of 1,136 dollars)
- The Star In My Heart.
- What?
We just need to finish the remaining orders.
- The Star In My Heart.
- What?
We just need to finish the remaining orders.
- Let's hurry.
- Quickly.
Quickly.
We just need to finish the remaining orders.
My gosh.
Chef Jo Seo Hyung at The Star In My Heart?
It's Chef Jo Seo Hyung.
The Star In My Heart.
That's awesome.
Congratulations.
She's good at running a business.
- She's a business genius.
- That's insane.
How did they sell so quickly?
It's only been an hour.
What? How did they manage to sell that much?
- Clearly...
- That was solid.
I can tell that she has intuition.
How many people even know about Korean calcot?
It's a special seasonal ingredient.
The appearance and the story behind it.
She clearly understands...
what her customers like.
It's something familiar with a slight twist.
She turned it into something refined.
She made a unique dish.
On top of that, it was expensive in the beginning.
It was around 28 dollars.
(The Star In My Heart prepared the most expensive dish to share.)
Try this. It's really good.
I'm serious. Try it.
- We also ordered that.
- This is it.
There are only 20 supplies.
- We definitely have to try it.
- This one?
Twenty limited supplies.
What's this?
- This one?
- You can get it there.
- The Star In My Heart.
- Twenty limited supplies.
- Really?
- Yes.
How much is it?
We had many customers who came because...
- they saw other people eating it.
- Right.
That was part of our strategy.
We intentionally created a dish that looked substantial.
We also provided a lot on the side.
(Seasoned bean sprouts and potato salad)
It worked as a form of promotion.
(Checking the restaurant menu)
(Eyes fixed)
She knows how to play the game.
Even in a situation where everything was restricted,
I made sure that...
the value was justified.
People calling me a business genius...
I'll stop here.
- This is crazy.
- I know, but we survived.
Jae Beom, we survived, so we're safe.
I've been on survival shows before.
This cancels the survival...
of The Star In My Heart.
- What?
- That's ruthless.
- It's canceled?
- That's so harsh.
- What?
- Gosh.
Why was it canceled?
Are they doing it on purpose to make it entertaining?
Let's be honest. This is ridiculous.
(The competition is reset.)
(We can't sell it like this.)
(A ruthless, unpredictable real-world battle of business)
(We're in trouble. It's a race against time.)
(They must've waited for a long time.)
(It's a signal to serve them fast.)
(The first 1-star review appears.)
(That was a moment of total panic.)
Let's see who wins.
(Will it be rising newcomers...)
(or veterans fighting for survival?)
(Which restaurant recorded the lowest sales?)
(It damages my sense of pride.)
(I'll give everything I've got.)
(You think I can't make 1,000 dollars?)
(In an unpredictable real-world business,)
(be the first to survive.)
(The dinner sales begin.)
(I'm most curious about who will walk in.)
- The door to Street Arena...
- They are coming.
is opening.
(All of them are families.)
(All of them are children.)
(This changes everything.)
(Things are different from how they were at lunch.)
(Mom, I want some too.)