This month,
there've been so many accidents,
all concentrated on Aimin Street.
Hello.
Factory Office Secretariat here.
This is bad.
Hello, Factory Office.
I've been exposed.
I need a clean up.
Who are you people?
Do you know who I am?
Why are you tying her up?
Where are you going?
To clean up.
Hold on.
He's going with you.
I'm used to working alone.
That's an order.
So you're Liu Tianqi.
You're my idol!
Let's swap notes later, yeah?
Secretary Jiao.
I just can't figure it out.
Why is Boss Long stirring up so much trouble?
I mean, everyone's moved out.
Is the land still worth anything?
Reportedly,
recent frequent accidents on Aimin Street
have caused many residents to move away.
The cause is under investigation.
Our reporter will keep you updated.
What rotten luck.
Isn't this all Brother Hai's territory?
Now property values on Aimin Street
have totally tanked.
I'm just saying,
can't you wish Brother Hai well?
Secretary Jiao, that chick inside
is pretty good-looking.
Let us have some fun.
Do whatever you want.
I'm taking off.
Sounds disgusting.
No problem, Secretary Jiao.
You three, stand guard.
I'll have some fun first.
Listen up, people inside!
You are surrounded!
Drop your weapons immediately!
Boss, what do we do now?
What do you mean what do we do? We fight!
I...
Hand over the hostage now!
You're surrounded!
Zhu Yihai!
I'll get you out of here!
Follow me.
Boss, let's just surrender.
Don't you dare.
I'll go down first.
I'll catch you at the bottom.
Hurry up!
I... I'm too scared!
I'll catch you!
Boss, those are gunshots!
Go grab that woman inside as a hostage!
Okay, okay.
They're all coming!
Hurry!
I'll carry you.
How much do you weigh?
You...
Boss, this is bad!
That woman got away!
What do we do now?
What do you mean what do we do?
Surrender, of course.
It's okay.
What... what is this?
What's going on?
Secretary Jiao!
What are you doing here?
Boss Long said
we can't be careless about this.
Don't worry, leave it to me. No problem.
Wei Wei.
You sure can fight, kid.
Move again, I dare you.
You brought a knife too?
Good thing Dahai knew all along
that you two would come.
Wei Wei, time's tight. Listen to me.
You and Dali, get to Huilian's place now.
And tell Dao Balian.
Have him bring plenty of men.
Where'd you two get such nerve?
Daring to bully my Huilian.
Huilian.
Don't worry.
I'm here.
Take them to the police station.
Useless except for screwing things up.
Where you off to?
What happened to being together forever?
What's wrong?
Why the rush?
Run into some trouble?
What do you guys want?
What could we possibly want?
Just here for a little chat.
Don't rush off.
Yeah, exactly.
Whatever the trouble is, we'll help fix it.
Go on, spill it.
Yihai,
Please, save me!
Long Xiao forced me to do it all.
Since Ge Zhendong gave you Aimin Street,
Long Xiao's been dying to get rid of you.
He had Liu Tianqi sneak into Ge Zhendong's
office and steal the public funds.
Then Liu Tianqi gave all the money to me
so I could frame you for it.
But I really didn't expect
that day it'd be Xiong Dali, not you.
Then thank goodness for Dali.
Without him, wouldn't I be in jail now?
If you had really gone to jail,
I would've surrendered
to make sure the truth came out.
Zhu Yihai.
Quite the charmer, aren't you?
Listen to her yapping away.
Everything I said is true!
Back then, to pay off my family's debt...
Later, Long Xiao bought my freedom.
I had no choice but to work for him.
I never want to go back to that life.
After meeting you, I started thinking,
if you were the one who saved me,
instead of Long Xiao,
would my fate have been different?
Jiao Jing,
Repent and be saved.
Alright, sis.
Say no more.
Take me away with you.
I'll find a way to explain things for you.
That's great!
Jiao Jing, don't move!
Put down the knife!
Nobody move!
This blade doesn't have eyes!
I'm warning you, don't do anything stupid!
I don't have a choice anymore.
Jiao Jing!
Didn't you say you didn't want your old life?
I can save you.
I can take you away.
But you can't lie to me anymore.
Take me away?
Where would you take me?
I don't have a home anymore.
Without Long Xiao,
I'm just a wandering ghost.
I can understand you,
Jiao Jing.
But the one Long Xiao wants is me,
not her.
Let her go, alright?
Aw, she's worried about you.
What I can't have,
you won't get either.
You're insane!
Didn't I tell you?
Don't do anything stupid!
Yihai!
Hold on!
Yihai, hold on!
Hold on, you have to hold on!
You have to hold on!
Doctor, I have Type AB blood!
Does he need a transfusion?
Into the OR, prep for transfusion.
Yihai, hold on!
You'll be okay.
Come on, hurry!