=The Embroidered Truth=
Rulan...
They're all forcing me.
Rulan.
(Rulan,)
(I was too weak.)
(I didn't stand with you.)
(I will avenge you.)
(Lin Rulan's Grave)
Wan, you still remember
we all love chestnut cakes.
I'll stay by Wu Lian's side
to send you word.
Step by step, lead him into our trap.
Let him taste
what it's like to be trapped
with no escape.
=Episode 18=
Nanny Du,
I feel truly old.
Nonsense. You're in your prime.
In my prime?
I would never let those two
play their games before me.
I was just thinking,
since you've seen through
their schemes,
why keep them here?
Those two...
One is an embroiderer who
preserves my youth,
the other is a cousin who helps me
keep the Prince.
If they stay,
they remain useful.
If I send them away,
they might cause even greater trouble.
I fear I couldn't explain it
to the Prince.
What about the real Lady Cheng'en?
Shen Ruoheng? She refused to come, fine.
But sending a maid to impersonate her?
I'm letting that slide.
That's her good fortune.
Would she dare confront me?
Don't forget,
my late father-in-law
saved her family's lives.
Very true.
But I just fear there may be secrets
between that girl and Lady Cheng'en.
She's just a girl with a grudge
against Wu Lian.
It doesn't matter.
As long as she pleases the Prince,
who at my manor would believe her?
Her life is mine to decide.
Besides, even if there are secrets,
wouldn't she fear implicating
the real Ruoheng?
You've thought of everything.
Oh, right.
Tell Luoxia to watch Meng Wan.
Let's see
what schemes they can hatch
right under my nose.
Yes.
Their antics have tired me out.
Now, I want to go out
for some fresh air.
Why are you here?
Come to gloat?
Wan, I sent the guards away.
You've suffered.
We must be careful.
Wu Lian is vicious and deceitful.
His hand was never hurt.
All an act for the Princess Consort.
Rulan, don't agree to anything.
If not for me,
you wouldn't be...
Three years ago, I thought
you were dead.
The next day, I went to
Yanyu Embroidery House.
I begged Wu Lian to take me in,
to work for him,
to be his servant.
I only wanted to find proof
that he drove you to your death.
Without your secret notes,
risking everything,
helping me in the shadows,
and Mr. Liu and the Yehu Gang,
I never would have lasted till today.
Wu Lian has done so much evil,
incurring public outrage.
Most of his victims dare not speak.
Only you stood up.
The day you went to your death,
we were too cowardly to speak.
Now, we're risking our lives
to help you and to make up for
the regret of staying silent
three years ago.
I couldn't save you then.
This time, I'll die with no regrets.
Don't say that.
Mr. Liu is safe now.
In a day or two,
I'll get you out.
The list is what matters.
Did Xiaoshou find it?
Why should I respect you?
Isn't it enough that you got my master
poisoned and his hand hurt?
Respect you?
Let me tell you,
my master holds secrets of
every powerful family in the city.
Your fate may not be better than mine.
How does it feel to be in prison?
Daring to curse the Princess Consort
with a headless pheasant.
When the Prince returns,
you're as good as dead.
How dare you hit me?
I wanted to see
what you look like now,
you wretched woman.
I'll make sure you can't live
and can't die.
Wan, why did you do that?
It's nothing.
Without that slap,
how could others believe you?
By the way,
look.
I accidentally broke it.
I remember back then,
you always snuck into the small kitchen
to steal chestnut cakes.
Wan.
Look.
You stole chestnut cakes again.
Try one.
Master Wu has arrived.
How is it?
As sweet as before.
Alright.
Go now.
Someone might see.
Wait for me, Wan.
I'll get you out.
I know.
Go.
♪My heart still shines through dust♪
Rulan.
♪Bare hands weave through the frost♪
♪Shadows linger, rain returns♪
♪Honor crowns my weary soul♪
♪For your faith that never broke♪
♪I shattered all the love I knew♪
♪No regrets, no debts unpaid♪
♪At dusk I walk away alone♪
♪If this tale becomes a storm♪
♪Old shadows fade from sight♪
♪One thought turns into ash♪
♪No future left to write♪
♪The lamp is out, you're gone♪
♪Heaven and earth fall silent♪
♪If we meet again someday♪
♪This longing sleeps beneath the snow♪
Be well.
You must be well.
Go.
Wait for me.
(Rulan,)
(three years ago, I was a coward.
I couldn't save you.)
(This time, let me be brave.)
(Your path to revenge
is too hard.)
(If sacrifice is inevitable,)
(let it be me.)
(Let my life)
(be the sharpest blade in your hand.)
(Rulan.)
(You must live on)
(for both of us.)
♪Night fades before the dawn♪
♪Old vows still guide my hand♪
♪The past no longer binds♪
♪My heart still shines through dust♪
♪Silent blooms, unchanged heart♪
♪Bare hands weave through the frost♪
♪Shadows linger, rain returns♪
♪Honor crowns my weary soul♪
♪For your faith that never broke♪
♪I shattered all the love I knew♪
♪No regrets, no debts unpaid♪
♪At dusk I walk away alone♪
♪If this tale becomes a storm♪
♪Old shadows fade from sight♪
♪One thought turns into ash♪
♪No future left to write♪
♪If I never fall♪
♪How could this waiting end♪
♪If I bear no scars♪
♪How could I challenge fate♪
♪I knew there was no way back♪
♪Yet I left this hope behind♪
♪For your faith that never broke♪
♪I shattered all the love I knew♪
♪No regrets, no debts unpaid♪
♪At dusk I walk away alone♪
♪If this tale becomes a storm♪
♪Old shadows fade from sight♪
♪One thought turns into ash♪
♪No future left to write♪
♪The lamp is out, you're gone♪
♪Heaven and earth fall silent♪
♪If we meet again someday♪
♪This longing sleeps beneath the snow♪