[The Legend of Rosy Clouds]
[Episode 10]
I'm back!
Dad!
Dad.
Come take a look!
Here.
You lost!
Drink up.
Come on.
When you leave the city tomorrow,
make sure to find these women.
Master.
What's wrong?
You work day and night.
You really need to take a breather.
How insolent!
These women are bewitching the governor.
That means
Her Ladyship's been secretly dissatisfied
for a long time.
We must
teach them a lesson.
-Yes.
-Go along.
What were you thinking?
My grandson.
Grandfather.
Time for your medicine.
Grandfather?
Grandfather.
You were against
the governor and Her Ladyship's
marriage.
Now they're finally getting a divorce,
why are you trying to
get them back together?
A governor of the Nine Cities
has never gotten a divorce before.
As one of the Three Elders
in the Nine Cities,
how can I just sit back and watch?
Moral codes and etiquette can be
destroyed by the slightest exception.
We can't let them set this precedent.
The precedent has already been set.
As outsiders, do we really need
to sincerely persuade them to reconcile?
You make a good point.
The crux of the issue is that
Her Ladyship is
unsatisfied
with the governor's show of affection.
How about this?
Women
like gifts the most,
like jewelry.
Tomorrow, go and pick
a gift with a young man's taste,
and present it
as a peace offering
on behalf of the governor.
Perhaps,
maybe,
Her Ladyship will
accept the apology.
Me?
You want me to make peace
for the governor?
Do I really have to do it?
Fine.
OK. Sure.
Your Excellency!
Lord Zheng said
we shouldn't come here again.
Hu Die sent a secret letter
asking us to come over.
But...
Wei Ying!
[Song of the Oriole]
Remove
your head scarves
for the gentlemen to have a look.
Take them off!
I...
What happened?
Weren't you fine the other day?
So a beauty really
doesn't rely on her hair and makeup.
There is
a distinctive charm to this look.
These ladies woke up today
to this crazy hair!
Your Excellency,
do you think
we're being targeted?
Right.
They're even intimidating us like this.
Who do you think would do such a thing?
Who else could it be?
It has to be Elder Zheng.
But this is unexpected.
He was so critical of Fan Yun back then,
so we didn't even factor him in
as a hurdle
in the divorce plan.
Why is he
against the divorce now?
Lord Zheng is entrusted
by the former governor to assist me;
to mold and restrain me
as a role model for the Nine Cities.
He would rather I be mediocre
than be out of line.
Let's go!
To the Fan residence.
-What about his... Yes.
-Let's go.
Goodness!
Who is it? So impatient!
May I ask if you are
Lord Fan Qi?
I am.
Who...
Who might you be?
I'm Lou Qiyan of Juyun Pavilion.
On the order of Lord Zheng, I'm here to
deliver apology gifts to Her Ladyship
on behalf of the governor.
Juyun Pavilion?
It's an honor to meet you.
However, my stubborn daughter
ran back home without permission.
How could we accept gifts?
Let me thank
the governor and Lord Zheng's kindness
on behalf of my daughter.
Please go back.
Let me explain.
Juyun Pavilion acts for money.
I don't want to
get involved in the governor
and Her Ladyship's private affairs.
I hope you accept the gifts,
so I can complete this commission.
Then tell Lord Zheng that
I, Fan Qi,
absolutely
refused to accept them!
Whatever happens,
you're exempted from blame.
That's it! Alright! Thanks!
Alright.
Smash all the gifts.
Yes!
Don't! Don't smash them!
Don't. Stop.
What a waste to smash them.
It was unnecessary to bring gifts
on behalf of the governor.
We'll just deal with it here.
Keep smashing.
Don't, don't...
You can return them!
What for?
Lord Fan, you're right.
These gifts are pointless to begin with.
-They're an eyesore.
-Exactly.
Smash them!
When did I say that?
I...
Stop!
This... This...
What nice sesame flatbread!
It's a pity to waste it. Goodness.
The sesame flatbread isn't worth much.
The sesame is fragrant.
Fresh sesame.
-It smells so good.
-Your Excellency.
Your Excellency!
We're here?
Looks like someone got here before us.
Look at this.
Clearly made with fresh sesame.
Him again?
Looks like he's making a delivery.
He's always pestering Fan Yun.
I've been sick of him for a long time.
Come.
Help me get off.
Your Excellency,
you came today
to discuss with Her Ladyship
tomorrow's arrangements.
If another conflict arises,
it might be used against us.
You have a point.
Every grain of rice
is hard-won.
Stop smashing the gifts.
Move them inside, please.
They're all ruined.
Let's forget about it.
No, no, no.
-Smash...
-No!
Move them inside.
Come on. Come.
But...
Please. Come in.
Hey, look!
The nerve of him to enter her home!
-Your Excellency,
-it seems he was dragged in.
I don't believe I can't keep you in check.
I'm getting off!
Please have some tea.
Dad.
Zheng...
Young Master Qiyan,
why are you here?
Miss Fan,
we meet again.
You know each other?
-I...
-I'm a merchant.
I've heard a lot about Teacher Fan
from the private school
across the street.
That's right.
The private school kids
are the apple of Yun's eye.
Well...
Young Master Lou,
is the tea
to your liking?
Dad.
There are hundreds of teahouses
under my Juyun Pavilion,
but none of them
can brew tea like this.
What does that mean?
Is it
good or bad?
Exceptional.
Well said.
You're clearly an experienced merchant
who has seen the world.
Young Master Lou was
entrusted by Second Young Master Zheng
to deliver
the governor's
apology gifts.
It's up to you
how we deal with them.
I'll go
boil more water
so you can
properly savor this tea.
Exceptional!
Did my dad just say
the governor
asked you to deliver these apology gifts?
You grew up drinking such tea?
Then I like it too.
It's quite nice.
Are you here today
representing
Juyun Pavilion
or
Lord Zheng?
It's purely business.
But I also have a personal question.
What is it?
Are you really set on
getting the divorce?
I'm afraid
this isn't
something you should be asking.
I'm still his wife right now.
Why use a title given by others
to label yourself?
You are you,
not anyone's accessory.
I heard someone is running errands
for my sake.
Let me see who is so concerned.
Your Excellency?
So it's you.
Did you bring
all these things here?
You know some manners, huh?
Today, I'm Lord Zheng's envoy,
here to share Your Excellency's burdens.
You're Elder Zheng's grandson.
I don't need his grandson
to worry about my affairs.
Since I, her rightful man, have arrived,
if there's nothing else,
you'd best take your leave.
This is my home.
Isn't your home my home?
Still here?
In that case, help me relay a message
to Lord Zheng.
Tell him that tomorrow,
my wife and I will visit
the Three Elders together.
I shall take my leave then.
Didn't we agree
to get a divorce?
Why'd you act all jealous just now?
Now the fight we had was for nothing!
All that acting was for nothing!
I just don't like that fellow.
You are my woman.
Why is he acting so attentive to my woman?
I won't allow it!
I...
I also think
his motives aren't pure.
Maybe
he was sent by Lord Zheng
to test us.
You should have been colder just now,
or just scolded me directly.
That's the right move.
Alright.
I have something to give you.
What is this?
Hey...
The divorce paper.
We just
barely mentioned it,
and it's already
caused a scandal all over town.
If we bring this divorce paper
to the Three Elders tomorrow,
and they still disagree, what then?
I suppose the Three Elders want to see us
to mediate a reconciliation.
But as long as we convince them,
we'll be close to success.
I doubt it'll be that easy.
We've had the fight,
and we've put on the act.
What else can we do?
How about we
get into a fist fight?
That's really not necessary.
We'll definitely
think of a compelling reason.
What reason?
What options do we have?
How can we make them agree...
Your Excellency,
I actually have an idea.
They can't refute this.
What crazy idea do you have now?
To divorce me,
do you have to go to such lengths?
Fine.
Tell me about it.
You... Well...
It won't work if I say it now.
Just tell me how much pressure
you can handle.
Pressure?
I govern the Nine Cities.
What do I carry on my shoulders?
The weight of an empire!
Is there anything I can't handle?
Bring it on.
So that means
you agree?
I can say whatever I want then?
Great.
Tomorrow's success
hinges on this.
They're finally willing to see us.
Maybe this mediation
will be a piece of cake.
Zheng, you're really something.
With just a few words,
you made the governor
realize his folly.
I'm adept at
settling external affairs
and pacifying internal turmoil.
But in the future, please don't bother me
with this kind of thing again.
Your Excellency,
I heard that your divorce
has become the talk of the town.
Today, I gathered the ministers
to help reconcile
Your Excellency
and Her Ladyship.
Your Excellency,
since Her Ladyship
moved into your residence,
you two have been a match made in heaven.
Her Ladyship
fulfills her filial duties to the utmost
and is highly praised for her virtue.
May I ask Your Excellency
why you want to divorce Her Ladyship?
Your Ladyship.
Since the wedding, His Excellency has
visited the inner chambers
every day, right?
He treats you with great adoration
and sees you as an equal.
May I ask
why you want to
divorce His Excellency?
Lord Lyu, you're right.
But since entering
the Qi Residence,
I've also been
deliberating day and night
about how to better serve the governor.
But the governor
is always moody.
I've become a punching bag for him
to vent his anger on.
Well...
It's like this.
His Excellency
governs the Nine Cities after all.
Moreover, this year, there have been
quite a few disasters.
The governor is
devoted to official duties all day,
so he inevitably
worries a lot for the people.
By the time he returns home,
he's bound to be a bit temperamental.
Don't take it to heart.
Spouses don't hold grudges overnight.
Not to mention
these are all trivial matters...
It's best for Your Ladyship to return
to the Qi Residence
as soon as possible.
Yes, yes.
Do you really want to know?
Of course.
The governor's divorce is a major affair.
Everyone in the world
is waiting for an answer.
I thought I should avoid
making such remarks
out of respect for the governor.
Now it seems...
I have no choice but to come out with it.
I forgot to tell you
I can't handle any more pressure.
Don't worry, Your Excellency.
The reason is that
the governor...
His Excellency...
can't function in bed.
-What?
What do you mean?
He...
can't function at all.
He can't function at all?
This embarrassment is too much to bear.
After Her Ladyship's remarks,
who'd still dare to
urge them to reconcile?
Exactly.
Zheng,
all the ministers in the Qi Residence
are watching the three of us.
Listen to me.
Be it the youngsters' ignorance,
or if they have other ideas,
or if he can function or not,
with Lord Jiang Shu here,
I doubt they'd dare to talk nonsense.
Lord Jiang.
Lord Jiang,
you're the best physician
in the Nine Cities.
We're counting on you.
I understand.
Please.
Your Excellency.
-You're awake.
-Your Excellency.
He...
Who are you?
Could it be that His Excellency is
traumatized by the verbal abuse
in the main hall yesterday?
Your Excellency,
the issue hasn't been resolved.
Feigning memory loss is useless.
Eight.
-Ten.
-That unconvincing?
Get your fingers out of my face,
or I'd really go blind.
Help me up.
Put my shoes on.
You two are the absolute best to me.
Look at this.
What is all this?
These are all tonics from the officials.
Let's put it this way:
as the governor and his wife
clamor for divorce,
all the tigers in the Nine Cities
had to suffer.
Are you serious?
Forgive me for my sins.
What are you doing?
-Your Ladyship!
We'll take our leave.
Don't go!
Enjoy the tonics.
Let's get out of here.
Your Excellency.
Your Excellency!
Are you mad at me?
Of course I am!
Your Excellency!
I only said that
because you said
you could bear immense pressure.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have said it.
Yes,
I did say
I could bear the pressure,
but I didn't say I could bear slander!
And couldn't you
have found a better excuse?
Why did you...
resort to that!
Don't worry.
I just made up an excuse.
It doesn't mean it's true.
What I say doesn't affect
your bodily functions,
am I right?
But now...
Don't be mad...
Your Excellency,
the Three Elders are here.
Lord Jiang Shu is also here.
Quick! Quick!
Not Lord Jiang!
W-Wouldn't we be exposed then?
Greetings, Elders.
Greetings, Your Excellency.
Elders,
His Excellency...
passed out from exhaustion.
-Lord Jiang.
-He passed out?
Do what you need to do.
L-Lord Jiang!
Today,
the governor is really not feeling well.
We couldn't wake him up
no matter how hard we tried.
Why don't we
-do this another day...
-It's fine.
I must take his pulse
to know what's going on.
Lord Jiang,
how is His Excellency?
It's over.
What's over?
Your Ladyship was telling the truth.
What?
This...
L-Lord Jiang,
are these tiger penises
and bear galls useless?
Are they?
Even dragon livers and phoenix brains
wouldn't work.
Miss Fan,
it seems
this is a tricky situation.
I'd advise you to
go through with the divorce.
But...
Then...
Your Excellency!
Your... Your Excellency!
Your Excellency,
don't take things too hard.
I'm sorry. I really am.
Y-You know
I really just made up an excuse
to fool the Three Elders.
Who knew
you actually really
-can't function...
-Fan Yun, stop talking.
I want to be alone for a while.
Your Excellency,
don't be afraid.
Dysfunctions can be treated.
I don't believe
there's no one
who can cure you in this vast world!
I'm not ill!
Your Excellency,
please, I'm begging you.
Don't just sulk alone and shut me out.
How about we
go to Lord Jiang
and ask him for medicine?
Maybe after a few doses,
you'll be fine!
Your Excellency.
Trust me.
This can definitely be cured.
I'm sure of it.
Absolutely.
Say something, Lord Jiang.
The governor has arrived!
The governor is here.
Welcome, Your Excellency.
You may rise, my dear ministers.
Thank you, Your Excellency.
My Lady spread rumors about me.
The divorce
is set in stone.
Effective immediately,
she'll resume her status
as a member of the Fan household
and move out of the Qi Residence.
You may leave.
We will take our leave, Your Excellency.
Proclamation from the governor:
"Although Her Ladyship is virtuous
and devoted to marital duties,
due to incompatible personalities,
we are divorcing.
From this day on,
she'll resume her status
as a member of the Fan household.
End of proclamation."
This is the first divorce of a governor.
Divorcing the governor
is unheard of.
Exactly.
But I heard that
the governor seems to have some issues.
What issues?
Don't ask too much.
Yeah.
I heard about it too.
What will become of our Nine Cities now?
I know, right?
Fan Yun, are you
taking these pieces of jewelry with you?
Nope.
I'll just take some
stuff I brought from home.
I'll leave everything else here.
Are you really leaving?
Yes, it's as real as it gets.
Besides, the governor's proclamation
has been issued.
I've been here for so long.
I miss home too.
The governor sure is ruthless.
He's clearly at fault,
yet you're the one to suffer.
This has nothing to do with him.
This is all my idea.
Anyway,
for me,
leaving the residence
is a good thing.
After all this time, have you
not caught any feelings
for the governor at all?
From now on,
he's the governor,
and I'm his subject.
You didn't answer my question.
Forget it.
Anyway, the governor
is used to a life of leisure
and has no interest in politics.
I don't think he's your cup of tea.
Actually,
the governor
isn't like what you see.
When the time is right,
I believe
the world will see the real him.
Then, everyone will
understand
his painstaking efforts.
I get it.
Friendship remains even if the deal fails.
You sure know how to speak up for him.
Anyway,
Miss Wei,
thanks for taking care of me
during my stay.
I owe it to you that
everything went smoothly.
Thank you.
I'm sad that I won't
get to see you here all the time
from now on.
Work is over.
Aren't you going back, Captain Gao?
You fellows go ahead.
Then we'll get going.
Miss Wei.
You walked up to me yourself.
What's wrong?
Fan Yun is returning home
tomorrow morning.
I'm feeling down.
Is it OK if we talk?