Dong Hwa!
Dong Hwa, wake up!
What? How did you get down here?
What's all this?
Why are you here?
Where's the killer?
Killer?
What do you mean?
Don't you know?
That guy in my house upstairs.
He's here to kill me.
What?
He locked you up like this?
Why?
I don't know.
He showed up out of nowhere to kill me,
but he didn't. He just locked me up here.
See that lock over there?
That punk up there probably has the key.
He always takes it out of his pants.
Dong Hwa, then I'll call Chul Jin.
- Chul Jin...
- No, you can't.
You can't trust the police in Dongcheon.
Tae Jeong, please, I'm begging you.
You're the only one I can trust.
Okay, I'll look into it.
Chu Tae Jeong?
First, find the phone.
We'll talk after that.
What are you doing?
That guy in my house upstairs.
He's here to kill me.
I didn't check this side.
Where have you been?
I've been home the whole time.
In the inner office.
Really?
Did you find anything?
That punk up there probably has the key.
He always takes it out of his pants.
What are you looking at?
Huh?
Nothing.
What's this on your hair?
You're so clumsy.
What have you been up to?
What's going on with you?
No, it's nothing.
That punk up there probably has the key.
He always takes it out of his pants.
What are you doing?
I said, what are you doing?
I don't know either.
What?
You should tuck in when you're sleeping.
Jeez.
This is driving me nuts.
Why do you think Min Ho died?
Because he failed to eliminate the target.
"Why couldn't he kill the target?"
I thought about it.
I think it was because he was a good person.
That's why he wanted to start fresh
with the woman he was supposed to kill.
How stupid.
You're up.
Drink up.
Thank you.
You look tired.
Why did you come out last night?
What, do you need something from me?
To see the scar on your chest.
It looked huge.
I got hurt, a long time ago.
It looked like a knife wound.
How did it happen?
It's nothing. Don't worry about it.
But when your friend
came over the other day...
You mean Chul Jin?
He looked down on you for being a wimp.
It's not like that.
He's just teasing me because we're close.
Yeah, sure.
You couldn't escape and got dragged around.
Hang on.
You must be good at defending yourself
in those situations, right?
Alright, come at me.
I'll really do it.
Take it easy.
Are you really a cop?
You just came at me so suddenly.
What criminal gives you time to get prepared?
See, this is why your friend
bosses you around.
I told you it wasn't like that.
Whatever. When someone
rushes at you like this,
just hit down their left arm like I just did,
or quickly step inside. Got it?
Okay.
Hey, can you teach me
how to escape a headlock?
Okay, put me in a headlock.
So, there are a few ways to do it.
It's simple.
You can turn around
and flip them over like I just did.
Or grab the closest leg
and take them down backwards.
How's that? Easy, right?
How is this easy?
What's so hard about it?
You're much bigger than me.
You can't pick and choose
smaller guys on the job.
Let me teach you an easy one. Grab me.
Lower your body a bit more.
- Go easy on me.
- Try to stretch out your right arm.
Lower your body, extend your right arm,
add some strength...
What are you doing?
Sorry.
Alright, last one.
Try to throw me.
Lower your body a bit more
and push your hips back.
Now try again.
Gosh, you're hopeless.
You really need to lift some weights.
Oh, forget it. I give up.
I'm done.
I'll go wash up first.
Lower your body a bit more.
Try to stretch out your right arm.
How did you get down here?
Where is that punk?
He's taking a shower. I have to hurry.
You found it.
I went through his pockets.
What?
How is that possible?
You've done well.
What?
We picked up Heo Dong Hwa's phone signal.
Ah, right.
Now leave that house. Your job is done.
What do you mean, done?
I haven't taken care of Heo Dong Hwa yet.
You don't need to worry about that anymore.
I had Hyeon handle the rest.
Since it seems you have no intention
of finishing him off.
I'll do it.
How much further
are you going to let me down?
The time the phone was turned on.
It was last night.
What's wrong?
This isn't the right key.
Is there another one?
Sorry. I'll go find it.
Be careful.
Why didn't you report it sooner?
You're still not telling me
about Chu Tae Jeong.
Did you think I wouldn't know about you two?
You're not thinking
of starting over too, are you?
I'll give you one last chance.
Would you prefer Chu Tae Jeong
to get killed by you?
Or by Hyeon?
Hey, what are you doing?
- I found the phone.
- What?
The proof I told you about. I found it.
Pack up. We have to get out.
But I'm staying here.
What?
I'll wait until Dong Hwa comes back.
Chu Tae Jeong, how do you know
if or when he will return?
He'll come back. I trust Dong Hwa.
What on earth makes you trust Heo Dong Hwa?
Heo Dong Hwa is a thug.
He's a piece of trash
with no sense of responsibility.
What are you two?
Are you really just friends?
Why are you so mad all of a sudden?
Come on. Pack your things.
Like I said, I'll wait for Dong Hwa here.
Yeah? Then go ahead.
What are you doing?
I won't say it again.
Pack your things.
Leave all you want.
There's no reason for me to go.
Tae Jeong, get out now, or you're dead!
Why? I didn't do anything!
Because I'm going to kill you.
Liar. But you didn't,
even though you could have.
Shut up.
Or are you going to lock me
in the basement like you did with Dong Hwa?
Do it. If you can.