(Respect copyright)
♪Memories hold you back
from fulfilling your dreams♪
♪Only by moving forward
can you find reunion♪
♪Endings only mark new routes♪
♪It's all part of the scenery♪
♪To the horizon's call♪
♪Your journey hasn't started♪
♪Towards mountains,
chase the stars bright♪
♪Let time embrace you
and wash away the past♪
♪Put every twist behind you♪
♪Drift leisurely through time♪
♪Make headway against the wind♪
♪Let mountains bow to your pace♪
♪Rush towards a life without regret♪
♪Let your nature burst free♪
=The First Jasmine=
=Episode 24=
Your Highnesses,
what are you doing here?
Waiting for you to open the shop.
Please, come in.
Look at this mess.
Why are you living here?
I worked on the accounts for too long
and simply stayed over.
What brings you here so early?
Is everything alright?
All's well. I'm just here
to pick up something.
Pick up something?
Please get that for me.
Alright. Let's go home.
You never answered me.
About what?
The first time we met,
did you like me then?
Didn't I already answer you?
When did you answer?
Just now.
You didn't.
I answered very clearly.
I didn't have a runny nose, I tell you.
- Would you believe me if I say I did?
- No.
I say yes, you doubt.
I say nothing, you pout.
Zuidie, you just recovered.
You should rest more.
Don't overexert yourself.
Ms. Wen, I'm fine.
I enjoy spending time with you.
I'd like to walk around a bit later
and pay my respects to His Highness.
Alright, have a seat.
Ms. Wen, I heard His Highness's marriage
was bestowed by the Empress Dowager.
So he and his wife
didn't know each other beforehand?
His Highness is slow to warm up.
Getting along with Her Highness
must not come easily.
They get along fine.
If you want to look around,
once we finish tea, I can take you
for a walk in the garden.
Sure.
Your Highness, perhaps I should do it?
It's crooked.
A little to the left.
Now to the right.
Still not right.
No.
Maybe a little more to the left.
Are you playing me?
Why did you suddenly decide
to hang the wind chime?
Well, I brought it down
from Lishan Mountain.
Come down now.
Let go now. People can see us.
I couldn't find you this morning.
Weren't you afraid I'd worry?
I left you a note.
Don't ever do that again.
I accidentally found a wooden box
on your dressing table this morning.
You touched my wooden box?
I was indeed curious
and took a peek inside.
But I didn't open any letters.
They're your private letters.
I can't open them.
It's fine. I'll show you.
What are all these? Why did you send him
so many pieces of sheet music?
He couldn't leave the mountain then.
I knew he loved the guqin deeply.
So whenever I came across a new piece,
I'd just copy it and send it to him.
Your bond surely runs deep.
Yes. It's better than what you have
with that Lady Su.
We were betrothed.
But back then, we were both young
and barely met.
Things changed later, and we lost touch.
Why the sour face?
I'm not sour.
Mo Jingli probably isn't dead.
I found a secret tunnel
inside Prince Li's mansion study.
It leads through Dehua Ward, Ziyun Ward,
directly to the river outside the city.
Afterward, I inquired with the boatmen.
The night Mo Jingli had his 'accident,'
a boat was anchored by the riverbank
and only left after midnight.
It hadn't rained those days.
When I went there, I found traces.
You're not surprised? You already knew?
I'd guessed as much.
Although a body was found
with matching wounds,
the face was disfigured,
making it hard to confirm the identity.
Moreover, after his 'accident,'
I made some inquiries.
He has been plotting far and wide.
He has placed his people
in the Six Ministries.
Even a clandestine group
like Tianyi Pavilion had ties with him.
Besides the assassination of Yuan Fang,
he's pulled other schemes.
His ambition to reclaim
the Eastern Palace is now crystal clear.
A person like him would never give in
if there was the slightest hope.
It's Imperial Court of Judicial Review's
case now. I can't intervene directly.
Are these all just music scores?
What about these two?
Not just music scores.
Didn't you say you'd show me?
I changed my mind.
Show me.
No.
Why go back on your word?
I'm not showing you.
Don't make me get them myself.
You usually take a nap around this time.
What happened today?
It's unbearably hot.
These cicadas are so loud.
I can't sleep.
Zuidie has been here for days,
and her health is clearly improving.
She said she wanted to pay you a visit,
so I accompanied her here.
Zuidie, didn't you say
you wanted to thank Yao and Li?
You're here in front of them.
Why so quiet?
I've been adrift like duckweed
for many years,
never dreaming I'd return to my homeland
to see you again,
Ms. Wen and Your Highness.
That day, as I was out on errands,
my old illness suddenly flared up.
Luckily, I ran into Ms. Wen.
Otherwise...
It seemed even heaven
refused to take my life.
I truly thank you, Ms. Wen.
And thank you, Your Highness,
for taking me in.
Don't mention it.
Everyone needs help sometimes.
You're Ms. Wen's old friend
and an acquaintance of mine too.
Just staying a few days
doesn't call for such deep gratitude.
Please sit.
After all these years, Your Highness
has grown more courteous.
Indeed, no need for such formalities.
Why are you standing? Sit down quickly.
Your Highness.
It's too hot.
Have some icy sweets to cool off.
Yes, it's truly scalding.
This late in the year.
How come it's still this blistering?
Back when I visited with Mom,
Yao's mom was still here then.
She also brought me a bowl of icy sweets
on that hot summer day.
The chefs here were so skilled.
They'd carve designs onto the dishes.
I loved butterflies,
so she had them
cover mine in butterflies.
They looked astonishingly lifelike.
I hesitated to eat it,
clutching it tightly instead.
But the tighter I held it,
the faster the ice melted.
Until only a puddle remained.
Nothing was kept.
Now you're dwelling on the past again.
The physician said
less brooding aids recovery.
All this melancholy slows your healing.
Thank you for your concern,
but truly, my health matters little.
An early passing would reunite me
with my parents.
You're talking nonsense.
Passing beauty
stays a moment in the stream;
people scatter like pieces
on a chessboard.
Don't ask destiny
when our paths will cross;
the clouds disperse
like silk blown by the breeze.
Our meetings and partings are fated.
Your Highness, the prefecture office
sent someone for you.
Go attend your duties if you must.
Business first.
Yes, Xiuyao, go deal
with your official matters.
We should leave as well.
These cicadas scream relentlessly.
Lady Su, I've been quite free
these past few days.
So I had someone investigate a bit.
It turns out you still have relatives.
After your family's exile, your brother
Su Huaizhong ended up in Huaizhou.
Now he's a prominent
silk merchant there.
Your younger sister married early
and escaped the exile.
Her husband became
the prefect of Caizhou last year.
He's well-regarded
and favored by his superiors.
And your maternal uncles and aunts
run teas shops in Jiangzhou,
prosperous from their tea business.
What do you mean, Your Highness?
I'm saying
you're not alone and without family.
If unwilling, you don't have to
serve as someone's maid.
But I owe Princess Lingyun.
I see. Then you should serve her
all the more faithfully.
Ms. Wen, I've imposed too long.
I'll take my leave now.
Li, I...
Ms. Wen, if she has other motives,
you won't be able to help her.
Come see!
One coin buys a full belly!
Fresh-off-the-oven steamed cakes!
New-style ones from Yangzhou!
Look here!
(You're not alone and without family.)
(If unwilling, you don't have to
serve as someone's maid.)
You're being unreasonable.
Look at your cart.
It was already a wreck.
It was fine until you broke it!
Broke?
Lady Su, this road's blocked.
We can't get through.
You should've come the other way.
Are you paying or not?
Are you?
Dream on! I owe you nothing!
Move those in.
Alright.
It's alright. I'll simply walk back.
You wretch, get lost!
(Marquis Muyang's Mansion)
Why won't you eat?
Where is Qin Cang? Father, where is he?
No more talk of Qin Cang.
Tianyang,
listen to me.
I've arranged everything for you.
You must leave the capital.
Return to Lingnan. Go back to your mom.
Tianyang,
listen to me.
Depart as soon as possible.
By the time you return to Lingnan,
it will be just the season
to enjoy pomelos.
Weren't pomelos
your favorite as a child?
You'll have fresh ones when you're back.
Isn't he also your son?
I heard Mom mention it.
You and his mom grew up together.
You kept him in an outer residence
against Mom's wishes.
For years, every matter in the mansion,
big or small, was entrusted to him.
I've always thought
he was your most valued son.
Father,
if one day, I am in your way,
would you also kill me?
Pack your things and depart soon.
(Tianyang said this thing
looks like a black gauze cap.)
(To me,)
(it looks more like a flowerpot,
perfect for planting flowers.)
What's the matter?
(Xiangqi Pavilion)
Open the door!
Master Feng booked the whole place.
Come back another day.
My apologies. Sorry about that.
The one performing on stage
is Lady Yusheng.
She is now the most popular dancer.
She debuted just last year,
and business at Xiangqi Pavilion
boomed instantly.
Today I pulled some strings
to book the entire place privately.
That's why we're lucky
to enjoy her graceful dance.
Good posture and a solid stance.
But she lets her gaze wander,
still lacking something.
Yun, you're quite the expert.
It seems you're a frequent visitor here.
I rarely come.
Only for occasional socials.
I'm far too upright.
I don't like debauched places
bustling with singsong girls.
Then why haven't you married yet?
Do you have a beloved in Cangbei?
No.
I do.
My beloved seems reluctant.
Not exactly reluctant,
just always evasive.
She's always evasive,
yet you're still into her?
That evasiveness
refers to outward appearances.
An evasive facade suggests
there might be something hidden within.
Perhaps when you know what she's hiding,
you'll change your mind.
I won't.
Alright. You won't.
Eat.
Shrimp dumplings.
Their shrimp dumplings
are considered unrivaled.
I remembered you don't like ginger,
so I told them to skip it.
Feel free to eat.
What's that in your hand then?
Something I carved for fun.
The bone of an exorcism beast.
It tests fortune.
How?
It's very simple.
You toss it up
and see which side lands face up.
Let me test yours.
Childish.
Try it.
You're a businessman.
So we'll test
your financial fortune first.
Blow on it.
(Auspicious)
Auspicious.
Purple clouds come from the east.
A sign of flourishing wealth.
It's simply unstoppable.
Alright, I'll hold you to that.
Now, let's test your marriage fortune.
See if you can find a good match
on this trip to Dachu.
Blow on it.
(Auspicious)
Auspicious again?
Yun, your trip won't be in vain.
It seems your destined partner is here.
Then this third time,
let's test your safety.
(Auspicious)
Still auspicious!
You have such immense luck.
See how fortune chases after you?
You can't escape it.
(Auspicious)
Both sides are auspicious.
A double blessing.
This means you
and this token share a fate.
Take it as a gift.
Alright. Thanks, Feng.
Now. Let's drink.
(Qingfeng Mingyue Tower)
Why call me here so late?
Help! Mo Lao'er!
Master Feng,
no food, but you're this drunk?
What should I do?
What do you mean?
I'm done for.
Your father has kicked you
out of the house?
He would never.
Qingfeng Mingyue Tower is closing?
Could you wish for anything good for me?
That sworn brother of yours
has abandoned you?
You get me.
Not that obvious, is it?
Seriously? Master Feng, you...
Adult matters aren't for you
to understand.
Leave.
I'll leave. Don't touch me.
- Out.
- You're dangerous.
Be careful, Your Highness.
Exactly as I thought.
Close correspondents meeting,
long separated and reunited,
will cause trouble.
You don't know the situation.
The very first time I saw her,
she was caked in mud from head to toe.
So dark and skinny
that I thought she was a man.
But how come
she seemed different this time?
I see.
Lust at first sight?
You still don't get me.
Does she know you're onto her?
I don't think so.
I've been very restrained.
So what are you going to do?
I'm simply confused.
The first time I saw her,
she was disguised as a man.
Given the circumstances,
it's understandable, right?
Why did she disguise herself
as a man to meet me again?
Could she be hiding
from revenge-seeking enemies?
Or did she flee a forced marriage?
I have no idea
whether she likes me or not.
What kind of man
do women from Cangbei like?
Scholarly ones?
Government officials?
Or someone like me,
a genius in business who's charming
and steeped in knowledge across ages?
If only I had learned some martial arts.
What are you doing?
Going home.
Aren't you going to offer some advice?
If you like her,
tell her clearly early on.
I...
Thank you, Master Zhong,
for arriving punctually.
I've been calculating a celestial event
involving a solar eclipse.
I've calculated it should happen
within these few days.
Could you help calculate the exact time
and visibility range over the capital?
I've also done calculations before.
The timing of a solar eclipse
is determined by the lunar phases.
It's tomorrow at noon. Your Highness's
estimation is mostly correct.
However, to precisely determine
the time, direction, and extent
requires further calculation.
Here, take a look.
(Sun and Moon Paths Meet)
This is the moon's path.
And this is the sun's path.
(Sun and Moon Paths Meet)
Where these two paths cross...
Ask her out.
The chrysanthemums
outside the city are in full bloom.
Or, you could go to the temple fair
at the East Market.
I've heard some Hu merchants
have come to the East Market.
Their pastries and sweets
are unlike any in the capital.
What exactly are you trying to do?
Didn't I say it already?
I've been waiting for the right moment.
The timing is upon us now. But how
to get the Dowager Consort to come out?
That's beyond me.
Do you happen to know
her recent whereabouts?
I don't know.
- You can find out.
- You...
This is the Dowager Consort's
Xiankun Miscellany.
It's for the Empress Dowager tomorrow.
Return it to the Dowager Consort
tomorrow at noon.
(Shende Shop)
Where is Wei Zhuang?
Why is he nowhere to be seen?
He... he went to gather new stock.
Business is slow today.
He left me alone to mind the shop.
Ye Li, don't you think the shop
feels different today?
No.
Well, what exactly
are you trying to say?
I tidied up the shop
from top to bottom this morning.
And I've counted all the inventory.
Are... are you sure nothing has changed?
Have you eaten?
I've just finished and haven't eaten.
Let's have a meal together.
If you're too tired to go out,
I'll bring food back for you.
I know a great flatbread shop.
Go eat by yourself.
Your Highness,
let's ignore him and go back.
Feibai?
Don't peek.
Just leave.
What's so appealing about it?
What did you go and do
to get injured this severely?
What happened?
Say something.
It's nothing.
I ran into some bandits
on the way and got into a fight.
I got scraped from the cliff fall.
That was too careless.
By the way, did you find Master Zhu?
Yes, he has returned to the mountain.
Really?
Good that he's back. That's good.
Li,
what do you plan to do
after Lishan Mountain reopens?
What else can I do?
To be with Mo Xiuyao and live well.
Do you love him?
Of course, he is my husband.
Your wish will surely come true.
Alright, go back and rest.
Get some good sleep.
Li,
no matter what happens,
always remember
you still have me,
and I'll always stay by your side.
So you'll never be alone again.
Why say this suddenly?
Nothing. I just hope you stay well.
I will.
Your Highness, I'll get the carriage.
He's not that formidable.
I clashed with him before,
a brawler with no proper training.
He even took advantage of my injury
and struck from behind.
Now if we fought head-on,
I might not lose to him.
Then go find him and have a fight.
I can beat him.
But I can't beat you.
What's that man to you?
Aren't you married?
Should you be alone with him?
Aren't you afraid
your husband will find out?
Exactly. My husband
is incredibly impressive.
If you keep loitering here,
I'll tell him.
I'm not leaving. I like working here.
Your Highness, the carriage is here.
As you wish.
Let's go.
Something on your mind?
Yao, let's make a bet.
Bet on what?
I bet the sun will disappear
at the start of the noon hour tomorrow.
I heard Your Highness arrived.
Why didn't you announce yourself?
Why the lantern in broad daylight?
And you? Why all the flashy clothes
in your own shop?
Well? How do I look?
The hat isn't great.
I just got it.
Perhaps it's the outfit's fault.
Let me change
and you can give me advice.
They're here.
Such strong wind!
Why the sudden wind?
A celestial anomaly!
It's a celestial anomaly!
Is a downpour coming?
Hurry back!
Pack up the stall!
Something's wrong.
Look!
What is that?
Mother, look!
The sun is being eaten!
Go home now!
Watch where you're going!
The Heavenly Dog eats the sun!
Run!
Wrap up quick!
Watch out!
Dowager Consort, are you alright?
Empress Dowager, we don't know
what this celestial phenomena...
What? It's getting bright again?
(Ren'an Clinic)
Let me.
No need to worry, Dowager Consort.
I know some medicine.
I'll treat the wound properly.
Princess Ding,
why were you there just now?
I own a shop
dealing in antiques and paintings.
It's not far from there.
An art dealer lighting a lantern
in broad daylight?
It was only a coincidence.
What a coincidence,
this once-in-a-century sky.
What a coincidence
that we were both on the street.
that you were also holding a lantern.
How could there be so many coincidences?
There are even bigger coincidences.
Lishan Academy compiled
historical records spanning millennia.
If you read them, you'd know
that given a long enough time span,
the strangest coincidences
become possible.
Dowager Consort, it's done.
Thank you, Princess Ding.
(Ren'an Clinic)
Safe journey.
(Office)
Get the carriage. We'll go back.
Yes.
(Preview)
In fact, I too have a slight grasp
of Master Xiankun's technique
of stirring the elements with his brush
and painting a dragon to summon rain.
Good, I would like to see
if that technique from the past
can still be recreated today.
If he learns the truth about the edict,
what will he think of you?
He is my enemy!
♪Memories hold you back
from fulfilling your dreams♪
♪Only by moving forward
can you find reunion♪
♪Endings only mark new routes♪
♪It's all part of the scenery♪
♪To the horizon's call♪
♪Your journey hasn't started♪
♪Towards mountains,
chase the stars bright♪
♪Both joy and grief
make the trip worthwhile♪
♪Trying to catch up
to your own lost shadow♪
♪Within the wilds, echoes thrive♪
♪Clear mind leads to a clear path♪
♪Be grateful to your losses♪
♪Make your steps weightless♪
♪Towards mountains,
chase the stars bright♪
♪Let time embrace you
and wash away the past♪
♪Put every twist behind you,
drift leisurely through time♪
♪Make headway against the wind,
let mountains bow to your pace♪
♪Rush towards a life without regret♪
♪Let your nature burst free♪
♪Unbound by form♪