Bro, the moment you left,
someone showed up to stir up trouble.
Could someone be mixed in with them, instigating?
Take a good look.
Don't end up going to prison
without even knowing why.
Go to prison?
Could it be her?
Lili, Lili.
Aunt Zhang.
What's up?
Is Yihai here?
No, Bro Hai went out on business.
Let me tell you,
Another family on Aimin Street had trouble.
Did you know?
Really?
I know.
Wasn't it carbon monoxide poisoning?
Let me tell you,
last night there was someone
sneaking around suspiciously.
I told Section Chief Dao,
but he said I was seeing things.
Alright.
Aunt Zhang, got it.
I'll tell Bro Hai when he gets back.
Okay, thank you in advance.
Aimin Street's business is Bro Hai's.
We always end up bothering you.
Thanks again, really.
No problem.
I'm off then.
Take care, Aunt Zhang.
Okay.
Where's Director Ge?
I'm the one looking for you.
What's going on?
Out with it.
What's the deal?
What do you mean, "what's the deal"?
This month,
there've been so many accidents.
Is it a lot?
Isn't it?
Over a dozen in one month.
Didn't you say they were accidents?
Gas tank leaks,
carbon monoxide poisoning,
elderly people getting electrocuted.
Don't worry.
We've already increased manpower
and educated them on safety.
All happened this month.
Just a coincidence, right?
Coincidence?
And all concentrated on Aimin Street.
Are you saying
someone did it on purpose?
What I'm saying is,
shouldn't you be investigating?
Well,
the Security Section
can only act once someone files a report.
If no one files a report, we can't act.
Fine.
I'll investigate.
Then I'll come file a report with you.
Fine.
Where you going?
Let go.
Honey.
Forgive me.
Are you a psycho?
Honey,
forgive me.
You can't keep hating me forever.
Her talk of illicit massage services...
So this was payback all along.
Looks like we got it wrong.
What... what nonsense are you spouting?
The reason you still hate me
is because
we never got to be together properly.
Honey...
Stop talking nonsense.
I never made you a promise,
but you can't bet your future on me.
Shameless!
I'm so shameless.
I'm shameless.
Get off!
Trying to mess with me?
Another one, huh?
What are you doing here?
Perfect timing.
Help me chase after her.
Zhu Yihai!
You've got some nerve!
Using your ex-girlfriend to chase a girl?
Just hurry up!
It's not what you think!
Let go of me!
Alright.
You should head back.
It might be dangerous up ahead.
Dumping me now that you're done?
There's real danger.
Then pay the cab fare.
Scan the code.
Scan what code?
Get lost.
This should be the place.
Hello.
Factory Office Secretariat.
Not good.
Hello, Factory Office.
I'm from the Factory Office Secretariat.
Are you the one who reported
that someone's been threatening you?
Yeah.
Come in and talk.
Okay.
Can't find Mom and Dad's place?
Sorry to bother you.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
Come on, let's go.
Mom and Dad already cooked dinner.
They can't wait.
Show some respect.
I'm trying to save you, you know that?
You think I'd believe your bullshit?
See for yourself.
Where are you going?
To save someone.
Are you crazy? You'll get yourself killed!
Look at all that's happened lately.
This guy's definitely behind it all.
Look.
How could this be related to Long Xiao?
How could it involve Long Xiao?
Like you don't know.
You two are thick as thieves.
I really don't know about this.
You think I'm an idiot?
Aren't you?
You...
Zhu Yihai.
That doesn't add up.
Director Ge already signed the contract.
Why would Long Xiao do this?
You think Long Xiao
would let you have a sure thing?
You're so easygoing.
You say he owes you money,
yet you're not the least bit worried.
He... he owes me money.
I'll lend you some men
to force him into submission.
We just need him to sign this agreement.
If he fires people again,
won't that prove
everything I just said is true?
So he's been using me this whole time.
Now you know who the idiot is, huh?
You stay right here.
I'm going to find some men.
Don't go anywhere.
Hello.
I've been exposed.
Need a cleanup.
Tie up the loose ends.
Leave no trace.
I'll arrange for you to go to Nanyang.