[The Legend of Rosy Clouds]
[Episode 7]
Here.
Careful, it's hot.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Here.
Careful.
Master,
Fan Yun is awake.
He really found the Myriad-Spirit Herb.
They say
the Dark Wolves presented it.
Then it seems the people
who rescued Fan Yun
from Linglong Tower
really were Dark Wolves.
To think
he actually found the Dark Wolves.
It seems Qi Zheng
really isn't entirely useless,
just as Gao Ran said.
Master,
since coming back
from the morning audience,
you don't seem to be in a very good mood.
The assassination failed,
and Gao Ran also refused to
take on this task.
And now the Governor
has Dark Wolves protecting him as well.
You mentioned last time that Suyin
was taken away?
Yes.
If Suyin hadn't acted on her own
to carry out the poisoning,
I wouldn't be
in such a disadvantaged position.
At this point,
she'll have to bear this herself.
Master,
you mean...
Who would have thought
that a momentary act of kindness back then
would nearly become my weakness?
It seems
that to achieve great things,
one cannot afford to be soft-hearted.
Abandon her.
Fan Yun,
Suyin's life is now
in your hands.
Suyin,
lift your head and look at me.
I said, lift your head
and look at me.
Right now, I just hope...
you can step forward
and testify against Lord Zheng.
Not for yourself,
but for the people of the Nine Cities.
Can you do that?
Here.
Slow down.
Eat.
When you're full, come home with me.
Can you?
Answer me.
I won't give you a second chance.
Suyin.
If that's your firm decision,
I'll deal with you according to the law.
I'll count down from three.
Three!
Two!
Suyin.
One!
Answer me!
Suyin!
You...
Suyin...
Suyin!
Hurry,
fetch a physician!
Fetch a physician!
Fan Yun!
Are you going to defy my order?
But didn't you just say
this was for me to decide?
Since what she wanted
was to serve only one master for life—
I've granted her that wish.
A person like her
is not worth keeping.
Suyin...
Hang in there.
Suyin.
Hurry.
Physician...
Fetch a physician!
He really is an impulsive young fool.
If Gao Ran hadn't
rejected it so resolutely...
Either way,
dead men tell no tales.
In that case,
we have to consider
how to move forward
from here.
Suyin is dead.
She served you for many years.
Though reckless,
she was loyal
to you.
Qi Zheng
may not necessarily know that this was...
You may leave.
Yes, Master.
I...
How did I...
I'm responsible for
escorting you out of the city.
You're free now.
This is
a letter from the Governor for you.
"The situation was urgent,
so I had no choice
but to resort to this plan.
The carriage will take you
out of the city.
You would not betray the one you trust—
that is your integrity.
I should've respected your choice.
But seeing how deeply
my wife cares for you,
I couldn't bear to break her heart.
Remember:
you've already died once for that person.
My wife is the one
who gave you this second life."
What's wrong?
Turns out...
Turns out all of you
were putting on an act.
Then why didn't you tell me beforehand?
If we'd told you beforehand,
the act wouldn't have been so convincing.
Besides,
I wouldn't have done it if I hadn't been
completely confident it would work.
Suyin is fine now, isn't she?
Right?
Come on.
I should've told you in advance.
I'm not mad.
I just wonder—in the eyes of the nobles,
are human lives really worth so little?
It's fine if you're angry.
I'll stay with you.
♪ Watch how flowers bloom and wither ♪
♪ Count how many springs
and autumns pass ♪
♪ Why the sighs and regrets? ♪
♪ Lovers wait a lifetime ♪
♪ Love cannot be cut away ♪
♪ How to let go? ♪
♪ All our fates were long inscribed ♪
♪ How to set free grief and joy? ♪
♪ Mortal life is but an ephemeral dream ♪
♪ No mortal soul may rule its life ♪
♪ If women are akin to blossoms ♪
♪ Can they be cherished tenderly? ♪
♪ For whom do they hide tears silently? ♪
♪ How could one bear to lay blame? ♪
♪ Time runs wild with reckless haste ♪
♪ Never mind fate dyes white crimson red ♪
♪ For whom does ♪
♪ This phoenix blossom bloom? ♪
♪ Love fills my years,
and my heart remains true ♪
♪ Let all worldly longing fade away ♪
♪ Fall deep within a single dream ♪
♪ Wait till a breath of wind arrives ♪
Zheng Yuan!
Your Excellency.
Is Your Excellency going to...
Zheng Yuan,
I have something to ask you.
I'll
hold nothing back, Your Excellency.
Ask yourself:
have you been
a good official?
Have you been loyal to me
and to the Nine Cities?
Why would Your Excellency
ask such a thing?
I would sacrifice everything
for Your Excellency,
for the Nine Cities—
and I already have.
But the Nine Cities
are on the verge of ruin!
Your Excellency...
Zheng Yuan! Zheng Yuan!
How can you live with yourself?
Shi.
Come, come.
Grandfather.
Grandfather, are you okay?
I just dreamed about
a lot of people who have passed away.
Come on, sit.
Here, Grandfather.
Shi,
tell me,
do you think I
am a good official?
Good official?
You've
simply been worrying too much lately.
It's time you put down
some of your burdens.
Others may not understand
and think you just love power,
but ever since I was little,
I've watched you lie awake
at night worrying about
the prosperity of the Nine Cities.
If you don't qualify as a good official,
then who does?
Shi,
I'm so glad to have you by my side.
Brush and ink.
Bring me the brush and ink.
Right away.
Elder Zheng has been
on leave for days now.
Has his condition still not improved?
Your Excellency,
Lord Zheng's illness
has been quite severe.
He may need to remain bedridden
for a few more days.
Your Excellency,
Lord Zheng is absent.
It's been scorching hot
for days since summer began,
and the transit permits for shipping ice
from Jing City to Ling'an,
as well as
the repair work on
West Bridge outside Ling'an,
have both been delayed for days.
Your Excellency...
Got it!
Next.
Lyu,
Zheng
has fallen ill.
Shouldn't we pay him a visit?
We should.
We definitely should.
I'd like to see for myself
what kind of illness he has
that could make him
set aside the government affairs
he cares so much about.
Right.
At his age,
he just lounges around all day
doing nothing?
He should...
He should get some exercise,
right?
Lyu,
I have to say,
you should
exercise more often too.
You can't spend all day cooped up
in your room reading,
right?
How about this?
When Zheng gets better,
I'll train both of you together.
Look at me now,
strong and healthy as ever!
I eat well, sleep well!
Look.
Let me teach you a couple of moves now.
Come on.
Don't move. Don't move.
What's wrong?
Don't move.
-What's wrong?
-Don't move.
What do you think you're doing?
You have a white beard.
How old are you?
How can you still be so simple-minded?
Well, well, Lyu,
you are insulting me, huh?
Calling me all brawn and no brains?
I'm healthy.
I'm happy.
One,
two,
three!
Look!
See?
What's wrong with being healthy?
Morning, Miss Wei.
Morning.
Miss Wei,
morning.
Morning, Miss Wei.
[Training Grounds]
Miss Wei.
Morning.
Morning, Miss Wei.
Miss Wei,
you're here so early.
That couldn't have been easy.
You should hurry along too. Don't be late.
Miss Wei,
you should head back.
As I told you earlier,
we have extra drills today.
Even if you wait here until nightfall,
Lord Gao Ran won't be coming out.
Extra drills?
Why extra drills?
The weather's getting hotter by the day.
The Guardian Corps
have been getting sluggish.
And with Lord Zheng ill
these past few days,
personnel assignments throughout the city
have run into problems.
So at a time like this,
we can't afford to let our guard down.
We need even more training.
Yes.
Does he have heatstroke?
But it's not even that hot.
What's going on?
Are you feeling unwell?
My head is spinning.
I'm seeing stars.
Seeing stars?
Did you skip breakfast today
to rush here?
No.
Before coming in,
I even had a bowl of sour plum drink
at the gate.
Sour plum drink at the gate?
Who made it?
Here you go.
There's enough for everyone!
How is it? Good, right?
I really
went all out with the ingredients.
Thank you, Miss Wei.
You're so considerate of us.
Have another bowl if you like it.
Put that down!
Lord Gao Ran.
Gao Ran,
I knew you'd come out.
My dear sister,
what heavy-duty stuff
did you put in this?
Ginseng
and astragalus.
Such a daring dose.
Putting ginseng and astragalus
into sour plum drink?
No wonder they're all seeing stars.
Is this a gesture of care
or an act of poisoning?
I...
I really didn't know.
I didn't mean to.
Miss Wei,
why did you do this?
I wanted to see you.
You're unbelievable.
This is a military compound.
The soldiers here are carrying out orders.
By law, what you've done
constitutes interference
with military affairs.
You could be punished for it.
I know you care about your soldiers.
But I also want to care about you.
If this is how you express
your care, Miss Wei,
then I'd rather do without it.
Don't show yourself in front of me again.
Gao Ran,
I know you're mad right now.
So whatever you say,
I won't take it to heart.
You, honestly.
You're the daughter
of our noble Wei family.
Why keep throwing yourself at him
when he's clearly not interested?
How do you know
I won't be the one he marries in the end?
Fine, fine.
Keep chasing your romance.
I have more important matters
to attend to.
Handle this stuff
yourself.
Wei Qiao,
take them back.
Help him up quickly.
What's wrong?
Did he get heatstroke?
You're here early.
Alright,
everyone is here.
General Wei,
is there something urgent
you need to discuss with us?
Your Excellency,
due to the extreme heat,
the Guardian Corps
are either falling ill
or neglecting their duties.
As for the policies
meant to address the heatwave,
they're all stalled with Lord Zheng.
It's not just the Guardian Corps.
Lord Zheng
neither attends the morning audience
nor says when he'll return to his post.
There are at least
a dozen vacant positions
waiting to be filled across the city.
Without official orders,
no one can mobilize anyone.
As a result,
officials across every department
are overworked
and collapsing from exhaustion,
which only worsens the situation.
If this continues,
there may soon be no one left
to keep things running.
I think
Lord Zheng's illness is just a pretense.
What he really wants
is to show Your Excellency
and all the officials of the Nine Cities
how dire things become
without him in his post.
The current situation
has made it clear just how much influence
Lord Zheng wields—
without him,
the Nine Cities indeed struggle
to function.
Now it seems
his move
was well played.
Your Excellency has been personally
overseeing governance for quite some time,
yet Lord Zheng still
behaves so arrogantly.
He clearly has no regard for
Your Excellency.
Zheng Yuan
has committed
the crime of insubordination.
Your Excellency was merciful
and spared his life.
Then why not take this opportunity
to strip Zheng Yuan of all his positions?
Without his positions,
he wouldn't be able to play his games.
That would be unwise.
Mr. Zheng has deep roots
among the officials—
a slight move could affect everything.
To solve the problem at its root,
we need careful planning.
But right now,
time is exactly what we lack.
Shi.
Grandfather,
Uncle Yi.
Young Master Shi, you're here.
Let me do it, Uncle Yi.
Okay.
Shi.
Look.
How is
my calligraphy?
I can see your strokes
are vigorous and bold.
So you must be feeling much better.
With you by my side,
of course I recover quickly.
Young Master Shi,
it's the sight of you
that has lifted Master's spirits.
Even this morning,
he was still unsettled by a nightmare.
Nonsense.
And he wouldn't let me tell you.
Are you still dreaming about past events?
When you get old,
the past keeps coming back to mind.
I wonder how things are
at the Qi Residence now.
Lord Lyu and Lord Zhao
are gathering people to
come up with a solution.
I think...
What good solutions can they come up with?
And as for those two...
I still won't see them.
[Void]
Give it to me.
It's getting late.
Why don't you head back and rest?
You don't need to
keep me company all the time.
How could I do that?
I'm not tired at all.
Look at Lord Zheng.
He's been claiming illness
and refusing to hand things over to you.
Now, so many matters have been delayed.
I may not be able
to help you with anything major,
but I can certainly help you
sort through all these documents
and correspondence.
You seem so full of energy.
I mean,
this spirit you have.
Many people, after running into
setback after setback,
eventually become resigned to
their circumstances,
feeling that nothing is worth it anymore.
But you seem different.
No matter what kind of blow you take,
you always pull yourself together
and face it.
Well, we can't just
get all depressed
and blame the heavens
every time things don't go our way, right?
Besides, Lord Wei and Lord Yan
have both picked themselves back up
and are working hard
to resolve things again.
We have to
take things one step at a time, anyway.
We'll deal with whatever comes.
Fan Yun.
Come out of the residence
with me tomorrow, will you?
Come out of the residence?
Governor.
Slow down.
Where exactly are you taking me,
Governor?
We're practically
outside the city already.
We're still not there yet?
I can barely walk anymore.
Did...
you
bring me out here just to relax?
If you want to think of it that way,
that's fine too.
Where exactly are we going?
Governor.
Are you
lost too,
like Lord Yan Jiang?
I'm taking you to a place.
Keep up.
A place?
Governor, wait for me.
I can't walk anymore.
Governor,
when are we going to get there?
I really can't keep going.
I...
Young Master Qiyan?
Why...
Why are you here?
Miss Fan,
could we have a word in private?
In private?
Well, what a small world.
Then let's all talk together.
Yun.
Let's go in.
Why are you here?