=The Embroidered Truth=
I want to see my master!
Let me see him!
Do you hear me?
Let me see my master!
Guards!
Stop shouting. You're a dead woman.
No need to yell.
Yes, I'm dying.
But I don't want to take
Lady Cheng'en's secret to my grave.
I won't tell that secret
without seeing Master Wu.
Take me to him now!
=Episode 19=
Master Wu is truly devoted
to you, Your Highness.
Why stop me?
Your Highness,
I fear
that if you praise him again,
he will clash
with Lady Cheng'en once more.
Those who deserved punishment got it.
Those who needed comfort received it.
If they're sensible, they won't
cause more trouble.
Your Highness,
Wu Lian.
Your people made a mistake,
so you should be punished too.
But your embroidery is exquisite.
So I'll punish you...
How should I punish you?
I accept any punishment.
Now, I can't think of anything.
No hurry.
You can punish me whenever
you remember.
Right now,
I'm at a critical point in
embroidering "National Beauty."
I dare not be careless.
All right.
(With the Princess Consort
as my shield,)
(no matter what Lin Rulan does,)
(she can't touch me.)
Careless fool.
What's the matter?
Ms. Meng has gone crazy.
She wants to see Master Wu.
She has a secret to tell.
What secret?
Your Highness, do you want to go
to the prison and see?
No need.
I have no interest in secrets.
I only know that
before the Prince returns,
nothing can go wrong in this manor.
Will you let Master Wu go?
That's up to him.
He can handle his own people.
As long as he doesn't cause
trouble for the manor.
Yes.
My Lady.
What's wrong?
Wu Lian went to the manor prison.
Why?
I heard Meng Wan wants to
tell him a secret.
To see him,
she's gone crazy.
Oh no.
My Lady.
Don't follow me.
If I'm not back in half an hour,
go find Mr. Liu.
Her Highness is resting.
Please come back tomorrow.
If it were my personal matter,
I could come back tomorrow.
But if it's about the manor,
aren't you afraid the sky will fall?
Wenyue.
Ruoheng.
What's the matter now?
She said
the sky over the manor will
fall tomorrow.
Leave us.
I want to hear
how the sky will fall.
Wenyue,
I have a request.
Speak.
I've thought it over.
Our deal wasn't fair to me.
You want to back out?
Don't be angry.
To keep me from backing out,
you just need to grant me
one act of merit.
I'm listening.
Since childhood, I've done
good deeds.
I never wanted to stain my
hands with killing.
But for you, I took that
sterilization medicine
to put your mind at ease.
And yet, I feel uneasy.
I think of all the children
who never got to be born.
Is that all?
There's a Buddhist hall in the manor.
Once you're settled in,
I'll have the monks chant
for their souls.
Chanting is good,
but not as good as real action.
Today, I came to tell you
that saving one life
is what matters the most.
Save whom?
Those people you mentioned,
I already had Magistrate Yu
release them.
I want you to save Meng Wan.
Someone from Yanyu Embroidery House?
Why would you want to save her?
Yes, she's from that house.
But you have keen eyes.
You must see
that Ms. Meng is just
Wu Lian's mouth
and hands.
We are both women.
Think carefully.
When has Ms. Meng ever
done wrong?
Every time she speaks, it's for Wu Lian.
True.
The pheasant's severed head,
I was the one who found it.
You were angry, so you
ordered her killed.
But
I don't want more killing between us.
Wenyue,
just having me here
is already a blessing.
But I'm afraid.
I'm afraid Ms. Meng will haunt me
in my dreams.
Is that all?
Be good. After the Flower Festival,
I'll release her.
Thank you, Wenyue.
Since you've agreed,
your word is as good as gold.
Now, I can rest easy.
Asking you to come to a place like this.
You must resent me.
You've already confessed.
Why lure me here with a secret?
I've been by your side for years.
Taking this secret to my grave
doesn't sit right with me.
For the sake of our years together,
speak.
I don't know Lady Cheng'en's secret.
But I know
I destroyed the Princess Consort's gown.
I lured Jia Yi over
and sent him to Rulan.
Even Xiaoyi's death... I set that trap.
You didn't know any of that, did you?
I don't know what you're saying.
Are you pretending not to understand?
Let me tell you.
The secrets of your embroidery house
won't stay hidden much longer.
Even if you follow the Princess Consort
like a loyal dog,
she won't be able to save you.
I've treated you well, haven't I?
Well?
You defiled me first.
Then you killed my sworn sister.
You treated us like gifts
between you and your rich friends.
You blackmailed them
to keep them silent.
Is that being good to me?
You fed your filthy soul with our blood.
Wretch!
Wu Lian,
I'm not the same Meng Wan I used to be.
But you are still the same Wu Lian.
Does it matter who you are?
A dead woman.
From the day the pheasant's
head was severed,
I never planned to live.
♪Night fades before the dawn♪
♪Old vows still guide my hand♪
♪The past no longer binds♪
♪My heart still shines through dust♪
♪Silent blooms, unchanged heart♪
♪Bare hands weave through the frost♪
♪Shadows linger, rain returns♪
♪Honor crowns my weary soul♪
♪For your faith that never broke♪
♪I shattered all the love I knew♪
♪No regrets, no debts unpaid♪
♪At dusk I walk away alone♪
♪If this tale becomes a storm♪
♪Old shadows fade from sight♪
♪One thought turns into ash♪
♪No future left to write♪
♪If I never fall♪
♪How could this waiting end♪
♪If I bear no scars♪
♪How could I challenge fate♪
♪I knew there was no way back♪
♪Yet I left this hope behind♪
♪For your faith that never broke♪
♪I shattered all the love I knew♪
♪No regrets, no debts unpaid♪
♪At dusk I walk away alone♪
♪If this tale becomes a storm♪
♪Old shadows fade from sight♪
♪One thought turns into ash♪
♪No future left to write♪
♪The lamp is out, you're gone♪
♪Heaven and earth fall silent♪
♪If we meet again someday♪
♪This longing sleeps beneath the snow♪