[The Legend of Rosy Clouds]
[Episode 9]
It seems you are
in a very good mood today.
This...
is all thanks to you.
Do you know that
I almost got heatstroke today?
Your Excellency,
I've finally understood.
You must have thought
I earned that 500 gold
too easily.
You deliberately made things
difficult for me, didn't you?
If you beg me,
arranging some easy tasks for you
isn't impossible.
More tasks?
What tasks?
Tell me.
I just remembered that
when I was at Huan'e House,
I lost a handkerchief.
How about you embroider a new one for me?
A handkerchief?
For your handkerchief,
just have the embroiderers
at the Tailoring Bureau make it.
Why must I do it?
That's different.
What's so different about it?
It just is.
It's the same.
However...
Your Excellency,
if you insist on my embroidering
a handkerchief for you,
it's not impossible.
It's just that...
Just what?
It's just that
we need to discuss
the selection exam again.
No way.
Why not?
Your Excellency.
Young Master Lou Qiyan from Juyun Pavilion
has arrived.
Young Master Qiyan?
Let him wait in the Huiyun Pavilion.
Yes.
Lou Qiyan?
You summoned him?
Wei and Yan failed
to get the blueprints from him.
Naturally, I have to meet him myself.
You,
get some good rest.
Also,
don't even think about the selection exam.
Go back and rest.
Your Excellency,
I want to go with you.
What are you going for?
You are the esteemed lady.
Of course, you can't go.
Your Excellency,
I can disguise myself as a personal guard
and go in with you.
Right?
No.
I'll embroider the handkerchief for you.
In your dreams.
Your Excellency,
just let me go with you
and hear what's going on.
Please?
Hide in the corner.
No eye contact.
Not even a glance.
I promise.
His Excellency is here!
Your Excellency, may I ask why you
have summoned me?
I heard
you only do business with one person.
One channel, one person.
This is my rule in business.
No matter how big the deal is,
I won't do it.
Are you saying
not even me?
If Her Ladyship comes to talk to me,
maybe it'll work.
Do you think you can see her
whenever you want?
Aren't you afraid I'll punish you
for disrespecting the Governor?
It seems you don't welcome me.
I'll take my leave now.
If I've offended you,
please calm down, Your Excellency.
For making you unhappy,
I am truly terrified.
I will excuse myself now.
Your beard fell off.
♪ Watch how many flowers
bloom and wither ♪
♪ Count how many springs
and autumns pass ♪
♪ Why the sighs and regrets? ♪
♪ Lovers wait a lifetime ♪
♪ Feelings that can't be severed ♪
♪ How to let go? ♪
♪ All our fates were long inscribed ♪
♪ How to set free grief and joy? ♪
♪ Mortal life is but an ephemeral dream ♪
♪ No mortal soul may rule its life ♪
♪ If women are akin to blossoms ♪
♪ Can they be cherished tenderly? ♪
♪ For whom do they hide tears silently? ♪
♪ How could one bear to lay blame? ♪
♪ Time runs wild with reckless haste ♪
♪ Never mind that
fate dyes pureness crimson red ♪
♪ For whom does ♪
♪ This phoenix blossom bloom? ♪
♪ Love fills my years,
and my heart remains true ♪
Your Excellency.
♪ Let all worldly longing fade away ♪
♪ Fall deep within a single dream ♪
♪ Wait till a breath of wind arrives ♪
Look.
The 24 types of pastries offered this time
correspond exactly to the 24 solar terms.
This uses the ancient method
to commemorate those meritorious subjects
and signifies that
our great Nine Cities
will have good weather
and grow stronger year by year.
As for Lord Zheng,
although
he is a bit conservative,
he
truly wants
what's best for the Nine Cities.
I don't know if doing this
can really move him.
Actually, agreeing to
repair the ancestral temple
isn't
entirely for Mr. Zheng.
Your Excellency,
I think...
I...
Forget it.
Let's talk somewhere else.
Where to?
Follow me.
-Don't follow us!
-I can't wait!
Can't wait?
Don't laugh.
What are you in such a hurry for?
Come here, Your Excellency.
Your Excellency.
I need to ask you a question first.
Tell me,
are you satisfied
with the offering diagram
I designed this time?
It's not bad.
Then does this count as me
successfully completing
the task you gave me?
Compared to the past 2 days,
your performance today
is indeed good.
Then...
then...
is there a reward?
Although...
But...
Isn't this a bit inappropriate?
What's...
what's inappropriate about it?
True.
There's nothing inappropriate.
Let's do it then.
I...
Your Excellency.
What are you doing?
Didn't you want a reward?
What I meant...
was this.
I wanted you to help review
my examination script
and assess my score.
Will you?
Let me see.
This is...
the exam paper
from the previous selection exam?
Why did you do this?
I want to...
I... I want to...
Of course, I want to participate
in the selection exam.
The national selection exam is inevitable.
Someone has to step forward first.
And I...
want to be the first to step forward
to share your burdens.
What do you think?
Are you serious?
Well,
of course, I'm serious.
Women of the inner court
can't interfere in politics.
As my wife,
even a national selection exam
is not allowed.
Well,
I naturally know.
But...
I've already thought of a way.
What way?
Divorce.
What?
Look,
we get a divorce,
and I take the exam.
Everything will be solved.
Right?
Look,
you were
forced to marry me.
And I'm your wife in name only.
Why not?
What did you say?
Nothing.
Continue.
Here's what I was thinking.
I originally thought
the two of us
could put on an act for a year or two.
By then, I won't have borne any children.
So for the sake of heirs,
we won't even need to say a word.
Lord Lyu and the others
will naturally force us to divorce.
But right now...
You're right.
It's in name only anyway.
Isn't it just for 500 gold?
I...
I see it's getting late.
Tomorrow morning,
I'll have to go to the Zheng Residence.
Rest early.
Your Excellency.
-No need to see me out.
-Your...
Y-You haven't answered me yet.
Are we getting a divorce or not?
Tomorrow,
I'll wait for you to come find me!
Isn't my idea
pretty good?
Miss,
you haven't slept for nights
studying the sacrificial offerings
with Her Ladyship.
If the Master finds out,
he will be heartbroken.
He deserves it.
Who asked him to send me to the residence?
But now,
for the man in the Guardian Corps camp,
you wish you could just live there.
Miss,
in my opinion,
he won't appreciate it.
Just like last time,
for the plum juice
you made for him yourself,
he just threw your kindness
back in your face.
In my opinion,
you should just...
It's all my fault
for being so clumsy last time.
His Guardian Corps
got nosebleeds from drinking it.
Good thing he didn't drink it.
Miss,
how did you hurt your hand again?
Your wound from yesterday
hasn't even healed yet.
It's fine.
The injuries from my fights
with Wei Rong were worse than this.
Look,
isn't it perfectly fine now?
Let's go.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Miss,
let's not suffer like that again
next time.
When you're in the residence,
you've never done this kind of work.
Careful.
This is a premium medicine for wounds.
At least, Wei Ying has a conscience.
Master,
His Excellency has personally
come here to visit you.
Elder Zheng.
Please forgive me for being unwell
and unable to get up.
Your health is the most important.
No need for formalities.
I heard you were unwell,
so I specially came to visit.
Seeing you bedridden now,
I am deeply worried.
I am just an old bag of bones.
I am fortunate
to have your concern.
Take it easy.
Elder Zheng,
on this trip,
besides visiting you,
there is one more thing.
I am here to apologize
to you on behalf of Fan Yun.
This is the sacrificial text for
breaking ground at the ancestral temple.
Fan Yun will focus on
the residence's affairs in the future.
Nine Cities can't do without you.
Thank you, Your Excellency.
Before coming to here,
I went to take a look
at the ancestral temple.
The repair project
is mostly completed.
I was thinking,
once you recover from your illness,
you can personally preside over
the sacrificial ceremony.
Along the way,
I was reminded of
when the late governor was alive.
You led troops to fight fierce battles
with Zhuiyue City for 3 years.
In the bitter cold lands,
you contracted a disease.
Thirteen years ago,
during the rebellion for the throne,
you wiped out the remnants
of the rebel ministers.
That's why we have the Nine Cities today.
I have always
kept in mind the efforts you have devoted
all these years to the Nine Cities.
[Zheng Residence]
You must rest well
and recover soon.
Thank you, Your Excellency.
No need to see me out.
Congratulations
on your smooth return, Master.
Everything
is back to normal.
Today, I
drank the wine
confusedly.
How did I
yield to him?
The days ahead will be different.
He can't touch me,
and I can't touch him either.
Such a good time
makes me miss the days before,
when I could frequently
leave the residence.
But for you,
being in the company of women
outside the residence
is truly more interesting, isn't it?
Try it, and you'll know
if it's interesting.
-Your Excellency.
It's only just past noon.
Why do you look
unwell?
I took a trip to the Zheng Residence.
It seems
it didn't go smoothly.
It went pretty smoothly.
Then why do you still look...
Let me ask you a question.
Do you think she can be an official?
-You mean...
Fan Yun.
I know.
Mr. Zheng
controls the government affairs
all year round,
all because of
the old system
that has existed since ancient times.
But now those old rules are full of flaws.
At the morning assembly,
it's full of old fogeys.
Not to mention the lack of talents.
For commoners, to be promoted
is even more hopeless.
Any power contrary to Mr. Zheng
will be ruthlessly suppressed.
This is what caused
his dominance today.
The matter of repairing
the ancestral temple
is a good example.
You are absolutely right.
Even though we are
from the Nine Noble Families,
this situation
is really shocking.
We have to find a way after all.
Have you had a plan already?
I have always wanted
to promote commoners to be officials,
to break the inherent selection system.
But I have never found
a suitable opportunity.
Now Fan Yun's ability
and charisma
is indeed a breakthrough.
But...
Nine Cities has long had a clear rule.
To prevent relatives of the royal family
from seizing power,
Her Ladyship can't be an official
under any circumstances.
If Fan Yun wants to be an official,
she can only...
Divorce me.
Yes.
Your Excellency.
I said leave me alone for a while.
Fan Yun?
Why are you here?
I waited all night,
but you didn't summon me.
I had to come here myself.
Your Excellency,
about your trip
to the Zheng Residence today,
how was it?
I have expressed
what I should.
When we can do this much,
Mr. Zheng's wariness
can also be mostly dispelled.
It's also time
to take a step back.
Then why do you
still look so depressed?
These submitted memorials
used to be shown to Mr. Zheng first.
When they came to me,
I only needed to draw a circle
and stamp them.
But now that Mr. Zheng claims to be ill,
all the memorials
are piled up here.
The task is heavy.
Fan Yun.
Why don't you share the burden with me?
Me?
Is it appropriate?
It's fine.
Just stay beside me
and keep me company.
Okay.
Then I'll continue to help you
sort out
these official documents.
Please wait a moment, everyone.
The sesame flatbread will be ready soon.
You go ahead and buy.
One, two, three, four, five.
You... you go first.
Gao Ran!
I...
Miss Wei.
Has Ling'an City become so small?
It's not that Ling'an City has changed.
It's the people living in it
that have changed.
Is this what the playbooks call
the fate written for mortals?
If there's nothing else,
I'll go back to the end of the line.
No,
y-you can just wait here.
But
can you help me
buy some more?
Are you really here to buy the flatbread?
Really.
What else?
I heard Fan Yun say
that Lord Fan Qi
craves their sesame flatbread.
I just received a letter from home,
so I thought I'd ask someone
to bring some back.
Let them know
I'm living well here,
so they'll feel better.
So you have a side like this too.
Wei Qiao,
I'm a little thirsty.
Can you go buy some mung bean soup for me?
Didn't you just drink some?
I'm still thirsty.
You're thirsty again?
Miss Wei, your hand...
Was it injured in a fight?
No.
But that's not important.
What's important is that
someone gave me some wound medicine,
so it healed very quickly.
So someone cares about you.
You care about me?
Why would it be me caring about you?
You just said
the medicine was given by someone
who cares about me.
I asked Ying this morning,
and he said he didn't send it.
That still doesn't prove it's me.
Still won't admit it?
This is specially supplied
to the Guardian Corps.
How could it not be you?
It wasn't me.
Was it?
It really wasn't.
It was you.
It really wasn't me.
It was, it was.
How could it not be?
They're ready.
I'll go buy some.
That's fine.
We have plenty of time.
Your Excellency.
What were you thinking about?
Fan Yun.
What's wrong?
Your tone is so serious all of a sudden.
It sounds quite scary.
Let me ask you,
the path of an official
is fraught with difficulties
and extremely dangerous.
Mr. Zheng is a visible one.
There are many invisible obstacles.
In this case,
do you still want to be an official?
I do.
To be able to contribute
to the people of the Nine Cities
has always been my dream.
But to be an official,
you must divorce me.
Are you still willing to do it?
I am willing.
Do you know
that I have long been in love with you?
Your Excellency...
I...
♪ Watch how many flowers
bloom and wither ♪
♪ Count how many springs
and autumns pass ♪
♪ Why the sighs and regrets? ♪
♪ Lovers wait a lifetime ♪
♪ Feelings that can't be severed ♪
♪ How to let go? ♪
Since you want to,
♪ All our fates were long inscribed ♪
I will allow you
to be my official.
♪ How to set free grief and joy? ♪
No taking back moves
♪ Mortal life is but an ephemeral dream ♪
once played.
♪ No mortal soul may rule its life ♪
♪ If women are akin to blossoms ♪
♪ Can they be cherished tenderly? ♪
♪ For whom do they hide tears silently? ♪
♪ How could one bear to lay blame? ♪
♪ Time runs wild with reckless haste ♪
♪ Never mind that
fate dyes pureness crimson red ♪
♪ For whom does ♪
♪ This phoenix blossom bloom? ♪
♪ Love fills my years,
and my heart remains true ♪
♪ Let all worldly longing fade away ♪
♪ Fall deep within a single dream ♪
♪ Wait till a breath of wind arrives ♪
♪ If women are akin to blossoms ♪
♪ Can they be cherished tenderly? ♪
♪ For whom do they hide tears silently? ♪
♪ How could one bear to lay blame? ♪
♪ Time runs wild with reckless haste ♪
♪ Never mind that
fate dyes pureness crimson red ♪
♪ For whom does ♪
♪ This phoenix blossom bloom? ♪
♪ Love fills my years,
and my heart remains true ♪
♪ Let all worldly longing fade away ♪
♪ Fall deep within a single dream ♪
♪ Wait till a breath of wind arrives ♪
Your Excellency,
how do you feel?
I feel refreshed all over.
And then?
And then,
continue.
Come on.
Okay.
Fan Yun,
how dare you!
What's wrong?
Did I hurt you?
No.
Then...
I'm just cooperating with you.
Come on, continue.
Hurry, hurry.
Continue.
How dare you challenge my bottom line!
Right?
W-What...
what bottom line
did I challenge?
I just hate your face!
This face of yours!
Look at you!
Your eyes may be big,
but they're lifeless!
Your brows may arch high,
but they're arrogant and overbearing!
And your nose!
It's straight,
but looks suspicious!
What should we do?
It's all just a game of pretense.
I think you just said
everything on your mind.
No, I didn't.
Yes, you did.
Let me do it.
Listen to me.
Do you...
do you think I want to be your wife?
Hurry, hurry.
But since you don't like it,
why did you marry into the residence?
Go back then.
I... I...
I'll go back then!
You think I don't want to go back?
Ever since I married you,
I've been
either poisoned
or
kidnapped.
Y-You're not a man at all!
You're just
a coward!
What you just said
are your true feelings, right?
They aren't my true feelings at all.
I was just making things up.
Your Excellency,
your health is important.
Please don't let anger ruin your health.
Who let you in?
Look how fierce he is.
He scared me to death.
Calm down, Your Excellency.
Her Ladyship meant no harm.
She even came all the way here
to bring you a midnight snack.
Yeah.
What a—
Midnight snack?
Alright.
Look.
Look what she made.
Is this...
for humans to eat?
My good intentions
are completely misunderstood.
Scold me. Scold me.
Scold me.
You are an attendant, right?
Write this down.
She's good at cooking,
but what she made tonight
is comparable to pig slop!
Well,
this is not for me to record.
What should I do?
I'm too ashamed to see anyone.
I'm going back.
I'm going back to my father.
Going home to my father.
Write it down word for word,
or you'll lose your head.
Yes.
Yes, yes, yes.