How's the investigation on the mole?
Chen Lezhang was on duty yesterday.
If it's true
that he lured the Crown Prince to the cell,
but he's also the one who caught him.
This Chen Lezhang
has been detained pending trial.
If he's the mole,
and he lured the Crown Prince there,
then the Crown Prince is innocent.
At that moment,
the Crown Prince was alone in the cell.
If it wasn't the Crown Prince who killed him,
could the Left Chancellor
have killed himself to frame the Prince?
Anything is possible.
Zhang Yuancang
used his Imperial Inspectorate identity
to smuggle gold into the capital.
Whoever could pull that off
must hold high rank in the Inspectorate.
Aside from the Purple Robe,
that only leaves the Golden Robe.
Why are you all looking at me?
It wasn't me!
I'm thinking,
besides you and Chen Lezhang,
are there any other Purple or Golden Robes?
Any progress on the identity tablet?
We've checked everything.
No leads.
The enemy hides while we're exposed.
Our only option now
is to lure the snake out of its den.
Speak plainly.
A diversionary maneuver,
a secret strike.
That tells us nothing. Isn't this just...
a jailbreak?
The Crown Prince has escaped!
Guards!
Your Majesty, please save the Crown Prince!
Tell me, how am I supposed to save him?
His Majesty decreed execution in 3 days.
And His Majesty has yet to awaken.
I don't even have a chance to plead.
Reporting to Your Majesty,
I have confirmed
that the Crown Prince was framed
for the Left Chancellor's murder
by a mole in the Imperial Inspectorate.
Ning Chen, this is a grave matter.
Do you have proof?
The proof lies with the Crown Prince.
The execution is in just one hour.
What are you still doing here?
Your Majesty,
my words carry little weight.
Blocked by the Imperial Inspectorate mole,
I had to take a desperate risk.
I secretly broke him out of prison.
I beg Your Majesty to uphold justice,
safeguard the royal bloodline,
sweep out the traitors,
and clear the Crown Prince's name.
How dare you!
Why should I trust you?
I stake my own head on it.
Your Majesty,
delay will bring disaster.
Acting in such a way
is just like you.
I'll trust you one more time.
There's no time to lose.
Tell me where the Crown Prince is.
The Left Chancellor's residence.
Is the Crown Prince safe?
I dared not draw attention.
I acted alone.
He's alone at the Left Chancellor's manor,
safe for the moment.
I will immediately
secretly have him brought into the palace.
Once His Majesty awakens,
we will decide our next move.
You are wise, Your Majesty.
Go, quickly!
Right away.
I've been waiting so long for you.
It's you!
You're the mole!
Arrest Ning Chen!
You've finally shown your true colors.
If I'm not mistaken,
your note said the Crown Prince was dead.
Actually, I had no idea
who the real mastermind was.
But if you'd actually gone to save him,
that would've cleared your name.
As it turns out,
the Crown Prince really is innocent.
I assume that by this very moment,
the Imperial Inspectorate mole is caught.
By the way,
I really should thank you.
Ning Chen, oh Ning Chen.
Quite the clever scheme indeed.
So what if you know?
Are you aware
that the moment you walked in,
you were already a dead man?
Take him down!
Impressive.
Just keeping it low-key.
What a fine Empress you are.
This poison...
You'd even use it on me.
Same old flavor.
Delicious.
So you believe
the Crown Prince really did it?
I merely raised one possibility.
And then?
He had a motive for the gold mine scheme,
but no reason to collude with foreigners
and betray his country.
After saying all this,
aren't you afraid I'll still trust him?
After all,
he is my own flesh and blood.
Ning Chen,
you wish to eliminate your rivals
and seize absolute power.
But that crown of yours
isn't quite secure yet.
Oh, my dear Your Majesty,
I'm doing serious work here.
Please stop teasing me.
Go on.
Since ancient times,
struggles for the throne
have always been fights over succession.
Whoever stands to gain the most
is the one behind it all.
If it isn't the Crown Prince,
who does Your Majesty think it could be?
I have a plan
that can kill three birds with one stone.
However,
it requires Uncle Tianxuan's cooperation.
I believed I treated you well.
Yet your methods
are utterly devoid of conscience.
I am the mother of this nation,
the Empress of Great Xuan,
your lawfully wedded wife.
But when have you ever truly looked at me?
What's wrong with my Zheng'er?
You chose a maid's son as Crown Prince.
Zheng'er is the legitimate heir.
That it has come to this
is all because of you.
I have said before,
the throne belongs to the worthy.
But your heart is twisted.
With a mother like you,
what good could Zheng'er ever learn?
You schemed endlessly,
only to bring about your own ruin.
If you show no mercy,
then don't blame me for showing none.
You think you've won?
Right now, my Zheng'er
has the Weilong Army besieging the palace.
By now,
they should be at the palace gates.
Prepare to die.
Zheng'er.
Zheng'er!
Mother.
Mother, we've lost.
They had set up an ambush long ago.
The Weilong Army we built with such care
is completely wiped out.
How could this happen?
Twenty thousand Weilong soldiers,
crushed just like that?
That is because His Majesty is wise.
When the Left Chancellor was imprisoned,
His Majesty foresaw your move.
He had already ordered me
to deploy Shenji Corps and 2,000 muskets,
lying in wait for the right moment.
All of this
was within His Majesty's grasp.
So he kept two thousand muskets
for this very purpose.
When did you begin to suspect me?
The moment you and the Left Chancellor
stole the gold mine, I already knew.
What did you say?
You knew all along?
Eight years.
Eight long years.
Even when you
had my beloved second son, Huai'en,
poisoned to death,
I
still endured it.
Waiting for the day you'd launch a coup,
so I could catch you all
in one fell swoop.
How ruthless you are, Your Majesty.
For Zheng'er, the Left Chancellor and I
plotted countless schemes.
That Your Majesty could endure it all...
I have lost.
I concede defeat.
Father.
Please spare Mother and me.
M-mother and I swear,
from this day on,
we'll never set foot in the capital again.
Get up.
Mother.
Don't beg him.
He is so cold-hearted,
how could he ever care
for what little family bond we have left?
Guards!
Yes, Your Majesty!
Take the Empress and Third Prince away,
to be publicly beheaded at Meridian Gate.
Come, Mother.
Mother!
Ning Chen.
Come with me.