You're blocking my shot.
Did your leg cramp up or what?
Well, well.
If it isn't Qiao Lili.
You know him?
No. Ignore that lunatic.
Jiao Jing.
You've got some nerve showing up.
I came to warn him.
Long Xiao is about to make his move.
What a crappy movie.
Vulgar, my ass.
I thought it was a porno.
Hey kid, what the hell are you looking at?
Dahai, let's go.
Damaged goods who got raped,
and now she's hooked another sucker.
Lin Qiuyun, you wanna die?
I'll rip that mouth right off your face.
No, no, no.
Look at you.
Hooked up with such a wimp.
Say that one more time.
Calm down.
Apologize.
I won't apologize.
What of it?
You gonna hit me or something?
Sissy.
You know who my bro is?
The Giant Wood Group.
Ever heard of it?
The number two of Giant Wood Group,
Zhu Yihai's good brother.
Xiong Dali is my blood brother.
Xiong Dali.
Punks like you,
ever heard of him?
Let's go, Lili.
Don't waste your breath on an idiot.
Who you calling an idiot?
Hold it!
Nobody move.
Women, stay put.
Check the men one by one.
Who the hell are you?
Causing trouble around here.
Know who my good brother is?
Who?
My good brother is Xiong Dali.
Your brother's name is Xiong Dali?
Damn right.
You guys...
Xiong Dali is exactly who we're after.
Move over there.
What are you doing?
Move, move.
Stop hitting me!
Hit him, not me!
I'm dying, I'm dying.
Stop it!
What?
You wanna stick your neck out?
Long Xiao sent you, right?
Who's Long Xiao?
Never heard of him.
Not gonna admit it?
Fine.
Dali, do it.
You think you can scare me?
Picked that up real quick, huh?
It wasn't me.
I just mean...
This many of you against one guy? Not fair.
Asking for a beating?
No, no, no, brother!
Talk.
Where's Zhu Yihai?
Zhu... Zhu Yihai...
Zhu Yihai is right behind you.
Trying to trick me, you bastard?
Don't say my brother didn't warn you.
Wait, wait, wait!
Who the hell are you?
Xiong Dali, Guohong Steel Plant.
Let my brother go.
Let my brother go first.
In your dreams.
Guess he doesn't want you in one piece.
Don't, don't do it!
He's got a weapon.
Hai, Lili!
Go!
Hold on.
What?
Who are you?
I'm Zhu Yihai.
Holy shit.
Get him!
Hai, you guys go first.
We're not leaving.
We leave together.
These small fry?
I can handle them.
Get out of here, now!
Don't give me any crap.
Go!
Forget about me, just go!
Dahai!
You're the one they're after.
If you stay, Dali has to protect you too.
Let's go!
Dahai, hurry up!
You stay safe.
We'll wait for you, Dali.
Dahai
Why are you back?
Wei Wei
You bastard Long Xiao, let him go!
It's been a while, Yihai.
What do you want?
What could I want?
Of course I'm here to see my good brother
to talk a little business.
You hurt my brother and want to talk business?
Long Xiao.
He's your brother,
so I'm not your brother anymore?
Besides,
he fell on his own by accident.
Don't believe me? Ask him.
Isn't that right, brother?
You...
Bullshit!
Long Xiao.
Yihai,
everyone says you're a loyal man.
You wouldn't abandon your brother
over some petty gains, would you?
What do you really want?
All this fighting and killing
isn't really my style anymore.
Let's keep things simple between us.
I'll give you two choices.
Either you sign this contract willingly,
or I sign it for you.
Your call.
Aimin Street.
For the sake of Aimin Street,
do you know how many people you've killed?
Don't make false accusations, Zhu Yihai.
A huge company like Giant Wood Group
is completely clean.
What happened on Aimin Street
were nothing more than accidents.
Zhu Yihai,
I'd advise you to behave yourself.
You wouldn't want
any more accidents to happen, would you?
Dahai,
we can't beat him.
Dahai!
Don't worry about me.
What's so funny?
Come to your senses?
Yeah, I have.
Then sign it.
I'm so glad I signed for 52 back then.
Otherwise, you'd have gotten your way.
Glad, huh?
Shouldn't you be regretting it instead?
Otherwise, your brother
wouldn't be in this state now.
Do you know why Director Ge
gave Aimin Street to me
instead of you?
Come on,
let's hear it.
Dad,
why bother talking with Long Xiao?
I also wanted to bet everything
on Zhu Yihai.
But he can't come up with six million.
Then take a look at this.
Do you know
that everything happening on Aimin Street
is all connected to Long Xiao?
This was all Long Xiao's doing.
Good thing I didn't sign with Long Xiao.
Otherwise, we'd be in deep trouble.
Why would you
sell it cheap to Zhu Yihai then?
He's the only one
truly trying to find a way out for our plant.
When the plant gets demolished,
I'll open a foot massage parlor on Aimin Street.
Everyone from the night market can come to my place.
You mean
you'd let our plant workers
all come work for you?
Right, come work at my place.
That's why I feel at ease
giving the plant to him.
How interesting.
I schemed with that old man forever,
and your foot parlor beat me to it.
Because you've done too many bad things.
If you'd cared even a little for these people,
I would've signed that contract.
But now?
Let me tell you,
no way in hell.
Really?
What if I cripple him?
I dare you to touch him.
Dali!
Hai.
I'm late.
Long Xiao,
let Wei Wei go!
Dali!
Oh, Xiong Dali, Xiong Dali.
You should really learn from Dahai.
Look how obedient he became after one stint in jail.
Speaking of that prison time,
I actually set that up too.
You thought you saved me?
It was all just a plan to lure you in.
After all, Zhu Yihai
is famously loyal far and wide.
Why would you do this?
Why?
Without you,
who'd deal with Ge Zhendong for me?
Alright, alright.
Let's cut the crap.
I'm running out of patience.
Sign it or not?
Dahai,
don't waste words on him.
Wei Wei,
when adults are talking,
kids don't butt in.
My eye!
Long Xiao!
I'll kill you!
Long Xiao, you're despicable.
You don't want to sign it?
Then I'll have to sign it for you.
See?
Such a simple little thing.
And you turned it into this mess.
Yihai!
All of you, stay right there!
Long Xiao!
I've already called the cops.
Let go!
Dahai! Dahai!
Dahai!
Wei Wei! Wei Wei!
Intentional assault.
Come with me.
Dao Balian.
You really think you're something, huh?
Get the hell out!
I'm still the Head of Security, you know.
Cuff him.
Huilian.
What did you do to her?
Take a guess.
Move!
Hurry!
Call an ambulance!
Hurry up, come on!