(Respect copyright)
♪Memories hold you back
from fulfilling your dreams♪
♪Only by moving forward
can you find reunion♪
♪Endings only mark new routes♪
♪It's all part of the scenery♪
♪To the horizon's call♪
♪Your journey hasn't started♪
♪Towards mountains,
chase the stars bright♪
♪Let time embrace you
and wash away the past♪
♪Put every twist behind you♪
♪Drift leisurely through time♪
♪Make headway against the wind♪
♪Let mountains bow to your pace♪
♪Rush towards a life without regret♪
♪Let your nature burst free♪
=The First Jasmine=
=Episode 29=
Mingxi, we have no way out now.
Once the Eastern Palace rises,
everything will be fine.
You wish.
You think he'll make you a high official
when he becomes Emperor?
You've done so many dirty deeds for him.
You know it in your heart.
If he wants to seem honest
and righteous,
the first person he'll silence is you.
He is not that kind of person.
- Zuidie and I trust him.
- Don't mention her again.
You've truly been bewitched
by that woman.
I'm telling you, she framed Ye Li.
I will definitely kill her.
(Mo Jingli.)
With the death of Princess Lingyun,
Cangbei will surely be enraged.
Peace will be hopeless.
War might even break out immediately.
They previously ordered Zhang Hengyuan
to kill Zhong Xingtong.
That was meant to sow discord.
Mo Jingli.
Are you really going
to persist on the wrong path?
I never meddled in their matters.
Fine,
you didn't before.
And never meddle then.
From now on, you'll be a regular worker
at Shende Shop.
Ye Li,
do I still have a chance?
Why not put it in the pond?
Mix some river water with the pond water
and let it stay for a few days,
so it can slowly get used to the water.
Then it'll be better
to put it in the pond.
Very thoughtful of you.
From now on,
it's going to live at our home.
Naturally, we must treat it well.
Just like when a person leaves home,
they watch the moon
to feel less homesick.
You miss Lishan Mountain?
If there's a chance,
I'll take you back to Lishan Mountain
to see the moon.
Isn't the moon the same anywhere?
Is the moon above Lishan Mountain
different
from the one above us?
Of course.
The moon above Lishan Mountain
is so big.
Lying in the courtyard every night,
I felt as if it was embracing me.
Lying in the courtyard?
Did you watch the moon every night?
What about other disciples?
I don't know.
Every night,
I watched it rise through the branches.
Sometimes, some clouds trailed the moon.
And the moon there is very bright.
When it snows,
the moonlight and the snowlight
blend together.
When walking in the snow,
you'll feel like you're in a fairyland.
Alright, we'll go this winter.
We can happily watch the snow
under the moonlight.
(Xiangqi Pavilion)
Are you hungry?
A new eatery opened on the street.
Their lamb dumplings are good.
Want to go try some?
How about noodles? Or noodle soup?
You have an appetite, but I don't.
Why not?
Are you full from drinking water?
My stomach is full of anger.
Li Feibai! Mr. Li!
You're really something.
Listen,
yesterday at Xihua,
it was such a big show.
Many people
were watching my performance.
Even the Vice Minister of Revenue,
just transferred from Qinzhou, was there.
When my performance was
at a crucial moment,
what did you do?
You suddenly carried me off
like a sack of grain!
Do you know
what the consequences would be?
What consequences?
Just get someone else to perform.
Li Feibai!
Stop yelling.
Listen, you shouldn't
have learned dancing at all.
With your good voice,
you should've learned singing instead.
Don't be mad.
Don't use this perfume anymore.
It's too strong.
Mind your own business.
Who are you to me?
Who am I to you? You tell me.
Feibai, what you did yesterday
ruined my reputation
and broke the business rules.
In the future,
nobody will pay me to perform.
And I won't be able to earn any money.
That's easy. I'll compensate you.
Compensate? You can do that this time,
but can you do that for a lifetime?
Alright, then I'll compensate you
for a lifetime.
Anyone can talk big.
Buying my freedom costs a lot of money.
How much?
A lot, anyway.
And I'm not easy to support.
You don't even have a house right now.
In the future,
where will I live with you?
You can't expect me
to drift around with you.
Also, if you want me
to be your concubine,
it's not impossible.
But your future wife
must be easygoing.
If she bullies me, I won't stand for it.
Why are you only thinking
about being a concubine?
What? Could it be
that you'd marry me as your wife?
Li Feibai,
when I was little,
I already had a rough time.
I can't let it happen again.
I won't go anywhere except the capital.
Apart from dancing,
I can't do any work at all.
If you want me
to live a poor life with you,
forget it.
If you can't support me,
don't even think about marrying me.
Well, that's not up to you.
So smelly!
Go wash up.
Is it really that smelly?
Yes, go!
(Jingzhao Prefecture)
Qin Cang,
under Marquis Muyang's command,
committed serious crimes
and should be executed by law.
However, you timely repented.
You testified against your accomplices,
truthfully confessed,
and voluntarily presented the evidence
of Marquis Muyang's crimes.
That was quite helpful.
Therefore, you're treated
with exceptional leniency.
By special grace, your life is spared.
Your property is to be confiscated,
and you are exiled to Qianchuan.
Yes, I appreciate it.
The Empress Dowager asks
if you have anything else to say.
Since she has already treated me
as a discarded pawn,
I have nothing more to say.
I only ask for one thing.
I hope Tianyang will be safe and sound.
After all these years,
I have not failed the Empress Dowager.
Keep up.
Qin Cang, you're not dead!
Sorry to disappoint you.
I'm lucky to be alive.
Marquis Muyang,
Qin Cang has confessed
that Chen Longxiang is still alive,
and that Gongshu Yang
found out the concrete evidence
of the weaponry case.
I never thought
I would be defeated by my own hand.
May I have a few final words
with Marquis Muyang?
Well, I'll let you two talk.
When I was a kid,
I lived with my mom alone.
At 14, you brought me back
to your house.
You hired a coach
to teach me martial arts.
The old servants told me
I was also a young master in the house,
and your son.
But you never
treated me as your son.
You sent me to Cangbei
to smuggle weapons out of the pass.
You made me kill for you
to eliminate your adversaries.
You asked me to amass wealth
and collude with the enemy.
You made me do all sorts of dirty deeds.
It was because I valued you.
Did you?
Then why did you want to kill me?
Marquis Muyang,
I just want to ask you one thing.
Without me,
if it were Zhou Tianyang instead,
what would you have done?
Would you also have silenced him
for your own protection?
Although you never treated me as a son,
in my heart,
you will always be my father.
Marquis Muyang, you gave me life.
For all these years, you have raised me
and taught me.
I'm grateful to you.
Father.
Take care.
They're here.
Come on.
What are you doing?
We are the family of Young Master Qin.
It will be a long journey.
Thank you for escorting him.
That's okay.
We'll take good care of him on the road.
We've prepared some food.
Please have some before you go.
Alright.
Be quick. We're kind of in a rush.
Master, I got you some money and stuff.
Take it with you.
Where is Zhou Tianyang?
He is at home.
Tell him from me
he should give up.
He should leave the capital right now
to go to his mother in Lingnan.
Yes, I will certainly tell him.
Master, the journey to Qianchuan
is long and tough.
Take care.
Thank you.
Master, give it to us.
My room is over there.
Your mansion looks nothing special.
There is not even a decent plaque.
(Tuisi Pavilion)
Isn't your Lishan Academy quite famous?
At your wedding, your tutors
didn't even give you an inscription?
This little fish is even shorter
than my nail protector.
What is this place used for?
So, you can actually fish here?
That's quite a nice hobby.
Ye Ying, why exactly did you come?
Bring tea.
Yes.
Your Highness, I'll go help.
Ye Li,
there's something
I don't know who to ask.
After thinking it over,
I want to hear your opinion.
You actually want my opinion
on something? That's rare.
Don't interrupt. I'm serious.
Go ahead.
His Highness passed away so suddenly,
and didn't have any children.
He was the only bloodline
of the former crown prince.
His death cuts off the bloodline.
Recently, some people around me
have advised me
to adopt a clever child
from close relatives.
Then, His Highness will have a child
to inherit his heritage.
What's your take on this?
Say something! What do you think?
Ye Ying, you are still young.
Why tie down your entire life so early?
If you live in an empty house
and raise a child who is not your own,
is it worth it?
His Highness is dead,
but I have to move on.
Sure, you do.
But to move on,
you have more than one choice.
Nowadays, social customs are more open.
A woman can divorce her husband,
can take the imperial examinations,
can engage in business,
can study and write books,
and even become an official.
Take Lady Lin, who writes books,
and Mrs. Yu,
the wealthy silkworm raiser.
Both of them are living a splendid life.
Besides, you also know
Mo Jingli is the son
of the former crown prince.
His identity is already a shackle.
All these years,
the Empress Dowager and His Majesty
have been deeply wary of him.
If you adopt a child now,
from the moment
that child enters Prince Li's Mansion,
he will also bear the shackle.
He cannot be an official
to pursue his ambitions,
and must live on thin ice,
and may even become someone else's pawn,
enticed and exploited,
ultimately drawn into a vortex,
just like Mo Jingli.
You won't be able to protect him.
Think twice.
You have a long way to go,
and don't rush to decide.
You always have a lot to say.
But does what I said make sense?
Master Qin, have some?
Thank you.
That carriage behind
has been following us for a while.
It looks like a rich family's carriage.
But still, stay alert.
Just in case.
Come on, guys, try some.
It's our own meat.
When traveling, we should look out
for each other. Try it.
- Come on.
- Alright.
Well, thank you then.
Where are you heading?
We are going to Qianchuan.
Qianchuan? What a coincidence!
We are also going to Qianchuan.
What a coincidence!
Sit. Enjoy your food.
- Let me know if you need more.
- Alright, thanks.
(I am Lin Tinglan.)
(T I N G, L A N.)
Have a try.
(Turns out a melon cut with your knife
tastes this sweet.)
(I told you it was sweet.)
(Lakeview Garden)
Master Qin, you're awake.
Come on, we're hitting the road soon.
And you have to put this on.
Alright.
(Lakeview Garden)
My Lady, why don't we go with them?
We can look out for him on the road.
And Young Master Qin
will suffer a bit less.
He broke the law. He deserves this.
Are we still going to Qianchuan?
Yes.
Qianchuan is a beautiful place.
Of course, we are going there.
As for him and me,
if we're meant to meet again, we will.
Let's go.
Make way.
Sir.
After countless hardships,
Liu Sanlang finally married Lady Meng.
Unexpectedly,
Liu Sanlang's mother
didn't like Lady Meng.
One moment, she scolded Lady Meng
for being impolite,
and the next, she blamed Lady Meng
for being unable to do farm work.
She found fault with everything
and cruelly broke a lovely couple up.
With a letter of divorce,
Lady Meng was kicked out of their home.
By the Willow Pavilion,
Liu Sanlang led his horse
to see her off.
They walked side by side.
When they reached the fork in the road,
they burst into tears.
Liu Sanlang said,
"My dear,
today you go home for now,
but I will surely bring you back soon.
Once I have pacified my mother,
I will personally go find you
and bring you home."
Lady Meng looked at her husband,
tears sparkling in her eyes.
Forcing a smile, she said,
"I hope you'll remember what you said.
No matter what happens,
do not betray me."
They swore to heaven
and parted in tears.
To know what happens next,
come and listen again.
- Bravo!
Good story!
Bravo!
Thank you.
Make way.
You've been coming here often
these days,
just to listen to this?
I haven't heard this story before.
It must be a new story.
So,
can Lady Meng and Liu Sanlang
end up together?
Probably not.
Why not?
Liu Sanlang's father died
in corvée labor,
and Lady Meng's elder brother
was the overseer at the time.
That's why Liu Sanlang's mother
doesn't like Lady Meng
and constantly nitpicks her.
And Liu Sanlang is a filial son,
unable to defy his mother.
So, it's quite tricky.
Maybe Lady Meng can move Mrs. Liu.
After all, she has nothing to do
with the death of Mrs. Liu's husband.
She is not to blame.
If you like,
we can pay off the storyteller
and make him tell the story
the way you want.
Where is Feng Zhiyao? Where did he go?
He's been in a bad mood lately
and left the capital
to clear his mind.
Li, I want
to discuss something with you.
What is it?
Look, Marquis Muyang has fallen,
and my clan's name has been cleared.
It's all over now.
You are not Lady Meng,
and I am not Liu Sanlang.
From now on,
the two of us can be together happily.
You will never be alone again.
So, can you let Qingshuang
go back to her own home?
Why?
Now, there are plenty of servants
in our mansion,
and Qingyu has been serving you.
Just let Qingshuang go home, okay?
She's stayed with you for eight years.
It's time for her to go home.
But Qingshuang has always been with me.
I will always be with you, alright?
Alright.
You agreed?
I'll tell Qingshuang about it later.
And don't think about her anymore.
From now on, whatever is on your mind,
or whatever you want to say,
just tell me.
Alright?
Alright, but never get tired of me.
(Now the enemy frequently nosed around.)
Zhou Jing, you are authoritarian,
forming cliques for personal gain.
You framed loyal officials,
causing wrongful convictions.
You smuggled weapons
and betrayed the nation.
With all these charges,
which one is unjust to you?
Even if you refuse to plead guilty,
I can still convict you.
Marquis Muyang, you should understand.
At this point,
denying what you did is futile.
Do you have any last wishes?
I want to see Mo Xiuyao.
Prince Ding is not
in charge of this case.
What's the point of seeing him?
Even if he is supervising the case,
given what you've done to his clan,
do you think he will let you off?
As long as I see him,
this case will be concluded.
(Qingfeng Mingyue Tower)
Your Highnesses, it just rained.
Our carriage is stuck
at the intersection.
They'll be here in a moment.
Yao.
Liu Sanlang and Lady Meng
really can't be together forever?
Why are you still thinking about it?
It's just a story.
Answer me.
I don't know.
Things change, and people change.
People's thinking is variable
and uncertain.
A thought arises.
And then, a thought disappears.
How they choose
is up to them, not us.
Then let's come back in a few days
and listen to the ending.
Alright.
Your Highnesses.
Chen Longxiang has confessed.
Gongshu Yang and Murong Shen
are interrogating Marquis Muyang.
But Marquis Muyang
suddenly wanted to see you.
Gongshu Yang wants you there right now.
I'll go there, and you go home.
Go.
♪You always love with pain♪
♪Forgetting you deserve to be loved too♪
♪How the rain outside
nurtures the heart♪
♪That's how you are cherished♪
♪You don't need to chase♪
♪After clouds that winds pursue♪
♪You can silently watch each sunrise♪
♪Finding happiness by your side♪
♪You don't need to chart a map♪
♪Of every bend where love winds on♪
♪Nor travel far to guide its course♪
♪To make your heart♪
♪Warm again♪
Stop!
- Your Highness.
- What's wrong?
Her Highness is behind us.
Why did you come?
Did I run fast?
What's wrong?
Let's come back tomorrow.
What?
To listen to the story.
To hear the story of Liu Sanlang
and Lady Meng. Come again tomorrow.
♪You don't need to chase♪
Alright, as you wish.
Don't get wet, or you may catch a cold.
Go home.
See you at home.
♪Nor travel far to guide its course♪
♪To make your heart♪
♪Warm again♪
(Jingzhao Prefecture)
Prince Ding.
Marquis Muyang
is insisting on seeing you.
We'll leave it to you now.
Sure.
You want to see me?
Prince Ding, you look good.
You must have been happy lately.
Seeing your current situation,
I can't help feeling happy.
It's risky to be an official.
Today, you're flattered by all.
Tomorrow, you're a prisoner.
Too early for you to celebrate.
Eight years ago,
you were in this cell,
while I was outside the cell.
Yes. What a pity.
Now, you're in this cell,
while I'm outside.
Things are ever-changing
and unpredictable.
The rise and fall of a person happens,
as illusory as a dream.
Back then, when I was in Huaixi,
I lived in a room of this size,
a side room made of straw mats.
Every time it rained,
the floor was all damp,
and I almost couldn't move.
Later, I was recommended
to take the prefectural exam.
And because of my outstanding results,
I had the chance to become an official.
And then, step by step,
I entered the central government
and rose to my current position.
But who would have thought
that in the end, I would return
to a dark, small room before death.
If you want to express your feelings,
you've found the wrong person.
The imperial family is heartless.
The court has been rotten,
full of hypocritical beasts.
But you are one of those
I think much of.
(Preview)
Aren't you curious
who cheated your brother
out of the late Emperor's edict?
Shut up!
Just wait to die!
Was it your mom who cheated my brother
out of the late Emperor's edict?
Yes.
Your Highness!
Yao...
He's dead.
♪Memories hold you back
from fulfilling your dreams♪
♪Only by moving forward
can you find reunion♪
♪Endings only mark new routes♪
♪It's all part of the scenery♪
♪To the horizon's call♪
♪Your journey hasn't started♪
♪Towards mountains,
chase the stars bright♪
♪Both joy and grief
make the trip worthwhile♪
♪Trying to catch up
to your own lost shadow♪
♪Within the wilds, echoes thrive♪
♪Clear mind leads to a clear path♪
♪Be grateful to your losses♪
♪Make your steps weightless♪
♪Towards mountains,
chase the stars bright♪
♪Let time embrace you
and wash away the past♪
♪Put every twist behind you,
drift leisurely through time♪
♪Make headway against the wind,
let mountains bow to your pace♪
♪Rush towards a life without regret♪
♪Let your nature burst free♪
♪Unbound by form♪