Jiao Jing, don't move.
Put the knife down.
What I can't have,
you can't have either.
Hold on.
Yihai!
Yihai, hold on!
Brother Hai.
The guy who hurt Huilian, we got him.
He can really take a beating.
Dahai...
Wake up soon.
Everyone's waiting for you.
Dahai, how long are you gonna sleep?
Don't worry, I'm here.
Where are you wiping?
You...
Is it any of your business?
Hand it over.
Give it to me.
Give it!
You're getting physical now?
You wanna fight?
I'd have kicked your ass long ago!
Fine, bring it on!
Stop!
I'm counting to three.
Both of you, let go!
Alright, one.
Two.
Three.
How can you fight so dirty, bitch?
You're no better.
You let go!
Are you letting go or not?
You let go first.
Lili.
Yihai, you're awake!
Ge Bing.
How long was I out?
You've been out for days.
How's Dali doing?
Liu Tianqi has been arrested.
The statement's all done.
See?
I told you I had nothing to do with Long Xiao.
I believe you.
Thank you.
For donating blood.
For saving my life.
Actually,
don't thank me.
Our blood types don't match.
Then aren't you my...
I'm not your what?
Nothing, nothing.
What are you gonna do next?
I have to make sure
my dad won't work with Giant Wood Group.
And if that doesn't work out?
If it doesn't,
then I'll go abroad.
I don't wanna see the factory ruined by him.
How about
you come abroad with me?
I-I don't wanna be a burden.
You can be my interpreter.
Silly.
Going abroad
isn't something you can just do whenever.
Here, this is for you.
Found it on the kidnappers.
You're awake too.
I'll head back now.
Get well soon.
Ge Bing.
Heh.
Not bad, Brother Hai.
Another one.
Wei Wei.
Little brat.
What are you doing here?
Applying medicine.
I heard everything.
You turned her down
because of Lili, right?
Let me ask you something.
Say a guy
time-travels into his father's body,
but he never meets his mom.
Could those two
ever end up giving birth to him?
No way.
That's what I thought.
So I gotta be with Lili.
With Lili...
With...
You wanna go after Lili!
Hurry up then.
Just go for her.
Quit hemming and hawing about it.
I saw her having dinner with another guy.
Who? How old was he?
I didn't get a good look.
But it was at the Seafood House.
Then he's gotta be a rich guy.
Totally unnecessary.
Brother Hai, you're awake.
That Liu Tianqi punk got locked up.
Don't worry.
Sooner or later he'll rat out Long Xiao.
Good.
Once Long Xiao goes down,
we'll all be in the clear.
Then shouldn't we take care of our own business?
What business?
You better get the red envelopes ready.
Red envelopes?
Brother Hai, come on, tell me.
Who is it?
Who do you think?
Lili.
Lili?
Brother, you're making your move?
Keep your voice down.
We're in a hospital.
So what's your plan?
That's why I was thinking,
you two should help me figure it out.
What's there to figure out?
Just use your old playbook
all over again.
What old playbook?
A little movie,
you watch it together,
her little hand,
you grab it,
and boom, you're in.
No way.
Going to a movie is too lame.
Isn't that how you went after Huilian?
Now suddenly it's too lame for you?
This should be enough, right?
Alright.
Holy crap.
Qian Huilian.
You're lurking around like a ghost all day.
What's the matter?
Haunting me?
Are you out of your mind?
When have I ever come here for you?
Let's talk.
Talk about what? I gotta get to the hospital.
Hurry up.
Spit it out.
This sixty thousand yuan,
you take it.
Hey, Qian Huilian, what's that supposed to mean?
You think this sixty thousand
is gonna make me give up Brother Hai?
Stop making such a fuss all the time.
This is insurance I bought without telling him.
Remember to renew it for him later.
Look at you showing off.
Don't tell him.
I'm leaving.
Hold on.
Qian Huilian.
What are you getting at?
Do you have any idea
how hard Brother Hai worked
to pay back this sixty thousand?
Why are you giving it back to him now?
Qiao Lili.
You don't really think
Zhu Yihai owes me money, do you?
What else?
Didn't you open this pool hall for him?
What's between us
can't be settled that easily.
That sixty thousand debt
was just an excuse.
Get it?
Hey, Qian Huilian,
What's with all this back and forth?
Brother Hai's doing fine with me looking after him.
You can rest easy.
Can't you tell good advice from bad?
Show some sense, would you?
Take this and keep it safe.
And don't say a word.
With all the fighting going on,
it'll come in handy sooner or later.
I'm off.
I was just saying...
Don't move!
What is your business here?
I'm with the Imperial Army.
You don't look like Imperial Army.
You must be a Collaborator Interpreter.
Pretty girl.
You're here.
Yeah.
This is for you.
How thoughtful.
Why'd you ask me to Dongxing Factory?
All mysterious like this.
Just out of the hospital and showing off?
I was just thinking,
they're playing my favorite movie here.
I figured I had to watch it with you.
What movie?
Come on, hurry up.
Or we'll miss the opening.
So weird and secretive.
Your leather jacket looks great today.
You like this style, right?
Not really.
Dahai
Why'd you ask me to a movie today?
Well, it's because Dali and the others
keep calling you
"Sis, Sis" all the time.
So I was thinking...
Thinking what?
Look at you, you're impossible.
I'll let you in on a secret.
I've got a surprise for you.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Have some seeds
while you watch.
Mm-hmm.
A surprise.
What's the surprise?
If it's really that, then I...
On behalf of my dad...
This is nice.
That's so weird.
Did your leg cramp up or something?
Isn't that Qiao Lili?
You know her?
No. Ignore him, he's a nutjob.
Excuse me
Is Zhu Yihai here?
No, he's not.
Who are you?
Oh my
Long time no see.
Jiao Jing.
You've got the nerve to show up?
Cut the crap.
Where's Zhu Yihai?
It's getting late.
You should head home.
Whatever happens with Zhu Yihai
has nothing to do with you anymore.
I don't mean anything by it.
I just came to warn him.
Long Xiao's about to make his move.