=The Embroidered Truth=
Your Highness,
the Prince has returned.
You should be happy.
Should I be happy?
The Prince is back.
I dressed so carefully,
yet he still went to her.
Your Highness,
your plan was to bring the Prince back
and keep him here.
That may be true,
but I'm still unhappy.
=Episode 22=
Like a lotus rising from clear water,
naturally beautiful without
decoration.
Do you know my favorite is
the light and plain,
like orchids?
Your Highness, I don't understand.
I meant I'm interested in you.
We haven't done the marriage rites.
It would be improper.
I wouldn't dare.
Are you afraid?
Or unwilling?
I'm already here.
Do you still need to ask?
If you are so inclined,
then on this full moon night,
give yourself to me.
My Lady!
So here you are.
I searched everywhere.
I finally found you.
Xiaotao said you'd drink a lot tonight.
She made you hangover soup.
Perfect.
I do have a bit of a headache.
Drinking really clouds the mind.
What a waste of this full moon.
Go on.
Miss Rulan,
are you alright?
Don't worry. I met the Prince today.
He seems straightforward,
nothing inappropriate.
Li Xiaoshou succeeded at
Yanyu Embroidery House.
Wu Lian embroidered the victims' names
onto handkerchief.
Ironclad evidence.
We can act now.
Wait.
One more thing.
His crimes are clear.
What else is missing?
We need an embroiderer willing
to testify.
Testify?
That's not easy.
But the Flower Festival is almost here.
If we miss it,
we may never get another
chance like this.
It's fine.
I've made arrangements.
I'm just worried about Miss Rulan...
I need one more thing too.
Mr. Liu,
Everything at the Flower Festival
hinges on this.
Your Highness,
Lady Cheng'en requests an audience.
You may enter.
You're not with the Prince?
Yet you come to see me.
I belong to you.
Of course I come to you first.
What is it?
After talking with the Prince today,
I discovered someone in
this manor
wants to harm you.
Who would wish to harm me?
Wu Lian.
If you're just going to keep
fighting with him,
don't bother telling me.
Wu Lian knows my taste perfectly.
In all of Jinxiu City,
only he can embroider
what I want.
Your Highness,
Master Wu has brought the
Flower Festival gown.
Please try on the gown, Your Highness.
Ask him in...
Wenyue,
If you care to hear my words,
I'll continue.
But if you prefer
to have Wu Lian help you
try on the gown,
then I'll take my leave.
Luoxia,
tell him to go back and rest early.
Yes.
Speak.
The Prince has been away for years.
He is no stranger to luxury.
But when he returned,
he only saw plain and light clothes.
Wu Lian's embroidery is excellent,
but he always uses light colors
for your gowns.
Now that the Prince is back,
seeing you dressed and acting
as elegantly as ever,
it may lack novelty.
Go on.
The camellia comes from a foreign land.
Beautiful as it is,
at the Flower Festival ceremony,
if someone claims you have ties
with foreign lands,
how will you explain?
He's just a craftsman.
What does he know of foreign matters?
An ordinary man might not know.
But Wu Lian is a master
in the embroidery world.
In Jinxiu City,
his associates are rich and powerful.
He would have heard.
The Prince went on a campaign
to pacify the foreign lands.
If he meant no harm,
why would he embroider this?
He dares to harbor such thoughts.
Master Wu,
Her Highness asks you
not to wait any longer.
Lady Cheng'en is discussing gowns
with her inside.
Does she like it?
Lady Cheng'en says you only know
elaborate designs
to please Her Highness,
but they don't suit His Highness's taste.
Perhaps you did it on purpose.
And the camellias
are from foreign lands.
What did Her Highness say?
Forget it.
Still no witnesses today.
I talked to those ladies,
but whenever Yanyu Embroidery
House comes up,
they clam up.
This last step is hard and risky.
If those girls won't testify,
the handkerchief and needles
would have died with Ms. Meng Wan.
Continue the search tomorrow.
How did it go?
After hearing my words,
she won't see Wu Lian anymore.
Without the Princess Consort as
his shield,
Wu Lian will never recover.
Xiaojiu, go and find Mr. Liu.
Tell them this is the final step.
We got it.
Yes.
Wu Lian of Yanyu Embroidery House
requests an audience
with Your Highness.
So you're the embroiderer
my wife favors most.
Yes.
What brings you here?
Your Highness,
I have something to say.
The Lady Cheng'en currently in the manor
is an impostor.
Are you aware of your crime?
I am.
I know speaking against a superior
is a grave offense.
But knowing the truth
and hiding it is worse.
I stake the reputation of
Yanyu Embroidery House
that every word I say is true.
If not,
I submit to your punishment.
Speak.
The current Lady Cheng'en
is an embroiderer from my house
in disguise.
Years ago, she fell for me.
I rejected her.
Three years ago,
she jumped from the city wall.
Continue.
I fear this woman will bring
disaster to Jinxiu City.
Nanny Du, I had nightmares all night.
You're carrying too much worry.
I'll have them make a calming tea.
Where did the Prince stay last night?
He never left the study.
But...
But what?
Don't hide it.
Master Wu went to the study
early this morning.
He spoke with the Prince
for a long time.
Is Wu Lian truly trying
to harm me?
I have seen Master Wu's loyalty
to you with my own eyes.
But
there are rumors among the people
that Wu Lian bullies others
and controls the manor.
A false lady
has exposed a true villain.
Get my change of clothes ready.
Yes.
If what you say is true...
Her Highness arrives!
Your Highness,
it's been years since you
tasted my cooking.
Don't you want to hear his words?
How dare you speak out
of turn before the Prince?
I've tolerated you like a dog
following me,
sparing your dignity.
Yet you dared to embroider
foreign flowers
on my Flower Festival gown.
Do you want to humiliate me
before the entire city?
No, no, no!
Your Highness,
I truly didn't know.
I only thought the flowers
were very vibrant.
How dare you!
You mingle with the rich
and powerful.
How could you not know?
Guards!
Confine Wu Lian to his house.
He may not leave.
Your Highness!
It's been three years.
You have no idea
what I've done to bring you back.
Now that I've seen you,
I wish I hadn't.
Is lawlessness part of your plan?
Have you investigated?
♪Night fades before the dawn♪
♪Old vows still guide my hand♪
♪The past no longer binds♪
♪My heart still shines through dust♪
♪Silent blooms, unchanged heart♪
♪Bare hands weave through the frost♪
♪Shadows linger, rain returns♪
♪Honor crowns my weary soul♪
♪For your faith that never broke♪
♪I shattered all the love I knew♪
♪No regrets, no debts unpaid♪
♪At dusk I walk away alone♪
♪If this tale becomes a storm♪
♪Old shadows fade from sight♪
♪One thought turns into ash♪
♪No future left to write♪
♪If I never fall♪
♪How could this waiting end♪
♪If I bear no scars♪
♪How could I challenge fate♪
♪I knew there was no way back♪
♪Yet I left this hope behind♪
♪For your faith that never broke♪
♪I shattered all the love I knew♪
♪No regrets, no debts unpaid♪
♪At dusk I walk away alone♪
♪If this tale becomes a storm♪
♪Old shadows fade from sight♪
♪One thought turns into ash♪
♪No future left to write♪
♪The lamp is out, you're gone♪
♪Heaven and earth fall silent♪
♪If we meet again someday♪
♪This longing sleeps beneath the snow♪