I just wanna ask
about this
What does fifty-two mean?
It's fate.
Can't be changed.
Well, I wanna see
if it really can't be changed.
Brother Long.
Xie Fan.
What are you doing here?
Dao Balian's looking for you.
What for?
How would I know?
Brother Yihai,
forget about that for now.
Let's sort our business out first.
It's fine, bro.
Let me see what Dao Balian wants.
He's always after me.
For a long time,
we've had some prejudice against feet.
But feet are just like hands.
They have tons of pressure points.
Zhu Yihai!
Get the hell out here!
Who is it?
What do you want?
None of your business, move aside.
No wonder you're never home.
So this is where you've been,
learning all this shady stuff.
Get your ass home now!
Embarrassing yourself here!
What's that supposed to mean?
What do you mean?
You're running a den of vice here!
Out of my way!
Hold on,
who are you calling a den of vice?
Beware of illegal massage services.
Protect your own rights.
Stay away from traps.
It's all written up there.
Don't listen to their nonsense.
What you're doing is illegal!
That's not true!
No, Brother Hai said
we're a legal massage place.
We're not illegal.
I recognize her.
She's always been a hooker.
Zhu Yihai tricked our wives into being escorts!
Who just said that?
Wanna die?
Holy shit!
Help! He's hitting us!
He's hitting us! Help, he's hitting us!
Was it you, punk?
It was him, he threw the first punch!
He's the one hitting people!
You can't just hit people!
He hit me!
Let's just talk this out.
No way! Dali!
Brother Dali!
You threw the first punch!
Brother Wei!
Whatever you do,
don't throw a punch!
Don't start trouble!
Wei Wei!
Brother Wei!
Why're you always after me? You like me?
Bro, soon as you left,
someone came and stirred up trouble.
And they beat up Wei Wei.
I just left and you dragged me right back.
Let me tell you,
lucky I got there in time.
So where's Wei Wei?
Laid up in the hospital.
Along with those injured family members.
You owe me one.
The families went to the hospital too?
You threw punches?
No, bro.
Then why are they all hospitalized?
Did someone mix in with them to stir trouble?
What?
Where's Sun Qian?
Sun Qian!
I'm screwed!
Where are you going?
Sun Qian.
Stop cleaning up.
Go get some rest.
Qian.
Yihai.
I'm sorry about this.
You said no one would look down on me.
But why did this happen?
Listen to me.
You and I are the same.
We earn money with our own hands.
There's nothing wrong with that.
Then why?
Why do they still call me a hooker?
It's okay now.
You did nothing wrong.
Believe in yourself.
Yihai, guess what I saw.
I guess I shouldn't have seen that.
Did you find Jiao Jing?
Holding one in your arms,
still thinking about another?
What do you know?
I didn't find Jiao Jing.
But I found some decent girl
publicizing your heroic deeds.
Who?
You're always messing around.
How would I know who?
On the bulletin board at the cultural hall.
Qian.
I'll stand up for you on this.
Go get some rest.
Dali.
Let's go.
Take one of these.
You take one too.
Take a flyer and have a look.
A bit of legal education.
Hold on.
Isn't this aimed at us?
Who's handing these out?
She's right over there.
Take it home and read it carefully.
What are you doing?
What's your problem?
Just legal education.
What are you really up to?
You're picking a fight on purpose, aren't you?
How am I picking a fight?
Does it have your name on it?
What?
Admitting it yourself?
Who sent you here?
I'm just doing legal education.
Don't flatter yourself.
I don't have the spare time
to Fight Qi with a scoundrel like you.
Enough.
I'm pretty busy myself.
Here.
Take a good look.
Don't end up in prison
without even knowing why.
Watch your mouth, will you?
Prison?
Could it be her?
Come on, get in the car.
Brother Hai.
That was Ge Zhendong, right?
Definitely.
That shiny, big forehead.
Robbing the cradle.
That's his girl.
No wonder he's coming after you.
What do we do?
What the hell is Ge Zhendong up to?
Tell Long Xiao to be careful from now on.
If anything goes wrong again,
this kind of stunt won't work.
Jing.
I'm sorry you had to go through that.
You still need to be careful.
It's all my fault.
I'm still being pushed around by that Yu guy.
You've stood by me all these years.
It hasn't been easy on you.
Brother Long.
Six years ago, you saved my life.
For you,
I'm not afraid of anything.
I promised you.
Once all this is over,
we'll leave this place together.
I've already arranged for Liu Tianqi to make the move.
Nobody's here.
This time, let's see what Zhu Yihai
has got left in him.