[The Legend of Rosy Clouds]
[Episode 8]
Young Master Qiyan,
what do you want to talk to us about?
Rumor has it
that Lord Zheng has been plagued
by nightmares recently.
I happen to have a plan.
He happens to have a plan?
What kind of plan?
Tell us.
Stop being so mysterious.
After all,
helping us is helping yourself.
Am I right,
Second Young Master Zheng?
What do you mean?
That day at Huan'e House,
you stole the fabric pattern
from my clothes for him.
Remember?
So Young Master Lou Qiyan
turns out to be
Second Young Master Zheng Shi.
You and Mr. Zheng share a deep bond
as grandparent and grandchild.
Meeting you here today,
I presume you are also looking for
the old ancestral temple
from Mr. Zheng's nightmares.
You're not as ignorant
of worldly affairs as rumors say.
I do want to repair the ancestral temple
to bring some comfort
to Grandfather's heart.
So you are
looking for the ancestral temple
that the Zheng family wants to repair.
I remember
the late governor Qi Hua,
to commemorate those meritorious officials
who died in battle,
specially ordered
the construction of the temple.
But
hasn't the temple
been lost due to the succession war
for a long time?
Not only do I know the exact location,
but I also have
the original construction blueprints.
Tell me.
What are your conditions?
Why?
You're brave enough
to negotiate conditions now?
Yeah.
Tell us your conditions.
How much money do you want?
This has nothing to do with money.
Then...
Second Young Master Zheng,
you are afraid that giving us
the blueprints
will offend Lord Zheng?
I've never been much concerned
with political and worldly affairs.
You're not afraid of trouble,
and you don't lack money.
Then what do you want?
If you want the map and blueprints,
I can give them to you.
Moreover,
the ancestral temple covers a large area.
Repairing it
will cost a considerable amount of money.
My Juyun Pavilion
is willing to bear half of the cost.
Bear half of the cost?
Do you think I can't afford to repair it?
If you ask me,
you know very well
how important the temple is to Mr. Zheng.
Yet you are handing it over now.
What are your true intentions?
Your Excellency.
We are short of money everywhere
in the residence right now.
We should save wherever we can.
Besides,
Juyun Pavilion
has plenty of manpower
and complete materials.
Why not go for it?
I do have one condition.
What is it?
I see.
I'll play a tune for you when I get back.
You...
It's been a few days. You...
Your Ladyship, you've become
even more amusing.
How about this?
You teach me a tune.
When I master it,
I'll give you the items.
What do you think?
Okay.
-Let's do—
-No.
Of course not.
This is highly improper.
Your Excellency.
Why not?
She's best at teaching.
You should know this
better than anyone else.
Fan Yun is my wife now.
I'm sure you know this better than anyone.
Besides,
your problem is fundamental.
It doesn't matter who teaches you.
Dripping water can hollow out stone.
Given time,
there will definitely be improvement.
Enough.
Give us the items if you want.
If you don't,
don't waste our time.
My Lady, let's go.
Let's discuss it again.
You can keep looking for them yourselves
and then fix it yourselves.
But as to the time...
Right.
Then why not...
This...
Your Excellency.
Second Young Master Zheng,
let us go back and think about it.
Wait for our word.
We'll think about it.
Your Excellency.
Did you find the blueprints?
No.
Then what were you thinking about?
I was thinking about
Lou Qiyan.
No,
strictly speaking,
it's Second Young Master Zheng.
Why were you thinking about that guy?
Your Excellency.
Lou Qiyan
is Zheng Shi, the Second Young Master
of the Zheng family.
Aren't you surprised at all?
I'm surprised.
No matter what identity he takes,
I find him annoying.
The blueprints were right there just now,
but you didn't want them.
Now we can't find them.
What should we do?
I don't believe it.
I am a genius.
In such a small library,
how can I not find a blueprint?
My goodness.
Still can't find them.
What should we do?
Keep looking for them.
I can't do it anymore.
Heading out?
Your Excellency.
Why are you
here?
I knew it.
You are brilliant, Your Excellency.
I don't want you to go.
Your Excellency, trust me.
One day.
I can get it done in one day.
I trust you,
but I don't trust him.
Why?
Your Excellency, think about it.
Not only is he giving us the blueprints,
but he's also giving us money.
What a great deal!
You...
Just...
Just this once.
Once.
No physical contact.
No joking around.
No staying out overnight.
No matter how hot it is,
you can't take off your clothes.
Take off...
take off clothes?
What are you talking about?
So childish.
Promise me now.
I-I promise you.
Then...
I have the carriage ready.
I'll wait for your return.
Thank you, Your Excellency.
Don't worry, Your Excellency.
I'll complete the mission successfully.
I'm leaving now.
Thank you, Your Excellency.
Slow down.
Don't worry!
[Huan'e House]
Before this,
have you ever hired a teacher?
They were all mediocre.
Then why not
play a piece
for me to hear?
Sure.
Since you are my teacher,
I will be honest with you.
How was it?
W-What do you mean?
My technique.
And the emotion
flowing from my fingertips?
Emotion?
A teacher once told me that
my legato is steady and solid,
my vibrato is like shaking jade
and pearls,
and my glissando is exquisite and light.
What kind of teacher
could give such a review?
This must have...
cost a lot.
A thousand gold a day.
What?
A thousand gold a day?
I understand.
Then that makes sense.
It makes sense now.
To be honest,
the tones I've heard since childhood
seem to differ from others
just slightly.
Almost all the teachers
advised me to give up early
and stop struggling.
Do you think someone like me
can still play a decent tune?
So that's how it is.
Young Master Qiyan,
I was impolite just now.
How about this?
Let me think of
a way to help you.
So what exactly are you thinking,
Your Excellency?
Dark Wolf...
Sit down and talk!
This is precisely because Mr. Zheng
targeted Fan Yun everywhere.
In order to let Fan Yun
gain recognition among the major nobles,
I had to act this way.
If you must mention
the matter of feigning illness,
you can understand it
as walking on the edge of a cliff.
But it can also be understood
as enjoying the unique scenery
from the top.
As for the repair work,
I actually think
Fan Yun must do it
and do it beautifully.
In this way,
not only will it ease Mr. Zheng's
so-called inner demons,
but it will also give the major nobles
a satisfactory explanation.
If, in the end,
regarding this repair work,
only a few people appreciate
Fan Yun's favor,
our goal is still achieved.
If Mr. Zheng wants to make another move,
he will have to think twice.
Besides,
if I can use someone else's money,
why should I spend mine?
Then why...
Are you really not worried
about what's going on
between Her Ladyship and Lou Qiyan?
I'm indeed worried.
Worried to death.
It's getting late.
I see you're tired.
Let's call it a day.
No, Young Master Qiyan.
Today,
I must get the blueprints.
Someone said,
I'm not musical at all.
It's a fundamental problem.
We can't rush this.
I-I understand.
But...
let me think about it.
Let me think about it some more.
Young Master Qiyan,
try to imitate this note.
What about this one?
I got it!
Young Master Qiyan,
how about this?
I have
a music score here.
Follow this score
and lower every note
by a half step.
Right, right, right.
Let's stop here for today.
Young Master Qiyan,
you just tuned up,
but why stop practicing?
The sun is about to set.
How about
I escort you back home for now?
I'll definitely deliver
the blueprints tomorrow.
Then tomorrow,
deal?
Deal.
Thank you, Young Master Qiyan.
I should be thanking you.
Although I'm average-looking,
you've peeked at me
over a dozen times on this journey.
Isn't that a bit too much?
I...
Young Master Qiyan,
you're overthinking it.
I'm just curious.
Curious about your attire.
You must be missing
a lot of sleep every day.
For things I consider worth doing,
I never count the cost.
You really go all out.
Young Master Qiyan,
since you are a noble of the Zheng family,
why go through all the trouble
to change your name to run Juyun Pavilion?
You shouldn't be short of money, right?
The Zheng surname is a glorious honor,
but also a heavy shackle.
When I was very young,
I thought
that one day,
I must become someone else.
Unrestrained
and free.
I see.
Have we arrived?
We've arrived.
Well,
why isn't there even a mounting block?
No need.
I... I can do it myself.
Thank you, Young Master.
Then,
see you tomorrow.
See you tomorrow.
I don't think you need
to see each other tomorrow.
Your Excellency.
Why did you come out?
You're so elegant, Your Excellency,
playing the zither at the gate
in the middle of the night.
Isn't this to prevent someone
from pretending to be lost
and not bringing my wife
back to the residence?
Um,
the residence gates are about to close.
Let's go back.
Yes.
Let us
go back to our residence.
Okay.
Um, Young Master Qiyan,
you must give me the blueprints tomorrow.
Remember!
You must!
He promised to give us the blueprints.
Shut up.
Absolutely ridiculous!
Yes.
His Excellency is young and inexperienced.
Please don't be angry, My Lord.
What?
Is His Excellency someone
you can criticize?
Yes.
I know my mistake.
It seems
this Fan Yun
is truly a disaster.
Has Shi returned?
Young Master Shi
is still studying
at the Directorate of Education.
One must marry a virtuous wife.
With His Excellency
as a warning example,
Shi's marriage
needs to be considered carefully.
Young Master Shi
is devoted to his studies
and stays away from women.
Please rest assured, Master.
Furthermore,
using the ancestor's dream as your excuse,
you've thrown His Excellency
into confusion.
Charge!
-Kill!
Grandfather.
Shi,
come here.
Grandfather,
are you feeling better these days?
I found a recipe
for soothing tea
and had the servants brew it.
Try it
and see if it helps ease your nightmares.
That's very thoughtful of you.
Did you just come back
from studying
at the Directorate of Education?
Yes.
I gave this recipe
to the servants before I left.
I brought it from the kitchen
as soon as I got back.
Sit.
My grandson,
you don't need to worry
too much about my health.
Look at you,
having to study
and care for me.
There is nothing wrong
with my health.
Don't worry too much.
While studying at the directorate
these days,
I heard some gossip.
Your illness these days
has greatly affected the Nine Cities.
What did they say?
You hold a high position
as the hub of the Nine Cities,
handling many case procedures.
It might not affect Qi Zheng,
the muddle-headed Governor,
too much.
But...
the people will be affected.
The people.
You asked me that day
if you were a good official.
I was thinking,
if the Nine Cities
didn't have a loyal official
like you who serves the people,
it would be in chaos.
The Governor
ignores state affairs all day.
They say he's been looking for some
ancestral temple these days.
Ancestral temple?
A temple built for dead nobles
after the founding of the Nine Cities.
It's long been abandoned.
I don't know what Qi Zheng is thinking.
He wants to repair it
to pay tribute
to those meritorious officials
of the past.
He also said something like
"never forget their merits
in protecting the city."
It's delicious.
Delicious.
What were you talking about so happily?
You two were reluctant
to part even at the gate.
Your Excellency,
why were you at the gate?
Don't interrupt.
He knew you were my wife,
yet he still touched you.
Isn't this a clear provocation to me?
I'm telling you,
from now on,
you must stay away from him.
This morning,
it was you
who let me out of the residence.
I...
He has promised me.
He will give us the blueprints tomorrow.
If you ask me,
you're so charming now.
Everyone is rushing to give you gifts.
I exhausted
all the skills I have learned in my life
to get it, okay?
You don't know.
Teaching Zheng Shi
to play a song
is harder than climbing to heaven.
Even now,
my back still aches.
All right.
I know you've worked hard.
Then tomorrow,
let Wei and Yan do the handover.
You don't need to go.
Why?
No reason.
I have my own considerations.
Don't worry about it.
Fine, fine.
Anyway,
you use Fan Yun when there is trouble,
and Wei and Yan when there's none.
After all,
you still trust the people
around you more.
Why?
Are you jealous?
It's not jealousy.
It's a lack of trust.
Hurry, hurry.
It seems that in this residence,
except for Second Brother,
no one has ever run around for me
so busily.
This feeling
is long lost.
Since
the one in front of me now
is the real you,
why don't you...
Why don't I what?
Why don't you
talk about
your selection exam reform plan?
Okay?
Do you really want to know?
Of course.
Since you are so nice,
I can tell you about it.
Can women
also take the exam?
To take...
take a step back,
even if women can take the exam,
you can't.
I can't?
Lord Lyu's 500 gold
is getting less and less worthwhile.
Wait.
What did you say about 500 gold?
Let me ask you a question.
What do you think of me?
Why is everyone so quiet?
With such quality,
it's only worth 500 gold?
Don't you think it's absurd?
Never mind.
Ultimately,
I am just a business deal.
Why didn't my wife come to greet me today?
Her Ladyship
was probably exhausted last night,
so she is still sleeping.
Still sleeping?
What time is it now?
Your Ladyship. Your Ladyship.
Qiuyue.
What are you doing here?
-We were ordered
-to wake you up, Your Ladyship.
Wake me up?
But...
what time is it now?
-Your Ladyship,
-it's dawn.
Dawn?
That's strange.
Why is my neck
so sore?
If you ask me,
lacking exercise
is the main reason why she feels
more tired after sleeping.
Wei Zhu.
Go and wake her up right now.
Today,
arrange horse riding, cuju,
and fifteen-pin bowling
for her.
Not a single one can be missed.
Qiuyue,
what are they
doing here?
Your Ladyship,
for some reason, His Excellency
has arranged a lot of
physical activities for you.
But the sun is so scorching today.
I am
afraid you might get heatstroke.
His Excellency arranged it for me?
It doesn't matter.
I love these
physical activities the most.
Come on,
help me change clothes.
-Great!
Zheng Yuan was previously
plagued by nightmares.
He kept dreaming of
the meritorious officials
who died in battle.
I remember when the late governor
built the city,
he specially built an ancestral temple
for the meritorious officials.
Therefore,
I plan to rebuild the temple
and start worshiping,
to commemorate
the nobles who made
great contributions to the Nine Cities.
Next one.
The Governor of the Nine Cities
is only worth 500 gold.
One month of purchase
equals half of my worth.
Rejected.
The budget must be reduced
by at least 30%.
Repairing the villa costs
twice as much as I'm worth.
Rejected.
Next one.
Next round.
Where is the next round?
Keep up, those falling behind!
Hurry!
I'm exhausted.
Rejected.
Next one.
Where is it?
Let's go.
[Taiji Palace]
What was wrong with His Excellency
at the morning meeting today?
He was kicking everyone out.
It's only natural for him
to lose his temper
when he hasn't had enough rest.
Your Excellency.
Why are you in such a rush?
What's the urgency?
You tell him.
Your Excellency,
Yan Jiang and I just
went to Juyun Pavilion,
but we were shut out.
What happened?
This Zheng Shi
is so bold.
He didn't even see us,
saying that
he'll only trade with Her Ladyship alone
and won't see anyone else.
How dare Zheng Shi!
Her Ladyship has arrived!
W-Where is His Excellency?
Your Excellency,
why did you
arrange so many activities for me today?
You all may leave.
Hurry up and go.
With Her Ladyship's attitude just now,
what if they really fight?
We have to go back.
Go back?
Why?
To break up the fight.
You always want to show off.
Go back if you want.
I won't be a third wheel.
No.
I'm telling you, we...
Wei Ying!