Crown Prince.
What brings you here today
to seek me out at the Music Bureau?
We said
upon your triumphant return,
We would welcome you with a feast.
We had Yudie
prepare a table of wine and dishes.
Crown Prince,
whatever you wish to say,
please speak plainly.
To be honest,
We quite admire you.
You have talent,
strategy,
and courage.
However, now,
though you returned victorious,
by toppling the Left Chancellor,
you implicated most of the court.
How many people's interests you've upset?
You've broken the rules.
Do you know how many people,
openly and secretly, want you dead?
Rules?
Are these rules to use any means necessary,
to treat lives as worthless,
and bring suffering to all?
If no one
is willing to break such rules,
then I shall be the first to do so.
Ning Chen,
your life is your own.
You must first stay alive
to have any chance to fulfill your ambitions.
Ideals are noble,
but reality is harsh.
We are the Crown Prince,
the future Xuandi.
We can protect you,
protect Yudie,
protect everyone you care about.
Only then can you
better pursue your ambitions and ideals.
Your Highness,
is this a threat?
Ning Chen,
swift steeds are plentiful,
but those who recognize them are rare.
We feel a kindred spirit in you,
and treasure your talent greatly.
As the heir to the throne,
We too wish to see
a realm of just and clear law,
peace and order across the land.
What does Your Highness want of me?
Now We are
caught in the struggle for the throne.
Our position as Crown Prince teeters.
We want you
to be Our trusted advisor.
With our strengths combined,
you'll help Us steady the court
and gain a firm footing in the army.
Let Father see
that We are the only one
fit to inherit the throne.
If Your Highness devotes yourself to the people,
His Majesty will see it sooner or later.
And Your Highness
will eventually attain what you desire.
Ning Chen,
do you know how many covet Our position
and want Us dead?
This is a dog-eat-dog world.
Only by becoming strong yourself
can you do what you wish.
The day We ascend the throne,
you'll stand below only one,
and above all others.
What rule could not be broken?
What woman could not be had?
The path,
you chose it yourself.
Your fate,
you chose it as well.
Her fate,
that too lies in your choice.
How to weigh it
rests entirely on a single thought of yours.
Your Highness's kindness,
I appreciate the thought.
Those of different paths
cannot plan together.
The hour grows late.
Crown Prince,
forgive me for not seeing you off.
Ning.
I'm the one who dragged you into this.
Don't talk nonsense.
Threats and bribes? Such old tricks.
You think I'd be afraid?
It's all right.
So, you've come after all.
A hundred years of life,
nothing more than
a fleeting moment.
Clouds shift and change,
the world is ever uncertain.
Your Majesty, you toil day and night.
Have a drink and rest a while.
Very well.
Still the same taste as before.
Terrible news!
The Left Chancellor is dead!
Who's there?
Seize him!
The... the Crown Prince!
Chen.
How is it?
He was poisoned to death.
The guards were off duty at the time.
Chen Lezhang arrived a step too late.
Our men are investigating now.
What about the Crown Prince?
He's been captured.
Once the investigation is complete,
I'll go to the palace to report at once.
Ning... Ning Chen!
You framed Us!
What do you mean?
You killed the Left Chancellor,
and then framed Us for it.
What a clever way to reap the rewards!
You think
just because Father favors you,
you can do whatever you please?
You want to use Huai'an to rise to power!
Let Us tell you,
that's nothing but wishful thinking!
Are you out of your mind?
I was at the Music Bureau all night.
I didn't even step out of the room.
You're the one who's crazy.
Only you knew Our whereabouts.
If not you, then who?
The moment We left the Music Bureau,
We received a secret letter,
telling Us to come to the Inspectorate
to discuss a deal with the Left Chancellor.
Little did We know,
We fell into your trap.
I really overestimated you before.
With such a brilliant father,
how did he end up with such a foolish son?
You...
Don't "you" me.
You were so eager to silence the Chancellor,
afraid he'd confess
that you're the mastermind of the gold mine case.
Yesterday, you tried to win me over at the Bureau
for this very reason, didn't you?
Don't think I don't know.
You planted a mole in the Inspectorate.
You could sneak in and kill the Chancellor,
but you couldn't escape unscathed.
Utterly foolish.
That's all nonsense!
You...
Guards!
We demand to see Father!
I'm innocent!
What audacity!
Your Majesty,
while investigating the gold mine case,
your servant found this Inspectorate badge.
Your servant lacked time to report it.
Your servant is still investigating the mole.
Outrageous!
Even the mighty Inspectorate has been infiltrated.
All evidence now points to the Crown Prince.
Your servant believes
this matter runs very deep.
The Left Chancellor alone
could not have stirred up such a storm.
Behind the Left Chancellor,
there must be someone of immense power.
Who?
If we suppose
the Crown Prince is the mastermind,
then his goal was to expand his power
and secure his position as heir.
Once the Chancellor was exposed,
he used the mole to silence him.
Failing to win your servant over,
he then framed your humble servant.
Such a theory
is not impossible.
Mother.
How could my brother do such a thing?
What should we do, Mother?
Huai'an.
Don't panic just yet.
Given the Crown Prince's character,
he would never do such a thing.
There must be
some kind of misunderstanding.
We'll go in shortly...
Issue a decree.
The Crown Prince murdered the Left Chancellor
and plotted treason.
He shall be executed in three days.
Mother!
Your Majesty!
His Majesty is coughing up blood!
He is coughing up blood! Your Majesty!
Your Majesty!
Father!
How is His Majesty's condition?
To answer Your Majesty,
His qi and blood violently surged,
which disrupted his heart's pulse,
causing his heart to stop.
His life hangs by a thread.
He could perish at any moment.
What did His Majesty consume today?
Everything was as usual, nothing unusual.
But...
The Imperial Medical Bureau must do everything possible.
If anything happens to His Majesty,
do not blame me for being merciless.
Your servant...
Your servant shall do his utmost.
Your Majesty.
Father.
By the Mandate of Heaven,
Xuandi hereby decrees:
The Crown Prince has manipulated the court,
formed factions for personal gain,
committed countless evil deeds,
and brought suffering to the people.
We are deeply grieved.
Yet royalty and commoners are equal under the law.
The Crown Prince shall be executed in three days.
So decreed.
Eunuch Quan,
please tell Father for me,
We did not do this.
We did not do this!
Eunuch Quan!
Your Highness,
please accept the decree.
If you knew it would come to this,
why did you do it?
Father,
you truly do not trust your son.