What are you doing here?
What? Why are you taking a picture?
Why aren't you coming to school?
What's the point of going
to a place like that?
You should at least graduate.
Is school over for today?
No.
Then what are you doing here?
What's the point of going
to a place like that?
You idiot.
Did you say your goodbyes to your dad?
Yeah.
Sorry I couldn't be there.
It's fine.
I wanted to send him off quietly,
so I ended it early.
To be honest, it still doesn't feel real.
I've been in a daze all day.
Well, then...
Come out of your house by 8 am tomorrow.
Why?
So that we can go to school.
If you don't, I'll drag you out myself.
What are you, my teacher?
How about we take a picture?
Here.
- Come on, smile.
- Jeez.
I'm taking it.
One, two, three!
Tae Jeong, you can't tell anyone
what I'm about to tell you.
You know the mayor, Seong Chang Geun?
I... I have evidence that could end
his political career, you know?
It's on my phone.
I tried to report it to the news,
but I got locked up here.
Instead of finding the key,
let's report it first.
- I'll tell Violent Crimes Unit.
- No, you can't.
Why not?
I think the cops are on their side too.
Then I'll tell Chul Jin.
- I'll tell him...
- No.
I can't trust anyone from Dongcheon police.
Tae Jeong, please, I'm begging you.
You're the only one I can trust, okay?
Did you find the key?
What are you doing? Hurry up and open it.
Before that, promise me one thing.
What?
When I open this cage,
run out of the house.
Why?
Because that man is still inside the house.
Promise me.
Okay, fine.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Thanks.
What are you doing?
What are you doing, I said?
So he's still upstairs?
Don't do it.
You want me to walk away after all this?
You promised.
That punk tried to smash my head in.
If I don't kill him now, I'll die.
How's it in there? Huh? Pretty crappy, right?
Stop it.
Stay out of it.
This has nothing to do with you.
The basement suits you perfectly,
probably because you do dirty work.
There's no need to go this far.
Seems this punk can't read the room.
You're not getting out of here alive, got it?
No, hang on.
It's no fun if you die so easily, right?
You son of a gun.
I went through crap
for days in here, you know?
- Look forward to it.
- Dong Hwa.
Chu Tae Jeong, come upstairs.
I didn't know Dong Hwa would go this far.
I'm sorry.
- What are you doing?
- Come on.
Oh, darn it.
What's all this money?
My phone.
Darn it, this son of a gun.
Come on.
Come on, you gotta be kidding me.
Where's the phone?
Dude, just say it.
You're really trying
to get yourself killed, huh?
There's something you need to know.
There's another killer on the way.
He's going to kill both of you.
Don't change the subject.
Let me go.
That's the only way you'll survive too.
Why should I believe you?
- There's no time.
- Then tell me where the phone is!
- I will if you let me go.
- Do I look stupid?
You'd kill me if I let you go.
No, but the other guy will!
Tell me where the phone is.
We can grab the phone
and leave with Tae Jeong.
That way, we both get to live,
right? Darn it!
Wait.
You... You don't want Chu Tae Jeong to die.
I especially like your ocean drawings.
Where is it?
Faroe Islands.
I'll buy that drawing from you.
Before its value goes up.
Where's the phone?
If you tell me, I'll spare Tae Jeong.
The phone...
It's in my art supply box.
Took you long enough.
Keep your word.
Please. Chu Tae Jeong has to come with us.
Ah, darn it!
It's not here, that lying crook.
Hey, did you touch anything here?
No.
He's really pissing me off to the end.
Why are you going that far?
Don't worry, I'm not going to kill him yet.
If I cut off his fingers one by one,
he'll tell me where it really is.
Are you really the Heo Dong Hwa I know? Huh?
Tae Jeong.
You need to get out of my house now.
The phone.
You said it has evidence
of the mayor's corruption.
Then you can just report it.
Why on earth are you trying to hurt someone?
Get out of here right now.
Tell me more about that evidence.
Because I need to know
why you're going this far.
If you hurt that guy,
I'll report it, even if it's you.
Tae Jeong.
I almost got killed by that guy.
I was locked up, living like an animal,
and barely made it out alive.
And you're going to report me?
Whose side are you on?
What was that?
Darn it.
Yes, it seems no one's here.
Looks like they already ran off.
I wanted to stab them myself
since it's been a while.
It's a shame.
Seems like that punk left with the cop.
Should I first take care of
Heo Dong Hwa in the basement?
Yes.
Then I'll finish him quickly
and go after the two who ran off.
Once we secure the phone,
I can kill them all, right?
Didn't think you'd die like this, huh?
Take a good look. This is the last thing
you'll see, you crackhead.
Dong Hwa.
Tae Jeong.
Ah, these cockroaches.
Why aren't you dead?
Tae Jeong.
What's going on?
You clueless idiot.
You don't need to know,
since you're going to die anyway.
Dong Hwa, don't shoot.
You can't kill people.
Yeah, listen to your friend.
You piece of crap!
Lower your body a bit more
and push your hips back.
Now try again.
No.
Heo Dong Hwa.
Where are you going?
I gotta kill that punk downstairs too.
Why?
Darn it!
Why? Why?
Are you... Are you stupid
or just pretending to be?
Drop the nice guy act now.
What about Tae Jeong?
Chu Tae Jeong is okay, right?
Wow, seriously, I'm about to tear up.
What are you two?
Did you play house while I was gone?
This is your last chance.
Tell me where the phone is.
You promised to let him go safely.
I'm so done with you.
Forget it. I'll just find it myself.
See you in hell.
The phone!
I have it.
Are you kidding me right now?
Give it to me.
Before that,
- I have something to ask you.
- You've been pushing your luck.
Stop it, or you'll regret it.
Tae Jeong.
My father's belongings.
This notebook.
Why is it in this house?
Why are you all so eager to kill my friend?
Stupid moron.
Can't believe you're friends
with Heo Dong Hwa.
Chu Dae Seok...
Your father wouldn't have died
if it weren't for Heo Dong Hwa.
You know my dad?
Go to the study.
There'll be something familiar.
What's that? I don't know anything about it.
This is my dad's signature.
Didn't you know?
I heard that if not for you,
my dad wouldn't have passed away.
- What does that mean?
- Tae Jeong, calm down.
How is your father's death my fault?
Who said that? Did that punk upstairs say so?
Tell me the truth.
I feel like an idiot for thinking of you
- as my friend.
- I said nothing happened.
Don't come any closer.
I said don't move!
Shoot me.
If you can.
- Tae Jeong.
- What is wrong with you?
Tell me.
What did you do to my father?
- Tae Jeong.
- Tell me now!
Because I know everything.
Isn't it obvious?
It's because your father died here.
Tae Jeong!