Oh ho.
White-Tee Lychee.
What did you just say?
Aww, all pale and tender.
Just like a lychee.
Beautiful once you peel it.
And the taste—
Mm.
even more juicy.
Don't talk crap.
Hey, get away from me.
You reek of liquor.
Cute is cute.
Just a little dim.
Hey.
I meant the lychee.
Keep talking trash—
and I'm filing a complaint.
Hey, threatening me again.
You win.
Hey.
That's my cup.
Give it back.
Hey.
Petty.
I just like your cup.
I just figured—
yours was too plain.
Lemme add some,
high-protein stuff.
Da da da da.
Hey, Senior Zhou.
How's it going?
Found yourself a fling in Lijiang yet?
Fling, my ass.
Professor's hounding me for the data like he wants me dead.
I'm flying out tomorrow and haven't been anywhere.
Data's not done either.
Damn, that's tragic.
Lijiang for nothing.
I'm not you.
I don't need a fling.
Don't be such a prude.
How old are you, still acting like a scared little quail?
Tell you what—send me your data,
I'll wrap it up for you.
Now download LIKE on your phone.
Doesn't matter, guy or girl,
just match with someone.
Drinks, dinner, photo trips—
go go go.
Uh.
It's fine, I'm okay on my own.
Ugh, stop dragging your feet.
Don't waste this Lijiang trip.
Get out and have a drink. Now.
It's just a drinking buddy.
Hey.
He's right.
Came all the way to Lijiang—
no nightlife, no drinks? What a waste.
Oh ho.
Little Lychee couldn't help himself, huh?
You—
White shirt, black shorts, white sneakers.
I mean you.
How is it you?
Were you following me?
Hey.
Don't go saying weird things.
You liked me first.
Maybe...
we're just fated.
Fate, my ass.
Creep.
Hey.
All right, creep—
can I buy you a drink?
Fine.
Ha, let's get this party going.
Excuse me.
This drink—lychee-flavored.
Suits you, perfectly.
Can you be serious for a second?
Okay. Since you came tonight,
I'll do whatever you say.
Go on, give it a taste,
Didi.
How is it,
Didi?
Why does it sound so weird whenever you call me anything?
Does it?
Yeah. Sounds dirty.
Aren't you called Didi?
Or could it be...
you're the one with the dirty mind.
You're the one with the dirty mind.
So,
how's the drink?
The boss made it himself, soaking lychees.
Mm.
It's really good.
I like it.
This drink—
it tastes a little sweet.
But the next thing you know, it'll go straight to your head.
For real?
This stuff can get you drunk?
Whoa.
Impressive. Didn't see that coming.
Excuse me.
Another round.
Guess I underestimated you.
Quit it. The drink really is good.
See, what'd I tell you?
You should've come out for a drink ages ago.
You looked so tightly wound every day,
like you had a personal grudge against Lijiang.
Your drinks. Enjoy.
Thanks.
I'm here on a research trip.
I can't go out before the work's done.
Ah, screw it.
I'm flying back tomorrow anyway.
Tonight, let's just drink up.
What?
You leave tomorrow?
Ah.
Okay.
Then we have to drink our fill tonight.
Let's play a game.
Loser takes a shot.
Sure. Drink till we drop.
Excuse me.
One shot.
You go first.
Four fives.
Whoa.
Aggressive.
What? You scared?
Pfft. Nothing scares me.
Damn, you're good.
Of course. Keep going.
Four fives.
Again?
That's right, again. What, getting nervous?
Four sixes.
Five fives.
Open.
You don't have a single five.
You really can drink, huh?
Of course I can.
Come on, keep going.
Since you can drink so much tonight,
don't blame me—
tonight, I'm gonna peel that lychee.
You talk way too much.
Annoying.
Hurry up.
Fine.
Okay, keep going.
Three sixes.
Why so cautious now?
No way. Hurry up.
Five sixes.
Open.
Looks like your brain
got fried from memorizing too many formulas.
You can't even shake the dice right.
I'm not like you arts kids,
with your bored asses and too much free time.
Where would I find time to shake dice?
Come on.
Bring it.