Let Wei Wei go, now!
Dali!
Stay out of this, kid.
My eyes!
Long Xiao!
I'll kill you!
I'm the Head of Security, after all.
Huilian!
What did you do to her?
Call an ambulance!
Hurry, come on!
Move aside.
Out of the way.
Move, move!
Doctor!
How is she, Doc?
Use the best medicine.
Money's no object.
Family, please calm down.
The patient's eye damage is irreversible.
And she's bleeding heavily.
She needs a transfusion immediately.
Doc, take mine.
Wei Wei and I are both Type A.
Hurry up, please!
That's great!
Nurse Zhang!
Right away.
Take them for cross-matching.
Prepare for transfusion.
Zhu Yihai.
I've been telling you for ages.
The doctor said to go home and rest.
Your wounds haven't healed yet.
Could you just go back?
Have some water first.
Dahai.
Drink some water.
The doctor told him to go home.
But he just won't listen.
Dahai.
Don't worry.
The blood types are bound to match.
Stop overthinking it.
Go home and rest first.
If you collapse too,
what will the rest of us do?
Let's go.
I'll leave Wei Wei in your hands.
Yeah, okay.
Wait here a second.
Let me clean up your wound.
Does your head still hurt?
I'm fine.
Give me your hand.
Lili.
Do you think I did the wrong thing?
If I hadn't been so stubborn...
Don't say that.
None of this is your fault.
I know you're trying to comfort me.
But all of this...
started because of me.
Don't blame yourself.
You shouldn't blame yourself.
How can I not blame myself?
Because of me,
Xiong Dali almost went to prison.
Ge Bing got kidnapped.
Wei Wei is still fighting for her life.
Dahai.
You need to pull yourself together now.
Become stronger.
Only then can you protect them.
Thank you.
You've helped me so much.
I haven't been much help.
But you've helped me a lot.
I know you've forgotten a lot of things.
But do you remember why you went to jail?
Wasn't it because Long Xiao set me up?
It had nothing to do with Long Xiao.
You finally found the man who violated me.
You did it to avenge me.
Thank you, Dahai.
Thank you for saving me.
Can you hold me?
You're the only one who won't look down on me.
Dahai.
Love me.
I love you.
We can't.
She's my mom.
Lili.
Let's just go to the hospital to see Wei Wei.
Nurse.
Doctor, about our blood...
What's the situation in there?
Is my blood a match?
As for the blood we need now...
I don't know when it'll arrive.
Dali, how is it?
Hai, our blood types don't match.
I've already contacted the city blood bank.
But I don't know when it'll get here.
Okay.
Thank you, Ge Bing.
No problem.
Doctor.
We're both Type A. Why doesn't it match?
I'm very sorry.
We need more than just matching blood types.
We need cross-matching.
So...
your blood isn't a complete match.
Lili.
Aren't you Type A too?
I don't know.
Let's go get you checked.
Fine.
Thanks.
Lili.
Thank you.
Nothing to thank me for.
Wei Wei isn't just your friend.
Family of the patient.
Citizen Qiao Lili's blood test results are in.
She has Type AB blood.
She doesn't meet the transfusion criteria.
So she's not my mom.
I can't help much here.
I'll head back to the pool hall to tidy up.
Lili.
Zhu Yihai.
Why are you standing here like an idiot?
What's wrong?
Isn't that Huilian's necklace?
Where'd you get it?
Long Xiao gave it to me.
The guest in the presidential suite,
no one is allowed to disturb him.
Is that clear?
Why is Long Xiao here?
I've searched the whole Guohong Factory.
Couldn't find her.
Where on earth could she have gone?
Huilian is in danger because of you.
If anything happens to her,
I'm not done with you.
I don't need you to tell me that.
I'm more worried than you are.
Let's go straight to Long Xiao.
Hai, let's take him down.
Jiao Jing, you've got the nerve to come here?
Zhu Yihai.
Look at you all, what a pathetic mess.
Spill it.
What did Long Xiao send you here for?
Long Xiao sent this for you.
What's in this?
I don't know anything.
I'm just a messenger.
What kind of crap is this? So hard to use.
Zhu Yihai.
We meet again.
Today,
I went out of my way
to bring you
an old friend of yours.
Come on.
Say hi to your Lover boy.
Bastard!
If you keep being stubborn,
and just like your little buddy,
I'll take a knife
and gouge your eyeballs out.
Let me tell you,
mess with me,
and it won't end well for you.
I'll take everyone around you,
one by one,
and torture them to death.
I really had no idea it was this.
Jiao Jing.
Listen to me.
You and I are in the same boat now.
Long Xiao doesn't just want me dead.
He wants you gone too. Get it?
That's impossible.
A scumbag like Long Xiao
will assume the worst about everyone.
Just because of this videotape,
believe it or not,
he expects me to kill you.
Dali, open the door for her.
You've got two choices now.
Either help me rescue Huilian
and take Long Xiao down,
or
you walk right out that door.
Go back to Long Xiao
and see if he doesn't eliminate you.
Do I even have a choice?
No, you don't.