[The Legend of Rosy Clouds]
[Episode 26]
Are you doing this on purpose,
or are you blind?
That's right.
I'm doing this on purpose.
I know.
The sweet dew tea,
lover's tea of Jing City.
It's usually
brewed by a woman for her beloved man.
I didn't expect you to be
so petty and calculating.
You tried to trick Fan Yun
with the sweet dew tea.
Good thing I found out in time. Otherwise,
Fan Yun would have definitely
fallen into your trap.
You have your principles,
I have my rules.
Besides, Fan Yun didn't feel that
I was setting her up today.
She made it very clear to me.
What did she say to you?
She said,
"This tea is very good."
Tea
is just a cup of drink.
It goes right through you,
and you forget it after drinking.
But what I'm giving her tonight
will definitely be unforgettable.
Enjoy your sweet dew tea.
I'm leaving.
[South Gate]
Fan Yun.
Qi Zheng.
Qi Zheng,
what's wrong with you today?
One minute you ran off in a panic,
the next you had Suyin call me here.
What's going on?
Well...
Just now, you two...
Did you...
Just now...
Did what?
It's getting late.
We have to hit the road tomorrow.
If you have something to say, just say it.
Never mind.
I just haven't
brought you to see
the night in Yong City yet.
Look.
Compared to the day we first arrived,
it's so quiet tonight.
Don't you think so?
Fan Yun.
Give me a moment.
Okay.
Where did
this come from?
I had Zhu Luan and the others
make it with the gunpowder
we found in the Spirit Immortal Cave.
Gunpowder?
It seems this Spirit Immortal Sect
is really dangerous.
But it's so beautiful.
Yeah.
To think they could make
something so pretty
from such a dangerous substance.
It's really beautiful.
Qi Zheng, look.
Although
the obstacles ahead are real,
so are
these gorgeous fireworks
before us.
Come with me.
Here.
You're letting me light it?
♪ All our fates were long inscribed ♪
♪ How to set free grief and joy? ♪
♪ Mortal life is but an ephemeral dream ♪
♪ No mortal soul may rule its life ♪
♪ If women are akin to blossoms ♪
♪ Can they be cherished tenderly? ♪
♪ For whom do they hide tears silently? ♪
♪ How could one bear to lay blame? ♪
♪ Time runs wild with reckless haste ♪
♪ Never mind that
fate dyes pureness crimson red ♪
♪ For whom does ♪
♪ This phoenix flower bloom? ♪
♪ Love fills my years,
and my heart remains true ♪
♪ Let all worldly longing fade away ♪
♪ Fall deep within a single dream ♪
♪ Wait till a breath of wind arrives ♪
♪ If women are akin to blossoms ♪
♪ Can they be cherished tenderly? ♪
♪ For whom do they hide tears silently? ♪
♪ How could one bear to lay blame? ♪
♪ Time runs wild with reckless haste ♪
♪ Never mind that
fate dyes pureness crimson red ♪
♪ For whom does ♪
♪ This phoenix flower bloom? ♪
♪ Love fills my years,
and my heart remains true ♪
♪ Let all worldly longing fade away ♪
♪ Fall deep within a single dream ♪
♪ Wait till a breath of wind arrives ♪
President.
A secret report from Wu.
[Secret report]
[Praying matters leaked. Return at once.]
Waiter.
Has Mr. Zheng in this room
checked out?
Yes.
He checked out last night.
It seems he had an emergency at home.
He left in a hurry.
An emergency at home?
Yes.
Could something have happened
to his family?
Fan Yun.
Why are you zoning out?
Let's go.
The carriage is ready.
Get in the carriage.
Get in.
Okay.
When we get back to Ling'an,
I'll treat you to steamed buns.
Okay.
Your Excellency!
Yun.
Zhu Luan.
Yun, thank you for coming to Yong City.
Thank you for coming to Hulin County,
and for coming to us.
My family made this.
I know you're leaving
Yong City today.
I don't have much to give you.
Have this snack for the road.
Thank you, Zhu Luan.
You must remember what I told you.
Keep helping the pharmacy save lives,
and don't forget
to study hard.
I already know
what I want to be in the future.
Let me guess...
Do you want to be
a physician?
Let me guess.
You want to be like Yun
and become a teacher.
Am I right?
No.
I want to be
an official just like Yun
and help others.
I will study hard.
One day, I will be like you two.
So until then,
you must wait for me.
Okay.
We will definitely
wait for you in Ling'an.
It's a promise.
[Peace and Harmony]
Farewell, Your Excellency.
Farewell, Lady Fan Yun.
Time to see the lords off!
The Governor of Nine Cities is renowned.
He cares for the people with benevolence.
Lady Fan Yun is insightful.
She risks her life to save the people.
They destroyed fake drugs, bringing peace.
They united against the epidemic
and assured the citizens.
Grab your tools and let's shout together.
Keep illness away and reduce disasters.
May our people be healthy and safe.
Lady Fan Yun.
The masses have witnessed
what you've done for them.
♪ Our hearts reach for the morning glow ♪
Farewell, Your Excellency.
♪ Our dreams fear no barren land below ♪
Farewell, my lords.
♪ What does it matter
if we fly against the wind? ♪
Farewell, Your Excellency.
Farewell, my lords.
♪ We vow to live up
to our youthful prime ♪
♪ To walk alongside ordinary folks alike ♪
♪ Sharing the same ray of light ♪
Let's go.
♪ Fear no strange land nor dim twilight ♪
Farewell, Your Excellency.
Farewell, my lords.
♪ All for this boundless world ♪
♪ To wear a robe of radiant glory ♪
♪ Face the light,
gaze ahead with brave eyes ♪
♪ Let all darkness and hurt step aside ♪
♪ It's unstoppable ♪
♪ Chase the light,
let our dreams unfold wide ♪
♪ With bold resolve, ignite plain faith ♪
♪ Light them up ♪
♪ Let the weathered past ♪
♪ Turn to countless beams
of light within my eye ♪
[Hulin County]
♪ Await the sight of you ♪
Keeping the people safe and happy
is the responsibility
of the Lord of Nine Cities.
Today is the first time I've ever felt
the satisfaction of being a governor.
So,
even if the road ahead is difficult,
it's still a worthwhile trip.
By the way, Your Excellency,
before Zheng Shi left,
did he say goodbye to you?
Why would he say goodbye to me?
Even if he did,
it would just be nonsense.
Nonsense?
What kind of nonsense?
Nothing.
Don't mention him.
But he just left quietly
without saying goodbye.
Did he really say nothing?
He told me
that you praised the sweet dew tea.
What did he say?
He told me
that you praised the sweet dew tea.
Your Excellency, speak louder.
Speak clearly.
What did he actually say?
Zheng Shi told me
that you praised the sweet dew tea.
The sweet dew...
Fan Yun, do you know
what sweet dew tea means
to the people of Jing City?
I...
Of course I know.
Then why did you...
I did say the sweet dew tea
was good that day.
But there was a second half to that.
He didn't tell you, did he?
Whatever.
I'm not that petty.
First half or second half, doesn't matter.
I didn't include him
in the fireworks show anyway.
Don't say it, I won't hear it.
Fine.
Then I won't.
The second half was...
The second half was,
although the sweet dew tea is good,
I don't like it.
I also told him
that he and I
are not on the same path.
Besides,
the people's worries
haven't been resolved yet.
How can I be in the mood for romance?
Don't worry, Your Excellency.
Before we fulfill
our pact to govern the city,
I definitely won't consider these things.
[Juyun Pavilion]
Boss.
Why did Grandfather
suddenly go to the temple?
And how did the abbot reply?
Tell me the details carefully.
No need.
I'll tell you myself.
Grandfather.
I just came back.
I haven't had time
to pay my respects to you at home.
Lou Qiyan.
Where did you come from,
and where are you heading?
I...
Just came back from Yong City.
Are you going to do business?
You...
Give me a straight answer.
Do you want to be
Lou Qiyan,
or
Zheng Shi?
Grandfather.
My subordinates told me
that the bandits
who seized the sweet wormwood
use moves similar to mine.
Shut up!
You have no proof,
so don't speak nonsense.
I have to say it.
Over the years,
you've been away from the family,
alone in Ling'an.
Though you hold a high position,
it's only superficial glory
with no real command of power.
I understand
the hardships involved.
What do you know at your young age?
Grandfather,
my engaging in business
is by no means belittling myself.
For the future of our Zheng family,
it's even more beneficial.
I really want to be Lou Qiyan.
Please understand, Grandfather.
[Ling'an City]
Finally home.
It is home,
but also a new battlefield.
Are you ready?
From the day I decided
to become a female official,
I was ready.
Gao Ran, Gao Ran!
Gao Ran!
Brother.
Did you see that?
Gao Ran just smiled at me.
At you?
I think he smiles at everyone
like that.
No.
In his eyes,
there was only me.
Gao Ran, you are so nice.
I knew you couldn't bear to let me fall.
Is that so?
Did you get to use the straw hat
I gave you on your trip to Yong City?
No.
Carrying a straw hat on a march
is too cumbersome.
You're lying.
Then what is this?
Miss Wei,
it's getting late.
You should go back and rest.
I won't go back.
I want to go back.
Tell me,
is this my straw hat?
I said it's not.
Tell me, is it my straw hat?
You're mistaken.
It's definitely my straw hat.
-Let me have a look.
-You're mistaken.
Let me have a look!
-I said you're mistaken.
-Feeling guilty?
You don't dare admit it, do you?
You actually missed me a lot, right?
Did you miss me a lot?
Your Excellency.
While you were in Yong City,
I followed your orders
and set up temporary clinics, pharmacies,
and relief stations in Ling'an City.
I also distributed all the sweet wormwood
in the warehouse
to the added stations.
Everything is running normally
in Ling'an City.
No plague patients have been found.
Thank you for your hard work, Lord Jiang.
I have been back
from Yong City for a few days.
Fan Yun, please elaborate on
the follow-up control of the plague.
The popularization of medicine
has been greatly enhanced.
The plague in Yong City
has also been fully controlled.
In just a few days,
all trade and farming in Yong City
can be restored.
Well done.
The plague in Yong City
was brought under control
in such a short time.
Lady Fan Yun
deserves much credit for this.
Just get to the point.
But,
I also want to ask
about the beacon tower incident.
Your Excellency,
do you remember it?
Lord Zheng!
Lord Zheng.
Do you really think His Excellency
is unaware of the robbery
of the sweet wormwood?
His Excellency
isn't holding it against you,
yet you are being insubordinate
and questioning him?
It's not a matter
of whether you should ask,
but whether you want to ask or not.
Go on, Lord Zheng.
Your Excellency,
I faintly remember
the promise you made to the officials
at the morning assembly,
that you'd handle it impartially
upon returning from Yong City.
Your Excellency.
The city has its laws.
I implore you, Your Excellency,
to keep your promise
and punish
Lady Fan Yun.
Please keep your promise, Your Excellency.
Are you trying to rebel?
The plague in Yong City has just passed.
Merits are unrewarded,
and faults are unpunished.
There are more imminent matters
that haven't been dealt with,
and you are already teaming up against
the hero who stabilized Yong City and me?
A gentleman's word is his bond.
Your Excellency,
If you are unwilling to do so,
then how will you
face your officials in the future?
Lord Zheng...
You are going too far.
Your Excellency.
I lit the beacon tower without permission.
It was indeed
an overstepping of authority.
Please punish me.
Fan Yun lit the beacon tower
to save the people of Yong City.
If she is punished now,
who would dare to sacrifice
for the people in the future?
Your Excellency.
Fan Yun overstepped her authority today,
yet she claims
it was for the people's will.
What about tomorrow?
What if
she uses the people's will
as an excuse again
and oversteps in other ways?
If every matter is like this,
and everyone is like this,
then,
Your Excellency,
what will become of our rules?
I'm afraid you may
never face the officials again.
Your Excellency, please reconsider
and punish Lady Fan Yun.
Guards!
Take Fan Yun
to the Interrogation Bureau
to await trial.
Lady Fan Yun, please.
I accept my punishment.
We take our leave.
Your Excellency!
Your Excellency, Your Excellency!