When has this old minister ever associated with you two?
Where does this talk of collusion come from?
Is that truly the case?
Do you actually have solid evidence?
Your guilty servant did indeed
exchange letters with Steward Ding of the Left Chancellor's residence.
But I was merely following orders.
But I never imagined this.
How could your guilty servant dare
embezzle the gold mine?
It was Ma Kaicheng who said
the orders came from the Left Chancellor.
Your guilty servant was only
carrying out duties as usual.
Your Majesty.
Whatever Ma Kaicheng says becomes truth?
Do you not use your head at all?
To pin baseless accusations
upon this old man's head,
what are your true intentions?
Your Majesty.
Steward Ding of the Left Chancellor's
residence has committed treason.
This old minister failed
to discipline him strictly.
I am guilty of negligence.
This old minister wishes to resign
and return home.
I beg Your Majesty to grant permission.
Your Majesty.
The Left Chancellor handles
countless affairs daily.
Some oversights are unavoidable.
Please show mercy, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
The Left Chancellor
has rendered great service.
If, for this minor charge of negligence,
he is dismissed from office,
this minister deems it improper.
This minister concurs.
The Left Chancellor cannot be
touched right now.
I have served as Chancellor for decades.
You think a bastard like you
can bring me down?
An ant trying to shake a great tree.
Utterly laughable.
Cunning old fox.
Ning Chen.
What about Ma Kaicheng?
Where is he now?
You want solid evidence, is that it?
I will give it to you.
You have grown up.
But you still act too rashly.
No matter.
Father shall make this final move for you.
Ning Ziming, have you gone mad?
Yes, I have gone mad.
Ever since the death of Ning Chen's mother,
I have been mad.
I have waited for this day
for far too long.
Alone, I could not bring you down.
But now my son has come of age.
I have nothing left to fear.
Your Majesty,
this minister can bear witness.
Every word they have spoken is true.
The Left Chancellor's crimes
are too many to record.
This minister has proof.
I beg Your Majesty's permission
to present it.
Granted.
Summon him.
Reporting to Your Majesty,
this man is Ma Kaicheng.
Your Majesty,
this guilty commoner,
on the Left Chancellor's order,
joined with Zhang Yuancang
to mine gold ore.
And as for Ning Chen's mother,
she discovered the gold mine
and reported it to the court.
To cover up the truth,
the Left Chancellor
ordered this guilty man to poison her.
Silence!
You beast!
This old minister bears you no grudge.
Why do you slander me?
No grudge, you say?
Lord Left Chancellor,
if Minister Ning had not
spirited me and my family away in time,
I fear
my entire family
would have long since fallen by your hand.
Is there hard evidence?
The evidence is here.
In the fourth year of Rende,
Bingzhou suffered great drought,
with no harvest at all.
The Left Chancellor seized the lands
and embezzled seventy percent
of the relief funds,
leaving Bingzhou strewn with the starved.
The people were driven to revolt,
and he then sent troops to suppress them,
killing and wounding civilians
by the tens of thousands.
In the sixth year of Rende,
the Left Chancellor secretly received
ten beauties from Tuoluo,
along with five hundred thousand
taels of gold,
and in return delivered
our border defense maps,
causing our frontier army to suffer defeat,
with losses among our soldiers
exceeding twenty thousand.
In the ninth year of Rende,
the Left Chancellor secretly
administered poison,
causing the sudden death of
the Second Prince of Great Xuan.
Afterwards, he sent men
to remove the tea set
the Second Prince had used,
to conceal the truth.
Ning Ziming,
why did you not report this in time?
Your guilty servant
acknowledges his crime.
Ning Ziming,
do you know what you are doing?
Of all the matters you just laid out,
which one did you not have a hand in?
Do you intend to drag the entire
Ning family down with you?
Have you no thought for
your wife and children?
Your Majesty,
the evidence presented here
suffices to prove the Left Chancellor's
manifold crimes.
This minister, too, is implicated.
I beg for nothing else,
only that Your Majesty,
in light of this minister's service
in bringing forth this evidence,
spare my second and third sons.
They knew nothing of any of this.
They are truly innocent.
Chang Suoxiang.
All these years We placed such trust in you,
elevating you step by step
to head all officials.
And yet you...
Is this how you repay Us?
Your Majesty.
Guards!
Throw this cur
into the imperial dungeon at once.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Geng Jing.
Your servant is here.
Seize and search
the Chancellor's residence.
All persons involved are to be
cast into the death cells.
Should anyone dare obstruct or resist,
strike off their heads,
one by one, in Our name.
Your servant obeys the decree.
Your Majesty.
In the case of Zhang Yuancang, Ning Chen
committed the crime of
deceiving the sovereign.
We nearly forgot about you.
Minister Yu,
in the case of the Left Chancellor,
you covered for him at every turn.
Yet in the matter of Ning Chen,
you pressed harder at every step.
You...
Do you truly take Us for a fool?
Take him away.
Subject him to severe interrogation,
and await Our judgment.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty is wise and just.
Court is dismissed.
Long live Your Majesty, ten thousand years!
Why have you come?
At a time like this,
should you not be cutting ties with me?
I came seeking an answer.
If not for your military merits,
I think for the rest of my life,
I would never have brought out
this evidence.
Now,
you are capable of protecting yourself.
One last move would checkmate
the Left Chancellor.
How could Father stand idle
and watch you fail?
I know
I have wronged your mother,
and wronged you as well.
Back then, when your mother and I
secretly pledged ourselves to each other,
I promised
that once I passed the imperial exams,
I would return and take her as my wife.
Who would have thought,
when the results were posted,
Chang Ruyue had set her sights on me.
She used your mother to threaten me.
But back then I was merely a scholar,
and she was the Left Chancellor's
daughter.
I truly had no choice.
But I do not understand.
If you feared the Left Chancellor so,
why did you bring me back
to the Ning residence?
And when did you
begin gathering evidence
of the Left Chancellor's crimes?
After what happened to your mother,
I guessed that Chang Ruyue
would surely seek to root out all traces.
With you staying at the Ning residence,
they would be constrained by appearances.
Even if they mistreated you,
at least your life would be preserved.
From that moment, I swore
I would bring down the Left Chancellor.
Because as long as he lived,
you would always be in danger.
And what of Ma Kaicheng?
When I learned you had captured
Zhang Yuancang alive,
I knew the time had come.
As your son,
I have no right to condemn your actions.
But neither do I have the standing
to forgive you on behalf of my mother.
Rest assured,
when I reach the underworld,
I shall apologize to your mother myself.
But I would like
to ask one thing of you.
Ning Xing and Ning Mao,
though they do not share your mother,
in the end,
you are all my children.
They are dull-witted,
and pose no threat to you.
Even if you drive them out of the capital,
just spare their lives.
What about Ning Gan?
Was he not your most prized son?
He is not my blood at all.
When Chang Ruyue first set
her eyes on me,
she had already conceived secretly
with a retainer of the chancellor's house.
That is why she was in such haste.
I shall try my best.
I am asking much of you.
Chen'er,
behind the Left Chancellor,
there is an even greater power.
What do you mean?
I cannot be certain myself.
I have always felt
that the Left Chancellor alone
could hardly stir up such great turmoil.
They have hidden themselves well.
I have never managed to find proof.
Now that you have toppled
the Left Chancellor,
those behind him will surely make a move.
So you,
you must take great care.
Understood.
You have grown up.
Father can depart this world
with peace of mind.
Father,
please accept your son's bow.
Take care.