Ge Zhendong sent me here.
The evidence.
It's by the bed at the guesthouse.
Where's Dali?
He's preparing a surprise for you.
Where are we going?
Jing'an Guesthouse.
Got it.
Hai, Weiwei!
I'm back.
Weiwei?
Hai?
Where is everyone?
You're not dressed warm enough.
Such a thoughtful kid.
Why isn't the bus here yet?
What's the rush?
He's a grown man, no one's gonna kidnap him.
Can't you say something nice?
But why does my right eye keep twitching?
Nothing bad's gonna happen, right?
What's going on?
We're screwed.
Dali was here.
Let's go!
Move!
Where's the money?
That was the money for the orders!
Director Ge.
Are you okay?
Why wouldn't I be?
It's gone.
It's all gone.
I just got an anonymous tip.
Saying that Zhu Yihai
stole money from the factory.
How could it be him?
Why would he steal the factory's money?
Section Chief Dao.
You need to go find him right now.
Those are public funds.
I can't cover this up!
On it.
Hurry up!
Wait
What's this?
Zhu Yihai
Someone reported
that Zhu Yihai stole money from our factory
Where is he?
Oh, damn it
Qiangzi
After him!
Don't let that punk get away
Go!
Xiong Dali
Slow down
Stop!
Slow down a bit
Stop right there
Stop!
Stop right now!
Xiong Dali
Little brat
Stop running
Stop chasing me!
I'm done chasing
Stop chasing
You stop running too
Alright
Buddy
Look at you, barely wearing anything
You must be exhausted
What are you looking at?
After him!
Slow down, slow down, Dali
Xie Fan
Can't you knock?
Someone sent me to find you
Who?
Secretary Yu
So you're here to threaten me?
Threaten?
Brother
If you had just given me
Aimin Street, which belongs to me,
there wouldn't be all this trouble
Am I right?
Brother Xie Fan,
My fault
Of course
Don't get mad
Come, sit down
Come on, come on
Sit, trust me
I was wondering what the big deal was
Making such a fuss
Come
Come sit
I know
you're upset
I know I wronged you recently
But think about it
If I hadn't done that
Zhu Yihai
why would he help me deal with Ge Zhendong?
Brother Xie Fan,
How many years have we known each other?
How could I ever sacrifice you?
Besides
the contract for Aimin Street
I already have it in my hands
Zhu Yihai
He's of no use anymore
Once I get rid of him
I'll let you
take back everything that was yours
Dali, stop blocking the door
Open the door
Dali
Section Chief Dao
He locked the door
You guys up there
Pry this door open!
Put some muscle into it!
Get this door open!
Dali
Damn it
Why are they still on my tail?
I fell right into that woman's trap
Zhu Yihai, Zhu Yihai
Please don't let it be you
Those are public funds
Stealing public funds
That'll get you locked up
Dali, don't do anything stupid
I'm freezing to death
I-I-I'm not waiting for you
Hey, sir
Give me a ride
What am I supposed to do if you leave?
I'm leaving, I'm freezing!
What about me?
Can I just sit on the crossbar then?
Running keeps you warm
My gloves
Little brat
Let's see where you can run now
Stay back
Don't come any closer!
Dali
Don't you move
I'm not moving
Mom
I've let you down, Mom
Dali
Throw that bag down to me
Here
Huilian
Hurry, go after him!
Get back here
Chase him? Are you crazy?
If anyone sees this
we'll be accomplices
You think I don't know?
Over there
Half an hour and still no sign of him
Don't worry, we'll find him
Zhu Yihai, oh Zhu Yihai
You really are a handful
Director Ge
Dahai
Missed me, didn't you?
What's this?
I just found it
You found it?
What is this?
Money
Is this my money?
Keep better track of your stuff next time
It really is my money
Thanks, man.
We're buddies.
Take it.
So you're Zhu Yihai.
Who are you?
You've pulled plenty of stunts while I was away.
No.
It's all a misunderstanding.
You believe everything they say?
Listen to me on this.
What do you mean?
Director Ge.
I'd call this returning what's found.
Right.
Shouldn't you give me a commendation banner?
I will.
Absolutely.
Scoundrel.
Little girl, you keep calling me
a scoundrel. What do you mean?
You listen to me.
I'm not going to put up with your nonsense.
Your good days
are over today.
Don't think signing the Transfer Agreement
lets you do whatever you want.
I'm officially notifying you now.
If your demolition compensation
doesn't arrive within a week,
the Transfer Agreement
will be immediately void.
Who the hell are you?
Your nemesis.