=The Embroidered Truth=
Wan, no!
=Episode 20=
From the day the pheasant's
head was severed,
I never planned to live.
Murder!
Wu Lian killed me!
She's dead.
So what if she's dead?
Master Wu,
the jailer knows you were there.
We can't hide this.
What's wrong, My Lady?
I dreamed about Wan's death.
It's not true.
Dreams are fake.
No.
I need to see her.
It's dark and slippery.
We'll go with you.
My Lady.
This dead body is so heavy.
Ms. Meng looked thin and weak,
but she weighs a ton.
You're making jokes at a time like this?
When the Princess Consort asks,
how do we explain?
We know nothing, of course.
We can't offend Wu Lian.
He's the Princess Consort's favorite.
Wan.
Why didn't you wait for me to save you?
(Wan,)
(I won't let your death be in vain.)
The Prince returns tomorrow.
And you cause a death
in my manor tonight?
Please see the truth, Your Highness.
Meng Wan said
she knew some secret
about Lady Cheng'en,
so I...
Silence!
She is my cousin,
a Lady of Cheng'en Manor,
soon to be a concubine to the Prince.
What secrets could she have?
I was rash.
I only wanted you
to shine at the Flower Festival.
I didn't think about the Prince
returning tomorrow.
Please forgive me.
Your Highness,
I've been loyal to you for years.
You know my heart.
What good does that do?
There are many servants in this manor.
If word gets out that you
went to the prison...
Wu Lian,
I indulge you
because you know what I want,
and your skill is exceptional.
It pleases me.
But since Ruoheng arrived,
you've repeatedly lost your sense.
I know I was wrong.
If I keep protecting you,
people will talk.
I deserve to be punished.
But I'm like the grass and trees,
cats and dogs of this manor.
Your Highness,
I rise and fall
with you.
Enough.
I know about
Meng Wan.
You had nothing to do with it.
When the Prince returns,
cause no more trouble.
Otherwise, this isn't about
honor or disgrace.
It's about your life.
Well?
Did you find Wan?
Yes.
Tossed at the mass grave.
I hear the Prince returns today.
Lady Cheng'en, are you there?
The Prince's troops have reached
the outskirts.
They'll arrive later today.
The Princess Consort
requests your presence.
The Prince's arrival is a major event.
My Lady caught a chill last night.
When she feels better,
she'll go to the Princess Consort.
But...
Tell Wenyue
I'll come after I wash and dress.
I'm her cousin.
I won't embarrass her before the Prince.
What do we do now?
Let's go.
I'm coming too.
Xiaotao,
you stay here.
See Wan off for me.
I didn't know her for long,
but I will never forget
her righteousness.
Let's go.
Master.
Is the Princess Consort summoning me?
No.
It's
Lady Cheng'en.
Follow her.
Yes.
Ms. Meng Wan is gone.
Please accept my condolences.
She was clutching this.
Wu Lian always keeps this on him.
I don't know if Ms. Meng
told you this.
She said if she's gone,
I should take you to see someone.
Who?
They're at the Yehu Gang.
You'll see when we get there.
♪Night fades before the dawn♪
♪Old vows still guide my hand♪
♪The past no longer binds♪
♪My heart still shines through dust♪
♪Silent blooms, unchanged heart♪
♪Bare hands weave through the frost♪
♪Shadows linger, rain returns♪
♪Honor crowns my weary soul♪
♪For your faith that never broke♪
♪I shattered all the love I knew♪
♪No regrets, no debts unpaid♪
♪At dusk I walk away alone♪
♪If this tale becomes a storm♪
♪Old shadows fade from sight♪
♪One thought turns into ash♪
♪No future left to write♪
♪If I never fall♪
♪How could this waiting end♪
♪If I bear no scars♪
♪How could I challenge fate♪
♪I knew there was no way back♪
♪Yet I left this hope behind♪
♪For your faith that never broke♪
♪I shattered all the love I knew♪
♪No regrets, no debts unpaid♪
♪At dusk I walk away alone♪
♪If this tale becomes a storm♪
♪Old shadows fade from sight♪
♪One thought turns into ash♪
♪No future left to write♪
♪The lamp is out, you're gone♪
♪Heaven and earth fall silent♪
♪If we meet again someday♪
♪This longing sleeps beneath the snow♪