Dali
Toss that bag down to me
Here
Missed me, huh?
Is that my money?
Your good days
are over.
Who the hell are you?
Your nemesis
Director Ge
Got your slush fund back, didn't you?
I came to congratulate you in person
Boss Long
You're behind all this
Director Ge
You're the bigger man
It's all because of this Aimin Street mess
I had no other choice
Well played, Boss Long
All for Aimin Street,
you really stop at nothing
Fine
It's just Aimin Street, right?
It's done
Done?
That fast?
What's this?
The business license for the foot spa
And the legal representative is your pal
Zhu Yihai
What kind of nonsense is this?
What are you playing at?
Boss Long
Do you really want to know
how Zhu Yihai used six million
to pull off what you couldn't?
Because he gave me a foot massage
A foot massage?
Boss Long
I heard your Giant Wood Group
has quite a few tricks up its sleeve.
But those little tricks of yours
in front of our two thousand workers
are an absolute joke.
Ge Zhendong
You think you've won?
Don't you forget,
Zhu Yihai,
he's still my brother.
Mr. Long
It's getting late
Please show yourself out
Sweetie
Zhu Yihai alone is enough of a headache
Spit it out
What's going on?
Wei Wei
You ask him
What the hell is going on?
Dali
Yihai wants to know what's going on
Wei Wei, you tell him
Here's the thing
Believe it or not,
it's up to you.
I know all about Ge Zhendong's business
The evidence is hidden under the bed
Shame on me
for believing this woman's lies.
You tell him yourself
Yihai
Dali told me to
I'm not deaf
You believe this crap?
Did she really set the old man up?
Zhu Yihai
Get out here!
What is it?
Hurry up, Zhu Yihai
Dao Balian
What's the deal now?
Take a photo
A hundred years!
Who's cursing me?
Plenty of people curse you
Come on, let's take a photo
Take a picture, come on
Come on, snap a photo
Vertical, take a vertical one
You're all ready, aren't you?
Hurry up
So embarrassing
Yeah, vertical, take a vertical one
Do you want him to stay mad at you?
Take a picture of us, come on
You can't see shit anyway, come on
Come on
Everyone, listen up
So, um
To help our factory workers
get reemployed after being laid off
Dahai Billiards Hall decided to offer
a free Foot Therapy and Massage Course.
Yihai guarantees everyone,
as long as you pass the course,
Guaranteed job placement.
Sign up fast
Limited spots
Everyone come on over
Are you serious?
It's real! It's real!
Listen to Zhu Yihai teach massage.
Hurry, hurry
It's real! It's real!
Let's go, let's go
Come on, come on
Hurry up, hurry up
Come on
Head inside
Come on, let's take another group shot
Take one, come on
One more shot
Hurry up
Come on
So you're saying
Zhu Yihai was playing tricks,
and exposing you to the factory was fake?
It wasn't fake.
It really wasn't fake.
You said you were being bullied,
that's why I came back from abroad.
And now you're covering for him?
No, sweetie.
I really think Zhu Yihai
isn't a bad guy.
Who was it?
Who said I'm an old maid nobody'd marry?
Was it him?
Yes, it was him.
Definitely him.
Fine.
Just for that,
Zhu Yihai,
You're dead!
Everyone, don't push!
There's no rush, okay?
Line up, one at a time.
All right?
Come on, line up.
Line up.
Never expected this.
So many people signing up.
Of course.
Who doesn't want a job?
I don't think they're here for a job.
Then what?
I think they're here for you.
So you're Zhu Yihai.
What is it, auntie? Need something?
Don't call me auntie. Call me sis.
I'm here to learn massage from you.
Come on.
Try out your sis's skills.
Come on, don't push.
Wanna learn the trade?
Line up.
Okay, sure, sis.
Okay, next.
He'll hold any hand he sees.
He wags his tail at anyone.
Dali.
Go get Sun Qian.
What are you looking at?
So what if I am?
Nothing.
Boss Long.
What brings my good friend Yihai
back here again?
Come on, have a seat.
Okay.
Hello, Secretary Liu.
I've got a VIP in my office.
Take good care of him.
No need, Boss Long.
Yihai,
are you here again
about the transfer fee?
That's right.
This Ge Zhendong,
I don't know where he dug up
a wild card,
saying if the money's not paid in a week,
the contract is void.
That won't do.
My friend Yihai here went through hell
to sign that contract.
Exactly.
Tell you what, man,
I'll go raise the money right now.
But there's one more thing
I'm still a little confused about.
Hold on a second.
Come over here first, come.
What is it?
Hey, man.
Something's broken.
Let me fix it for you.
It's fine, it's fine.
Don't mind him, he'll be done in a sec.
It's nothing, just ignore him.
Let's get back to our business.
I just wanted to ask,
this...
what does fifty-two mean?
Oh, the fifty-two?
Yeah.
I always go with fifty-two.
Why does it have to be number fifty-two?
You don't get it, do you, man?
For folks in our line of work,
it's fate.
It can't be changed.
"Can't be changed," huh?
Well, let's just see
whether it can be changed or not.