=The Embroidered Truth=
(Jingyuan Manor)
Your Highness,
a report just came.
The Prince has reached the city gate.
(Jingyuan Manor)
=Episode 21=
So much for your watch.
Remember, speak only
when I tell you to.
Got it?
This is...
Xiaojiu.
How did she end up like this?
This is Xiaoyi?
After Wu Lian assaulted her,
this is what she became.
So the embroiderer at the mass
grave wasn't Xiaoyi?
No.
Ms. Meng Wan switched the bodies.
She saved Xiaoyi
and entrusted her to me.
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
Ms. Meng didn't want to
distract you.
She said...
What did she say?
If one day she's gone,
take good care of Xiaoyi.
Don't be afraid.
Xiaoyi,
look at me.
Do you recognize me?
I'm Rulan.
Xiaoyi,
let's take revenge together.
Will you do it?
But you must learn to speak.
Get better, you hear me?
Yes.
Wu Xin.
Master Wu.
Wu Xin went out and hasn't returned yet.
Why are you panicking?
It...
It's the Prince's return.
The steward told everyone
to gather at the inner gate.
I...
The Prince is back?
Yes.
(First Among Princes. Mengqiu Pavilion)
Lady Cheng'en's birth chart is blessed
and processed through all proper rites.
It just needs to match the Prince's.
Please take a look.
(Marriage Contract)
(Xiao Zhengyang, Prince Jingyuan)
Are you pleased?
Where is Lady Cheng'en?
So it's clear
you returned for her.
Didn't I already come to see you?
Your beauty is as great as ever.
Do you really mean that?
The contract has been delivered.
Why haven't you invited her yet?
Your Highness,
your wish is to keep the Prince
in the manor
by your side.
Besides, Lady Cheng'en is only...
There's no need to rush.
She's already in the manor.
You are virtuous
and wise.
Are you displeased?
If you're happy,
then I'm happy.
I was just thinking,
when I was young,
you always stayed by my side.
We've been married for over
a decade.
Why do you still say that?
Go and invite Lady Cheng'en again.
Yes.
The Prince has returned today.
Please be very careful.
Don't worry. We've long been prepared.
But Xiaoyi...
I'll take care of her.
You can count on me.
If anyone gives you trouble tonight,
don't push yourself too hard.
Don't worry. I know my limits.
I'll wait by the west side gate
for your word.
Thank you, my friends.
Tonight at the third watch,
same place.
Let's go.
Explain for your Lady.
My Lady kept changing her clothes today,
unhappy with each.
Then she said she wanted
to find garments that would please
the Prince at the market.
I've never seen Ruoheng so particular.
Now that the Prince is back...
Who are you talking about, Wenyue?
You. I see you every day.
Now that the Prince is back,
after so many invitations,
and you still don't show up.
I came here for you, Wenyue.
Don't make fun of me.
It's not that I don't want
to see the Prince.
It's just...
So you can be shy too.
Ruoheng,
greet the Prince.
Greetings, Your Highness.
Raise your head.
Why stare so eagerly?
There will be plenty of time later.
It's our first meeting.
I hope you'll forgive my awkwardness.
Could Ms. Meng Wan have
made a mistake?
Wu Lian is so sinister.
Found it?
That scumbag!
A true beast.
Ten beheadings wouldn't be enough.
I couldn't quite believe it myself.
Someone who can create
such fine embroidery...
I never thought he'd stoop so low.
But...
This beast
risks everything to keep this on him.
He'll take it out and savor it
again and again.
But he ended up weaving his
own trap.
So many embroiderers,
but only Rulan dared
to report to the authorities.
I hate my own cowardice back then.
Should we proceed carefully?
Exactly.
This involves too much,
too many reputations,
and even lives.
We need to be careful.
Xiaoyi,
don't be afraid.
It's just a handkerchief.
Don't be afraid.
No one will hurt you anymore.
You're good now.
We need to tell Rulan right away
that we found the list.
I'm here.
Don't be afraid.
♪Night fades before the dawn♪
♪Old vows still guide my hand♪
♪The past no longer binds♪
♪My heart still shines through dust♪
♪Silent blooms, unchanged heart♪
♪Bare hands weave through the frost♪
♪Shadows linger, rain returns♪
♪Honor crowns my weary soul♪
♪For your faith that never broke♪
♪I shattered all the love I knew♪
♪No regrets, no debts unpaid♪
♪At dusk I walk away alone♪
♪If this tale becomes a storm♪
♪Old shadows fade from sight♪
♪One thought turns into ash♪
♪No future left to write♪
♪If I never fall♪
♪How could this waiting end♪
♪If I bear no scars♪
♪How could I challenge fate♪
♪I knew there was no way back♪
♪Yet I left this hope behind♪
♪For your faith that never broke♪
♪I shattered all the love I knew♪
♪No regrets, no debts unpaid♪
♪At dusk I walk away alone♪
♪If this tale becomes a storm♪
♪Old shadows fade from sight♪
♪One thought turns into ash♪
♪No future left to write♪
♪The lamp is out, you're gone♪
♪Heaven and earth fall silent♪
♪If we meet again someday♪
♪This longing sleeps beneath the snow♪