This series is a work of fiction inspired by
questions that arise within the human heart.
It is not intended to offend or pass judgment
on any beliefs, religions, or individuals.
(Previous Chapter)
Sorry.
Wow! That's our Christmas play couple
right there.
Joseph and the Virgin Mary.
Cherry asked me
to be in the Christmas play.
What does it have to do with me?
I want you to be okay with it.
Tanrak, why are you running?
I'm not running.
You're running from yourself.
I'm not God's favorite son.
Tanrak, I like you.
I'm not God's favorite son either.
What about you, Tanrak?
Have you ever had doubts?
Actually,
I do have doubts sometimes.
My heart isn't that steady.
There are still…
things that…
make me…
waver.
LOVE IS PATIENT
1 CORINTHIANS 13:4–7
Jesus said to His disciples,
“This is My commandment:
Love one another as I have loved you.
No one has greater love than this:
to lay down one's life for one's friends.”
Dear brothers and sisters,
I'd like to thank you all
for your donations to Magdalene Church
and for helping us
through Christmas so smoothly.
Uh, everyone.
Keep anything we can still use.
Throw out the broken ones.
Yes.
Come on, keep it up.
We can use them again next year.
Tanrak.
Could you get some people
to pack up the lucky-dip booth
outside for me?
It's already done, Father.
I assigned the younger boys to handle it.
Excellent.
Let's save this for later.
You can just take it.
I'll print a new one.
Can I keep this?
Sure.
I'll print another one.
Wait.
You don't want my picture at all?
I do. I'll take all of them.
Huh. I thought, like,
the rector banned photos
with girls or something.
No idea.
But I've seen people have them.
They do.
Tons of them, actually.
Just don't get caught.
Right?
This is Phai.
And this is Barth. Tanrak's friend.
Yeah. He's my boyfriend.
So…
can church scholarship boys
seriously date someone?
I don't think so.
Maybe not.
I don't know.
Really?
Is that so?
Me?
I don't have anyone.
That's sad.
Having to keep it to yourself
if you like someone.
But as a church scholarship boy,
you probably shouldn't even like anyone
to begin with, right?
You liked me.
What?
Didn't you like me first?
Can we go eat now?
- Let's go.
- See you.
See you.
Babe, you're heavy.
How could you say that?
Ow!
Let's go.
Okay.
What are you doing?
It's a secret.
A secret?
So we're keeping secrets now?
Oh!
Hey, Tan! You'll tear it.
It's the only one I have.
Where did you get it?
I asked Cherry for it.
It's a cute picture.
Can I have it?
No.
This is rare, you know.
Barth.
What?
Let's trade.
I saw you take that from the trash pile.
Well…
It felt like a waste to throw it away.
And I thought…
it…
kind of looks like you.
Let me see.
Here. See?
Doesn't it now?
No, it doesn't.
What kind of trade is that?
Come on.
Fine. I'm losing out here, you know?
Losing out how?
You got the photo for free.
You got that for free too.
Let me see the photo.
Your face looks so funny.
Hey, Barth.
Father needs help moving tables.
Hurry.
Yeah, I'll be there.
I should go help them.
Or they will say I'm slacking off again.
Take good care of it.
"Ticket to Heaven"
(Episode 4)
What's this?
You're tired already?
Father, Ryu kept complaining
the whole time.
It's true.
No, Father.
I worked the hardest.
I could carry chairs for ten more rounds.
I saw you slacking off right after Mass.
What? That's not true, Prince.
You didn't help with anything.
It's all right.
God will remember
who didn't abandon their work
even when they were tired.
Since I can see
you're all genuinely tired today,
I'll give you extra movie time tonight.
Yay!
If anyone wants to watch anything,
go tell Master Phak
so he can rent it for you.
Sit with me during the movie.
All right,
go take care of your own things.
Go on.
Ryu, move.
What?
Move. Come on.
What the hell?
Oh, Tanrak.
Your group has to help
with traffic duty tomorrow.
I need you to go a bit earlier.
Okay.
Keep an eye on your friends too.
Want to trade blankets?
Sure.
♪ Every second that I have you near ♪
♪ Feels like I've found
the land of my dreams ♪
♪ My world turns so beautiful
I wanna stop the time ♪
♪ And hold this moment
for as long as I can ♪
♪ If heaven is real,
how beautiful could it be ♪
♪ I'm not so sure if I need to see ♪
♪ As long as you're the one here
standing next to me ♪
♪ If heaven doesn't have you there,
that's not where I wanna be ♪
♪ Every second ♪
♪ From that moment ♪
♪ I have you near ♪
♪ Feels like I've found
the land of my dreams ♪
♪ My world turns so beautiful
I wanna stop the time ♪
♪ And hold this moment
for as long as I can ♪
♪ If heaven is real ♪
♪ If it's not real ♪
♪ How beautiful could it be ♪
♪ I'm not so sure if I need to see ♪
♪ As long as you're the one here
standing next to me ♪
♪ If heaven doesn't have you there,
that's not where I wanna be ♪
Tanrak.
Tanrak, rotten head boy!
Hand out the report books.
- Yes?
- Come get the report books.
Oh.
For the scholarship students,
Father has added his comments already.
Make sure you read them
and sign to acknowledge them.
So, how did everyone do this term?
Full marks? Full marks?
Full zero.
Hey! Joe's here!
Wow!
Joe's here?
Hey, what's with you all?
You're acting like
your seniors are celebrities.
I'm better-looking than him.
Boo!
Okay, then.
For guidance period,
go find an activity you want to join.
Okay. That's all for today.
Class.
Thank you.
Promotion readiness, 4.5.
Tan.
What did Father write for you?
What?
What score did you get?
Give me a sec. I have to go.
See you. Thanks.
SENIORS GUIDING JUNIORS
You can sign up first.
Hey, who's this? I don't know him.
Barth. He's new.
- Hello.
- Oh. Hi. Have a seat.
Barth, do you want to go to university?
Come on.
Hi, Joe.
Oh, hi.
Is that you, Tanrak?
You've gotten so much taller.
Yeah.
You haven't changed at all.
I have.
Seminary is a whole different world
from here.
Really?
Is it… tough?
Not tough.
It's just really quiet.
So quiet I sometimes wonder
what I'm doing there.
Well, if you want to see lots of girls,
or get a girlfriend,
this is the way to go, right?
Am I right?
Weren't you at seminary at first, Bank?
Another one changing their mind.
Like I said, it's hard.
Everyone wants to have someone.
But we have our own kind of love.
You get it, right?
What kind of love?
The kind that doesn't belong
to just one person.
Of course it gets boring.
Having to make up with your girlfriend?
Such a pain.
Even a bad boy worries.
“What should I do?” Right?
It's so much drama.
You'll understand once it happens to you.
When you get to university, I'll tell you.
I'll show you around.
I know you all have a lot
on your minds right now.
It's not strange.
I was the same at your age.
But if your heart is pulling you
somewhere else,
don't force it.
But don't run away from it either.
Listen carefully to your heart.
When your parents come
pick you up tomorrow,
don't forget to take the gifts home.
If your family already has a calendar,
you don't have to take one.
Yes, Father.
Get it done tonight.
Barth.
This one smells nice.
But it smells familiar.
I can't put my finger on it.
Smell it.
- Right?
- It smells…
like Father's room, doesn't it?
Yeah. That's it.
Da-da-da-da-da-da!
Hurry up. We're going home tomorrow.
Look at you, Ryu.
You're so pumped to go home.
My mom said she'd take me to Dan Neramit.
I'll enjoy it for you guys.
But you were singing
the Siam Amazing Park theme song?
Just going home.
Why is he so happy?
I mean,
break is kind of nice.
When school is empty, it feels like
the whole place belongs to you.
But this year, you're staying with me.
Tan.
Have you signed up with Joe yet?
Joe said I don't have to decide yet.
Right. And…
what did Father write for you?
Oh.
I left my report book at school.
I thought you'd take this more seriously.
Safe travels, everyone. God bless.
Father, I'll get going now.
Hello.
- Hello, Father.
We brought some fruit from our orchard.
Dragon fruit and oranges.
Thank you.
They may not look perfect,
but they're really good.
You didn't have to bring anything.
I feel bad.
You've already come such a long way.
It's just a small gift.
It's nothing compared to how much
you've helped our family
by giving Kongdech a scholarship here
for a bright future.
I'm not the only one
who gave him this chance.
Kongdech works very hard.
He always helps out
at the scholarship dorm.
That's good, son.
Make sure you give back
to the church and the priests.
See? You always say I don't do anything.
Here is a scented candle.
- Thank you, Father.
- Thank you.
And this is a calendar.
It has all the important dates.
People in the village can use it too.
- Thank you.
Oh, Tanrak.
What a shame.
I thought you'd come home with us.
Oh.
Oh, right. I brought you a gift too.
Thank you.
Have a safe trip.
We'll get going now, Father.
- Goodbye, Father.
Let's go, son.
Hey. See you later.
Hey.
That shirt is so cool.
Did you just get it?
Kongdech's mom bought it for me.
Who gets a gift and looks this grumpy?
His mom is nice.
But him?
He sulks over everything.
About the other day?
I mean,
I just forgot my report book.
He didn't have to get this upset.
You're closest to Kongdech, right?
Well,
probably the closest.
Just watch.
He'll come back,
act like nothing happened,
like he always does.
Isn't that a good thing?
Yeah, exactly.
So I don't get why he's mad.
How about this?
When he comes back,
wear the shirt to make up with him.
I'm not making up with him.
What? Then what?
Want me to punch him?
Hm?
Here.
This is Kongdech.
Punch him.
Come on.
Here. Punch him.
Here.
Barth.
What?
See? Now you're smiling.
Punch him. Here.
Why would you do this?
Ask him if it hurts.
Does it hurt?
What are you doing?
See? You can smile.
You two, tomorrow
help me organize the library.
Yes, sir.
Joe…
is seriously cool, isn't he?
Mm.
When he was here,
he was good at school, music, sports.
Everything.
His nickname
was “the hope of his class.”
Girls waited outside the church
for him every week.
Wow.
If I were him,
I'd feel so much pressure.
But his heart was so steady.
Yeah.
I saw his eyes
during the guidance session.
He didn't seem unsure at all.
Where should I put these books?
All the way at the back.
But wipe the dust off first.
Got it.
You two,
go help him.
What about you, Tanrak?
Have you ever had doubts?
Well,
I've always pictured myself that way.
A priest's robe.
The altar.
And me standing there preaching.
That's the picture I see most often.
Then your heart
is just as steady as Joe's.
I wouldn't say that.
My heart
isn't that steady.
There are still…
things that…
make me…
waver.
Yeah.
So,
how do you deal with it?
I'm trying.
It's not easy.
Yeah.
I know.
It's hard.
But…
when I really think about it,
if one day I have to choose,
I'd choose God over anything else.
What about you?
Have you ever had doubts?
Well,
I have doubts all the time.
You know how long this path is.
Who knows what the future holds?
Even you still has doubts?
I don't know.
Let's just say, in my class,
there are only two of us left.
My family
has high hopes for me too.
It's…
kind of a lot of pressure.
Being expected to be something.
For me, it's more fear.
I'm not afraid of God
but of the people around me.
Afraid I'll disappoint them, hurt them.
Afraid they'll think I gave up,
that I didn't have what it takes.
But hey, if that day ever comes,
that's their problem, isn't it?
Then,
what are you living for now?
What am I living for?
Because I know
I'm not here to be anyone's hope.
What is it?
Done helping Phak?
Yeah.
The church with no one around
is pretty quiet, huh?
Yeah.
So quiet you can hear everything.
So…
have you heard the voice
inside your head yet?
Were you waiting for me?
No.
Hey, wait.
When you said you were wavering…
is that all it is?
Well…
how could I feel
anything more than that, Barth?
Can't you just let it happen?
Let it go even further?
Barth.
You know what?
When I'm near you,
I can't control myself.
But are you happy?
Yeah.
Barth.
Why are you calling me so loud?
I'm right here.
I'm not going anywhere.
Thank you.
The school at night
really is as quiet as you said.
I like it.
Have you been here since you were a kid?
Hm?
I've…
been here since Grade 7.
I know the sound of the bell
better than my own front door.
Wow. Didn't you get lonely?
I can't even imagine it.
Lonely?
I…
Didn't understand it as a kid.
Now that you're older, do you?
I think I understand it more now.
I don't feel lonely like I used to.
What's wrong?
There's something I want to tell you, but…
Okay.
I'll tell you.
When I was little,
I cried every day
when I first moved into the dorm.
But I was embarrassed.
So I had to cry alone
in the bathroom.
Seriously?
So you were a crybaby.
Hey, wait.
I have a question.
What if you had a choice,
would you choose this path?
No.
You wouldn't?
I'm not telling.
Not telling?
Tanrak.
Tell me.
No.
- Come on. Tell me.
- No.
Whisper it. No one will know.
I'm not telling.
Hey, Tan.
Come on.
Want to go?
Hey. Wait.
What are you doing?
Keeping watch over you.
I'll stay here until I get an answer.
You really don't give up, do you?
I'm not usually this persistent, you know.
Just answer me.
I really want to know.
I'm not answering
because I really don't have an answer.
You know,
I've slept in this bed since Grade 7
I've never changed beds.
Tanrak.
Can I sleep next to you?
What's with you today?
You really want to be close to me.
I'm lonely.
Without you here,
I'd be dying of loneliness.
Hey.
Thank you.
HAPPY NEW YEAR
Okay, everyone.
Father Arnon isn't here today.
So… you get a free day.
You spilled the water.
Master.
Can I go watch a movie, then?
Sure. I'll rent one for you.
Wait, I totally forgot.
The church needs our help today.
They're setting up
for the New Year's party.
Any volunteers?
I'll go.
Okay, we've got one: Barth.
Anyone else? Come on.
Bird?
Sak?
Wow. You were so loud
asking to watch a movie.
Come on, have some heart.
You're letting him go alone?
No one else?
Master, I'll go too.
Okay.
Barth and Tanrak,
after you finish eating, come with me.
You can wash this part first.
We only used these a few days ago.
Where did all this dust come from?
Can you wash this part for me?
Man, it's hot out here.
Barth, aim at the chairs.
You're spraying me instead.
I'm cleansing your sins.
You like that, don't you?
Cleansing sins?
Then let me cleanse yours.
Someone like you needs half a day.
Tanrak.
Tanrak, don't.
God doesn't listen to me anyway.
Wait.
Is this Songkran?
Turn off the water.
So hardworking.
Even working on your day off.
Aren't you going anywhere?
How can we?
It's New Year's
and we're stuck working at church.
Poor you.
Where do you want to go?
Anywhere without piles of chairs.
Here.
Wait.
Fill up the gas too.
Hey.
Want my Walkman too?
That'd be nice.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Barth, hurry.
Babe.
Hm?
You just made your friends
break the rules, you know.
You're in on it too.
Should I really lend them my bike?
Let it slide.
A troublemaker
and a scholarship kid making trouble
aren't the same thing, you know.
Then…
if you were a Magdalene scholarship kid,
would you still date me?
Of course.
I would.
Barth.
They're having fun, aren't they?
Want to join them?
Do you have Modern Dog?
One cassette left.
How much is it?
90.
Here you go.
Keep the change.
MODERN DOG
♪ Before the sky could turn so bright ♪
♪ Before the sunlight warmed the day ♪
♪ Before the flowers bloomed in sight ♪
♪ Before sweet dreams
could find their way ♪
♪ My heart had had no one ♪
♪ Until your love entered ♪
♪ Filling my eyes bright with colors ♪
♪ My side had had no one ♪
♪ Until your love showed me grace ♪
♪ To give me strength I never had ♪
♪ Before the stars filled up the sky ♪
♪ Before this life could feel its worth ♪
♪ Before my faith all ran dry ♪
♪ Before my fire was all burnt ♪
♪ My heart had had no one ♪
♪ Until your love entered ♪
♪ Filling my eyes bright with colors ♪
Woo!
♪ My side had had no one ♪
♪ Until your love showed me grace ♪
♪ To give me strength I never had ♪
♪ To carry on in this cruel world ♪
You really like this song, huh?
♪ My heart, my soul ♪
♪ Are yours to own ♪
♪ All my life, I promise you ♪
♪ I'll keep on fighting for you ♪
Here.
It's okay. You eat it.
Once I found out why he wrote this song,
I liked it even more.
It's cool, right?
Putting “you'd left” in the blanks.
You'd left
before the sky could turn so bright.
before the sunlight warmed the day.
You'd left
before the flowers bloomed in sight.
before sweet dreams could find their way.
I wonder
how my parents are doing now.
Don't do that.
Your parents are at peace now.
I just wonder,
if my parents were still here,
would I still be who I am today?
I can't even imagine it.
Hey,
your life is good, isn't it?
Don't get stuck in your head.
You don't have to comfort me.
I mean it.
You're way stronger than you think.
Your parents would be really proud of you.
Look at me.
I punched a friend and got expelled.
Hey.
I got it.
I want to be
a gold-medal hero like Somrak.
"I'm not bragging."
I don't like serious stuff.
And I'm not good at school.
But you're good with computers.
Should I open a computer shop?
I'd play games all day.
I don't want to go back yet.
Who said I was going back?
Be careful.
Hey, look at this.
I carved my name here once.
I even spelled my own name wrong
back then.
Did you come here a lot?
I used to come with my mom.
My dad too.
I used to think my family was normal.
I didn't even know it wasn't.
I saw my mom…
with bruises almost every week.
I saw her crying every day.
As a kid, I thought,
maybe it was just grown-up stuff.
But when I grew up, I knew it wasn't.
My home was messed up.
I once asked my mom,
“Why stay together
if you don't love each other anymore?”
She didn't answer.
Neither did my dad.
So back then, I thought
maybe they…
stayed because of me.
But that wasn't it at all.
My mom stayed because she feared sin.
She feared breaking her vows.
Feared God wouldn't forgive her
if she left her husband.
So they just kept going
even though they didn't love
each other anymore.
If that was all, I could take it.
But it wasn't just that.
In the name of the Father,
and of the Son,
and of the Holy Spirit.
Lord,
please…
We weren't done praying.
Barth, apologize to your father.
I'm sorry.
In the name of the Father,
and of the Son,
and of the Holy Spirit.
Lord,
please bless us and the food
we are about to eat,
so we may live to serve You and others.
In the name of the Father,
and of the Son, and of the Holy Spirit.
Amen.
One day, my dad found out I was gay.
What the hell is this?
What kind of book is this?
This filthy book is yours?
What are you doing?
It can be cured.
God will help you.
I'm not sick, Dad.
Not sick?
How could you do this?
Is this how I raised you?
Don't!
You make me ashamed before God.
Please don't! Don't do this!
Stay out of it!
Mom, help me!
You can't be like this.
Is this who you've become?
You make me ashamed before God.
How could you do this?
Mom! Mom!
Mom, stop!
Mom, that's enough.
Barth.
I never thought it would get that bad.
My dad died.
My mom went to prison.
So I ended up as a scholarship kid.
Are you still going to ask me
why I don't believe in God?
I used to pray, you know.
I prayed every day.
I prayed for my dad
to stop hurting my mom.
For my mom to stop crying.
For things to get better.
For my home to be normal again.
But it wasn't normal.
I guess God was busy.
Or maybe He thought
my family deserved all of it.
I just don't know
how I'm supposed to believe in God.
Then…
I'll pray to God for your mom.
Thanks.
Hey.
Come on, we're on a trip.
Why the gloomy face?
I want you to remember
our first waterfall trip
as something happier than this.
Don't tell me this is your first time
at a waterfall.
Can you believe it?
I live in this province,
but this is my first time at a waterfall.
Too bad I didn't bring a camera.
You don't need it.
Next time you want to come, tell me.
I'll bring you here.
I'm holding you to that.
If I'm bluffing, may my house blow up.
♪ With you right here ♪
♪ With us right here ♪
♪ There's nowhere else I'd rather be ♪
♪ Every second ♪
♪ That I have you near ♪
♪ Feels like I've found
the land of my dreams ♪
♪ My world turns so beautiful
I wanna stop the time ♪
♪ And hold this moment
for as long as I can ♪
♪ If heaven is real,
how beautiful could it be ♪
♪ I'm not so sure if I need to see ♪
♪ As long as you're the one here
standing next to me ♪
♪ If heaven doesn't have you there,
that's not where I wanna be ♪
♪ Every second ♪
♪ From that moment ♪
♪ I have you near ♪
♪ Feels like I've found
the land of my dreams ♪
♪ My world turns so beautiful
I wanna stop the time ♪
♪ And hold this moment
for as long as I can ♪
♪ If heaven is real ♪
♪ If it's not real ♪
♪ How beautiful could it be ♪
♪ I'm not so sure if I need to see ♪
♪ As long as you're the one here
standing next to me ♪
♪ If heaven doesn't have you there,
that's not where I wanna be ♪
BATH TANRAK
(Next Episode) You're going on to
the seminary with Kongdech, right?
Right?
I'm asking you seriously, Tanrak.
That calling from God you hear…
is it still as loud as it used to be?
I love you so much.
I love you so much, Barth.
I'm tired.
Tired of having to hide this relationship.
I don't care how God says this is wrong.
You can't not care.
God always gives us chances, Tanrak.
But His path…
is not easy at all.