This series is crafted for the purpose of entertainment.
All characters, behaviours, settings, and events depicted in this drama are entirely fictitious.
They are not designed to allude to any particular entity, occupation, or group of people.
Viewer discretion is advised.
[North Star Entertainment]
[IQIYI]
[Present]
♫Never met anyone who could make me understand this word♫
♫But when I met you, my heart started beating fast♫
♫You’re the only one in my heart who could make me feel this way♫
♫This long-awaitied moment is now over♫
♫From now on, my heart and soul will be yours for the rest of my life♫
♫Always have each other, never let go♫
♫Trust in me ‘cause I’ll be by your side♫
♫Hold my hand, Baby♫
[Desires in the Wind]
[Previously]
Lom told me to get you. We have to go now.
They’re there!
Look out, Miss Vayo!
I’m well aware of the situation.
But I’m afraid those traitors will never let me return to Madelin alive.
I didn’t expect you’d be here yourself, Mr. Henri.
As I thought, it’s you, Chief.
The car is coming to take you to the safehouse in Khao Yai.
How do you feel about me?
I love you.
I truly appreciate it. But I’m afraid I can’t return the feelings.
We’ll go back to Thailand to get rid of the princess.
What grudges are you holding against the royal family?
It’s none of your concern. Just do your best as a fake princess.
You will visit Thailand again, Your Highness?
Yes.
But according to your schedule,
you are to return to Madelin next week after finishing all engagements , Your Highness.
I’d like to visit Thailand for a private leisure before going back to Madelin.
Are you going to obstruct me in place of Father, Miss Isabelle?
Not at all, Your Highness.
I wouldn’t dare defy your will, Princess Blew.
Then, please have it taken care of, Miss Isabelle.
I will attend to it immediately, Your Highness.
Having power in your hand is amazing, isn’t it?
Wouldn’t it be too risky?
But going back to Madelin this time,
you’ll be taking over King Arthur’s throne as the appointed crown princess.
And I can’t risk having this plan go wrong again.
The princess won’t always be that lucky.
If Henri fails again, I’ll take this matter into my own hands.
[Normandy, France]
I can’t believe something this serious is happening to my sister.
No wonder why she seemed a bit off when I was on the phone with her last time.
That was probably the imposter, Your Highness.
Is my sister safe right now?
Yes, Your Highness. Despite having to keep running away, she’s still safe.
I’ll let Father know immediately.
Please tell my sister to look after herself.
I’ll find a way to help her as soon as I can.
Yes, Your Highness.
Have some tea first.
Thank you.
Are you mad at me, Miss Blew?
Mad about what?
Well, about…
What are you doing here?
I’m afraid you’d feel uncomfortable.
Are you mad at me?
It’s me who should’ve asked that–are you mad at me?
Why would I? I’m the one who asked you first.
I’m not mad at you.
I’m actually afraid.
Afraid of what?
I’m afraid you might hate me–that I’d make you feel uncomfortable since you now know how I feel about you.
But I’m still here with you.
Do I look uncomfortable to you?
Isn’t it funny? I’m the one who’s still the same but it’s you who has changed.
How could I not? I just confessed to you.
I know.
But can you please stay the same to me?
So that one day I might finally understand the meaning of love.
Sure.
If I do anything wrong or inappropriate to you, you can always say it, Miss Blew.
If it makes me feel awkward, I’ll stop you and warn you myself.
Miss Fah should have met Karel by now.
Once Karel sees the letter, I’m sure he’ll tell Father and they’ll find a way to help us as soon as they can.
And you’ll have to go back to Madelin after that.
Madelin is my home.
I’ll miss you a lot.
Don’t you have airplanes in Thailand?
I beg your pardon?
Madelin might be far but you can always fly there to visit me.
You’re more than welcome there.
And I believe Father and Karel would also be pleased to welcome you,
since you’re the one who has saved my life.
What if I move to Madelin for good? Is there any job position for me there?
We have plenty of royal guards there. I’d rather not bother you.
What about other positions?
Well, I’m not sure.
Unlike Father, I still don’t have enough power to appoint any position to you at my own will.
There’s no need to bother King Arthur for the position that I want.
Let’s…go inside.
Why did you help me when I fell off the boat that day?
I don’t know.
And I’m actually not good at swimming.
That was very dangerous.
I was shocked.
Please don’t do that again, no matter how shocked you are.
But your life is important too.
My life means nothing compared to yours.
If that time comes when I have to choose, even my life–I can sacrifice it for you.
Don’t let me hear you say that again.
Whether dead or alive, it’s my own life.
I don’t want you to sacrifice your life for me anymore.
I just want to protect you as someone who loves you.
If you love me, then don’t die.
Never say you’ll sacrifice your life for me again.
I’m sorry.
I’ll never say that again
We will get through this together alive.
I’ll wait for that day when you finally love me too.
[Princess Blew]: If it makes me feel awkward, I’ll stop you and warn you myself.
If you think I’d be mad, why did you do it?
Because you didn’t stop me.
I’m sorry.
I’ll be more careful next time and won't do anything inappropriate again.
So, you won’t do that again?
No, I won’t. I will not kiss you like that again.
What if I allow you to, will you do it?
Huh?
I still have no idea what love is.
But I didn’t mind when you did that to me.
What’s wrong?
You just kissed me.
[Thap Lan National Park]
Right here. This is the main entrance they’d pick.
Send in our sniper team.
Well take them down there.
Have you spread the news about the princess through Santi?
All done, sir.
Excuse me, sir. Why don’t you just send some of our men to help Chief Santi catch Henri?
Because judging from the latest information I got from Santi about the fake princess returning to Thailand,
I’m very positive all those attempts to assassinate Princess Blew are not Henri’s doing alone.
I need to get all of them.
Understood, sir.
You have three days.
I’ll be in touch.
General Wathit wants to talk to you.
Yes, sir.
Everything is going according to the plan.
Have you called for backups?
They’ll be here by tomorrow morning.
Now that we know where they are, why don’t we just go finish them tomorrow?
Not yet.
It might be a trap.
They might have spread fake news to Santi.
Go study all entrance and exit routes of that safehouse.
When everything is ready, we’ll do it.
Yes, sir.
Dad said Henri already found out where we are.
Do we have to run again?
No.
Then what?
Dad will lure Henri here and arrest them all.
I’m sorry for using you as bait, Miss Blew.
But I don’t want both of us to run anymore.
I’m willing to do it.
But catching Henri won’t be easy.
But if we can get him, Grace and the fake princess will lose all their bargaining power.
Please don’t worry. I’ll make sure everyone is safe.
Let’s get some sleep–get ourselves ready for tomorrow.
Can I sleep while listening to your heartbeat?
Yes?
Once everything is over, I mightn’t be able to sleep next to you like this again.
I want to memorise the sound of your heartbeat.
[The Kingdom of Madelin]
Can we contact the authorities in Thailand to handle this matter and arrest the traitors, Father?
No. If they find out that I know about this, you might be in danger.
Besides, we still don’t know if Sir Antoine is also involved.
Let me make sure about it first.
Will you consider my plan, Father
I’m listening.
[Taipei]
You and Karel will come to Thailand, Father?
Yes, so that we can have some family time before you’ll come back to take the throne as the Queen.
But it’s boiling hot there, Father.
That’s all right. I want to spend time with you and escort you home myself.
Then, see you in Thailand, Father.
Deal.
What should we do now?
What should we do?
I’m out of here!
Calm down.
I’m out! I won’t do it!
Stop!
I won’t do it!
We have to get rid of Blew.
How?
Henri, listen to me. King Arthur is going to Thailand.
You need to get rid of Blew before he gets there.
Don’t worry, I already know where Princess Blew is.
This necklace represents my heart.
Don’t you know the maximum sentence for offending the royal family is a death penalty?
I’d rather be executed than letting you fall sick from getting cold.
Are you cold?
Nope.
In Madelin, it snows every year.
I want to see the snow in Madelin.
The first snow will probably come in a while.
When everything is over, let’s go see the snow in Madelin together.
Want some cocoa? I made it for you.
Cocoa? It’s my favourite drink.
Then, you have to take me back to Madelin with you so you’ll have someone to–
[Signal flare]
That’s from the resort. We need to get out of here.
Let’s go.
I told my team to wait on the other side of a creek.
Please put this on.
What about you?
I have mine ready.
[Signal flare]
Please hurry up.
[Gunfight]
Drop your weapon!
[Continuous shootout]
[Police]: Let’s go! Quick!
[Police]: Quick! Move it!
We got all of them except Henri, sir.
[Gunshot]
Contact that team.
B team, over! B team, over!
[Gunshots]
You two keep watch here.
Yes, sir.
The rest follow me.
[Gunshot]
[Gunfight]
You’re not wearing a vest!
You lied to me!
I’m okay.
But you’re bleeding a lot.
Let’s hurry. Let’s go.
Miss Vayo.
Let’s go.
[Hitman]: Drop the gun and hand her over.
It’s you who should drop the gun.
Drop the gun!
Drop it!
[Gunshot]
Miss Vayo!
Miss Vayo…
[Henri]: Get up!
Henri!
Just  give up, Princess.
I don’t want to hurt you.
Put the gun down.
Do it, Miss Blew! Let’s end this!
I said put the gun down!
Okay, okay! I’ll do it.
Miss Vayo!
Miss Vayo! Miss Vayo!
Why don’t you just kill me?
Grace will take care of you herself.
Grace…
Don’t!
Come here!
No! Don’t! No!
Don’t! Don’t!
[Gunshot]
Stop!
Move!
Miss Vayo! Miss Vayo!
[Continuous shootout]
Lom!
If you stop now, I promise I’ll convince Father to forgive you.
I’ve come too far to turn back, Your Highness.
You’ve changed so much.
If Sir Antione knows, he’d be so disappointed in you.
He has never been proud of me anyway.
That’s not true. Mr. Antoine is very proud of you.
He told Father that once I ascend the throne, he would resign and pass on his position to you.
No, that’s not true. Don’t lie to me, Princess.
I’m telling the truth.
It doesn’t matter.
You’ll never get to take the throne anyway.
Tell our men to keep watch.
Never let Princess Blew out of your sight.
Yes, sir.
Lom!
Lom! Lom, are you okay?
How are you feeling?
Where’s Miss Blew?
So? Is Miss Blew safe?
Miss Blew.…They got her.
What?
But now, you’re–
[Lom]: I have to help her!
[Fai]: Geez, calm down.
Your wound might tear open.
Have you looked at yourself?
You’d only be a burden to them if you go now.
I’m sure Miss Blew will be all right.
[Phone ringing]
You got the princess?
Good, we’re in Thailand now–on our way to the meeting point. See you there.
This is getting way too much for us to handle.
I don’t want to do it anymore.
If you quit now, the one who’ll die as a traitor is you.
Grace!
We have to hurry, before King Arthur and Prince Karel will be here tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Yes, and Sir Antoine, your father too.
This isn’t what we’ve planned, Grace.
If my father and King Arthur find out, wouldn’t we all be executed?
Henri, we’ve come this far. We can’t turn back now.
Even if we kill the real princess and make Helena take her place,
that cop, Vayo, will tell King Arthur everything anyway.
I don’t think she’ll let her lover die for nothing.
What? Who loves who?
I said put the gun down!
Okay, fine! I’ll do it!
Miss Vayo! Miss Vayo!
Are you sure it’s not just a cop doing her job to protect the princess?
If it’s just that, she wouldn’t have given the princess a keepsake.
[Henri]: Walk!
[Princess Blew]: Let me go!
Quiet!
I’ve never seen you wear this necklace before, Princess.
Don’t you dare!
GPS.
She must have put it on the princess to track her.
But I already shut it off.
If that’s true, then good.
What are you planning to do?
Grace.
I’m so glad you still remember me.
How could I forget the person who betrayed me?
Father and everyone in the royal family have always been nice to you
How can you do something so despicable to us?
I want King Alderic to pay for what he did.
The whole De Laina family must suffer the loss like I did.
And you, as his beloved granddaughter, only have to pay for it.
What did Grandfather do to make you feel so vengeful?
Have you ever heard of a Bruzzo family who was wiped out entirely before King Aruther took his throne?
[Lord, you are the God who saves me;]
[day and night I cry out to you.]
[May my prayer come before you;]
[turn your ear to my cry.]
[I am overwhelmed with troubles]
[and my life draws near to death.]
[Your wrath lies heavily on me;]
[you have overwhelmed me with all your waves.]
[I am confined and cannot escape;]
[Grace]: I was the only one left. I did everything…to get myself a position at the palace.
[my eyes are dim with grief.]
[Grace]: And wait for the day to take my revenge on De Laina people, like what they did to us Bruzzo!
[Your wrath has swept over me;]
[your terrors have destroyed me.]
[All day long they surround me like a flood;]
[they have completely engulfed me.]
[Grace]: All power shall fall into the hands of Bruzzo.
[You have taken from me friend and neighbor—]
And after that, I’ll kill each and everyone of you!
[and now I’m only left…]
- Please let it end with me.
- No!
[with darkness (misery).]
I won’t let you die so easily.
What do you mean?
I’ll make you feel the pain when you have to watch the ones you love die…
without being able to do anything!
I’ll make you suffer like I did!
Lieutenant Vayo.
She has nothing to do with this!
You love her so much, don’t you?
No, I don’t love her!
So, if she has to die, I guess you wouldn’t feel anything then.
Leave her alone!
Please drop the formalities.
King Arthur has spread words to trick the traitors that he’d arrive tomorrow, and asked me to escort him here in private.
How is my sister?
The police are tracking down her whereabouts.
She has been captured, Your Majesty.
Where is Miss Vayo now?
My daughter was injured during the encounter.
She is now in a hospital, Your Majesty.
Excuse me, sir!
What is it?
Lieutenant Vayo has been missing.
Check the surveillance cameras and have someone track her down right now!
Yes, sir.
What’s going on, General?
Helping you sneak out like this, I’m a bit worried.
But would you rather let her do it alone?
It’d be more dangerous that way.
Us coming with her is better.
But what we’re going to do is extremely dangerous.
Don’t you think we should tell your dad, Lom?
If we tell him, there’s no way he’d let me go help Miss Blew.
But what if–
At least, let me find out where she is first. Then, I’ll tell Dad.
I already turned it on.
They should be here soon.
Good. We can kill two birds with one stone.
Have you got any sign of her?
Not yet.
What should we do now?
Just go to where the signal was last seen.
Hey! It’s the signal from her necklace!
Don’t!
Easy there, Miss Blew.
That cop is willing to walk into a death trap herself.
I said don’t!
Helena!
Keep an eye on her.
Find something to blindfold and gag her too.
Where are you going?
I’ll go get ready to welcome Princess Blew’s important guest.
You look exactly like me.
Din, pull over here.
I think the signal is coming from deep in the forest.
Honestly, I think it’s strange. Why did the signal suddenly pop up? Is it a trap?
I know. It might be a trap, but I still have to go. You and Fai just wait here.
Just send this location to my dad.
The backup team should be on their way.
I’ll go with you.
No, it’s too dangerous.
Let her go with you. Two heads are better than one.
Yeah. Don’t try to stop me, I’ll go anyway.
Let’s go then.
Lom just sent me the location of the suspects, Your Majesty.
I’ll go help my sister too.
Let’s leave that to General Wathit and Sir Antione.
Please rest assured, Your Majesty. Should Henri try to do any harm to the princess and royal family,
despite being my own son, I shall take him down with my own hands.
I trust you. Please save my daughter.
Helena, Grace wants you to–
Grace! Helena’s gone!
She probably got scared and ran away.
I’ll go after her.
No need.
Just leave her.
Let’s take care of Miss Blew first.
We’ll get to that later.
Excuse me, sir.
Our informant said that Vayo is coming to this house.
She’s really asking for it.
Get up!
Come here.
Is it really this one?
Why is it so quiet?
It’s here.
[GPS beeping]
I’m going in.
Don’t go in if the backup team isn’t here yet, got it?
Do you want to get yourself killed?
We already know where they are. Why don’t we just wait for backup first?
They’re using Miss Blew to bargain with me.
If we wait for backup, it’ll put Miss Blew in more danger.
Wait here.
Please be careful.
Vayo, I know you’re around here.
Come out. Don’t make your girl sacrifice herself for nothing.
I’ll count to three.
One!
Two!
I’m here.
Walking right into your own death.
It’s you who deserve to die, Traitor.
How dare you!
Grace, let’s finish this fast or else the cops might be here soon.
If you’re hesitating, I’ll do it instead.
[Gunshot]
Grace! Why did you shoot me?
Haven’t I told you to mind your own business? I’ll kill her myself!
It’s your turn now, Vayo.
Come out! I said come out!
Don’t hurt her.
Time to watch your loved one die right before your eyes.
[Gunfight]
Go in! Go!
[Princess Blew]: No!
[Grace]: Go in!
- [Princess Blew]: No!
[Grace]: I said go in!
[Princess Blew]: No!
[Grace]: Go!
[Princess Blew]: No! Let me go!
Go in! Go!
[Police]: Freeze! Drop the gun and turn yourself in!
[Lom]: It’s over, Grace.
Shut up! This isn’t over yet!
But you have no one left.
Henri just took the bullets for you because he loved you.
That’s because he’s a fool! He thought I loved him.
Just like you, who’s willing to die for something stupid like love.
It’s those who see love as something stupid that are actually stupid.
You don’t get to patronize me!
[Gunfight]
[Continuous shootout]
Miss Blew!
[Princess Blew]: Please don’t get hurt because of me again.
[Lom]: I can’t promise that.
But there’s one thing I can.
[Lom]: As long as I’m here, I’ll never let anyone hurt you.
I’ll protect you with my own life.
How do you feel about me?
I love you.
♫They mean so much to me. Stay with me, please don’t go♫
♫All my heart, there’s only you♫
♫Stay with me, now and forever♫
♫Let there be only you and me, please don’t go♫
Miss Blew…
[NEXT EPISODE]
Lom, how are you?
Fai told me about it.
I was worried sick.
Why did you risk your life like that?
She’s probably found someone she truly loves.
Miss Blew…
Have you heard from Lom, Din?
I’m worried sick about her.
If we still can’t get ahold of her, I’m going to report a missing person.
The first snow, are you watching?
♫It’s okay, you don’t have to say it now♫
♫I want you to take your time♫
♫Those things we’ve been through, those time we’ve spent together♫
♫They mean so much to me. Stay with me, please don’t go♫
♫All my heart, there’s only you♫
♫Stay with me, now and forever♫
♫Let there be only me and you, please don’t go♫
[Desires in the Wind]
♫What should I do?♫
[North Star Entertainment]