(Respect copyright)
♪Memories hold you back
from fulfilling your dreams♪
♪Only by moving forward
can you find reunion♪
♪Endings only mark new routes♪
♪It's all part of the scenery♪
♪To the horizon's call♪
♪Your journey hasn't started♪
♪Towards mountains,
chase the stars bright♪
♪Let time embrace you
and wash away the past♪
♪Put every twist behind you♪
♪Drift leisurely through time♪
♪Make headway against the wind♪
♪Let mountains bow to your pace♪
♪Rush towards a life without regret♪
♪Let your nature burst free♪
=The First Jasmine=
=Episode 36=
Your Highness, your bed is made.
It's fine to throw away the rouge,
but the bedding sets
were perfectly good.
What exactly is Nanny Xu trying to do?
Is His Highness back?
Yes.
Yao,
are you in there?
Yes, I am.
Why is the door locked?
I'm fine. You may leave.
You don't sound well.
Did you catch a cold?
You may leave,
and I'll be there in a while.
Why did you lock the door
while you're reading?
And without lamplight?
It's so hot.
Let me feel your pulse.
No, no need.
I'll go have some water.
Aphrodisiac incense?
Who gave it to you?
You've been married for almost a year.
You and Yao are in your prime.
Aren't you eager to have a child?
Ms. Wen?
I only took a sip, so it's no big deal.
You may leave.
Please.
We're husband and wife.
We can talk it out tomorrow.
This swallow's nest is rare.
Steam it and send it to Li later.
My Lady,
I have already prepared it.
And I've also given the nutrition recipe
to the cook.
The cook will follow the recipe
to make nutritious food.
Don't worry, my lady.
Your Highness.
Why did you do this?
You ask me?
Yao, you should know why.
You are going to Suixue Pass.
I cannot stop you.
You want to serve the court
and protect the country.
That's your righteousness,
and who dares to stop you?
But before you leave,
you must have a child with Li.
Li is still young.
Indeed, she is.
Nobody knows what will happen to you
on the battlefield.
She has no family left.
And Lishan Academy is also gone.
She has no child now.
Well,
what if something happens to you?
How is she supposed to live alone?
I didn't do that
for your Mo family.
I did it for Li.
As long as you and Li have a child,
Li and I can raise the child together
and move on.
And you can achieve your ambitions
without any worries.
You brought Li down the mountain
precisely for this day, didn't you?
Yao.
Have you talked with Ms. Wen?
You already know?
Ms. Wen is not an unreasonable person.
Given what she did
and your state after Gongshu Yang left
the other day,
it's not hard to guess what happened.
When are you going to leave?
I haven't decided yet.
Commander Xiong Yisong was murdered,
so the deputy is in charge for now.
His Majesty and Gongshu Yang
both want me to go.
But I...
Yao,
do you know why I fell ill
when I was on Lishan Mountain?
That's because I wanted to survive.
I was too young then,
unable to cope with that situation.
That's why I fell ill.
I was saving myself.
Finally, I survived a hard time.
So, what else is there to fear?
Ms. Wen is worried about me,
and you should understand.
Besides, there is no war at Suixue Pass.
If you go there,
you'll just garrison the frontier
and train troops.
You're in a high, powerful position,
so what is there to worry about?
I'll write to you when I miss you.
If I miss you too much, I'll go see you.
Suixue Pass is far away.
How will you go?
On horseback.
I've been there. Remember?
I remember.
You were almost caught by bandits.
They can't catch me now.
I am as formidable as Master Zhu now.
Thank you, Li.
These people
couldn't name a candidate when asked to.
But after Gongshu Yang
proposed Prince Ding,
they all submitted memorials together
advising me not to send Prince Ding
to Suixue Pass.
Calm down, Your Majesty.
Prince Ding is familiar
with the frontier
and capable of leading troops.
He is the ideal candidate
to take over as commander.
Your Majesty,
just ignore opposition.
What about Duke Hua?
Duke Hua is old.
He is almost retired
and rarely meddles in court politics.
When I visited him yesterday,
his old injury had recurred
due to the continuous rain.
He was tormented and looked miserable.
He is indeed not the best candidate.
Your Majesty,
allow me to speak bluntly.
In terms of the ability to fight,
Prince Ding is the best in our nation.
But when it comes to
guarding Suixue Pass,
holding military power,
deterring Cangbei,
and commanding the army,
he is absolutely not the right person.
Why not?
That is
because the court once broke his heart.
Although Mo Xiuwen's death was caused
by Marquis Muyang,
who was behind it?
Back then,
as Mo Xiuwen led troops to the capital,
the Eastern Palace caught fire,
and the Crown Prince died.
Otherwise, what would have happened?
Li Duo,
without any evidence,
how can you maliciously speculate?
Prince Ding is utterly loyal.
It's clear to all.
Generally, military power
is imperial power.
I certainly hope
Prince Ding is absolutely good.
I hope that he remains loyal
to Dachu and Your Majesty
after being wronged for years.
I do not wish to suspect a good general.
I only want to remind Your Majesty
that people could change.
We cannot gamble.
Do you have anyone else
in mind?
Your Majesty,
I've learned
military strategy since childhood.
I once served
as General of the Left Army,
wrote the "Frontier Farming Strategy,"
and led troops in military drills.
I believe I'm able to lead troops.
Li Duo,
what do you mean by that?
I request
to let me guard Suixue Pass.
Li Duo is going to Suixue Pass?
Yes.
The edict has been issued,
and Li Duo will leave for it tomorrow.
Suixue Pass is a frontier fortress
and Dachu's northern gateway.
With Suixue Pass standing,
if Cangbei invades,
they must cross the mountains
and camp along the way.
Without Suixue Pass,
if Cangbei intends to invade,
they only need to cross the Hukou Plain
and head south
to reach the capital directly.
I know.
Since Your Majesty knows,
why send Li Duo to Suixue Pass?
He has never been on the battlefield.
Can he guard such an important fortress
like Suixue Pass?
I don't believe
he can do it.
So, who do you think I should send?
My clan has guarded Suixue Pass
for generations.
If my brother hadn't been framed...
Xiuyao.
Your Majesty,
are you questioning my loyalty?
I just don't want you to suffer
on the frontier anymore.
Life is harsh there.
Your leg injury has just healed.
What if your old injury is back?
You've only been married for a year
with no children.
Suixue Pass
is a dangerous place.
If something happens to you,
how will I explain
to your wife and Ms. Wen?
Li Duo has never been
on the battlefield,
but he is experienced
in assessing the situation
and managing subordinates.
I am sending him, only hoping
that he can manage people well
and keep the frontier peaceful.
I don't expect him to go into battle
and win.
Xiuyao.
I am no longer a child.
I can tell
if outsiders want to sow discord
between us.
But I have my own reasons
to make this decision.
Li Duo
has been loyal to me these years.
Since he requested it,
why not give him a chance?
Military power is a huge thing.
If Your Majesty trusts him,
it's fine.
Gao Wenhuan will go with him
as the army supervisor.
Rest assured,
there won't be any trouble.
(Prince Ding's Mansion)
Jin just told me
that His Majesty won't send you
to Suixue Pass.
Aren't you happy?
I just feel like something is off.
How so?
I don't know.
I just feel uneasy.
The edict has been issued.
It means His Majesty
has made up his mind.
For now, we can only wait and see.
Look on the bright side.
You can stay and keep me company.
Mingyue,
are we leaving today?
They made their move.
The guards will
strengthen their patrols.
They killed Xiong Yisong.
What are they up to?
Are they going to fight?
Not so fast.
When their man takes over,
they will start a fight.
But for now, they will definitely hide.
So even if they find us missing,
they won't act rashly.
It's just a bit difficult
to leave the city now.
Hyah!
Their men.
Eat your food.
Where is Han Mingyue?
He went
on a mission.
A mission?
How come I didn't know?
Your Highness.
What mission did Han Mingyue go on?
Didn't you say
we would do nothing
before Li Duo takes over?
He hasn't been back all night.
Could something have happened?
Your Highness.
Mingyue, how did it go?
(Travel Pass)
Where did you get this?
It's fake.
Be careful when leaving the city.
With so many patrolling guards now,
will we get into trouble?
Since we've decided,
let's bet our lives on it.
Okay.
With you, I'm not afraid of anything.
(Cloth Shop)
Master,
something happened at Suixue Pass.
Do we really have to go to Cangbei?
What if something happens?
We've asked around for days,
but we still don't know
what Cangbei will do with Su Zuidie.
She killed their ruler's sister.
She should be publicly executed.
Maybe Cangbei
makes a different decision.
Maybe she hasn't been executed yet.
If so, we should go and find out.
Only then can Lingyun rest in peace.
Eat your food,
and then we'll hit the road.
Okay.
Are you leaving?
Answer me.
Zuidie,
we can leave together.
Why?
Why are you leaving?
Have you forgotten our revenge?
Have you forgotten
what we've been through together?
How many more times
are you going to bring it up?
You only saved me once.
My brother saved you so many times.
Isn't that enough?
Mingyue.
Let's go.
Tell me.
Are you really leaving?
Yes.
I'm leaving.
Fine.
Then leave.
As long as you can get out alive.
Su Zuidie,
you lunatic!
Did you hear that?
What?
Mingyue!
Han Mingxi!
Su Zuidie!
I'll kill you!
This is for Lingyun.
Ruyi!
Master!
Kill her!
This stab
is for Dachu.
Ruyi.
Ruyi!
Mingyue.
Mingyue!
Mingxi.
Go!
They will come again.
You promised
you would definitely take me away.
Mingxi,
listen to me.
Go live the life you want.
Mingyue.
Mingyue!
(Tomb of Han Mingyue, Tomb of Ruyi)
It was my brother
who saved that bad woman.
I'm sorry.
Your brother has paid the price.
I've avenged Lingyun's death.
It will pass soon.
(Tomb of Han Mingyue)
Rest for two days,
and then return together.
I want to stay with my brother
for a few days.
Don't forget your brother's words.
Go live the life you want.
Your brother and Su Zuidie
worked for the same guy.
Who exactly is it?
It's Mo Jingli.
They killed Xiong Yisong.
Their man replaced Xiong Yisong's place.
Once the new replacement arrives,
I'm afraid something big will happen.
Where did you go this morning?
You came back so late.
I went to Qingfeng Mingyue Tower.
After Feng Zhiyao left the capital,
I got no news from him.
I'm a bit worried.
So, I sent someone
to his hometown to inquire.
The death of Princess Lingyun
was a heavy blow to him.
But he is optimistic.
I guess
he left the capital to relax.
When he calms himself,
he will return.
Are you thinking about Suixue Pass?
Commander Xiong Yisong died suddenly.
It was said he was killed by a groom.
But I always feel something is off.
I'm afraid someone is behind it.
And Li Duo has been steady and quiet.
Unexpectedly, he recommended himself.
I feel quite confused and uneasy.
So, how do you plan to do?
I have ordered Jin
to travel day and night
to Suixue Pass and investigate it.
I only hope this is all a false alarm.
May the Suixue Pass
be safe.
Congratulations,
you're going to take office tomorrow.
Thank you.
Among the three of us,
Zhuang is the most capable.
A commoner, gifted in mathematics,
is exceptionally promoted
to Vice Director
of the Ministry of Revenue.
From now on,
you will have a bright future,
rising to the top.
Zhuang.
I hope
you will back me up.
Stop making fun of me.
If you were given a position,
would you take it?
With my personality,
I'm not official material.
It's better for me
to travel around freely.
Now, Marquis Muyang is dead.
Guo Jin has returned her power.
And Lishan Mountain has been open again.
Finally, I have no regrets now.
I can finally live a good life.
May we live well.
Right,
do you know any familiar brokers?
I want to buy a house.
Not a very big house,
with a two-courtyard layout
and a good location.
It's best to be near the market,
with taverns and eateries nearby,
so it's convenient for daily shopping.
What?
Why are you buying a house?
Of course, to live in.
- Strange.
What's wrong?
Didn't you always say
that you would travel around
and never settle down?
We just heard you.
Are you going
to give up traveling freely?
Well...
Who exactly do you buy a house for?
We understand.
What do you understand?
Zhuang.
Have you
ever heard of a lady
in the capital named Yusheng?
Of course, I've heard of her.
She is talented, beautiful, and kind.
It's a pity
that she took a fancy to a vagabond.
But I heard
that the vagabond suddenly changed
and wanted to settle down.
So, he has to buy a house, right?
Alright, enough.
Stop making fun of me.
Are we drinking or not?
Drink.
This is
to the future.
May we live well.
To the future.
Feng Zhiyao has fled to the capital.
We sent men to track him down,
but he escaped every time.
Han Mingxi should
still be at Suixue Pass,
but
he's gone missing.
Ignore him.
Your Highness,
the Han brothers know a lot
about Suixue Pass,
especially regarding Li Duo's identity.
If Feng Zhiyao brings the news
to the capital,
we might lose Suixue Pass.
Tell me about military supplies
for Suixue Pass.
Your Highness,
we have a standing elite infantry
of 30,000
and 12,000 cavalrymen
under control.
In the armory,
there are 5,000 heavy crossbows,
and enough spears
and sword-and-shield sets.
There are also over 8,000 warhorses.
Enough.
Your Highness means...
These warhorses,
soldiers,
plus us,
are enough to break through the gate
of the capital?
Your Highness, do you mean to rebel now?
To achieve great things,
the right time,
right place,
and right men
are all indispensable.
I have loyal, wise, and brave men
like you all.
You're all the right men.
Suixue Pass stands
on the northern frontier.
We can either march down
or retreat behind the pass.
That is
the right place.
Now,
the news has leaked.
This is a heaven-sent opportunity,
the right time chosen by heaven.
The time has come.
It's time to give it our all.
Your Highness,
what should we do with Gao Wenhuan?
Kill him.
Since that day,
Han Mingxi has never come back.
That day, he said
he'd return at night and buy me drinks.
However, he didn't come back.
What about his things?
They are
all still here.
Keep them safe.
Go do your work.
Yes.
Little Li,
how did Lishan Academy end up like this?
Last time I saw you,
you told me
that Qingyun was healthy,
writing books every day,
and fishing and planting
in his free time, right?
At that time,
I indeed believed so.
After they perished,
I fell ill.
Perhaps,
to get through a hard time,
I subconsciously hid all the truth
and felt they were still with me,
talking to me,
eating with me,
and working together,
as if nothing had ever happened.
All these years,
you've endured it all by yourself.
Until recently,
Yao came up the mountain to find me
and stayed by my side.
Only then did I finally face it all.
How could this happen?
(Back then,)
(it was I who begged your grandfather
to seal the mountain.)
(The evidence of the fire)
(at the Eastern Palace
pointed to Marquis Muyang.)
(But Guo Jin made him the Chief Minister
of Imperial Court of Judicial Review.)
(The evidence was instantly destroyed.)
(The case took a turn,)
(and Prince Ding's clan was
in a crisis.)
(It was all to pave the way
for Guo Jin.)
(She was malicious.)
(How could she be allowed
to rule the state?)
(But the court
was full of Marquis Muyang's men.)
(Well,)
(I had no other choice.)
I understand.
You don't need to blame yourself.
Since my grandfather did it all
by choice,
nobody is to blame.
Your grandfather cared about the nation
all his life.
By sealing the mountain,
he not only cut off Guo Jin's delusion
of holding the Fengshan ceremony
but also aroused the response
of scholars nationwide.
Unfortunately, a disaster struck.
It's hard for me to take it.
Even Master Helai
couldn't cure them all.
Back then, Lishan Academy had been
under siege for three years,
lacking both food and medicine.
Even if Master Helai
had the best medical skills,
there was nothing he could do.
Siege?
Who dared to besiege Lishan Mountain?
The Imperial Guard.
They did so by the order
of the Empress Dowager.
Lu Changfu led the troops to besiege us.
Sir,
it's all in the past.
It is my fault.
All these years,
I've never considered the safety
of Lishan Mountain,
causing such a great disaster.
I cannot shirk my responsibility.
After Prince Ding's crisis,
you were still ill,
yet you guarded the frontier
for six years
until the frontier was stable.
For this,
you were bedridden.
The integrity of Lishan Academy
and my grandfather's choice
have never been a burden to anyone.
We have never resented you for a moment.
Under siege,
your calls for help went unanswered.
I wanted to go down the mountain
to seek help, but was forcefully stopped
and locked up.
By the time I broke open the room,
they were already dead.
They kept their promise
at the cost of their lives.
I feel truly sorry.
Whatever we do
cannot ease the pain.
Yes.
Gentlemen
shouldn't have to prove their resolve
with their blood.
(Back then, Lishan Academy had been
sealed for three years,)
(lacking both food and medicine.)
(Even if Master Helai
had the best medical skills,)
(there was nothing he could do.)
(I wanted to go down the mountain)
(to seek help,
but was forcefully stopped)
(and locked up.)
(By the time I broke open the room,)
(they were already dead.)
Sir!
What's wrong, sir?
Sir?
Are you having a heart attack?
There's a clinic ahead.
Let's go get you checked.
My illness
cannot be cured.
Let's go home.
Whoa!
Master Feng.
Jin.
What's wrong with you?
I need to see His Highness.
Okay.
Get a physician!
Yes.
What happened? Who hurt you?
Li Duo works
for Mo Jingli.
I didn't expect
that Li Duo had been a spy
right under your nose, Your Majesty.
Mo Jingli, a despicable
and shameless traitor,
actually faked his death to rebel!
Calm down, Your Majesty.
The military situation is urgent now
and must be responded to in time.
What is the situation now?
Your Majesty,
I've checked it.
The rebels are cunning.
They've won over some military officers
at Suixue Pass.
Moreover,
they took advantage of a shift
to secretly sneak in troops.
Their vanguard has sneaked in
and crossed the Heishui River.
Their forces are marching
towards Luoxia Pass.
Once they take Luoxia Pass,
within ten days,
the rebels
will break open the capital.
Then,
what should we do?
Opportunities in war are fleeting.
We must dispatch troops immediately
for a head-on strike!
Your Majesty, I request to go to battle.
I wish to lead the troops
to crush the rebels
to restore peace
for the sake of Dachu.
I swear not to return
until I defeat the rebels.
Xiuyao.
I shall entrust the peace of Dachu
and the safety of the people
to you.
(Prince Ding's Mansion)
Uncle.
Come on.
Let's go home.
♪My life is full of ups and downs♪
♪Every wound shows traces of love♪
♪I've seen all the withering plants
in this world♪
♪Until you went over the hills
to come close to me♪
♪I saw your tender yet unwavering eyes♪
♪Quietly full of joy and sorrow♪
♪When it's over, I stand in the light♪
♪In the reunion,
I comprehend the parting♪
♪With half a lifetime of separation,
I send love to the distance♪
♪As I travel through wind and frost,
I gaze at your figure♪
♪You never forget me,
and I always miss you♪
♪Until our hair turns gray♪
(Preview)
I will definitely come back safely.
Then I wish Your Highness
a triumphant battle.
Are you crazy?
My heart
is wrenching.
It aches so much.
Has His Highness written to you lately?
No, he hasn't for half a month.
Rumors are spreading outside.
Some say Luoxia Pass has been breached,
and others say His Highness
has defected to the enemy.
♪Memories hold you back
from fulfilling your dreams♪
♪Only by moving forward
can you find reunion♪
♪Endings only mark new routes♪
♪It's all part of the scenery♪
♪To the horizon's call♪
♪Your journey hasn't started♪
♪Towards mountains,
chase the stars bright♪
♪Both joy and grief
make the trip worthwhile♪
♪Trying to catch up
to your own lost shadow♪
♪Within the wilds, echoes thrive♪
♪Clear mind leads to a clear path♪
♪Be grateful to your losses♪
♪Make your steps weightless♪
♪Towards mountains,
chase the stars bright♪
♪Let time embrace you
and wash away the past♪
♪Put every twist behind you,
drift leisurely through time♪
♪Make headway against the wind,
let mountains bow to your pace♪
♪Rush towards a life without regret♪
♪Let your nature burst free♪
♪Unbound by form♪