"Lost To You"
(Episode 10)
If happiness has an expiration date,
then before it expires,
let's carve it into our bones.
Brother, we're open for business!
Thank you, everyone.
Things will only get better from here.
They will.
Thank you.
Delicious!
What would you like to eat?
Coming right up. Just a moment.
We'll have the signature dish.
Fish soup and fishball noodles, right?
Yes, exactly.
Two orders, right?
Here it comes!
Boss, can I get a Coke?
Enjoy your meal.
Sure, thanks.
Here are your noodles.
Thank you so much.
Alright, coming right up.
Mom, you've worked hard.
It's nothing.
Eat more.
What's wrong?
Nothing, I'm fine.
Are you okay?
What are you taking?
Vitamins.
I've been a bit tired lately,
just getting some nutrients.
Are you sure you're okay?
I'm fine.
Xiao Yuan.
Go grab those drinks.
Okay.
Just a moment, coming right up.
Thanks for your hard work, Mom.
It's nothing. You should eat too.
Come on, let's eat.
Let's eat.
Xiao Xia hasn't tried this before.
Have some more.
What... what is this?
This is goose barnacles.
You've never had it, right?
Come on, everyone try some.
- Try some.
- Thank you, Auntie.
Thank you.
Is it good?
Tastes good, right?
Come on, let's all
celebrate the grand opening!
Cheers!
Congratulations!
Thank you. Cheers!
Thank you, everyone.
Auntie, there's no need
to be so polite with us.
I'll be coming over for
free meals all the time.
Just don't get tired of me.
You're all welcome anytime!
Auntie, I wish your new shop smooth sailing
and great prosperity!
Thank you.
Mom,
Sister Xia set up a new
Instagram account for me.
She wants to turn me into
the 'Fish Noodle Beauty'.
Once I go viral,
our shop will become even more popular!
Really?
Just don't let it affect your studies.
I know.
Come on, let's
raise our glasses again.
To a booming business,
and to us being together forever!
Together forever!
Let's take a group photo.
For the grand opening,
we need a family portrait!
Great, let's take a photo together.
Then...
You are all my wonderful children.
Should we hang it here?
Can we put it over there instead?
Sure, that works.
Come closer.
Hurry up and come over.
Hold on.
Let me adjust the framing.
Xu Yuan,
get a little closer to Mom.
Come on.
Hurry up and get in here.
Get ready.
Everyone, smile!
Zhan Wang!
Brother Wang!
Zhan Wang! Zhan Wang!
Zhan Wang, are you okay? Zhan Wang!
Brother Wang! Zhan Wang!
Are the family members here?
I'm his brother.
The situation is not looking good.
The patient has a tumor
in his right temporal lobe.
A tumor?
What kind of tumor?
Doctor, he's only eighteen.
How could he have a tumor?
Doctor, please check again.
He's just been too tired lately.
Xiao Yuan,
don't get too worked up.
Our priority right now
is his illness.
Doctor,
after the diagnosis,
what are the treatment options?
We must operate as soon as possible.
The tumor is in a sensitive
location, so surgery is risky.
But if we delay,
a more dangerous situation
could happen at any moment,
such as a brain herniation.
You, as his family, need
to discuss this quickly
to decide on a treatment
plan and schedule the surgery.
Also,
does the patient know
about his condition?
He probably doesn't know yet.
I need to contact our family.
Is he
awake yet?
Not yet.
But his vital signs
have stabilized for now.
He'll be moved to a ward shortly.
You can go see him then.
Alright. Thank you.
Brother Xu,
How could this happen?
How could he possibly have a tumor?
When he first fainted
and came to the clinic,
I suspected something was wrong with him.
But no matter what I asked,
he wouldn't say a word.
It's all my fault.
I should have given him a
proper checkup back then.
I'm to blame.
I spent so much time with him,
yet I didn't notice anything.
I didn't notice a thing.
I'm just a jinx.
Brother, don't be like this.
No one could have foreseen this.
Brother.
Brother Wang.
Brother Wang, can you hear me?
Yuan.
What's wrong?
Why the long face?
It's nothing.
I just got a bit too excited when we
were taking photos at the noodle shop.
My blood sugar probably dropped.
The doctor is making a
mountain out of a molehill.
I'm fine.
Brother Xu has already
contacted a better doctor for you.
You'll be fine in no time.
It's my own body.
I know it best.
There's no need to trouble him.
Zhan Wang.
Why?
You had headaches time and time again,
took medicine over and over,
and felt unwell repeatedly.
Why didn't you tell me?
Is it because, to you,
telling me wouldn't make a difference?
No.
Xu Yuan, that's not it.
Or is it
that you never even
envisioned a future with me?
No.
I did think about our future.
But I was terrified
that I wouldn't have a future.
Actually, when I first
found out about this illness,
I was terrified too.
I was scared I'd die and
no one would even know.
But I had no one to talk to.
I never expected to meet you
when I came here.
Every single day I spent with you,
felt like borrowed time.
We played basketball together,
tutored each other,
watched the sunrise together,
and just finished setting up the new shop.
I thought I could live like this forever.
I just never expected
that my life would be so short.
Brother Wang,
I'm sorry.
That's not going to happen.
It won't.
I'm sorry.
You'll be fine.
You're definitely going to get better.
Yuan, I'm sorry.
You're going to get better.
You can't leave me all alone.
I'm sorry.
Xiao Wang,
what's wrong with you?
If you're sick, you need to get treated.
You shouldn't get so worked up right now.
Dad...
is already on his way.
Why did you tell him?
To watch me die?
He doesn't care about me at all.
Xiao Wang,
he does care about you.
He cares?
All he cares about is the
Zhan family's reputation.
He's just afraid I'll end up like you.
If you're mad at your dad,
why are you snapping at him?
Brother Wang,
with something this serious,
I think your dad should know.
My dad is not like your mom.
He only cares about making money.
All he cares about is his reputation.
Whether I live or die,
he doesn't give a damn.
But you care about him,
don't you?
I don't.
If you didn't care about him,
you wouldn't be this angry
and this sad.
It's because you care about him
that you're angry.
You're sad
because you feel he should care about you,
but he hasn't.
Actually,
I'm actually...
scared that we...
Your dad has the medical resources,
and you need him.
Just let him come.
For your sake,
and for ours.
Xiao Wang.
Whatever.
It's okay.
You are...
This is ridiculous!
Keeping something this big from the family!
The plane is ready.
We're heading back to
Jingzhou this afternoon
for a full checkup and
to prepare for surgery.
I'm not going back.
How long are you going to keep acting up?
Dad,
I'm not acting up.
I know exactly what I'm doing.
Let me introduce you.
Xu Yuan,
my boyfriend,
Zhan Wang.
Do you have any idea what
nonsense you're talking?
I'm clearer than I've ever been.
Why are you just like your brother?
What does this have to do with my brother?
The one I love is Xu Yuan.
This is my own choice.
I'm not wrong.
Young man, please step outside.
We have family matters to discuss.
No need to leave.
Right in front of him,
let's make this clear.
Look at the state you're in.
And you still have time for this nonsense?
You are coming back to
Jingzhou with me right now.
Fine, I'll go back to Jingzhou.
But take him with us.
No way.
Then I'm not going back.
I'll just die right here.
You've never treated me as your son anyway,
and I don't have a father like you.
You ungrateful brat!
I...
Uncle,
Zhan Wang needs treatment right now,
and he also needs respect.
What you're doing right now
isn't helping him at all.
Going back to Jingzhou
is non-negotiable.
Dr. Wang,
give him a thorough examination.
Yes, sir.
Everyone else,
please step out.
Don't you leave.
Get your checkup.
I'll come see you when it's done.
Be good.
Get some rest, and
don't do anything foolish.
Keep a close eye on him.
I'm sorry.
Except for Mr. Zhan,
no one is allowed in here.
Can't you just take this soup inside?
I'm sorry, but no.
Xiao Yuan.
Brother Xu.
Xiao Yuan,
give it to me.
How were the test results?
Not very promising.
But it's not completely hopeless.
The medical facilities in
Jingzhou are much better.
So,
we should convince him to
go to Jingzhou for treatment.
I understand.
You've been by his side for days.
Go back and get some rest.
But I'm worried...
Don't worry.
I'm here.
Bian-bian
will also help me look after him.
Don't worry.
Leave it to Brother Xu and me.
Okay.
No unauthorized entry here.
I'm his older brother,
and the son of your boss.
No matter what,
you still have to call me Master.
Master Zhan,
we're just following Mr. Zhan's orders.
You guys leave first.
I need to have a word with my brother.
Yes, of course.
Let's go.
Xu Yuan made this for you.
Where is Xu Yuan?
Brother,
help me get out of here.
Get on.
How did you sneak out of the hospital?
I'm all better.
Shouldn't I be discharged if I'm fine?
It doesn't work that fast.
The doctor allowed it.
I've been cooped up for too long.
I needed to get some
energy from my lucky star.
Get on.
Skip class,
and elope. Do you dare?
Let's go.
Hold on tight.
Xu Yuan,
we're eloping!
Zhan Wang,
focus on getting treated.
Once you're better, we can go anywhere.
Look,
the sun is setting.
It will rise again tomorrow as usual.
But what about me?
I won't let you ask such
depressing questions.
Yuan,
if,
I mean, what if
we eloped
to a place where nobody knows us,
where there's no sickness,
and no pressure?
Would you be willing?
Don't talk about 'what ifs'.
Wherever you want to go, I'll go with you.
But I need you to get better.
When I was little,
my grandmother told me
that if she was no longer around,
she would turn into the ocean.
She'd be able to hear
whatever I say to her.
Grandma,
I've come to see you.
Grandma.
Can you hear me?
I found someone who loves me,
and whom I love very much.
His name is Xu Yuan.
He's a really good man.
You don't have to worry.
Granny,
I'm Xu Yuan.
I will take good care of Zhan Wang.
Please rest assured.
Zhan Wang.
I know you miss Granny very much,
but I won't let you go see her so soon.
I absolutely won't allow it.
Zhan Wang.
He stopped taking his medication
before running out of the hospital.
He even refused today's dehydration
therapy to lower intracranial pressure.
He did it on purpose.
He...
He doesn't want to be treated anymore.
Zhan Wang.
Didn't you promise me
that we'd open Yuan's Noodle
House all over the country?
Didn't you promise to
watch the sunrise with me?
Zhan Wang.
You're breaking your word.
Xu Yuan.
I know the success rate
of this surgery is very low.
And...
even if I have the surgery,
I might go deaf,
go blind,
and I'd have to shave my head.
Why don't you
just remember how
handsome I look right now?
Wouldn't that be better?
No, it wouldn't.
No matter what you become,
I want to be with you.
Zhan Wang,
just do it for me.
Try one more time.
Try one more time, please?
I'm begging you.
Okay.
For you.
Amitabha.
Young benefactor,
an obsession in the heart
can be a curse or a blessing.
It can change in an instant.
Master,
I...
I see that you,
though bearing the sign of a lone star,
actually harbor the
essence of a lucky star.
Fortune and misfortune are intertwined,
and the tide can be turned.
Master, do you mean...
Thank you, Master.
Amitabha.
All things in this world
are impermanent and fleeting.
From love comes longing,
and from love comes sorrow.
But if you find a kindred soul,
all hardships shall cease.
On December 12th,
at exactly 4:15 PM,
at the place where the comet falls,
make a sincere wish,
to reverse the course of fate.
Uncle,
come on up. Let's talk.