"Lost To You"
(Episode 11)
When the world is on
the brink of destruction,
I finally realize
I only want to save
the corner where you are.
Leave Zhan Wang.
Never contact him again.
Uncle,
My meeting with you today
wasn't to negotiate terms.
This isn't a discussion.
It's a notification.
And a deal.
I've looked into it.
Your mother's shop
is struggling,
and barely getting by.
Furthermore,
the apartment you live in
belongs to my mother.
Even though the title
was transferred to you,
I believe
I have the power
to take it back.
I can set your mother up
with a shop in a better location,
guaranteeing a steady stream of customers.
I can also help your
sister, who loves acting,
go to Jingzhou
to pursue her dream of becoming an actress.
Or,
I can make things much harder for you.
Hard enough to run your
mother out of business,
and ensure that apartment
never truly becomes yours.
Uncle,
are you threatening me?
I'm just showing you reality.
Love is not a luxury
that people your age can afford.
Zhan Wang's life
shouldn't be dragged down
by such an unstable relationship.
Especially now,
his condition requires better medical care
and absolute focus,
without any distractions.
And you
are clearly the biggest distraction.
Take this money,
solve your family's immediate problems,
and leave Zhan Wang.
For you and your mother,
this is the wisest choice right now.
And for him,
it lifts an unnecessary burden.
It's a win-win.
Uncle,
you have the power to
take everything from me??
my shop, my home.
But you can't take away my
determination to stay by his side.
You can solve anything with money.
Perhaps
you can buy him better medical care,
but you can't give him a reason to live.
But I can.
So, I won't leave.
The money,
please take it back.
I will be there when he goes into surgery,
and I'll be waiting when he comes out.
As for everything else,
as his father,
you can do whatever you think is right.
But I won't be the one to let go.
This is my decision,
and I don't need your approval.
I knew
you'd find me.
Why did you run out of the hospital?
I've been in bed for days.
My bones were getting rusty.
Come on.
Spar with me.
But in your condition,
you shouldn't be doing strenuous exercise.
My dad came to see you, didn't he?
Let me hear it.
How much am I worth?
A lot.
Enough for my family to buy a new house,
open a new shop,
and fund my sister's acting dream.
I didn't realize
I was worth that much.
That's good.
At least I could leave you with something.
I didn't take it.
I don't want money.
I want to stay with a big
jerk named Zhan Wang
until he gets better.
Do you know
how risky this surgery is?
So what?
Zhan Wang,
listen to me.
I don't need you to be a hero,
nor do I want you to
give up so tragically.
I want you to try again
for my sake.
I really can't say no to you.
Okay.
For you,
I'll try again.
Then,
let's go back to the hospital.
What's the rush?
One day won't make a difference.
I want to make
some beautiful memories with you.
What?
Let's go.
I'll take you somewhere.
Why are we here?
I just wanted to take a photo.
Surprise, Bro!
After Brother Zhan Wang told me,
I've been planning this for a long time.
Lin Xia helped me pick out the clothes.
Today, we'll definitely
get the best couple's photoshoot.
A couple's
photoshoot?
You didn't know?
Brother Zhan Wang wanted??
I just wanted...
I realized
we don't even have a
single proper photo together.
Just to have a keepsake.
Okay.
Let's take it.
Bro,
look a bit closer.
Put your arm around him.
Bro,
turn your right cheek a bit more.
Lean your left cheek closer to him.
Just like that.
So sweet!
One more!
Here, take this.
It's beautiful.
Like a painting.
The sea is so beautiful today.
Xu Yuan,
let's make a wish.
Think about what we'll
be doing in ten years.
Okay.
In ten years,
I still want to be with Zhan Wang.
I still want to be with Xu Yuan.
We'll be together forever.
In ten years,
I'm going to be the absolute best!
I hope my clinic
is set up wherever it's needed most,
and the person by my side
is still the same person.
In ten years,
I'll have a sunlit art studio,
painting all the stories and people I want,
and I'll paint the most beautiful posters
for the star who takes on the bigger stage.
In ten years,
I will definitely be a superstar.
When that time comes,
you all must come to see my show.
We must stay together forever.
Together forever.
Let's go.
Who gave you this necklace?
I've never seen you take it off.
Are you jealous?
This...
I won this in a boxing match
in the youth division.
I won it.
No one gave it to me.
It's proof
of the first time I used my fists
to prove myself,
and the first time I had the courage
to be my true self.
Now,
it's yours.
My lucky star.
I want to...
have it engraved on my body.
Since we're happy today,
I'll let you have a beer.
Okay.
Don't you think my brother and
Brother Wang make a perfect match?
They really do.
It's amazing.
Brother Wang's arrival,
and your appearance...
It's like seeing novel plots come to life.
Sis,
this is for you.
It's beautiful.
These shells...
I picked them up one by one on the beach,
and made them into a bracelet.
Don't think it's ugly.
I spent ages learning
how to do it from a tutorial.
Let me put it on for you.
Thank you, Xu Nuo.
I love it.
I'll always cherish this time.
Xu Nuo,
I have to go back to Jingzhou.
My wrist is mostly recovered.
The doctor said
I just need regular checkups
and physical therapy.
My school exchange period ended long ago.
I've already delayed for too long.
I know.
I can't keep you here.
You never belonged here anyway.
I don't know
if in your heart,
you just
see me as a sister,
or if you actually like me.
And I don't know
what you're really thinking.
So, I think...
Actually,
I want to go to Jingzhou with you.
I want to be by your side while you paint.
I want to be with you.
I don't know
if that's what you want too.
Have you decided?
What are you getting tattooed?
A star and a moon.
Why a star and a moon?
Because you said before
you'd take me to see a comet.
We might not make it to a comet,
but the stars and the
moon are there every night.
And I think
you're more like the moon.
I want to keep you with me.
Then I want one too.
I want to get a star.
You're my lucky star.
With you tattooed on me,
I won't fear any hardships.
Okay.
According to the latest observation data,
Comet C/2023 X1...
This is the nutritious meal
made from Xiao Xu's recipe.
Make sure Xiao Wang eats more of it.
Okay, got it.
...is spreading with Hong
Town as the epicenter.
It is currently expected
to crash in a week.
Yours is the only shop still open.
The other shops on this street
have all closed down
and fled to the shelters.
When are you guys planning to leave?
The school hasn't notified us yet.
We'll wait until the kids' schedule is set.
It's all those clickbait
accounts hyping it up,
causing unnecessary panic.
However, this information
has not been verified
and is still undergoing
further confirmation.
The moment of impact will generate
a localized shock equivalent to
a magnitude 5 to 8 earthquake,
and is highly likely to trigger
tsunami waves of 10 to 15 meters high.
The meteorite is coming.
Are we leaving?
Let me think.
Do you think we'll see the comet?
There's still a week left.
What is there to see now?
Did you guys see that
video in the group chat?
It says the comet will crash early.
And the impact of the crash
will be equivalent to a nuclear bomb.
Come on, you actually believe that?
This morning they claimed inside info
that classes would be suspended
and the whole town would evacuate.
But look, classes are still on schedule.
I'm telling you,
this time is really different.
Isn't my brother an astrophysicist?
He called yesterday and told us
to leave as soon as possible.
Is something really going to happen?
Then ask your brother,
if it really crashes,
will it look like
fireworks magnified tens
of thousands of times?
It must be spectacular.
I wonder if we'll get to see it.
Spectacular, my foot!
A 200-meter object crashing down,
plus the shockwave and tsunami...
It's a question if Hong
Town will even survive.
You think you're watching a sci-fi movie?
True, that does sound terrifying.
If that were really the case,
the school would have
suspended classes long ago,
instead of having us sit
here staring at the sky.
Zhan Wang, look.
Zhan Wang will definitely be fine.
I hope so.
Let's hope.
Please don't make things difficult for us.
I promised Brother Wang
that I'd visit him every day.
Please leave.
Just let me see him for a second.
Just one look.
Please just go back.
Could you please bring this in for me?
Zhan Wang, time for your injection.
I'm not taking it. Go away.
Don't touch me! I told you to leave!
Zhan Wang!
I told you not to touch
me! Didn't you hear me?
Calm down.
Please calm down.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Brother Wang!
Come in from over there.
Mr. Zhan.
The young master's emotions are unstable,
and he's refusing treatment.
Let's go.
Dad.
That's more like it.
Just focus on getting treated.
In a few days,
we'll return to Jingzhou
to continue with systematic treatment.
You're still very young.
You still have a long life ahead of you.
Keep this attitude
and cooperate with the doctors.
Understand?
I understand.
Where is your tattoo?
Find it yourself.
Are you leaving already?
I have to go back to school for class.
Don't go.
Alright.
I'll come back to keep
you company after class.
What's wrong?
Do you have a headache?
Should I call the doctor?
It hurts here.
I really don't know what to do with you.
What are you two doing?
Why is he here?
Take him away!
Let go of him!
Brother Wang!
Xu Yuan, I'm fine.
Just focus on your treatment.
Stay right there!
Xiao Wang's condition
is still deteriorating.
The medical facilities in Hong Town
cannot cure him at all.
If you want him to live,
he must be transferred immediately.
Right now, because of you,
he refuses to go back.
He's practically killing himself.
I can go to Jingzhou with him.
How can you accompany him?
In what capacity?
As his boyfriend.
Do you also want him
to be despised by everyone around him?
If you truly care about him,
you should leave him
so he can focus on his treatment.
I understand.
Before he leaves,
don't let him suspect anything.
Just send him off peacefully.
It's for the best for both of you.
Sweetie,
should we take this?
Take that one.
What about these two?
Leave those two behind.
Brother Xu,
Xiao Yuan,
Is Zhan Wang's illness
really that serious?
The technology and equipment here
are already the best we have.
But Jingzhou does have
a more professional team
and more cutting-edge treatments.
Going back is the best,
and only, option.
Our father's methods
might be a bit harsh,
but on this matter,
he isn't lying to you.
The comet is coming.
I received word
that this time,
it's supposed to be
worse than 18 years ago.
Hurry home
and pack your bags with Auntie Meixi.
Bian-bian and I
are also preparing to evacuate.
Okay.
Stop playing and come help.
Mom,
stop packing.
A lot of bloggers have debunked it.
This whole comet thing is a hoax.
Bro, talk some sense into Mom.
She actually wants to evacuate.
How is it possible
for a comet to wipe out the whole town?
"Pack your bags, we need to go.
The comet is coming."
Bro,
what's wrong with you?