=Visage and Soul=
("The Unique Her"
Trilogy on Women's Relationships)
=Episode 23=
What?
You're really Ye Xiaoduo?
Yifei,
about that jacket...
You washed it
and wanted to return it to me.
But you were afraid
that Qiao Xiaomi would find out.
So you hid it in the parcel box
outside my house.
There was even a note inside the pocket.
And on it, you wrote, "Thank you".
Ye Xiaoduo.
It really is you.
But
why do you look like Qiao Xiaomi?
The doctor said
the chances of me
recovering my memory were very low.
So,
my father had me
undergo facial reconstruction.
Maybe he thought
it was better
for both of us this way.
How could he be so selfish?
He's already gone.
What's the point of blaming him?
I'm sorry.
For the way I treated you before.
I'll pay for all the wrong I've done.
Yifei,
it's all in the past now.
Xiaomi...
No.
Xiaoduo.
You're so brave.
Don't worry.
I know what I need to do.
Thank you, Yifei.
What did he ever do to you
for you to be this hard on him?
I heard you're getting married soon.
I just gave him
a little lesson.
He needs to learn
what's acceptable
and what's not
in the Qiao family.
Getting married?
To him?
That liar?
Right now, I could kill him.
By the way,
I remember everything now.
About who I am
and who he is.
And how good you've
always been to me.
If you hadn't warned me back then,
and helped me catch
those two cheaters,
I'd probably
still being fooled by them.
Xiaomi,
you finally remember
everything I've done for you.
I won't let anyone bully you.
You're not allowed
to see that liar Qin Yu ever again.
Do you hear me?
Dad's only looking out for you.
Mind your own business.
Stop right there!
Dad gave Ye Xiaoduo
a herbal clinic.
Did you know that?
Why should I care?
Then what about the fact
that your boyfriend Qin Yu
and Ye Xiaoduo have been
getting cozy at that clinic?
Does that concern you?
What are you talking about?
My silly little sister.
Dad and I have known
about it for a long time.
You're the only one
who's been kept in the dark.
If you know something, say it!
Go see for yourself.
Just prepare yourself.
Don't say I didn't warn you.
Give me the address.
Nice.
There's always drama to watch.
Hello.
Is Xiaomi here?
Who?
Qiao Xiaomi.
There's no one here by that name.
Sorry.
Wait.
Please tell Qiao Xiaomi
that I'm done
with the Qiao family.
And if she comes after me again,
I won't let her get away with it.
Do you have
a misunderstanding about Xiaomi?
Did she do something bad?
Who exactly are you to her?
I...
I'm her...
So this is your type now?
That's what you're into these days?
No.
And you, the illegitimate daughter.
Just like your mother,
always trying to steal
other people's men, huh?
Xiaomi.
Are you okay?
Get away from me!
My dad was right.
I never should've gotten
involved with trash like you.
What are you talking about?
I'm saying you're trash.
How did you become like this?
I get it now.
She's your girlfriend, isn't she?
Do you see
who she really is now?
You finally get it, don't you?
B*stard child.
Believe it or not, I'll burn
this lousy herbal clinic to the ground!
Qiao Xiaomi!
The world doesn't revolve around you!
Get out of my way!
Do you realize
what happens if you do this?
I'd like to see
what could possibly happen.
Xiaomi,
calm down.
What are you doing?
Stay away from me!
Xiaomi!
Everyone, calm down!
But there's still
one thing I want to ask.
You were standing outside that day.
Why didn't you do anything?
Xiaomi!
Is anyone there?
Help!
Xiaomi!
Is anyone there?
Help!
Isn't this better?
That illegitimate girl is dead.
You're still alive.
You should cherish the life you've got.
You think I'm still the old Qiao Xiaomi?
The one you could kill so easily?
Enough talk.
Give me what I want.
Or you're not leaving here.
What are you so cocky about?
You're the one who's dead now.
Try me.
Give it to me.
You don't actually think
you can threaten me
with this liar, do you?
You've got to be kidding.
We've been brother and sister
for over 20 years.
Drop the act.
Give it to me!
Enough talking. Do it.
I'll count to three.
Three.
Two.
One.
Wait!
(Share Transfer Agreement)
If you hadn't fought me for it,
I wouldn't have had to
set you up to start that fire.
If Dad had been
half as sensible as you,
he wouldn't have died so early.
Don't tell me Dad's death
was your doing too.
Not exactly.
But when he was lying
in that hospital bed
begging me to save him,
I ignored him.
You monster.
Doesn't matter anymore.
Everything belongs to me now.
You got all that recorded, right?
Got it all.
Qiao Xiaomi,
what are you trying to do?
So once again, we need your help
to use his mindset
to guide him into telling the truth.
I'm sorry, Xiaoduo.
As a psychologist,
I've done so many things that hurt you.
It's okay, Chen Yue.
The person who truly did wrong
is the one who should apologize.
Alright.
I'll help you.
Which means
Qiao Zhiwei,
you're finished.
♪We say good morning, we say good night♪
♪We say we miss each other,
but never speak of the hurt♪
♪The sweeter it is, the luckier we seem♪
♪Yet the more romantic,
the rougher the road♪
♪Let me go, set me free♪
♪Let me drown in reckless silence♪
♪We were perfect for each other,
yet you never admitted it♪
♪The freedom you gave me♪
♪Became the heaviest chain I bear♪
♪Love can barely move forward♪
♪Yet the words still linger unspoken♪
♪The closeness I long for♪
♪There's no need for you
to keep avoiding it♪
♪I don't want to break free♪
♪Take back the chains
disguised as freedom♪