=Visage and Soul=
("The Unique Her"
Trilogy on Women's Relationships)
=Episode 24=
Qiao Xiaomi,
what do you mean?
It means, Qiao Zhiwei,
you're finished.
You all
want to see me ruined, huh?
Then don't expect
to walk away unscathed either.
Qiao Zhiwei,
we'll pay
for what we've done.
What about you?
Boring.
Then let me tell you
something interesting.
I'm not Qiao Xiaomi.
The girl Dad wanted you to see
was Ye Xiaoduo all along.
Qiao Xiaomi,
have you lost your mind?
What are you talking about?
Let me tell you
something even better.
Want to know who I really am?
I'm the real Qin Yu.
The guy who dated Qiao Xiaomi years ago,
his real name was Ji Ran.
I lent him my name and my identity.
Everything he said is true.
He's the real Qin Yu.
The one who died
in that fire three years ago
was my younger brother,
Ji Ran.
Every single one of you
is insane.
You're the insane one.
Qiao Zhiwei,
Qiao Wenfu turned you
into a rat that lives in the shadows.
And now you want to drag us all
down into the gutter with you.
Look at me.
Do you know why you're kneeling?
Because...
I forged your signature.
Wrong.
Try again.
I...
I really don't know, Dad.
Because you're stupid.
You couldn't even cheat properly.
You left evidence behind.
You don't even have
what it takes to be a villain.
Because you're stupid.
Too stupid.
Do you know what a son
of the Qiao family should be like?
Either
you become the very best.
So good that no one can question you.
Or you do things so cleanly
that no one ever finds out.
But you managed to do neither.
How could you possibly be my son?
Useless trash.
Trash.
I'm trash.
I'm
a rat in the gutter.
He made me this way.
Qiao Wenfu made me this way.
What did I do wrong?
Ever since I was a kid,
everything I did was wrong.
When I did well,
he said it was expected.
When I failed,
I was trash.
No matter what I did,
it was never enough.
Why?
I'm the eldest son of the Qiao family.
I should've been the one!
You still refuse to admit your mistakes?
Xiaomi.
Qiao Xiaomi.
I...
I was wrong.
I don't want anything anymore.
I don't want any of it.
I was wrong.
It's all yours.
Take it, take it all.
I don't want it anymore.
I... I'm begging you.
Please let this go.
Save it for the police.
I graduated.
I'm going back to Aiye Town today.
What for?
To open a clinic,
just like Mom did.
Did she
say a lot of bad things about me?
You're wrong.
She never once said a bad word
about you in front of me.
She really
didn't hate me?
She always told me,
the opposite of love isn't hate.
It's forgetting.
Xiaoduo,
from now on, this is your home.
This is your sister, Xiaomi.
And that's your brother, Zhiwei.
What a hick.
Never lived in a house this big before?
You think it's a skating rink?
Say that again.
Say that again!
What are you staring at?
Got a problem with that?
Ye Xiaoduo,
no matter what happens,
I won't let you be in danger.
I'll do everything I can to protect you.
Have you really thought this through?
I have.
Okay.
ظآزWe say good morning, we say good nightظآز
No matter where you want to go,
I'll be right there with you.
ظآزThe sweeter it is, the luckier we seemظآز
ظآزYet the more romantic,
the rougher the roadظآز
ظآزLet me go, set me freeظآز
ظآزLet me drown in reckless silenceظآز
ظآزWe were perfect for each other,
yet you never admitted itظآز
You know,
just a few months ago,
the doctor said
the chances of me
recovering my memory were almost zero.
And yet, it wasn't long
before I remembered everything.
Isn't that amazing?
Maybe your mom missed you.
She could never bear
to let you forget her.
ظآزAbout the choice I took most seriouslyظآز
ظآزNo matter how beautiful time is,
it still slips awayظآز
One day, I'll be just like you, Mom.
I'll learn about all kinds
of medicinal herbs
and help people get better.
ظآزA gentle cageظآز
Xiaoduo, one day,
you'll be even better than me.
Xiaoduo,
do you know why I
named you Xiaoduo?
Because Mom hoped
you would be like a little flower.
You don't have to shine the brightest,
but you must be resilient.
No matter whether life
brings storms or sunshine,
always be brave enough
to grow into
the person you're meant to be.
Ordinary, perhaps,
but one of a kind.
I'm your one-of-a-kind Xiaoduo.
Come here.
ظآزLove can barely move forwardظآز
ظآزYet the words still linger unspokenظآز
ظآزThe closeness I long forظآز
(Ye Lan. Time fades faces,
not a mother's love.)
ظآزThank you for these chains
called freedomظآز
Tell me,
when people die,
do they go somewhere else,
or do they disappear forever?
There's a saying.
It goes,
as long as someone
still remembers them in this world,
they never truly disappear.
Close your eyes.
Close them.
ظآزI'm with youظآز
ظآزCome with meظآز
Open them.
ظآزTake me to the new seasonظآز
ظآزI'm with youظآز
ظآزTake me pleaseظآز
ظآزTake me to the new seasonظآز
ظآزLet old regretsظآز
ظآزAnd future smilesظآز
ظآزBurn away without a traceظآز
ظآزI'm with youظآز
ظآزCome with meظآز
ظآزTake me to the new seasonظآز
ظآزI'm with youظآز
ظآزTake me pleaseظآز
ظآزTake me to the new seasonظآز
See?
You insisted on coming back here,
and now you're thinking about all those
painful memories again, right?
Don't be afraid.
I'm here.
I'll always be by your side.
Actually,
I'm not afraid of those memories.
It's just that I'm so happy now.
It all feels unreal.
I'm afraid that when I wake up,
I'll be back in that darkness again.
I'm afraid...
that the person you love
is the Ye Xiaoduo from your memories,
and not this Ye Xiaoduo,
broken and pieced back together again.
Whether it's Qiao Xiaomi
or Ye Xiaoduo,
they're just names.
You've always been yourself.
The only person I love
is you.
I want to hold an art exhibition.
I want everyone to see
the colors we once forgot
and the brilliance we found again.
Some losses are not the end,
but a new beginning.
Okay.
Who are you?
I'm Qin Yu.
I came back to marry you.
ظآزThat song suddenly came back to meظآز
I'm your fianc├ر.
ظآزWhy am I thinking of you again?ظآز
Okay.
Pinky promise.
ظآزI already told the whole world
that you meant nothing to meظآز
ظآزMy friends all laughed at meظآز
ظآزAsking why I couldn't move onظآز
ظآزBut how could they ever know
how wonderful you are?ظآز
Were you always this mean to me?
Of course.
Back then,
if you didn't listen,
I'd beat the crap out of you.
ظآزTossing and turningظآز
ظآزYou keep running through my mindظآز
I know what you're afraid of.
ظآزNothing matters more than youظآز
But I'm here.
ظآزWhat's wrong?ظآز
From now on,
you don't have to be afraid of anything.
ظآزYou are my only cureظآز
ظآزGive me one more hugظآز
I admit that since I came back,
sometimes you feel like a stranger.
So much so that
it's like I don't know you at all.
But other times,
you feel so familiar.
So familiar that
it's like you've never changed.
ظآزYou keep running through my mindظآز
ظآزNothing matters more than youظآز
ظآزWhat's wrong?ظآز
ظآزYou just walked out of my worldظآز
ظآزYou are my only cureظآز
ظآزGive me one more hugظآز
Even though
we both became someone else,
thankfully,
we're still the two people
who love each other.
We're still ourselves.
And we will
find our way back to ourselves.
(Qiao Zhiwei faced charges.
Chen Yue faced penalties.)
(Xu Yifei surrendered and assisted.
Qin Yu confessed. No charges filed.)
(Ye Xiaoduo regained her identity.
She resumed life under her real name.)
ظآزWe say good morning, we say good nightظآز
ظآزWe say we miss each other,
but never speak of the hurtظآز
ظآزThe sweeter it is, the luckier we seemظآز
ظآزYet the more romantic,
the rougher the roadظآز
ظآزLet me go, set me freeظآز
ظآزLet me drown in reckless silenceظآز
ظآزWe were perfect for each other,
yet you never admitted itظآز
ظآزThe freedom you gave meظآز
ظآزBecame the heaviest chain I bearظآز
ظآزLove can barely move forwardظآز
ظآزYet the words still linger unspokenظآز
ظآزThe closeness I long forظآز
ظآزThere's no need for you
to keep avoiding itظآز
ظآزI don't want to break freeظآز
ظآزTake back the chains
disguised as freedomظآز