[Alarm]
After losing him,
for me, every day
is like a repeating note.
This repetition
is like the eighth fret of the guitar,
a sound
that transitions after breaking.
Can a broken heart
restored?
[Smile After Tears]
[The eighth fret.
We're still where we are.]
Okay, next,
chemical energy.
For example, when a substance burns,
the burning substance produces
heat energy.
After we eat something,
it will have chemical changes in our body.
The energy stored
in the chemical structures
is called chemical energy.
I accidentally bought one more.
This is for you.
You can have it.
Thank you.
Junjia.
Do you want to go to
the basketball court with me after school?
I can teach you how to play basketball.
It feels good after exercising.
Watch out!
Why did you climb so high?
What if you...
What if I jump, right?
I'm fine.
Thank you.
This is my secret base.
Secret base?
Do you want to write the lyrics with me?
I want you to sing the verse,
and I'll do the chorus.
[Senior He,
I practiced the guitar well today.]
[Senior He, are you doing well?]
[Good morning, Senior He.
The weather is great today.]
[Senior, I'm so tired from work today.
I'm going to sleep now. Good night.]
[Senior He]
Thank you.
Hello, Mr. He.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
My wife
just fell asleep.
Come on, sit.
Sit down.
Ever since
Yankai passed away,
my wife has had insomnia.
I have to stay with her so she can sleep.
Yankai
called you Jiayi, right?
You must have been very important to him.
In his room,
he left something for you.
I fell asleep last night.
Why didn't you wake me up?
It was you who held my hand tightly.
Let my thoughts come to you
when I am gone,
like the afterglow of sunset
at the margin of starry silence.
When you turn around,
I'll wipe your tears.
I'll smile and say goodbye from afar.
[Smile After Tears]
♪ Watching you drown in sadness ♪
♪ In your tears ♪
♪ I wonder what love is ♪
Jiayi.
♪ It's when you're alone,
someone is by your side ♪
For this day,
it took me a lot of courage.
I hope
♪ It's when you're lost,
someone points out the right direction ♪
we can enjoy
every day.
♪ Though you have nothing,
you won't turn around ♪
[It's when you're alone,
someone is by your side]
After listening to your demo,
[It's when you're lost,
someone points out the right direction]
I composed this for you.
♪ But you are in midsummer ♪
♪ In spring flowers ♪
♪ In the aurora full of stars ♪
This guitar and pick
are for you.
♪ I can only wait for you ♪
I want to tell you
♪ I can't be afraid of you getting hurt ♪
[Smile After Tears]
that in this world,
[Hugging and hovering, only in dreams]
there is someone
who is always by your side,
♪ It reminds us that
freedom is also a cage ♪
♪ Between us ♪
putting you
♪ Repeating ♪
in the most important place.
That person
♪ After you turn around,
I'll wipe your tears ♪
is me.
♪ Hugging and hovering, only in dreams ♪
Jiayi.
[After you turn around,
I'll wipe your tears]
I love you.
♪ After you turn around,
I'll wipe your tears ♪
♪ Hugging and spinning,
in the room that doesn't exist♪
♪ Hope, hope again ♪
♪ You have no tears ♪
♪ I'll smile from afar, goodbye ♪
You're here.
You called us here in a hurry.
Did something happen?
He's gone.
What's the point of BACKSPACE?
Did you guys look at
the music score I sent yesterday?
That's He's final work.
I want to finish it.
And use the name BACKSPACE
[High School Hot Music]
in the competition.
Competition?
Sounds good.
And me.
I want to join, too.
Gu Yitong?
She is He's...
She is He's cousin.
Great.
Our band
is complete again.
Doesn't that mean
I can hit on her?
He,
we are back to our normal lives.
This time,
I'll study and live well
with thoughts of you in my heart.
We reorganized the band
and started to work hard
to finish the music you left behind.
Yitong became our manager.
She said
you didn't take good care of the band,
so she will take care of us for you.
And
don't worry,
I'm doing great.
At work,
I have Wei to chat with.
Secretly telling you,
Wei is dating someone now.
Even though you are gone,
it feels like
I'm moving every step forward
together with you.
I think
this is my reason to live.
[Houshan Coffee]
You don't have to treat me.
I should.
You taught me English so hard,
but my grades
haven't improved at all.
At least it's not as bad as before.
Passing is good enough.
Remaining stagnant is not okay.
It's like basketball.
If you keep dribbling in place,
eventually,
the ball will be stolen.
Dribbling in place is a strategy too.
You can wait for teammates to move,
and wait for the next chance.
I thought you didn't know
how to play basketball.
How do you know this?
I learned it from watching you play.
But
just like you said,
dribbling in place is also a strategy.
But if you keep waiting,
time will run out.
In the end,
you might get nothing.
So,
I don't want to waste time anymore.
I want to finish his work.
We've been practicing a lot lately.
It's just a small injury.
Let me see.
It's fine.
I'm a beginner too,
no need to worry about small cuts.
Look.
If it hurts,
why didn't you tell me?
That's it for today.
I'm heading back first.
Junjia.
What's wrong?
I'll walk you home.
It's fine.
Where's the strap?
I've replaced
the old strap.
Junjia.
I wanted to
fix it up,
so it'd be more comfortable to hold.
Where is the original one?
It looked a bit old,
so I threw it away.
You threw it away?
Why did you do that?
He gave that to me.
Now that it's gone,
do you know what that means?
Don't think you're helping me!
It's none of your business.
-I just want to help you.
-No need.
How can you help me?
Can you bring back the people I've lost?
Can you do that?
My dad.
My mom.
My uncle.
And now, He.
I'll never be able to
get those whom I've lost back.
I've worked all day.
But there is no hot water
for a shower in the home.
Zhang Junjia.
I'm talking to you.
We're out of gas.
Can't you just order it yourself?
Don't you usually handle it?
You didn't even tell me
we were out of gas.
I let you handle everything,
but this is what happened.
Can you stop talking?
What's your attitude?
Why do I have to carry everything?
Why do I have to do everything?
I never asked you to carry everything.
I just want you to learn to
handle things yourself.
As for rent, utilities and internet,
you can pay for them yourself.
You also know how to cook.
You can do everything.
Why do you think
I can do all this?
Do you think I like doing ti this way?
Your uncle passed away.
Your parents passed away too.
They left you to me!
I had to push through.
I make you pay the bills
and learn how to
take care of yourself because
I want you to be independent.
If I leave you someday,
you can keep going.
Why can they just leave like that,
and we have to keep going?
How else are we supposed to live?
Do you think I'm not tired?
Do you think I don't want to let go?
So,
am I the one making you so tired
and unable to let go?
If I were gone,
you wouldn't have to work so hard.
[Senior He]
No matter what happens,
I will always find you
in the midst of the crowds.
[Preview of the Next Episode]
As for what's bothering you,
just tell me whenever you are ready.
You can stay
as long as you want.
What are you doing?
No, no.
You can't tear that down.
Hey.
Don't tear it down.
Junjia.