This is…
How does the melody sound?
Is this music?
Just kidding.
The melody is pretty smooth,
especially the chorus.
It has a strong sense of imagery.
After what I told you last time,
I went home and got inspired,
so I wrote this melody.
You're so talented.
As expected of my good apprentice.
Since you said my melody
is so visual,
then,
do you want to write the lyrics with me?
I want you to sing the main section,
and I'll take the chorus.
Let's give it a try.
You even brought a guitar.
I borrowed it from the school.
I don't have my own.
When your fingertips press
the seventh fret of the guitar,
the sound suddenly
becomes very unfamiliar.
Could that be a new movement?
A heartbeat
doesn't short-circuit.
It should be…
A flutter.
Just take it.
Otherwise,
you'll get wet when you wait for the car.
Besides...
It's quite cold like this.
Senior!
Why are you so nice to me?
Senior,
taking care of me
makes me happy.
Taking care of you
feels the same to me.
Isn't this perfect?
There's a veterinary clinic ahead.
It might still be open.
Even if they're not by my side, it's okay.
At least
when I need them,
they are the ones
that I can see when I turn around.
They are in my heart.
That's enough.
Tell me.
What did I do wrong?
You did nothing wrong.
Then why are you avoiding me?
Because I fell for you.
We're going to the aquarium tomorrow.
Remember to dress up a bit.
[The Seventh Fret:
A Voice No Longer Familiar]
Auntie,
I'm heading out.
It's nothing.
I'll be home a bit late today.
Bye.
[Hello Ms. Chen Ruojiu, your endowment
insurance policy is about to mature.]
[xpark]
Put your hands like this.
Lean forward,
like me.
Look, we move when they move.
I don't think they're going to move.
Let's go.
No.
Then let's waddle over like penguins.
You go first.
Okay.
You have to keep up with me.
Okay, I'll keep up with you.
Why didn't you learn?
Go.
There's something over there.
There's something else over there.
-Hurry up and learn with me.
-There's something else over there.
There's something else over there.
So cute. Look.
You're cute too.
Just as cute.
There's another one over there.
Hello.
Excuse me.
I just saw that you two
seem to have a good relationship.
We have a couple's wishing event.
Would you like to join?
We're not...
Sure.
Just treat it as a game.
Don't overthink it.
Okay.
Now hold hands,
close your eyes,
and silently
make a wish
in your heart.
Okay.
Open your eyes.
I'll take a photo of this moment for you.
Your wishes
and your love will all come true.
[Heartbeats and Underwater Shadows]
Aren't you curious
about what I just wished for?
No.
Wishes should be kept
in the bottom of your heart.
And I believe
they will definitely come true.
Was it something like
getting first place in exams
or traveling around the world?
Of course not.
My wish is...
I'm not going to tell you.
This is for you.
You keep this for now.
This is
our first photo together.
Oh, right.
This is our first photo together.
You keep this for now.
From now on,
all the rest are mine.
Okay.
I'll take this one first.
The rest from now on are all yours.
Be careful.
[Good Friends Guitar Instrument Store]
[You have a new message]
Okay.
What do you mean by that?
Wait for me here.
I'll be right back.
So mysterious.
Boss.
Welcome.
Where is this?
I'm not...
This is the boundary
between life and death.
You can call it
the Six Gates.
Everyone dies,
but only those with unresolved wishes
and lingering regrets
end up here.
So what you're saying is
I'm dead?
[Smile After Tears]
[Alarm Clock]
Morning.
[Maybe it's because you're
in your senior year of high school]
[The club has been
on break these past few days]
[I still work part-time every night]
[And I told you]
[Wei is dating someone again]
I bought you a new wrist wrap.
Change it if you want.
Junjia.
Morning.
You didn't
ride your bike today.
It's broken.
We are surrounded by the sea.
There are sandy coasts and rocky coasts.
Do you know the difference between them?
The wrist wrap you gave me is badly worn.
I've been reluctant
to ride my bike lately.
Junjia,
why are you here?
Senior,
I'm sorting through
photos of his favorite, Galu.
Tie
has already taken several days off
because he is so sad.
What about you?
Just like this.
You know
what that guy is like.
Moody, unpredictable.
He does whatever he wants.
No one can stop him.
He.
Well…
-I mean
-He just got here. He doesn't know.
everybody out.
Okay.
From now on,
you are our guitarist.
How long are you planning
to keep practicing like this?
Then I'll drink
this one.
That's mine,
not yours.
Even...
Even now that he's gone,
he didn't say goodbye.
No.
I know
He has always been by our side.
[Learning has no end]
The last word is describe.
Come on, read after me.
Describe.
Good.
It's a verb.
He,
I often see you standing here
and spacing out.
Is this your favorite scenery?
Be careful.
What are you doing here?
It's dangerous.
Come down.
Why did you climb so high?
-What if you...
-What if I jump?
I'm not kidding.
Do you know it's dangerous?
Then you know
that I'm not that fragile.
But
once something happens,
there's no turning back.
In terms of many things,
we don't have a second chance.
I'm fine.
Let's go.
Class is starting.
Welcome.
Are you
Jiayi?
I didn't come to find you.
Do you know
you're very happy?
Every time I meet He,
all he ever talks about is you.
"Jiayi
rushed the beat again
at band practice today."
"Jiayi is really good at ordering drinks."
"Jiayi is always smiling.
Doesn't his mouth get tired?"
Every time school comes up,
you were the only one
he ever talked about.
He really
liked you a lot.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Wait.
Don't tell me
you actually believe those school rumors?
You didn't do anyone wrong,
and you didn't do my brother wrong.
Your brother?
He...
He's my cousin.
Then why does everyone
at school say you two are...
There's a reason for that.
Gu Yitong!
What's going on now?
I...
You're Jin Xianzuo?
Who are you?
I'm her boyfriend.
What are you doing?
What are you saying?
Gu Yitong is my girlfriend.
What do you want?
You didn't answer my calls;
I couldn't find you!
What do you want exactly?
Yitong,
I was wrong.
I shouldn't have hit you.
Let's make up, okay?
She doesn't have to answer you.
This has nothing to do with her.
Talk to me if you have something to say.
So you're cheating on me now?
Or are you dumping me?
Enough, Jin Xianzuo!
Gu Yitong is mine.
With an ex-boyfriend like you,
she's better off without you.
Stop hitting him!
Go away!
To gather evidence,
my brother didn't even fight back.
Psycho!
But that day,
I also found out
that my brother was sick.
Let's go to the hospital.
You didn't know?
I can't believe he didn't tell you.
It seems
he must have given
a lot of happiness and joy
to you.
My brother smiled a lot
during that time.
Thank you,
Jiayi.
It seems
he must've shared a lot of
his happiness and joy with you.
My brother smiled a lot
during that time.
Familiar smiles.
Familiar figures.
They left all their joy and happiness
to me.
[Heartbeats and Underwater Shadows]
But
in the end,
I couldn't hold on to any of them.
I've already experienced loss.
Now, facing loss again,
I realized
that what hurts more than death
is having to keep living.
Are you saying
that I'm dead?
How is that possible?
Are you kidding me?
Jiayi is still waiting for me.
I can't die.
I can't.
Jiayi.
[Preview of the Next Episode]
Those whom I've lost,
I will never be able to get them back.
Your uncle passed away.
Your parents passed away too.
They left you with me!
If I were gone,
you wouldn't have to work so hard.
[Senior He,
I practiced the guitar well today.]
[Senior He, how are things with you?]
[Good morning, Senior He.
The weather is great today.]
[Senior, I'm so tired from work today.
I'm going to sleep now. Good night.]
[Senior He]