Why is Punlop targeting you?
Can you just leave me alone? Let go!
Tell me the truth. How is 3C Corp.
planning to release the pathogen?
Punlop…
killed your father.
Remember this.
If Rin ever finds out, you're dead!
We need to talk.
I have nothing to say to you.
Then we don't have to talk.
I'm not letting you go anywhere.
If you want to throw a tantrum,
why not do it in your own room?
This isn't your room either!
I wish Taiga could see you
acting like a mad dog right now.
You think I'm the only mad dog here?
Do you know who Taiga is with right now?
Do you know who's in his house,
in his room, in his bed? Who?
- Rin.
- Speechless, huh?
You love asking men for help, don't you?
"I want this, I want that."
Someone who didn't even ask
got straight into the house.
Rin.
Taiga is with Rin.
Rin, are you okay?
Okay, Aru. We're talking here.
Techut admitted
that Fire Phoenix created the pathogen
because they want to sell
the medicine and the vaccine.
Rin.
You're not a bad person.
Help me stop this.
I can't help you right now.
Punlop is targeting you.
Everyone you care about
is in danger right now, both Aru and Sun.
I know you're sick.
You need me to protect you.
What? I said it's canceled. Hello?
Hello?
PUNLOP
There's no negotiation, Taiga.
Have Rin give me her father's hard drive
in exchange for Ratee's life.
That's mine!
What's on this?
Punlop wants this hard drive.
Otherwise, Ratee dies!
I underestimated a pretty girl like you.
When I reviewed all the cameras,
I saw that you helped Dhammatat.
You bought up 3C Corp. shares.
You knew it was a nominee, rigged stocks,
and laundered money for Fire Phoenix.
The 3C pathogen would make
your father insanely rich
and put the entire economy
under your control.
Does Taiga know
what you're thinking
and what you're going to do?
With that face,
- it means…
- How many million?
Huh?
How many millions do you want?
To spare Taiga's life?
Yes, I'll pay you right now.
How many million?
Would a hundred million be enough?
If you overestimate yourself,
you'll end up just a servant,
working for someone else until you die.
Not someone who gives orders,
not someone who wields money as power.
And if you kill Taiga,
I'll use everything my father has,
money, influence,
to destroy your life,
until you wish you were dead.
Punlop's trying to kill you
because this hard drive
holds Fire Phoenix's secrets.
Stay here until I get back.
Wait.
Take it and help your girl.
Save Ratee's life.
I know you're not a weak woman.
You've always been stronger
than anyone else.
You don't have to force yourself.
I'll make Ratee understand…
that I love a woman who tried to kill me.
I love her without ever thinking
about the end.
Everything has an end.
For me,
happiness doesn't last forever.
Help Ratee, the one who loves you.
Taiga.
What about my niece?
This is all you want, isn't it?
Rin handed it over so easily.
Love really does make people stupid.
Let Ratee go.
Ratee!
Taiga!
Don't worry about me.
Go catch him, quickly!
Get over here.
Let go! I have to get Punlop.
But he will kill you.
I know you're worried,
but I have to handle this myself.
Don't go, Rin! Let Khanin go after him.
Rin!
Shit.
Mr. Naruban.
Rin sent us to help.
All cameras are off.
We've got three minutes.
The guards and workers have been sedated.
Then hurry.
We'll get you somewhere safe.
What are you doing to Mr. Naruban?
Let's go.
Are you okay, my dear?
Ugh.
Dad!
Dad.
Uncle Punlop must pay for shooting you.
I'm going to do the work
you gave your life for.
I'll go after Damon myself.
I'll take down Fire Phoenix for you.
You can't even watch over one person.
Send a letter to the shareholders
and the board,
saying Mr. Naruban is in a coma
and I'll take over.
Anyone who disagrees, report to me.
Aren't we having a board meeting?
Alright, no meeting.
I'll quickly email everyone.
Within one hour. Anyone with an issue,
give me their names.
Yes.
This is all the evidence Phumin collected…
…on Fire Phoenix.
NARUBAN - CEO 3C
GIRANUN, TECHUT, NUNNAPAT
PRIN - DEAD, SABAIPRAE - DEAD
POK - UNFOUND, PRAB - UNFOUND
PUN - UNFOUND
Punlop's probably scared of being exposed.
But at this rate,
he won't stay quiet,
neither Punlop nor Damon.
Force them out of hiding.
And we'll unmask them.
NARUMIT - BROTHER, CAR CRASH, DISABLED
Rin's hunting Punlop just like us.
Will Rin help you?
Even if she doesn't,
I'm sure she won't get in our way again.
Please, Khanin.
Don't hurt Rin.
Fine.
But remember, Taiga.
Your past and your family,
Phumin protected them with his life.
Don't let good people die
in vain.
Board member Surachet was in a car crash
this morning and is in a coma.
As for Lady Ploy,
a major shareholder,
her mansion caught fire.
She was trapped inside and inhaled smoke.
She's not doing well.
Her heart stopped once already.
Both of them
are against you
taking over for Mr. Naruban.
They've emailed the other board members,
saying they'll oppose you to the fullest.
You think I'd kill anyone
who disagrees with me?
I've worked for a long time.
I'm ready to serve you, Mrs. Giranun,
just like I devoted myself to Mr. Naruban.
Very good.
From now on, you're mine.
Report everything from 3C Corp. to me,
when I'm not at work.
Yes.
Thank you so much
for handling
those two ridiculous board members.
But Taiga still hasn't shown up
at 3C Corp.
I'll have Nun check again.
I need to find Rin too.
While you're tracking them down,
I want you to move in here.
Bring your people so they can help guard.
Okay.
I'll overhaul the entire
security system as well.
Once we find Taiga
and Rin, we'll find Naruban too,
since they're working together.
When that happens,
take care of all of them.
Anyone who helps, eliminate them.
I'm sick of them.
Okay.
You already know who you are, don't you?
That's why you came here.
Inspector Phumin's files
say the gunman who killed my family
was one of your older brother
Narumit's workers.
All the gunmen have been dealt with.
My brother didn't know anything
about the gunman.
On the day Prin died,
he saved one boy.
My younger brother?
I'm not sure.
But Narumit said
the boy was left in front of the farm.
He was in shock,
couldn't remember anything.
Feeling sorry for him,
he raised him until he grew up.
Indhorn?
I had a gut feeling
ever since Narumit's car accident.
It was around the same time news came out
that Fire Phoenix
found the three children of Prin.
Then the leader of the Yakuza gang,
the Blazing Tiger, was killed.
Dad Kenji died because of me.
Now Fire Phoenix is hunting
the three of us siblings.
Calm down, Taiga.
I believe your two younger brothers
are still safe.
But the moment
you give Fire Phoenix confidence
and confirm your brothers' identities,
they'll be in immediate danger.
Here's the medicine.
Here you go.
I tried giving these to the workers.
They got better.
This medicine really works.
It can cure the disease, right?
Yes.
My workers who were sick with Ms. Rin
took it continuously for months.
Their bodies got better,
breathing easier, and less tired.
Exactly!
Rin gets tired easily
and once mentioned bleeding.
It's probably because
of the anti-pathogen medicine.
Then should we try giving Ms. Rin
the medicine?
It's natural, no chemicals.
It can fight the pathogens and vaccines.
I'll bring it over.
On the day Prin died,
he saved one boy.
I just came from Mr. Naruban's farm,
so I stopped by here.
I'll head back to the farm.
I've got some business.
Okay.
I need to see Rin, Aru.
Rin usually contacts us herself,
like when we helped Mr. Naruban.
Mr. Indhorn also wants
to give Rin the medicine,
but I don't know how to reach her.
Right now,
how sick is Rin?
I know you're worried about Rin.
We love Rin, and we're worried too.
But whatever we can do now,
we have to do it fast.
My son and I don't know
where the pathogen was stored.
I really don't know.
Is there any way
to force Fire Phoenix to act?
If 3C Corp. is a nominee
laundering money for Fire Phoenix,
we should strike there.
Don't let my employees
get caught up in this.
They're not part of anyone's grudge.
Then who is Damon?
Not me.
And no one knows.
Damon's identity has never been revealed.
We have to lure Damon out,
tear off that mask.
No one else should suffer
because of their greed.
Nun, I need to talk.
The purchase volume, the investment
in 3C-Coin, it's plummeting,
even though 3C-Coin
is backed by its reputation.
Why is this happening?
It used to be fine.
But after news of Dad's illness
and you taking over management,
people lost confidence.
Then restore their confidence.
You can do that, right?
Credibility isn't built in a day.
We should hold off on the coin for now.
No. We won't stop anything.
We must get as many people as possible
to invest in our coin.
We'll change the world with our coin.
Our coin will have value,
backed by gold, and tied to the US Dollar.
We'll collect as much cash
as possible from coin sales.
I've already set a target, a billion.
What about the returns?
If the coin can't actually be used,
isn't that just tricking people
into investing
and giving us money for free?
People holding our coin
will get the right to buy shares
in the pharma and vaccine factories.
We'll make the best medicine and vaccines
to protect ourselves.
Medicine? Medicine or pathogens?
So it's you, the one helping your dad,
helping Techut.
Mom, stop!
You're doing something wrong.
Let go!
Weren't you going to do as I ordered?
I can do anything,
but I won't kill my own family.
You have to choose.
You want to win,
to prove yourself, don't you?
Yes, but not with him getting in the way!
How is he any better than Dad
that you'd be foolish enough
to let him use you?
I'll take care of your daughter.
Calm down, okay?
Mom!
Let me go! Let go!
I said let me go!
How's Mr. Naruban?
He's okay.
But are you okay? Where are you now?
The less you know,
the safer you'll be, Aru.
Take care of yourself.
Tell Sun and Dhammatat too.
Hey, Mr. Taiga came to the farm.
He checked on Mr. Naruban,
then went to Mr. Indhorn's farm.
Don't let Taiga know you can contact me.
Don't stay alone anymore.
Lee.
Whatever you do next, let me know.
That's it for now, Aru.
Take care of yourself.
Lee, don't hang up yet! Lee!
Aru.
Where's Lee?
Can you not ask, Sun?
I can't.
I can't say anything.
But Lee is our friend, Aru.
Do everything you can, Sun.
Finish 3C Corp. and Fire Phoenix
once and for all.
Then our friend Lee
can return to her normal life.
Any progress from the two farms?
Mr. Naruban and Techut are safe.
What about Rin?
What are you going to do, Taiga?
Find her as fast as possible.
If you don't find her,
you'll keep looking?
I'm confident Rin can help us.
If there's anything I can help with,
just tell me.
3C Corp. is my responsibility.
Taiga, I'll continue the investigation.
Fire Phoenix has several safe houses.
If we're going in,
we need to block all escape routes.
If we're lucky,
we might find Rin lurking nearby.
The one who reopened your family's case
was Inspector Phumin.
He has a daughter.
She's the one who inherited
everything from her father.
Hard drive
from Inspector Phumin.
She just found out that her father
was shot by Fire Phoenix.
Are you telling me
that Rin is Inspector Phumin's daughter?
Yes.
I just confirmed it.
Rin had a plan all along.
She wasn't fooled by Fire Phoenix.
She went along with them
to use Punlop to get to Damon.
But she only just realized it was Punlop
who killed her father.
I'm the one at fault
for only telling her now.
Help Rin, Taiga.
Don't let anything happen to her
like her father.
Rin.
You can't take out Punlop on your own.
Come back to me.
We'll take down our revenge together.
Dad.
We'll see each other soon.
I will finally be with you.
3C-Coin is crashing again.
Who's trying to bring it down?
Damon called an urgent meeting.
Welcome, members of Fire Phoenix.
This is the most important meeting,
the one where Fire Phoenix
will change the world.
Fire Phoenix
will have its own nation,
built on our coin.
From now on, every command in the world
will depend on Fire Phoenix.
I will change the world with our coin.
Every country will have to use
the same currency.
Our coin will have value in the system,
usable in online casinos
or to buy the newest,
most advanced weapons.
Our coin will be asset-backed by gold
and equal in value to the US Dollar.
We won't stop anything.
We must get as many people as possible
to invest in our coin.
We'll change the world with our coin.
Our coin will have value,
backed by gold, and tied to the US Dollar.
We'll collect as much cash as possible
from coin sales.
I've already set a target, a billion.
The pathogen war
will make our coin
as valuable as human life.
Fire Phoenix will lock down
the entire world,
controlling every country
with biological weapons.
Equality and justice
must prevail.
Equality! Justice!
Equality!
Hey.
Ratee, help me!
I've been captured in the house.
Come save me!
Taiga!
Calm down, Taiga!
Damon won't come out again.
We've already lost our best chance.
But we still have 3C Corp.
Yes. I can still get in there.
Even if Giranun blocks me, I have ways.
There are many who don't agree
with Giranun taking over for Mr. Naruban.
I'll bring them over, pressure 3C Corp.
to stop being a money-laundering front
for Fire Phoenix.
Push them from every angle.
But the key question is,
where is the pathogen now?
It's Damon's final card.
If he releases it, it's over.
Naruban and Techut don't know.
But Ms. Nun might.
She could find a lead for us.
Ms. Nun is safe now.
Dhammatat sent a message.
She's on her way to Mr. Naruban's farm.
Good.
We need to take away
all of Damon's leverage.
You said you'd upgraded
the security system.
How could Taiga get to Nun?
If I wasn't in the building today
and if I'd been here?
- You were at 3C Corp. today?
- Yes.
Didn't go anywhere?
Yes. Why?
I'm wondering,
where did the pathogen Techut created go?
Who's keeping it?
Do you have any idea
where your son would store
something this important?
I don't know.
Based on what Ms. Nun said the other day,
is it possible it's at 3C Corp.?
If the pathogen is a weapon
that can destroy our enemies,
why not put it to use for our benefit?
- Unless you're worried about your husband.
- I want him dead!
And for you,
Naruban deserved to die
a long time ago, right?
You can't die.
Don't sacrifice yourself alone.
You still have me.
Let me die alone, Taiga.
Then you can be with the woman
who loves you.
Fire Phoenix is finding a way
to release the pathogen.
Release it at their own event?
Goodbye, you foul-mouthed kid.
Hope you die happily.
Whoa!
Subtitle translation by:
Chomchanach Yanaharn