Hello?
So it was you
who helped your dad and Techut.
We have to lure Damon out and unmask him.
The virus is a weapon
that can destroy our enemies,
so why don't we use it to our advantage?
NARUBAN AND THE NEXT STEP OF 3C
Our company got scammed!
The CEO here, his name's Narubodee.
He stole our money and gave it to his son,
that bastard, Naruban.
Dad! Mom!
Take good care of yourself, Giranun.
Your dad and I really have to do this.
- Mom!
- Giranun!
Remember,
take your revenge.
Make sure they fall like us!
Dad, don't. Please don't do this.
Don't leave me.
Go after Naruban!
Dad!
Dad…
My parents killed themselves
because of your family.
It's time you paid
for their lives with yours,
Naruban.
I've tried every way
and everything to get close to you,
Naruban.
Nun.
Nun, what's wrong?
Nun!
Why are you all bruised up?
What's wrong? What happened?
Mom captured me.
Giranun captured you?
She chooses Punlop over her own family.
How could she do this to our family?
What? Nun!
It's my fault.
I never cared about anyone's feelings.
All I did was give orders.
I've been so self-centered.
Even when I teach you,
I teach you to exploit others
and to be selfish.
That's why our home doesn't feel like one.
It feels more like hell.
Nun.
Te.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for putting your lives at risk.
And I'm sorry for raising you so poorly.
I've been a horrible son.
I kept causing you trouble.
Listen.
I'll help Taiga.
We need to stop the virus.
Dad.
I'll testify to expose Fire Phoenix
as a secret society.
At 3C, we've laundered money for them
for far too long.
Secret society?
Fire Phoenix ordered us to create a virus.
Dad.
If you talk about the virus,
you'll go to jail.
And you'll die in jail.
I need to take responsibility for it.
My word carries the most weight.
It can be used as evidence.
No way, Dad.
You can't go to jail.
I will testify that I made
all the decisions on my own
and that the executives at 3C had no idea.
No way.
We can't let you go to jail.
Right, Te? Right?
There's got to be another way, Dad.
Let's find another way.
Please?
Can you give me a hug?
Thank you, honey.
Thank you for worrying
about a horrible dad like me.
This area is being turned
into an entertainment complex.
The payback period
won't take more than two years.
You're really talented, Ms. Giranun.
It's hard to believe
you're new to real estate.
Okay, I want to invest with you.
But I want to be the majority shareholder.
I want to invest
with you too, Ms. Giranun.
If you're investing, don't forget
to ask Fire Phoenix to help you.
They can handle anything for you.
What is Fire Phoenix?
What? You really don't know them?
Just mention their name,
and all the big shots are intimidated.
Fire Phoenix's leader, called Damon,
is being replaced.
The new leader has to have it all.
Money, power, and connections.
Then, in order to have it all,
you can't just be someone ordinary.
Yes.
The next Damon has to be
a businessman in IT
who's skilled, rich,
famous, and promising.
Naruban Asawawong.
I tried everything to get you to marry me.
But it turned out you're not Damon.
Fortunately, luck was on my side.
It allowed me to destroy your 3C
even further.
The leader of Fire Phoenix
can rule the world
or destroy anyone.
Die, old man.
I will be the new leader of Fire Phoenix.
Now, I'll start my revenge on you,
Naruban!
I'll make sure you die
in front of the 3C building,
just like how you made my parents die.
If you talk about the virus,
you'll go to jail,
and you'll die in jail.
Prin.
Chanchai.
I'm getting my karma now.
They must be together somewhere,
and they're targeting this place.
Where else could Naruban be hiding?
If my guess is correct,
he's got to be at a farm.
Either his farm
or his brother's farm nearby.
Then, I'll send my men to make sure first,
then we'll deal with them.
I really appreciate you and your friends
for helping my family.
Right now, only your mother
is still at 3C.
How could I possibly stop my mom?
She has the virus.
We need to steal it as soon as possible.
Is there any way we can do that?
I…
I really can't think of anything.
My mom might've moved it somewhere else.
Mr. Indhorn said there's a suspicious man
driving around the farm.
Could it be one of Punlop's men?
I think so.
You and your family need to stay here.
Don't go anywhere.
Mr. Indhorn will send workers we can trust
to help take care of you.
Sure.
How can we possibly stop your mom?
If she's willing to poison her own son,
she's probably got no love left.
Nun, is there anyone at 3C
who can still keep us posted?
I'm organizing a promo for the Hi app.
But you said the project was shelved?
Well, I just changed my mind.
And where's Ms. Nun?
She came up with the idea.
She's been removed.
Why?
It's my orders. Don't ask questions.
You shouldn't have an issue with it.
You're an outsider, after all.
You don't even work here.
Although I don't work here, I also matter.
After all, I hold
almost as many shares as you.
What's up, Atinuch?
Mr. Ryu Dragon's agency just confirmed
he can do the Hi app's promo.
He can fly here
for a promo shoot tomorrow.
This is none of your business.
Please leave.
I want him to do a promo video
somewhere outside.
I'll pick the location myself.
No objections.
Listen to my orders for everything.
Of course.
Yes, Aunt Giranun?
Indhorn, can I ask you a favor?
I want to shoot my promo video
at your farm.
My farm?
Yes. It'll take just one day.
There'll also be a foreign idol
who's a guest at 3C.
Sure, Aunt Giranun.
I really appreciate it.
I'll have my secretary
follow up with you on this.
Okay.
Ryu Dragon will allow us
to search the farm,
both Naruban's farm
and Narumit's farm that's nearby.
We're just hunting Naruban down.
You didn't have to use
Ryu Dragon as an excuse,
not to mention the Hi app's debut.
Well, I wanted to mess with their heads,
and the best decoy is the virus.
Are you really spreading the virus?
No.
It's not time yet.
Fire Phoenix is looking for a way
to spread the virus.
They'd spread the virus
at their own event?
That'd be far too suspicious.
Lots of people will be infected
before it's even detected.
And then, they'll make a profit
selling the vaccines and the cure.
We need to hurry and steal the virus.
If you enter the 3C building now,
you'll end up getting shot
before finding the virus.
I can get you inside.
I just don't know
where they're hiding the virus.
Naruban's office.
Too simple.
Well, if it's simple, it goes unnoticed.
I'll go too.
Don't. The more people we bring,
the higher the risk.
I'll go with Ratee.
Be careful once you're inside.
If you don't find anything, leave quickly.
Right now, 3C is the most dangerous place.
The virus is at 3C?
Come on, look harder.
My ring didn't cost just three or four
hundred thousand. It's worth a million.
Rin!
Why the hell is she making us
find a ring at this hour?
Yeah. How are we supposed to find it?
Exactly.
What are you doing here?
- What are you doing here?
- The virus is hidden here.
- Well, have you found it?
- Not yet.
You're looking for
both the virus and Punlop,
the man who murdered your father.
How did you know?
You're Inspector Phumin's daughter.
Rin, you and I share the same goal.
We want to take Fire Phoenix down.
We can help each other.
You need to stay alive.
Don't sacrifice your life.
You still have me.
Taiga. Taiga,
are you around here somewhere?
Taiga, let's leave.
The cameras are turning back on.
Let's leave now.
You need to stay alive.
Don't sacrifice your life.
You still have me.
The cameras are turning back on.
Let's leave now.
Let me die alone, Taiga,
so you can be with the woman
who loves you.
The virus will rule the world.
People's lives will cost as much
as I want it to be.
Thanks.
The hell are you doing?
You've gone too far!
All of you need to leave. Get out.
They're my team. Are you the owner here?
I'm the owner here.
Look, do me a favor.
Wrap up the shoot in an hour.
No way. I'm here to do my job,
so I need to do my best.
An hour isn't enough.
Then, forget about shooting here.
Before you leave,
I'd like to search every car
and everyone on your team.
No.
Guys, I'm heading to the set now.
Scoot over.
But that's a bomb.
Obviously.
If you want money,
I can send it to you right now.
I don't want money.
Scoot over.
Quick.
Why would you want to kill me?
Who hired you?
Just scoot over.
Quick!
Hey, why don't we just go out
and see for ourselves?
I told you, we can't!
If the virus is spread outside,
at least we'll be safe in here.
Aru!
- It's Sun.
- Aru!
How's everything? Is everyone okay?
How are things outside?
No virus has been spread yet.
I know you don't want to die.
But it can't be helped.
It just so happened you're here with them.
If you have a problem with someone,
just go deal with them.
Don't just pick random fights.
It's awful. Skilled people
wouldn't do this.
Either way, I'm more skilled than you,
and I'm smarter than you.
You little baby.
So long, smart-mouth.
Rest in peace.
It went according to plan.
Taiga and everyone is here.
They thought we'd spread the virus
while Ryu Dragon is here.
Please make sure everything's sorted out.
Of course. I assure you,
everything will be sorted out.
The van driver isn't part of my team.
He said if I move,
the bomb will go off.
Run as fast as you can.
Go.
- I'll call the cops.
- It'll be too late.
Listen to me, Ryu.
Listen carefully.
We'll risk it.
Stand up as I count.
You've got five seconds
before it goes off.
Get up and run as far as you can.
You've got this.
You two, back off!
I'm right here, Ryu. Let's go together.
I told you to back off! Go!
We'll sprint away together.
Don't be afraid.
Listen to me carefully, Ryu.
I'll say it once again.
I'll count from one to three.
One,
two,
go!
Go!
Are you okay? Are you?
What the hell is going on?
You're lucky you're even safe.
Easy for you to say.
I deserve to know
what almost took my life.
Relax. Can we talk somewhere else?
Why can't we talk here?
Because if the bomber returns,
we're all dead!
You can't just stand here
asking such silly questions.
What was that noise?
An explosion.
Narumit's farm?
Sun, stay here. I'll go see Taiga.
I had public health professionals
check around here.
They didn't find any virus.
They weren't planning to spread it here.
What virus?
Mr. Indhorn,
lock down the farm for now
so Mr. Narumit and everyone can stay safe.
Got it.
I'm going to see Mr. Naruban.
Don't walk away from me.
Tell me. What's going on here?
Why do I have to risk my life
in this place?
- It's nothing.
- No, it's not. Take some responsibility.
Let me explain.
We suspect that someone's
spreading a virus here,
and our farm is in trouble.
Yet you want me to shoot here?
Does 3C know about this?
3C was the one who asked to shoot here.
Taiga, Taiga.
Khanin.
Ryu Dragon. An idol from Hong Kong.
Hong Kong?
I don't have time for your stare.
If you keep going quiet on me
and I don't get any answers,
I won't leave this farm.
And I'll tell the police.
Mr. Ryu,
why don't you go shower?
Come on, follow me.
Go.
I'll tell you everything later.
- Tell me now.
- Not right now!
What is it, Khanin?
Please make yourself at home.
No one's here.
My parents are in Bangkok
for a doctor's appointment.
Thanks.
You seem like a good guy.
Thank you.
So who do you think is the bad guy here?
The maniac who drove the van, of course.
I'm sorry for everything
that happened today.
It's not your fault.
Why are you apologizing?
I'm apologizing as the owner of this farm.
Sorry for giving you bad memories
about this place.
I want you to see this place
in a new light.
My farm
welcomes you to be here privately.
You can come over anytime.
We'll treat you as a VIP guest.
If you'll excuse me.
Hello?
I'm fine.
Tell everyone to tighten the security
at the entrances and exits.
And don't forget to tell the locals nearby
to look for the van driver.
Naruban said Indhorn's adopted.
Were you the one who left
my brother in front of the farm?
Yes.
I brought your younger brother
and left him here
because I had to hurry and find you.
I saw a woman who worked here
carry your brother and walk into the farm.
At least, it made me certain
that he won't die.
But when I came looking for him again,
everyone said he'd left the farm.
A family among the workers
had adopted him and moved out.
But I never expected…
that Narumit would help cover up
the kid's background
and raise your brother like his own son.
Indhorn…
Indhorn's my brother?
What about my youngest brother, Khanin?
You saved him, and where did you put him?
As for your youngest brother,
I left him in the care
of Sabaiprae's older sister.
Your mother, Sabaiprae, is half Hong Kong.
Her older sister's
a famous celebrity named Wei Bozhi.
After I heard that she left the industry,
she just disappeared.
I tried my hardest,
but I couldn't find her.
Ryu Dragon is from Hong Kong.
If he's my brother…
See, Taiga?
You have to do whatever you can
so that you, Indhorn, and Ryu Dragon
take a DNA test at the same time.
That way, you can be sure
that you three are brothers.
Not now, Khanin.
I can't put my brothers' lives
on the line.
Why?
If Fire Phoenix can confirm
the identity of both my brothers,
they'll hunt them down like they used to.
You're right. Once we've dealt
with Damon, it'll all be over.
The three of you will be safe,
and you won't have to cover up anything.
That damn Damon's
destroyed my family once.
I won't let him touch my brothers.
Someone's there.
- Here you go, Mr. Ryu.
- Thank you.
Ryu!
Who are your parents?
Hey, why ask about my background
all of a sudden?
You can look me up. I'm not just some guy.
On social media,
it only says
your mother's a living legend.
Wei Bozhi.
But it doesn't say who your father is.
Why are you even curious about my father?
You may know as much
as I want to share with you.
You're an outsider,
yet you're asking about
my personal matters? Learn some manners.
We're not just being rude here.
We have reasons.
Taiga just wants to warn you.
About what?
Watch your back.
- Make sure your family's safe.
- Why?
Safe from what? From who?
You experienced it firsthand.
You know how dangerous it is.
Think I'd be scared
just from what you said?
Well, we can't say much else yet
until everything's sorted out.
When the day comes,
you'll get to know everything you need to.
My life is mine alone.
Absolutely no one can poke their nose
into my business.
Mr. Ryu,
you should shower
and get changed right away.
I'll have my driver
drive you to the airport.
If you'll excuse me.
Taiga.
One day, they'll both find out
just how much
their older brother loves them
Don't do it!
Well done, Giranun.
From now on, I am Damon.
If being brothers means we're all dead,
I'd rather be alone.
Crap! Duck!
Mrs. Giranun told me to tell you
she's taking leave
to look after her husband.
If you have no business here,
leave the room.
Subtitle translation by:
Ramil Natnitiwitaya