Dream.
I wish I could dream of you...
I don’t think I can sing.
Try a little more, Mai.
Just a bit more.
I know my little brother can do it.
Are you saying I’m not trying hard enough?
No.
That’s not what I meant.
I believe you can do it
if you put in more effort.
So I’m not putting in enough effort?
No, that’s not it.
Forget it.
I’m done.
I’m not debuting.
I guess this is as far as my dream goes.
You should open your own music label
and debut some artists.
Don’t waste your time on me.
Sorry, I wasn’t looking.
I’m really sorry.
It’s okay.
I wasn’t paying attention.
Well,
are you auditioning for Ultimate Wolf too?
Mhm.
Hello, bro.
Alright, I’ll help you.
He looks familiar.
It’s like we’ve met before.
He’s quite good looking.
If he joined our group,
he’d be the visual.
More like the vicious.
He annoys me.
Hey, Yu.
You said the car was almost here.
Where is it?
It’s almost here.
There it is.
It’s here.
Come this way.
A rescue vehicle?
Yeah.
Cutter is in bad shape,
so I called them.
No one will want to be in our group anymore.
Isn’t it pretty unique?
Maybe we can appear on The Ghost show.
Let’s go.
Not a contract.
I had Sean prepare mascot costumes.
Four of them.
You’ll perform on Children’s Day
at Wat Yai Nong Khai School.
Hm.
Whoa.
Damn.
Hm.
Not a contract.
Hey, bro.
What happened last night?
Why did I dream about doing yoga?
What yoga? Bruh.
You were so wasted,
but Yu took care of you.
Otherwise, you would’ve been a mess.
Cantaloupe, my baby.
Don’t talk to him. He hasn’t showered.
He smells terrible.
Damn, you're right.
Take some, Cutter. It’ll help with your hangover.
Whoa, thank you.
You know me so well.
Ow!
Ah! Ahh! It’s hot!
Why didn’t you warn me?
If I burn my tongue, how am I gonna rap?
And it’s mala flavor. My tongue is getting numb.
Hey, guys.
I’m wondering.
Is Boss really making us wear mascot costumes?
If we really have to wear it, can I be the purple one?
That one looks pretty and expensive.
Haha.
The purple one?
Don’t be kidding.
You’re going to be the yellow one.
With all that flashy and cheerful energy.
Then what color am I?
Yu.
You’re the red one.
Because you’re cute.
Not a contract.
I had Sean prepare mascot costumes.
You’ll perform on Children’s Day
at Wat Yai Nong Khai School.
Guys.
Huh?
I’m going to talk to Boss.
I’m quitting.
What?
Calm down, bro.
You can’t quit yet.
Wait until we shower first.
Then we’ll quit together, okay?
You look happy.
Because I’m so happy.
Boss.
What is it, Jeng?
I…
We want to quit.
Huh?
What did you say?
See? I told you we should practice first.
Well, I thought Boss would say,
“Hah. Good riddance.”
Something like that.
What the heck?
I’ve tried my best, Boss.
Maybe being an idol
really isn’t for me.
I did everything I could,
but the result was the opposite.
Thank you for giving me opportunities
and for trusting me.
Even though my last boy group failed,
you still let me create a new one.
Now I admit it.
I’m just a loser.
I don’t want to waste more of your time.
Let’s disband the group.
Who said this isn’t for you?
And I’m not disbanding the group.
But Boss...
Jeng doesn’t want to be a mascot
He wants to be an idol.
And he was born to be one, Boss.
I’m not making you wear a mascot.
We will...
debut a new boy group.
Huh?
Really, Boss?
Yes.
But four members are too few.
It doesn’t feel complete yet.
We need another member.
Sure, I’ll help you find him.
I’ll listen to the fortune teller
and go to every place we missed.
Yes, yes!
Whether it’s north, south,
or sailing across the ocean,
I’ll find him for you.
Me too, I’ll look at dance cover schools.
That’s right.
I’ll search at crime scenes too.
Places where someone just—
Shh.
Enough.
I already found a new member.
Sean, open the door.
Let’s welcome our new member.
Yes, sir.
This is Mai, our new member.
From now on,
Mai will become a member of your group, Ahh wolf.
Take some responsibility for throwing up at it.
We meet again.
But we don’t know each other yet, Boss.
We don’t know if our positions will overlap.
And we don’t know what he’s like.
At least someone has to accept it first.
Do you have a better option?
We don’t have time to choose anymore.
Or do you want me to...
Ah!
Boss really has a great vision.
I wonder if our group will become famous
for being talented or being pretty.
Hello, my new friend.
My name is Cutter.
Nice to meet you.
Hi, I’m Fong. Welcome.
I’m the main dancer who can dance any style.
But I’m good at Korean songs.
Let me know if you need anything.
And what’s your name?
His name is Yu.
He’s not a talkative person,
so if you want to talk to him, just talk to me.
I’m better at talking.
And this is…
the first member of our group, Jeng.
You’ll get close soon.
He’s just a little sensitive today.
I guarantee that when we perform next time,
we’re going to be a hit, no doubt!
You’re Jeng?
Alright, everyone.
Do your best.
Jeng, hurry up and write a new song.
Our label has to become more famous than Bai Liu’s.
But Boss…
No buts.
Now we have a new member, let’s go practice dancing.
After that, shall we go celebrate?
Sounds good.
Let’s go practice dancing.
Let’s go, my friend.
He looks familiar, though.
This time,
you’ll see what I’m made of, Bai Liu!
What are you looking at?
The future.
Why are you still here?
Take them to the Wolf Den practice room.
Yes, sir.
Bai Liu.
You’ll see!
This is the Wolf Den practice room.
Is this really our practice room?
It’s covered in dust.
Can we really practice here?
Come on in.
Whoa.
It's pretty big.
Is it still good?
This is the legendary secret room of our label.
Our first trainee used to practice here
before going to Korea to debut.
Korea?
Our label had someone go to Korea?
Yes, that trainee…
practiced every day before flying to Korea when he was nine.
He was determined to become an artist.
But in the end,
he lost to someone with connections in Korea.
That’s so sad.
Where is he now?
Oh.
He is—
Ahem!
Shall we start practicing?
This is why you’re not making any progress.
Yeah, let’s practice.
Come on.
Let’s practice, guys
Can we practice here?
It'll do.
I’ll turn on the music.
I’m so exhausted.
Freaking exhausted!
Bruh.
What are you tired of?
You moved like an old man.
No way.
You barely danced.
-That’s you.
-No, you.
Alright, stop fighting.
Ha.
Even though we’re tired, we’re happy.
Because we have a new member.
Everything feels right since you joined us.
Honestly,
I’ve never seen anyone as handsome as him.
Oh.
I’m curious.
The name "Ahh wolf" of our group.
It's dog howling, right?
Is it considered lucky?
I don’t know.
It just feels kinda weird.
What do you think?
Well, if our label is a wolf,
then we’re the howls of love.
Whoa!
Damn.
You nailed it. That line really hits hard.
It's like an ads tagline.
Wait,
how did you know?
Yeah, how?
I asked when I signed the contract.
-Oh, that time.
-He was so careful.
Don’t tell me
you signed without reading it.
You didn’t ask any questions?
Oh.
A little bit.
Boss wouldn’t scam us anyway.
He's Si Tian Sinwatchara.
Scam or not,
shouldn’t you be careful?
At least,
you should protect yourself.
What if the contract said
you have to pay 10 million if your group fail.
What will you do?
You can’t even figure this out?
Someone like you
surely don't know what friendship is.
Wait, wait.
Calm down, guys.
I read it, and there’s nothing like that.
It only talks about income and profit sharing.
But right now, we don’t have to worry.
Do you know why?
Why?
We haven’t made any money.
So we don’t have to worry.
Yeah.
When is the train coming?
Right?
At least the MRT has air conditioning.
Yeah.
I'm so tired.
I wanna eat. I wanna eat!
You can take my jacket if you're cold.
Hey, the train is here.
Uh…
It’s here.
Come on.
Wait.
Let the people inside get off first.
Right.
I'm so hungry.
Let’s go.
Ugh.
I don’t understand Boss at all.
Our company has practice rooms.
Why did we have to come this far?
Good thing we have the MRT here,
so it doesn't feel too far.
Do you know the word “laying low”?
It’s when we take things seriously, and hide our failures.
We lay low.
But it’s okay.
Think of it as a training strategy before we come back shining
with style and skill.
I agree.
Boss wants us to be wolves.
But now,
we’re just underdogs.
I think he wants us to work hard
and bring back greatness.
No matter where one practices,
if you have no talent, you’re just a stray dog.
Hey, hey.
Let’s not worry about practicing yet.
I think we should
talk about our positions first.
For example, I’m the main rapper.
What’s up, bro? You know?
Hey, I want to be…
the main dancer. Please give it to me
Go ahead.
I’ll be the main vocalist.
Well.
My position is…
I signed the contract as the group’s center.
Huh?
Damn!
You’re the center?
Mhm.
Wait a second.
If you're the center...
Aren't you taking Jeng’s spot?
No.
I can be in any position.
As long as it benefits our group.
You should be the center.
How about this.
Someone handsome and charming like you
should be the visual.
You have a handsome face, a great figure,
and your talent is unmatched.
This position is just for you.
I agree.
I’m getting shy.
P’Sean.
Are we going to eat omakase tonight?
The boss said we need to cut costs.
Cut costs?
We can only afford noodles.
Noodles?
Noodles.
Noodles? Noodles again?
My hands are becoming noddles.
It’s really good.
It's so nice.
Should we ask for more bitter melon?
Yeah, get some.
Auntie, can I have more bitter melon, please?
Call me big sis.
Normal people don’t like bitter melons, you know.
You’re so cute!
Eat up.
Enjoy your meal.
Want some more?
Big sis?
Jeng.
Don’t we have a songwriter?
P’Amp, P’Golf F.HERO,
P’Tan from Lipta,
or P’Mix Chalermsri.
Don’t we have anyone like that?
It’d be nice if we had money to hire someone.
It probably costs a fortune.
So who usually writes the songs?
We all help.
But I wrote most of them.
You’re so good.
Yu.
Why does your noodles look so bland?
I don’t like bitter melon.
It’s bitter.
Why don’t you try it?
Who knows, one day
you might fall in love with it.
Should I?
Here.
Try a bite.
Say ah.
How is it?
Bitter melon.
Be my love.
Oh.
Bitter melon, be my love.
There are songs about sharks and mangosteens.
Now it's time for bitter melons.
Ahh Wolf!
Oh.
Bitter melon, be my love.
That sounds catchy.
Right?
If we make a good melody and lyrics,
it’ll be a hit.
Who knows,
this might be our lucky bitter melon.
I’ve found my passion.
Do you want a bitter melon?
Hello, I’m here.
Huh? You’re already there?
I just woke up.
What?
I’ll be there soon.
It’s fine. Don’t rush.
I have Jeng.
Okay, see you.
Hey.
What about the others?
-The others?
-Yeah.
They’ll come soon.
So, how’s the song writing?
It’s not going anywhere.
I can’t think of any lyrics.
Doesn’t something like this
come from your love experience?
Love?
I don’t have any love experience.
I only hang out with Boss.
Just try it. Maybe it’ll help you.
Well.
Easy for you to say.
A guy like you…
must be an expert in love.
No.
I’ve never been in a relationship.
Really?
Are you serious?
Yeah.
I used to focus only on studying.
I was always the class president.
I’ve never had a lover.
Then…
Will a class president give in to a group leader?
I’d only give in to one person.
So...
I’m going to help Boss find some clothes.
Do you want to come with me?
Sure.
My leader.
If you agree to go,
make a pufferfish face first.
A pufferfish face?
Yeah.
How?
Like this.
Puff up more.
Even more.
More.
Alright, that’s enough.
Come here.
Let me see the lyrics.
Seriously,
these clothes are cool.
It looks pretty sporty.
Hmm.
Boss said our next concept look
is sporty vibe.
But I don’t know how to style it.
Here.
Try this one.
I’ve never worn this style before.
I usually just dress the same way.
It’d be nice if our agency had a stylist.
Try this style then.
I’ll be your stylist.
I’ll pick out your whole look.
But you…
have to wear what I choose for you,
and step into my world.
You too.
Wear what I choose,
and step into my world as well.
Let’s try it on.
Yes, leader.
Hello.
Are you here to see me?
Master.
Looks like
their agency always has projects with fans.
Who’s that?
He’s an actor
from “The Crisis”, sir.
Bai Liu hired him to make a song.
By the way,
do we have to dress up this much?
We can’t let Bai Liu know we’re here.
It’s embarrassing.
But we dressed like Power Rangers.
Doesn’t this
make us stand out even more?
Come on.
Little deer.
Just by walking in,
You gave yourself away.
You raise a deer?
Jarassi.
Do we have a kid project today?
I don’t think so.
I haven’t heard anything about it.
Look at those Power Rangers over there.
Is it one of our CSR projects?
Shall we go take a look?
Let's go.
What are you doing at my agency?
Which project are you working on?
Remember not to go upstairs today.
They’re rehearsing for Lisa’s year end concert.
You don’t want to talk?
If you don’t talk to me,
I’ll let you talk to Nong Ngor Ngae.
Huh?
We’ll talk.
Could you help us buy these?
The proceeds wil go to the children.
Yes, please.
How cute.
Helping the kids.
Would you like to buy some?
Sure. I’ll help you,
so your school won’t have to close down.
How much is all this?
Is 1,000 baht enough?
Yes, it is.
Would you like to pay by transfer or cash?
Uh.
This is suspicious.
Why do you want us to transfer money?
These days, there are many scammers
who trick people into transferring money like this.
I better call security.
Wait, please wait.
Here you go.
You’re not selling anymore?
Uh…
Please don’t forget to help our school.
Please.
Let’s go.
Thank you.
Young Master, I think…
they’re really suspicious.
We should call security.
No need. I know who they are.
What are they playing at?
Hello, Bai Liu.
Why are those Power Rangers running around like that?
They almost knocked over our agency sign.
Really?
Are they here to sell something?
But they came in a BMW.
Oh?
Their sales must be good.
You can join them.
But you don’t need a mascot costume,
because you already look like one.
For god’s sake, look at yourself first.
Why?
If I’m a mascot, you’re a pregnant male seahorse!
So what?
You little brat.
You’ve got some nerve.
Come on, stop fighting.
You take one each.
I think…
I have a job for you guys.
We’re so late. Will Jeng get mad?
We’re only a little late.
Jeng is nice. He won’t be mad.
It’s been an hour, though.
Come to think of it,
this place has a good atmosphere.
It’s peaceful,
and has lots of trees.
No wonder Jeng likes to write songs here.
Uh…
Cutter, can I ask you something?
What is it?
Do you like me, Cutter?
Why...
Why do you think that?
Well…
There were many times
when you seemed worried about me.
And I could tell from your eyes.
Yu, why are you so cute?
Cutter, you're drunk.
Why don’t you try it?
Who knows, one day
you might fall in love with it.
You like me, don’t you?
If…
I told you
that I liked you,
what would you do?
Well…
Have you ever had a lover?
No, I haven’t.
Then…
Do you want one?
How about we try being a couple?
But...
If we don’t click,
I’ll step back.
Okay.
I like a little excitement.
Then…
Close your eyes.
You said...
you like excitement, right?
It looks good on you.
Where do I tie this?
Let me do it for you.
There.
It’s done.
You look great.
Next mission, let’s take some photos.
Where?
I bet you’ve never been here.
Our photos will appear on the LED screen.
Sounds good?
Really?
Shall we?
How did you know about this place?
It’s famous.
They just opened in Siam.
I read the reviews.
You can play games, watch movies, and watch cartoons here.
It has everything.
Actually, I wanted to come here for a long time,
but my old group members all left.
So, you’re the first person
who made my dream come true.
When you act like a child,
you’re quite cute,
Leader.
Silly you.
Let’s take photos here, Mai.
Sure.
Which kind of photo?
You choose.
This one is cute.
-How about this?
-It looks nice.
Sure.
How should we pose?
Let’s stand next to each other first.
Sure.
I think we’re too far apart.
Come a little closer.
That’s better.
Ready?
Mhm.
It's not good.
You’re almost out of frame, see?
Can you crouch down?
Okay, you’re right.
Here we go.
Can we move closer?
Sure.
Where should I stand? Here?
Yes, move forward and crouch down.
While we wait for the photo,
shall we wait in the room next door?
Sure.
What are we doing in the recording room?
Oh.
Didn’t you said
you like things that are exciting?
But there are security cameras here.
I already checked.
All of them are broken.
Is it as good as when you do CPR?
We removed some clothes for CPR, though.
This room is nice. It even has an octopus.
I feel like I’m a kid again.
You’re not that old yet.
Even when we get old, everyone still has a little childish side.
It feels nostalgic.
Mai, should we...
bring the others here to help write our songs?
Maybe we’ll get new ideas.
Is bitter melon not enough?
Now you want an octopus?
Mai.
Thank you for helping me talk about my position yesterday.
Honestly, I still don’t know what I’m good at.
So when Cutter asked me,
I didn’t know how to answer.
I think I’m a jack of all trades, master of none like they say.
Who said that?
The comment.
Someone commented about me.
How many people?
One.
Just one?
Can I be that one person instead?
Out photos are about to go on the LED screen.
Let’s go see it.
Let’s go.
You want me to go undercover?
Isn’t it too difficult?
What if I accidentally give myself away?
Bruh.
Even scammers have to pay you respect.
I bet you’ll be super convincing,
except for one thing.
What?
Your face, haha.
You keep roasting me. Are you done yet?
Save your mouth for barking at your roommate.
What if they catch me, Bai Liu?
There’s no way.
I know my people well.
Just don’t blow your cover.
And I just heard that
he fired an employee who’s a fan of our artist.
He hasn't changed at all.
So what do you want me to do?
I want you to apply for a job there.
Tomorrow morning.
Okay?
I think Young Master has something up his sleeve.
He looks so evil.
Right?
Okay, Bai Liu.
(Watch the uncut version only on iQIYI and IQ.com.)
That’s amazing. You all did a great job!
Get ready for a poster photoshoot.
Who is she?
Her name is Medyer, your new manager.
You couldn’t afford it?
Then I’ll take this one and this one. All of them!
Wanna take a photo together?
I won’t give in to anyone else but you.
You look so cute when you smile.
Smile a little more.
My smile is already right in front of me.