"Unfold"
(Episode 4)
That little girl I mentioned last time...
her father jumped to his death.
After we talked that day,
I went back and did some digging.
Take a look.
The organ sources
matched with your father...
all came from these hospitals.
I had someone look into it.
They were all accidents...
that resulted in brain death.
The families' behavior was also strange.
They were too cooperative.
And they're private hospitals.
Plus,
these hospitals clearly knew
about our organization,
yet they never reached out to us.
Except for Minhua Hospital.
Come to think of it,
during the handovers,
the families seemed way too numb.
Even if they were overwhelmed with grief,
they wouldn't act like that.
In my experience,
we're lucky if the families
didn't lash out at us.
Yeah.
I've seen that firsthand.
So,
you suspect the families were fake?
Thank you.
Let's eat first. We can talk while we eat.
Just helping out.
Do you want some?
Thank you.
Do you usually eat alone?
My dad was rarely home,
so I just grab whatever.
You can come over to my place next time.
I'll cook for you.
Didn't you say last time
that the sweet and sour
ribs were pretty good?
So,
do you often cook for others?
No.
Then why...
Just eat.
You still haven't told me.
When are you coming over?
Once I'm done dealing
with my dad's affairs.
I'll be waiting.
I'll have the ribs ready for you.
Nanyang Hospital.
Type O blood.
[Scene cleaning fee]
Take a look. Do you still
need to sign to confirm?
No need.
(...in a bathtub.)
(...must wait for police investigation.)
[Liver donated, type O
blood, donor last name Xie]
For the eight patients
your father and I handled,
within two weeks of their admission,
these private hospitals
would miraculously find organ donors
with matching blood types.
That's too much of a coincidence.
Now that you're working on your own,
remember to ask them
for the files before you go.
Things like
autopsy certificates and death reports.
You don't want to handle
a body with some virus
or an unnatural death
without even knowing it.
I got it.
I've already transferred the
twenty thousand yuan to you.
Look at you, only sixteen,
and making this much money.
You can spend it however
you want. How great is that?
I'm just glad I could help.
Only sixteen and making this much money...
For the eight patients
your father and I handled,
within two weeks of their admission...
That's too much of a coincidence.
An organ donor would appear.
These private hospitals...
an organ donor would appear.
[Dad: July 28th, Mingyue Pavilion,
Hexi district #366, Unit 3, Room 702]
It's all taken care of.
You just need to sign here.
Bai Che.
Where are you going?
I'll give you a ride.
What were you doing just now?
Was it some kind of manual labor?
You're sweating a lot.
It's nothing.
Just some routine cleaning work.
Want me to take you out for a bite?
No, thanks.
I need to get back to the bookstore.
A'Che, the bookshelf outside is broken.
Should we get a new one?
Don't worry.
No one will find the ledger.
When your father and I did the handovers,
I saw him write down
some patient information.
[A collection of dates, bits of information
like gender, blood type, and maybe hospitals?]
What's wrong?
This afternoon,
I saw you wearing a hazmat suit.
That was just...
Don't tell me
it was just "cleaning work."
Why won't you tell me the truth?
I'm under no obligation to...
Can you just leave me in peace?
Bai Che.
Do you know what I cleaned up today?
It was a woman.
Twenty-eight years old.
Type O blood.
Her liver
is probably inside
that little girl's body right now.
Do you think I'm complicit in this?
That's not what I meant.
Then what do you mean?
You suspect me?
I don't.
I'm just scared.
Scared of what?
Scared that you'll get hurt.
Scared that I won't be able to protect you.
Just leave.
I'm closing up.
Go.