[You Have My Heart]
[Episode 13: Hard to Deal with Evil Power]
He...
He looked at my chest,
saying the heart is here with me.
I don't understand his words.
He is using demonic words to confuse you.
Ignore him.
Rest assured.
He can't hurt me.
Okay.
I overthought it.
The most urgent matter right now
is that this Wish Fox is still at large.
Li Mao's tragedy is definitely
not an isolated case.
As long as he is in
Yin-Yang Crossing for a day,
more people with obsessions
and desires
will be his targets to toy with
and even torture to death.
So, talking to him
is the only prerequisite
for him to harm people?
You can understand it that way.
If no one talks to him,
or makes a wish to him,
then he will be helpless.
My Lady, I have a plan.
We can take drastic measures
and cut off the source.
We won't issue an arrest warrant,
but the highest-level warning.
Cooperating with Xiqianhua
and the county yamen,
we'll post the portrait of the Wish Fox
in every corner of Yin-Yang Crossing
to notify all the commoners and demons
that whoever sees the scholar in white
must not talk to him.
Go home quickly when seeing this guy.
Do not make eye contact with him.
Do not talk to him.
Go home quickly.
Lock your doors and windows.
Don't talk to this person.
[Warning]
Order all spirit envoys of Xiqianhua
to send orders to the demon leaders
of all regions,
telling them to restrain the demons
and spirits under their jurisdiction,
and let them be careful with their words
and actions recently.
If they meet a scholar in white,
don't have any involvement with him.
They should report to Xiqianhua
via voice transmission immediately.
[Xiqianhua]
My Lord.
Can we really
guard against the Wish Fox like this?
I don't know.
Just do our best.
In the past, I was just an idle person,
I didn't feel anything.
After I came down the mountain
and became a constable, I realized
that I am incompetent.
There are so many troubles
down the mountain,
yet I only thought about learning magic
to show off in front of everyone.
My Lord.
Sometimes, compared to you,
I am indeed quite thoughtless.
Whether it's learning magic
or being a constable,
it's all just following your own heart.
A person
must first be true to himself
before he can see others.
Although I didn't understand,
what you said must make sense, My Lord.
Have a seat.
My Lady.
Yin-Yang Crossing
isn't just for humans.
When I first arrived at Yin-Yang Crossing,
I thought morality was ruined
and laws were nonexistent here
because you used your power
to oppress the government.
But now,
I'm starting to doubt myself.
Can I really manage this place well
with the books of sages I've read,
and
the human laws I believe in?
What are you afraid of?
Do what you believe in,
and what you're good at.
Judge fairly and accurately.
Protect the peace of the people
within your capability.
My Lady.
Warning the people can only help them
avoid harm temporarily,
but
how can we take the initiative
to capture him?
Leave the rest to me.
You said that
when I'm by your side,
your spiritual power recovers faster.
So, at times like this,
don't carry it all by yourself.
I put all my trust in you.
My Lady,
I hope I am of use to you.
Bai Shanjun.
You are useful.
It's because you are so useful
that I hope
I can keep you safe.
Grinding it every day,
you're going to grind this knife thin.
The shop has been closed for a day.
We've lost so much money.
When will these awful days end?
Just listen to Lady Fufeng.
It's for our own good.
Who is it?
Hurry up and go inside.
Have mercy.
I'm a passerby.
I ran into a wolf in the mountains
and injured my leg.
I just want a bowl of water.
Fufeng.
So heartless.
We haven't seen each other for years,
and you're guarding against me like this.
Master.
I just received a report
from a demon leader.
In the South Alley,
a broom spirit who hasn't taken human form
sent a message,
saying
that two hours ago
he saw a woodcutter.
It was suspected to be Wish Fox
in disguise.
But that thing came and left
without a trace
and didn't leak any demonic aura.
It is really hard to track.
I didn't expect that after seventy years,
he hasn't repented at all,
and his methods have become
even more secretive.
Master,
is it because
you've consumed too much
spiritual power lately,
and the seal loosened
that he has
an opportunity to exploit?
Not to that extent.
Someone
helped him from the outside.
So, he opened part of the seal.
Bai Han?
By the way,
Master,
I just checked the secret room.
The five hundred demon hearts
sealed in the secret room
are all gone.
If all of them are devoured by him…
The Five Hundred Demon Hearts Massacre.
Wish Fox, a half-demon,
within 21 days,
slaughtered five hundred demons
and took all their hearts.
Liu Fufeng bound him,
and sealed him in Xiqianhua,
along with the five hundred demon hearts.
My Lord.
I've patrolled the streets
and haven't found anything
unusual for now.
The refugees and beggars on the street
have also been settled
by your wishes.
Good.
Come and take a look.
Do you know about the Five Hundred
Demon Hearts Massacre?
Oh, this case.
I know.
This incident happened seventy years ago.
It's about Lady Fufeng's
romantic history.
Romantic history?
Don't talk nonsense.
It's true.
It is said that back then, a fox demon
admired Lady Fufeng so much
that he went crazy.
He thought demon hearts were great tonics,
so he sneaked around and dug out
five hundred demon hearts,
offering them to Lady Fufeng
as a tonic to show his love.
But Lady Fufeng
couldn't tolerate his behavior.
She personally sealed this demon.
Wish Fox
[The tragedy of 500 demons' hearts]
is the demon.
Really?
Yes,
it's him.
Oh no. We're doomed.
That demon has been sealed
for seventy years.
If he breaks the seal,
he must hate Lady Fufeng deeply.
We have to quickly think of a way
to help Lady Fufeng.
What about this case file?
It's recorded too briefly.
We need to know more clearly,
so we can help her at critical moments.
Keep looking.
There must be more detailed files here.
[Zuiwang Tavern]
Wish Fox
is a half-demon.
His mother was a fox.
She died of dystocia
on the day he was born.
His human father saw him as an ill omen
and abandoned him
in the wilderness as a baby.
He grew up alone in the street
and later worked
as a servant at Zuiwang Tavern.
Due to his half-demon body
and weak nature,
he was heavily bullied.
Let me wipe it for you,
sir.
Let me wipe it.
Little bastard, are you blind?
I know I was wrong, sir. I...
I was wrong.
Bastard!
Let me take a look.
Little bastard.
You little bastard!
I'll beat you to death!
You deserve to be bullied.
Little bastard!
You spineless coward. Do you yield?
His aura is strange.
That suppressed resentment
is mixed with a talent
for twisting wishes,
like a young beast hiding venomous fangs.
If left unchecked,
I'm afraid he will become
a source of evil.
Liu Fufeng worried about
his long-accumulated resentment,
fearing he would fall into an evil path,
so she brought him to Xiqianhua.
Stop!
She intended to guide him towards
goodness and the right path.
From today on,
I will bring you to Xiqianhua.
Why are you here?
Didn't I send you to
the demon academy to study?
Why did you sneak back?
Skipping class?
I just want to
serve you forever.
Little fox.
No one will bully you again,
and you don't have
to serve anyone anymore.
Cultivate well.
In the future,
you can do whatever
you want.
I...
I just want to stay by your side
and fulfill all of your wishes.
Your eyes
are quite clear.
I was just praising them.
What are you doing?
You said they are beautiful.
Doesn't it mean you want to have them?
Whatever you want,
I will give it to you.
Whatever I don't have,
I will definitely find for you.
My God.
He doesn't look like a normal one.
No.
He is not a normal demon
from the very beginning.
However, his nature was already set,
and cultivation had little effect.
As long as that half heart doesn't return,
your heart
will never be stable.
Heart.
Fufeng
needs a heart.
Later, he accidentally learned the secret
that Fufeng had lost half of her heart.
Within 21 days,
he killed five hundred demons
and took all their hearts.
This demon feeds on wishes.
It's inherently evil.
Has she always been
facing all this alone?
My Lord, Constable Chen.
Why panic?
What happened?
My Lord,
we have patrolled the city.
Nothing unusual so far.
But there's a situation at Zuiwang Tavern.
Zuiwang Tavern?
Yes.
Lady Fufeng went there
and dismissed
all the staff staying overnight.
Right now, she is alone
drinking in the tavern.
Zuiwang Tavern.
That was where they first met.
She was waiting for him.
I have a new wish.
Are you
still unwilling to show yourself?
What?
You swallowed 500 demon hearts
and strengthened your body,
but you don't even have the courage
to come out and see me?
Fufeng.
I stayed in that dark jar
for 70 whole years.
70 years.
I prayed for you every day,
hoping you could get your heart back.
But what about you?
All you want
is to catch me and lock me up again.
Right?
Wish Fox.
You slaughtered 500 demons.
By law, your body and spirit
should be refined.
I sealed your spirit in the jar
just to see
if time could make you understand that
those beating in the chests you cut open
are not just tonics
but living lives.
I know I was wrong.
I will never harm anyone again.
As for the child, Li Mao,
I just saw
my past self in him.
He was so weak
and helpless.
That's why I helped him once.
I will never do it again.
Lady Fufeng.
Can you trust me once again
like before?
Then tell me.
What did you promise the person
who rescued you?
There is no one else.
It was me.
I really wanted to see you.
I didn't betray you.
And I never will.
I thought
all living things could be saved.
But I
cannot save you.
I told you she didn't need you.
Why did you beg like a dog?
Offer yourself to me.
Lady Fufeng.
Look.
I have refined their hearts
altogether.
It is strong enough
to make up for your missing half.
This way,
you can be powerful forever
and stay with me forever.
My heart is with Yin-Yang Crossing.
I don't care about petty romance.
Nor would I have any involvement
with a monster like you.
Fine.
If you need it,
then take it.
Fufeng,
you're too cruel.
Lady Fufeng.
Bai Shanjun.
Fufeng,
every time we met,
we ended up fighting.
You didn't even give me
a moment to catch up.
This time,
let's have a good talk.