[You Have My Heart]
[Episode 9: Truth as Bait]
The pool water has dropped again.
The spiritual power isn't increasing,
but the evil power is
popping up everywhere.
If this continues,
I'm afraid we won't
survive this rainy season.
I was on duty yesterday.
When I got close to the evil power rift,
the force was
ten times fiercer than usual.
Freshly tainted?
While washing clothes,
I accidentally got it on my forearm.
I hope Lady Fufeng can hold on.
If even she...
Master.
That Young Magistrate
took the selected scrolls early
this morning
and went down the mountain
back to the county yamen.
I see.
He put on a good act,
but he left just like that.
I didn't expect him to do anything.
That day, I noticed that the evil power
in Kuquan Valley was restless.
I'm afraid something will happen.
Lead all the spirit envoys
and the spirits of Xiqianhua
to suppress it.
You must hold the line.
Then, are you going to be alright
if you are alone?
It's okay.
Go ahead.
Yes.
Clumsy.
Am I not handsome?
I'm sorry, Lord Bai.
I was reckless.
Sorry, I was just upset.
Is something bothering you?
Nothing.
Let me do it.
If you are worried about cases,
you can ask me.
I know everything,
from humans to demons,
in Yin-Yang Crossing.
Really?
Of course.
Then, if demons get hurt,
how should they get treated?
If they get hurt,
they must be treated with demonic arts.
It also depends on the situation.
Whether it's an injury
or they got possessed during cultivation.
Your question is too amateur.
What if their spiritual power is damaged?
What medicine should be used?
Medicine?
There should be
spiritual power replenishment.
Treating like with like, you know.
The medicine we humans take
is useless for demons.
But I read in the ancient records
that some medicines are useful for demons.
Could it be a deceptive book?
You haven't read any books anyway.
Asking you is useless.
What do you mean?
Besides,
look at my movements.
It's obvious I'm a warrior.
What are you doing?
Brewing medicine.
Do you think the medicine you brew
can cure demons?
I went to your secret room
and found some records related to demons.
I found some spiritual medicines
that have miraculous effects on
restoring spiritual power.
So, I brewed some to try.
You have a lot of spare time, huh?
Don't worry, My Lady.
I didn't delay any official business.
There are just
a few disputes among spirits
that I'm not sure about.
I'll wait until you recover
to make a decision.
So, please take your medicine.
You can't abandon
the people of Yin-Yang Crossing.
Take a look.
Don't waste your effort.
Even if you brew ten more pots,
it's just a drop in the bucket.
It smells bad,
but it's effective.
You'd better drink it, My Lady.
I'm a mortal with a lifespan of
several decades.
I'm only working here temporarily.
I don't know what arrangements
the court will have for me later.
So, My Lady,
you can't pin your hopes on me.
Since you have guarded Yin-Yang Crossing
for thousands of years,
you must continue to guard it.
Bai Shanjun.
Are you really willing to stay?
I decocted medicine and served you
willingly.
Please don't give up.
My Lady.
This is another prescription.
Taste it.
It's very bitter.
Why didn't you put some honey in it?
I will.
My Lady.
The light is so dim
that it upsets me.
Bring that candlestick over.
Okay.
My legs are sore.
Lord Bai,
could you massage them for me?
Okay.
My Lady,
it is inappropriate for a man
to touch a woman.
I will find a wooden mallet tomorrow
to massage your legs.
Bai Shanjun,
you seem to care about me a lot.
My Lady,
everyone cares about you.
When you first came here,
you looked gentle,
but you were actually very stubborn.
Now it seems
you have became gentler.
My Lady,
when we first met,
you wanted to kill me.
If I weren't tough enough,
I would probably be ashes by now.
My Lady.
Bai Shanjun,
what if...
My Lady,
I...
There are no what-ifs.
You will definitely get better.
My Lady.
My Lady?
[May Lady Fufeng recover.
From Bai Shanjun.]
My Lady.
I pray to you,
wishing for your good health.
Is it strange?
But don't you fulfill
all the wishes of the people?
I, Bai Shanjun,
am also one of your people.
My Lady,
can you fulfill my wish?
Who is there?
Who are you?
Me?
I am you.
Have you been
looking for this?
Look closely.
Is this the answer you want?
Stop playing tricks!
How could there be two of me
in this world?
Who exactly are you?
What do you want?
How stubborn.
I have been patient enough with you,
but you ruined my plans time and again.
It's been a hundred years,
and you still only use
these sneaky, despicable tricks,
Bai Han.
You were faking your illness.
Realizing it now
is probably too late.
Lead all the spirit envoys
and the spirits of Xiqianhua
to suppress it.
You must hold the line.
Then, is it okay for you
to be alone?
It's okay.
Go ahead.
You little spirit.
You are still alive?
Lady Fufeng anticipated
that you would kill me after using me,
so she made a substitute
with her spiritual power
to lure you into devouring it.
What you devoured
was just a bait made of
My Lady's pure spiritual power.
Bai Han,
stop it.
Fine.
My Lord and My Lady.
I have paid for
what I owed you.
She has always felt guilty
for almost hurting you that day.
Just consider it her compensation.
But there was no need to
compensate with her life.
Though the mirror is broken,
it can be fixed.
Can she come back?
Don't be afraid, little bronze mirror.
This place
is full of spiritual power.
In less than a hundred years,
you'll be able to take human form again.
My Lady,
the one who stole your heart
a hundred years ago
was Bai Han, right?
Did you get it back?
Will you die?
There's no point discussing this now.
Bai Han is still alive,
hiding somewhere in Yin-Yang Crossing.
I must lure him out to
eliminate the root of the problem.
So,
your injury and being bedridden
were all fake.
Yes.
Why didn't you tell me?
Bai Shanjun,
if I told you everything,
other than making you worry,
what would be the point?
Fine.
Since you're fine, My Lady,
I won't disturb you anymore.
My Lady,
I'm angry that you deceived me,
watching me run around like a fool.
I know
little about Yin-Yang Crossing
and evil power,
so I understand why
you didn't tell me the truth.
But I never wanted you to die.
It's good
that you're fine.
Though you're not a fool,
you're a nerd.
Why did Bai Han choose you
to be his vessel?
Master,
has the evil power
dissipated?
I felt that
it went a bit too smoothly.
Smoothly?
If the evil power is
dispersed in one place,
it will return from another.
In the past hundred years, Bai Han
must have learned many wicked methods.
He's harder to deal with than I thought.
Then,
can we take back
the half tree heart
in Bai Shanjun's chest?
It's not the right time yet.
Send someone to the capital to ask
if the person in the painting
is really
the county magistrate demoted
from the capital to Yin-Yang Crossing,
Bai Shanjun.
Yes.
[May Lady Fufeng recover.
From Bai Shanjun.]
Thank you.