[You Have My Heart]
[Episode 12: The Tempting Wish Fox]
Can you draw him or not?
It's been a whole night.
Or was there never such a person,
and this is all just an excuse
for you to get away with it?
No.
That's not true.
I...
I remember his eyes.
His eyes looked like this.
And his mouth was like this.
But somehow when I put it together,
it just feels off.
Maybe I was too drunk that night.
The memory has already become blurred.
Hurry up and think harder.
Is it him?
Yes, it's him.
Right, that's him!
Lady Fufeng.
How could you draw it so exactly like him?
Send this portrait
to the county yamen at once.
Hand it personally to Bai Shanjun.
Tell him,
if he encounters this demon,
he must not speak to him,
and absolutely
can't agree to any of his requests.
This demon is extremely dangerous.
Yes, Master.
[Dedication Above Self]
Where is Lord Bai?
Lady Fufeng has urgent news to tell him.
Deputy Magistrate Shi!
Where is Lord Bai?
Miss Fengling.
Lord Bai is...
He and Constable Chen
took the men out early this morning.
They said they received a new lead,
so they're searching the whole town
for the scholar in white from the drawing.
The scholar in white?
Yes.
They said it was a new lead provided
by the leopard cat demon.
It's that suspicious man
he saw at the Li residence.
Well,
it's the one drawn
in the student's painting.
They're in trouble!
You two.
Sir,
two bowls of tea.
Coming right up.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Here's your tea.
Enjoy.
Take care.
According to what Li Mao said,
the scholar in white
should be somewhere nearby.
This area isn't small.
We may be searching for quite some time.
My Lord, let me see.
Speak.
Tell me your wish.
Was he sitting here a moment ago?
Let's go take a look.
Don't be afraid.
Tell me your wish.
I will make it come true for you.
Sir,
we suspect
you may be connected
to a murder case in town.
Please come back to county yamen with us
and assist in the investigation.
Is that so?
I have nothing to hide
and fear no shadows.
Of course I'm willing
to cooperate with you both...
to prove my innocence.
Hu.
He's not human.
What?
Did you sense his demonic aura?
My Lord, that's what you don't understand.
In Yin-Yang Crossing,
the real powerful demons
carry no demonic aura at all.
Look at how he walks—
his feet never stir a speck of dust,
and his steps make no sound.
There's not a single
drop of dew clings to his robes.
And after walking all this way,
as a scholar, he isn't even out of breath.
You're right.
You two officials
must be quite burdened with duties.
Such an exhausting journey,
surely there's something you want, right?
For example, soaring in the sky
to be spared the hardship of travel.
Why didn't you say you can fly earlier?
My feet are killing me,
walking down this road.
Stop chatting.
Focus on the road.
And you, handsome young magistrate.
What about you?
What is it that you desire?
Do you want people to believe in you?
Do you want to be respected,
or
to no longer be alone?
I desire nothing.
Save your tricky words.
No.
You do want something.
Say it.
I can make it come true for you.
I'll say it again.
I don't have any wishes.
Tell me your wish.
If I must name one,
then I wish the benches in the yamen
were a little taller,
just enough to sit comfortably.
As you wish.
What's wrong, Hu?
If your legs were broken,
the benches would be taller.
The benches would be taller.
Hu?
If your legs were broken,
the benches would be taller.
Hu, wake up!
If your legs were broken,
the benches would be taller.
Hu.
Still conscious, Young Magistrate?
You're tougher than I expected.
So those two murder cases
were your doing?
Interesting.
Very interesting.
You speak of benches and chairs,
yet that isn't your true desire.
What you really want
is to find the missing half
of Liu Fufeng's heart,
right?
Don't worry.
Such a sincere wish,
I will definitely fulfill it for you.
My Lady.
My Lady, what are you doing?
Saving your life.
But...
but your spiritual power...
You shouldn't be wasting it on me anymore.
Behave.
My Lady.
Are you
starting to believe me now?
Lady Fufeng,
does it hurt
losing half your heart?
I don't want to see you suffer.
Lady Fufeng, I...
Sleep.
Get up.
Stop playing dead.
I know you're awake.
Which arm is hurt?
Ouch, ouch!
Feeling better?
Drink the medicine.
Did you make this yourself?
Did you make it just for me?
Stop talking nonsense!
Just drink!
I'll drink it!
Feeling better?
Thank you, Fengling.
If there's a next time...
There won't be a next time.
Silly.
I mean,
if there's a next time,
send someone else to save me.
Lady Fufeng,
about that demon in white...
You should be
worrying about yourself first.
Thank you, My Lady.
Let me ask you something.
Yesterday, did you make any kind of wish,
or have a passing thought
while facing that demon?
He did ask me to make a wish,
but I didn't know what he was,
I just said something to brush him off.
I said I wished the benches in the yamen
were a little taller.
Thank goodness.
My Lady,
what exactly is that demon?
He's a
troublesome Wish Fox.
He feeds on wishes
and is evil by nature.
He can pry into the deepest
and strongest desires of the human heart,
then fulfill them
in the most twisted and extreme way,
and draw power from it.
I thought Li Mao
and Ji were harmed by Bai Han.
I never expected
it was because this Wish Fox escaped.
His demonic power isn't strong,
but he's skilled
at exploiting people's weaknesses.
Yesterday,
did he say anything to you?
What you want
is to find the missing half
of Liu Fufeng's heart,
right?
What are you talking about?
No wonder...
her presence lingers on you.
Just as I thought.
Her heart is beating inside you.
Can't you feel it?
Can't you feel her warmth
and her pain?
Nothing.
Lord Bai,
don't let anyone control your heart.
This is mine.
Lady Fufeng,
I just ran into Fengling outside,
so I figured,
you must've been worried
about Lord Bai and me.
Thank you for saving my life.
But speaking of which,
Lord Bai, you are really lucky.
You fell from such a height
and came away completely unharmed.
Your injuries aren't even
as serious as mine.
It's all thanks to
Lady Fufeng using her
spiritual power to heal me.
How is that possible?
Lady Fufeng's demonic spiritual power
can't heal a mortal's wounds.
If it were forcibly transferred,
at best, it would damage your meridians;
at worst, your body
would explode and you'd die.
That's common knowledge.
You were probably just lucky.
When you fell,
you must be caught by a tree.
Don't flatter yourself.
Claiming Lady Fufeng saved you?
-Don't you feel ashamed?
-Enough.
There's no point dwelling on this.
What matters now
is finding the Wish Fox quickly,
and bringing him to justice.
First thing tomorrow morning,
I will pay Li Mao a visit.
Yes, My Lady.
Understood.
Lord Bai.
I'm sorry.
My Lord, do you no longer mind
that the benches
in our county yamen are too short?
You don't want to soar in the sky,
do you?
It hurts! It hurts!
[Xiqianhua Mansion]
Lady Fufeng.
Lord Bai.
Have you found
the scholar from the ruined temple?
He can prove my innocence.
He can also prove I never left that night.
I...
When can I go home?
My mother must be worried sick.
Li Mao, think carefully.
That day at the ruined temple,
what exactly did you say to that scholar?
I was very drunk back then.
There are a lot I can't remember clearly.
I only remember feeling suffocated inside.
It seems
I poured my heart out to him.
How pitiful.
This world has treated you too cruelly!
But it's okay.
Tell me,
what do you desire most
deep down in your heart?
What is your truest wish?
Wish?
I...
I don't want them to bully me anymore.
And I don't want my mother
to suffer anymore.
Then, do you need my help?
You want to help me?
Are you really willing to help me?
When it comes to granting wishes,
I have never failed.
My Lord, My Lady.
Did I...
did I say something wrong?
Mother!
My Lady, I...
What is it?
Mother!
My Lady, I lied to you.
The Wish Fox discovered my wish,
and it wasn't about the benches—
it was hoping you could
find the missing half of your heart.
Seeing Li Mao just now
made me realize something.
If he really helped fulfill my wish,
would that put you in danger?
What else did he say?
He...
He looked at my chest
and said the heart is inside me.
I... I don't know what he meant by that.