[You Have My Heart]
[Episode 8: Now I Know Your Heart]
My Lady.
Thank you for helping me regain my senses.
Here in Yin-Yang Crossing,
there aren't many people who would show me
such kindness.
Once my mind cleared,
I remembered something.
That day in prison,
an elder told me
that if
I could obtain Magistrate Bai's heart,
I would possess
the greatest beauty in the world.
But at the time, I was so exhausted
that I couldn't tell
whether it was real
or just a dream.
Do you remember what he looks like?
At first, he spoke with his back to me.
Then he slowly turned around.
It's that one-eyed old man again!
You should say,
it's Bai Han again.
Have you forgotten?
This is just Bai Han's vessel.
And he has more than just one vessel.
You're right.
There's also Bai Shanjun.
Anyway, I just want to know
how to retrieve the other half
of the tree heart inside him.
Bai Han's cultivation is strong,
and he's far too cunning.
Without the tree heart,
how can we possibly stand against him?
Born of evil power,
and nourished by it.
As long as evil power surges
in Yin-Yang Crossing,
he can continue absorbing it
to heal himself
and grow even stronger.
Don't worry.
It's fine if we can't
retrieve the tree heart.
We'll simply use
the county magistrate as bait.
We can't keep letting
Bai Han lead us around by the nose.
[Dedication Above Self]
Greetings, My Lord!
What are you doing?
Lord Bai, we treated you poorly
at Huichun Brothel the other day.
I've felt guilty ever since.
I came here today specifically
to offer my apology.
Well...
Lord Bai is wise and upright,
clean as still water,
and impartial as a mirror.
My deepest gratitude to you, Lord Bai.
Please, get up.
Thank you both.
Guys, bring these stuff in.
Yes, sir!
Lord Bai.
Not bad.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
My Lord.
Our Yin-Yang Crossing
hasn't had a useful magistrate in years.
Back then,
Xiqianhua took care of us,
so we didn't feel much difference.
But ever since you arrived,
things have become even better.
Now,
many families don't even bother
locking their doors when they go out.
If someone finds money on the road,
they'll bring it straight
to the magistrate's office.
All of this is thanks to you.
Besides,
Lady Fufeng's standards
have always been incredibly high.
Since she approves of you,
we naturally
trust you as well.
Lady Fufeng approves of me?
Of course.
I've never seen her
pay this much attention to anyone.
To be honest, this yamen
hasn't been this lively in years.
Back then,
if Lady Fufeng hadn't guarded this place,
it would have fallen into chaos long ago.
When the sky fell, she was the one
at the front lines holding it up.
When order collapsed,
she rebuilt it with her own hands.
The peace Yin-Yang Crossing enjoys today,
where humans and demons
can live and make a living together,
exists all because of her.
She's the anchor of our Yin-Yang Crossing.
And now that she stands behind you,
we trust her,
so naturally, we trust you too.
Place your bets!
Small.
Big.
I won again!
Magic and sorcery are strictly forbidden
at the Golden Toad Gambling House.
Move aside!
They're yours.
Thanks.
What are you doing?
Grandpa,
why can't I ever
finish plucking your beard?
Is that so?
Magistrate Bai.
Do you want to play a round?
No, you guys go ahead.
Come on.
Big or small,
place your bets!
[The Magistrate's Office]
Master.
Lately, petitions about theft
and neighborhood disputes
have decreased significantly.
They're probably being reported
to the county yamen now.
Looking at it this way,
that bookworm county magistrate
is quite capable.
How many of today's petitions
are related to evil power?
Cases about panic, madness,
and beast attacks
have increased 30 percent
compared to last month.
The dead field in West Village
is expanding again.
If you've seen enough, just come inside.
My Lady.
Take a look if you want to.
It's fine.
My Lady.
Do you need to review these every day?
Of course she does!
What kind of place
did you think the Xiqianhua Mansion was?
A gathering den for demons and monsters?
Lord Bai,
it's not even 9 PM yet.
Why are you here so early?
My Lady, can we speak in private?
My Lady.
Today, Madam Chun and Wan
came to the county yamen.
They talked a lot,
and I heard
many rumors about you.
Don't take Madam Chun's words
too seriously.
A thousand years is a long time.
Even I can't remember most of it.
But the people have the clearest memory.
It's far more real
than any official records.
Lord Bai, did you hurry all the way here
just to tell me this?
Of course not.
My Lady,
I want to know the real Yin-Yang Crossing.
Can this willow tree
really connect to
Yin-Yang Crossing's earth veins?
Of course.
My Lady,
what kind of demon are you?
A tree demon.
A willow tree
that spent 1,000 years
cultivating a human form.
A willow tree?
This spirit willow
is my true form.
I didn't know that.
A willow tree can turn into a human form?
No wonder the spiritual pool
uses these willow leaves to channel water.
It feels like an endless supply.
This willow tree is so big.
Lord Bai, you've improved a lot.
Associating the willow tree
with a spiritual pool,
you're starting to look more like
a true citizen of Yin-Yang Crossing.
My Lady,
when you spoke of willingness,
you wanted me to stay
in Yin-Yang Crossing of my own will,
didn't you?
I was born into a humble family.
My original intention as an official
was simply to help people.
So I devoted myself to my duties,
only to end up
taking the blame and being demoted
for a superior born into nobility.
When I first arrived at Yin-Yang Crossing,
I just let things take their course.
But once I got here,
everything I've seen
has overturned everything I once believed.
Lord Bai.
Cut the bureaucratic tone.
My Lady, this is not a bureaucratic tone.
After arriving at Yin-Yang Crossing,
for the first time, I truly feel that
I'm doing something as an official.
And all of this was
because of you, My Lady.
It seems
you've finally thought it through,
unyielding Lord Bai.
But,
I cannot blindly
step into this world.
My Lady.
Please show me the real Yin-Yang Crossing.
Show me what it is you're protecting,
and why...
it has to be me.
Once I see it clearly
and figure it out,
I will
stay here of my own free will.
Come see me tomorrow
between 7 AM and 9 AM.
Don't be late.
This is the source of evil power?
You could say that.
Only this lies at its very bottom.
It's the filth of this world
that cannot be dissolved or dispersed.
It breeds greed, malice,
and the urge for self-destruction.
Why does something like this exist?
Where did it come from?
Legend has it that Yin-Yang Crossing
was formed from the eye of the earth
when Pangu split heaven and earth apart.
Above ground,
spiritual power gathers
to nourish all living things.
Below the ground,
evil power surges endlessly,
capable of destroying everything.
That is why
the land of Yin-Yang Crossing is fertile,
and all beings gain sentience
through spiritual power.
But it can also be devoured
by evil power at any moment.
This is the price.
A hundred years ago,
someone and I
barely managed to seal it.
If it's sealed,
why does it keep leaking out?
Look over there.
A seal is like blocking a spring,
while evil power
is like underground water.
It will always find another way out.
We call these seepages.
There is no pattern
to when or where they'll appear.
What the Xiqianhua has been doing
for the last century
was simply mending the land,
suppressing evil power,
and purifying the earth.
With your spiritual power?
Spiritual power can drain,
but the seepages never cease.
I don't know how much longer
we can keep mending it.
But recently,
these seepages have begun appearing
with alarming regularity.
Are you saying
someone's deliberately
releasing evil power?
What's wrong?
Someone touched the seal. Get back!
Lady Fufeng.
Are you okay?
What's this?
Suppressing the corruption
with my spiritual power.
Lady Fufeng.
The corruption has invaded
her vital meridians.
This time,
I'm afraid she won't be able
to hold on much longer.
What do you mean
she won't be able to hold on much longer?
Young Magistrate.
My Lady.
If I truly pass away,
can you govern
Yin-Yang Crossing for me?
My Lady, you're a thousand-year-old demon.
I'm just a...
My Lady?
Fengling.
Come quickly.
Check on Lady Fufeng.
What's happening to her?
A hundred years ago,
Master gave half of her heart
to her deputy at the time so they could
suppress evil power together.
Unexpectedly,
that jerk broke his word and betrayed her.
The moment he got Master's power, he fled.
Half a heart?
Over the years,
Master has been pushing through
with only half a heart.
While maintaining order
of Yin-Yang Crossing,
she had to suppress
the corruption everywhere.
Her spiritual power
has long been exhausted.
And she has reached her limit.
Then... how do we save her?
Do you know
why Master wanted you to stay?
Why?
Because whenever you're near her,
her spiritual power recovers more quickly.
Although you are a mortal,
your physique is unique.
You are highly compatible with Master.
And you can help Master
restore her spiritual power.
So that's why
you asked me to stay—
only for your spiritual power.
I thought...
My Lady.
Didn't you say
your spiritual power
recovers faster when I'm around?
Just keep holding my hand.
That won't be necessary anymore.
All the records gathered
by Xiqianhua over the years
are stored in the secret chamber behind.
You''ll find methods
of suppressing corruption,
records of land purification,
civil cases,
the traits of all kinds of demons,
as well as how to regulate them.
Didn't you want to know
how to govern Yin-Yang Crossing
where humans and demons coexist?
Everything I can teach you
is in there.
Go back to your county yamen.
From now on,
unless it's official business,
there's no need to come see me again.
My Lady.
What are you...
Bai Shanjun,
you are free now.
My Lady.
I promise you.
I will stay.
Well done.
I can't extract a human heart.
This is the best I can do to help you.
Liu Fufeng's days are numbered.
You can do whatever you want.
Just don't look for me again.
You can't extract a human heart?
If you hadn't run away just now,
wouldn't you have already succeeded?
I wasn't thinking straight at the moment!
Since you are unwilling to take the heart,
then give me all your spiritual power!
Fufeng,
we'll soon meet again.