[You Have My Heart]
[Episode 14 Hearts Laid Bare]
Fufeng.
Every time we meet,
we always end up in a fight—
you never even give us a moment
to catch up.
This time,
let's have a proper talk.
I have nothing to say to you.
What, can't bear to deal with him?
That really doesn't sound like you.
Do you really have feelings for him?
This face of his—
I gave it to him.
His heart is yours,
and only that pitiful will of his
is his own.
But unfortunately,
even that is already under my control.
Fufeng.
According to ancient records,
what surges up from the depths
of Yin-Yang Crossing
is not merely corruption,
but pure primordial power.
Why must we keep acting like mere fixers,
endlessly patching it up?
Sealing it and guarding Yin-Yang Crossing
is our duty.
Duty?
That's just shackles.
If we can control this power,
it would go far beyond Yin-Yang Crossing.
We could rebuild order itself—
cleanse this filthy world
and bring about a total upheaval.
You wouldn't have to be trapped
in this tiny Yin-Yang Crossing.
Fufeng, come with me.
Do you understand what it means
to take that step forward?
It means...
I will no longer stay here with you,
guarding Yin-Yang Crossing.
I will prove
that my path is the right one.
Liu Fufeng,
you're nothing more than that after all.
Do you really think
escaping Yin-Yang Crossing
means you'll be free as the sky and sea?
The moment I lent you half my heart,
I cast the Treebound Curse.
If you dare betray me—
betray Yin-Yang Crossing—
your body
will turn into deadwood.
So you were scheming against me
from the very beginning?
I kept a backup plan.
I didn't expect
it would actually come in handy.
Fine.
Now that you've lost half your heart,
let's see how long you can hold on.
I'd like to see
which of us will have the last laugh.
The Treebound Curse is taking hold!
I must replenish my strength
and find a new vessel.
Corrupting power—
this is a gift from the heavens.
With this corrupting power,
I can sustain myself here
until I find a new body.
Bai Han,
you've finally come.
Do you see it?
All those countless failures
were just for this moment.
You are not Bai Shanjun—
that was only a name you used briefly
when you lost yourself.
Back then, my spirit left my body.
I let you take our heart
and leave,
while I stayed behind
to deal with this damned curse.
What you're seeing
isn't someone else's story—
these are our memories.
Come back.
Don't resist this natural fusion.
No... That's not right.
I just want to do my job properly.
Forget it.
The three-day deadline has arrived,
and the case remains unsolved.
I will keep my promise—
whether I live or die is up to you.
My Lady,
what's wrong?
Do you need spiritual power?
Nothing will go wrong.
You'll definitely be all right.
Don't carry everything alone.
I place my full trust
in you.
My Lady,
I hope I can be of use to you.
Bai Shanjun, don't believe him.
Look at me. Look at Yin-Yang Crossing.
Your persistence, your sense of justice,
everything you've done
to uncover the truth—
none of it is anything
like that faithless coward.
I am not you.
I would never harm innocent lives,
and I would never betray Lady Fufeng.
You've simply forgotten
the most crucial memory.
You've been misled
by her narrow-minded fixation
on staying in one corner of the world.
That's all very normal.
But once you and I merge,
you'll understand everything I've done.
You are me—Bai Han.
We have always been one.
Bai Shanjun,
hold on to yourself.
Don't be deceived by him.
No...
I am not you.
M-My Lady. My Lady.
My Lady—
strike now! My Lady.
My Lady!
Do it!
You would rather die
than break a promise,
rather shatter than bow.
I must admit, I'm growing
a little more impressed with you.
A life-saving grace—so you intend
to repay it with yourself?
My Lady, why are you suddenly
so concerned about me?
Because I want you to stay
and become mine.
Do what you believe in
and what you're best at—
uphold justice with clarity,
judge cases with insight,
and protect the peace
of those within your reach.
As long as corruption does not perish,
neither will I.
Liu Fufeng,
we have a long way to go.
Fengling,
how has My Lady
been recovering lately?
My master briefly awakened today,
but her spiritual energy is still weak.
She is currently resting
in the spirit pool.
Then I'll go in and take a look.
My Lady.
You're here.
How is Yin-Yang Crossing now?
The restriction has been lifted.
The people are living in peace—
everything is well.
Your heart
has not yet been recovered,
but don't worry, My Lady.
I will help you.
You are already helping me.
Not enough.
It's enough as long as
it's within your power.
My Lady,
you expect too little of me—
or rather, you simply don't
trust me enough yet.
Humans and demons are of different paths;
everyone has things beyond their reach.
People always say humans and demons
are of different paths,
but what I see in Yin-Yang Crossing
is humans and demons living together
in peace and prosperity.
How can there be any "different paths"?
Perhaps so.
Humans and demons may not
be on different paths.
But with different ambitions
and desires,
it truly becomes impossible
to walk the same path.
My Lady,
when you once asked me in return
what it means to be truly willing...
I used to think
you meant for me
to willingly stay in Yin-Yang Crossing.
But now it seems
I was wrong, wasn't I?
Can you guess it now?
When Bai Han possessed me,
I glimpsed his memories—
or more precisely,
the memories of this heart.
What did you see?
I saw him, in order to keep
his spiritual power from dissipating,
plunge into corruption,
taking one vessel after another
until he finally found me.
When we first met,
your hatred toward me—
was it not only because of this face,
but because of this heart as well?
Yes.
I wanted to reclaim my heart,
but I couldn't.
Perhaps it had been away
from me for too long
and no longer
recognized its original owner.
I was afraid that if you knew the truth,
you would resist and refuse to return it.
So I led you closer to me,
made you accept me,
made you rely on me—
waiting for you
to come to me willingly.
If, when we first met,
you had told me the truth,
I would never
have tried to possess and cling
to what was never mine to begin with.
Bai Shanjun...
back then,
I didn't understand you.
My Lady.
You don't need to give me
such insincere answers now.
This isn't you—
and I don't want you to be like this.
I say all this today
only to tell you:
I willingly
return this heart.
It's not something you deceived me
into giving up.
No matter how you see me—
as human, as vessel,
as real or illusion—
I exist because of you,
and I came for you.
Fufeng...
I am fond of you.