[roaring]
♪
[narrator]
It's wild how fast life can change.
A year ago,
I moved to London for a fresh start…
[engine humming]
…and everything
I was running from found me.
["Hot" by Avril Lavigne playing on radio]
But somehow, I survived
and fell for the last person
I was ever supposed to.
The bad boy cliché.
The kind your mother warns you about.
Too bad mine married his dad
and moved us in together.
[giggles]
I never stood a chance.
[door closes]
God, how could I resist Nick Leister?
[screams]
[music continues, muffled]
But the only thing harder
than finding true love…
- [music continues, normal]
- …is holding on to it.
[volume increases]
Come on!
Catch me!
[tyres screech]
[laughs]
I couldn't believe he was mine.
I wanted to tell the whole world.
But Nick wanted to keep us a secret.
- [tyres screech]
- [engine revs]
I get it.
You hide something to keep it safe.
But some secrets can't stay hidden.
They come out and blindside you.
Shit! Damn!
- And when they do…
- Whoo!
…well, it's wild how fast life can change.
- [Nick] Fair enough. You win.
- [giggles]
- Shock.
- [music fades]
- What do you want as your prize?
- You know what I want.
Well, you're gonna have to come get it.
[chuckles] Come on.
- [scoffs] What?
- Come on.
[dreamy music playing]
Nick.
Hey, come on.
Come back. [chuckles]
[door opens]
[whispers] Nick.
Nick!
What are you doing?
Nick! Oh, my God. You're such a…
[all] Surprise!
- [chuckles] Oh, my God, you guys.
- [cheering]
- [music stops]
- Happy birthday, babe. [chuckles]
Who are all these people?
These people are the great and good
of British polite society, dear,
so just smile and wave.
- I haven't got a clue, all right?
- Okay.
- Hello.
- Hey.
Happy birthday.
[mellow music playing]
I just can't believe
that you did all this. It's amazing.
- Was Nick really that convincing?
- [chuckles] Yeah, a bit too convincing.
- [Nick scoffs]
- Aw.
- They didn't have any blue ones. [laughs]
- [chuckles] Mom.
Blue ones?
When Noah was about five, I gave her
a little bit of garden to look after,
and all she wanted to do
was grow blue roses.
- [chuckles]
- You mean like those tacky fake things
you see in art shops?
- I think they were beautiful, actually.
- [Noah's mum laughs]
[Nick] Well, you can take
the girl out of Florida.
- [Noah's mum] Hey!
- [laughs]
[Nick] Here she is.
What is this?
It's for you to take to Oxford.
Aw.
- You can cuddle her if you get homesick.
- Aw.
Oh, my goodness, it's a cat.
- [stepsister] I love it.
- [Noah's mum, Noah, Nick chuckle]
[Noah] Now I won't be lonely at school.
[exclaiming, laughing]
- Beers have run out. Saved us two.
- [chuckles] Thanks, man.
Cheers, brother.
- Oh. [chuckles]
- [friend] Can you keep a secret?
What?
I've got my grandma's ring,
and I'm gonna propose to Jenna.
Like, what, today?
- [chuckles] No.
- No?
- No, no, no. Not today.
- Actually?
- Yes, actually.
- Well, congrats.
- Thank you, thank you. There's--
- Best man?
- Yes, best man. Yes.
- Okay, this is good. I'm liking this.
There's… There's some stuff
- I wanna sort out first.
- Okay.
I wanna clear all my debts, you know?
Have nothing hanging over us.
I've got you. Yeah, I'm here to help.
Nick, I ain't taking your money.
But there's a race.
And I-I've bet the gym on it.
- Nah, nah. No.
- Nick?
- You know I don't do that anymore.
- No, no, no.
- You can beat this guy in your sleep.
- I'm… I'm done. I'm out.
I've promised Noah. I've got work.
You win, and I'm clean.
It was a stupid bet, and I can't back out.
Come on.
Oh. Hey, guys.
Why do you look so suspicious?
- Why do you look so suspicious?
- [Noah laughs]
Great question.
- [glass clinking]
- Gather around, please.
[Jenna laughing]
You got him good.
Nick. Wait, please.
If I do this, Noah can never find out.
For sure. We keep the girls out of it.
- Yeah?
- All right.
Some of you may already know,
but today is a double celebration.
Not only is it my beautiful,
brilliant daughter's birthday,
but she's also gotten into Oxford…
- [whoops]
- [guests cheering]
…where she will study Engineering Science.
No doubt she'll be technical director
of a Formula One team before you know it.
- [whoops]
- [guests cheering, applauding]
- To Noah…
- [all] To Noah.
- [cheering continues]
- …and her bright future.
- [car horn honking]
- A-ha!
Is that another surprise I hear before me?
Yes. Follow me to the drive, please.
[guests chattering]
- What is going on? What is going on?
- [chuckles] Nearly. You're warm.
[gasps]
[horn honks]
[chuckles] What?
[both] Happy birthday.
- [chuckles] Are you being serious?
- [Noah's mum] Yes.
Something to make the drive
to Oxford a touch more fun.
- [chuckles] No way. I love it.
- [guests exclaiming]
Thank you.
[chuckles] What?
- [Nick's dad] Come on! Fire it up!
- [Noah's mum] Come on, Noah.
- Fire it up!
- [engine roars]
[engine purring]
[engine revving]
[Noah breathes heavily]
So, good surprise?
Yeah. I don't love how easily
you lied to me though.
Hey. Organising a surprise party
isn't lying, it's romantic.
Fine.
[birds chirping]
[sighs]
[kisses, whispers] Noah.
- Hey.
- [grunts]
Sorry to wake you,
but we have approximately three minutes.
- All right. [grunts]
- [giggles]
[sighs]
You know, I'm gonna miss this view.
[Nick chuckles] You checking me out?
Behave.
[both chuckle]
- All right, close your eyes.
- Why?
Close your eyes.
Come here.
Open them.
[Noah gasps]
Happy birthday.
[Noah] I love it.
[Nick] This is so you don't forget
about me when you're in Oxford.
I love you.
It never gets old, hearing you say that.
Go on then.
- Say it back.
- [giggles]
Say it.
I love you too, Nick.
[both chuckle]
Mmm. Right.
[grunts] Stay.
- [shushes]
- [chuckles]
- His alarm went off two minutes ago.
- [sighs]
- When are we telling them again?
- Soon.
I just… Not now.
My dad's got a lot on his mind. Okay?
- We'll tell them. Just not right now.
- Fine.
God, you look good.
I just wanna stay in bed with you.
- Mmm.
- [giggles]
- See you at breakfast.
- [scoffs]
[floorboard creaking]
- Morning, Nick.
- [breathes shakily]
Morning. Hey.
- You're up early.
- [Nick] Yeah.
Couldn't sleep, so I just thought I'd
start working on that acquisition speech.
I could do with your help
if you don't mind.
- I'd be delighted.
- Great.
I must say, I'm very impressed
with your dedication to this launch.
- Let's go in my office.
- Great.
Uh, yeah, so I've got, like,
three openings.
- [Nick's dad] Yeah?
- [Nick] Yeah…
[Jenna] So am I getting a Porsche
for my birthday then?
- [Noah's mum chuckles] No.
- [Nick] Morning.
[Nick's dad] So how's
the boxing gym going? Business good?
It's good. Um, Jenna's been fundraising
quite a bit, you know.
Getting… Getting kids from different
backgrounds involved, and that.
[Jenna] Mmm. Yeah, honestly,
it's got so much potential.
The kids are getting so much out of it.
It's just beautiful.
- That is good.
- She's the brains, I'm the brawn.
- [chuckles]
- [Nick's dad] I'd love to see some time.
Seriously.
[Noah's mum]
Well, that's a sweet necklace.
Oh, yeah. Uh, it was a gift.
[Noah's mum] Who gave you that?
Uh, Jenna. It was a birthday present.
- What?
- The necklace.
Yeah, I got her that necklace.
- Oh, yeah?
- Mad budget for pressies this year, me.
- [Noah's mum] Oh.
- See what you're getting for Christmas.
[chuckles]
Coffee, anyone?
- [Noah's mum] Yes, please.
- Yes, please. Thank you.
Gonna miss this, and you,
little miss Oxford.
[all chuckling]
["You Got It"
by Your Friend Polly playing]
♪ I've been lookin' for it every day
and every night ♪
♪ I've been seein' things I like
to the left and to the right ♪
♪ I've been walkin' round in circles
I've been goin' out my mind ♪
♪ I can feel it all around me
I don't even have to try ♪
♪ I don't even have to try
I don't ♪
I don't, now ♪
[vocalising]
♪ You want it? You got it ♪
♪ I wanna take it with me
everywhere I go…
[music continues faintly]
- [car door closes]
- Package securely delivered.
- She drives like a dream.
- Did she?
You wanted to give the chauffeur
the day off, did you?
Yeah, well, Noah has a lot of stuff, so I
thought you could use the muscle power.
[Noah scoffs]
♪ Running fast, let's take it slow now…
- [Noah's mum] Oh, my God.
- [Noah] It's crazy.
- [Nick] Training to be a wizard, are you?
- [Noah chuckles]
- [music continues]
- [students chattering]
♪ You want it? You got it ♪
[vocalising]
Oh, God. Here we go.
It's freshers drinks in the JCR tonight.
See you there?
Oh. Sounds good. Thanks.
You can bring your sister if you like.
[Noah, Noah's mum chuckle]
Can't stand rugby boys. [sighs]
- Oh, rugby boys are my favourite.
- [Noah] Mom!
- I am number 11. Where's that?
- [music continues]
[speaks indistinctly]
♪ You want it? You got it ♪
[music ends]
That's nice.
Do you know anything
about your neighbours?
- We could say hi.
- Yeah, maybe.
Right… [strains] …that's the last of them.
What do you wanna do with these?
Uh, just put… Just…
You can leave that there, it's fine.
- I could make the bed.
- We could help you decorate.
Uh, I'll take it from here.
She doesn't need anything else?
- No, no.
- Mmm.
Oh! Forgot her key. [chuckles]
Oh, yeah.
[door opens]
[passionate music playing]
- You forgot your key.
- [keys jingle]
[chuckles]
[breathing heavily]
[breathing continues]
[whispers] I want you
to think of me when you're out tonight.
[whispers] I will.
[exhales sharply]
Good.
[music continues]
[door opens]
No way.
- [door closes]
- Nick Leister.
- Briar.
- What are you doing here?
Oh, I was just, um…
uh, dropping off my stepsister.
Uh, really? So, Will remarried then?
- Yeah, yeah.
- [gasps] My God.
Got into Oxford then?
Well, yeah. [chuckles]
Look, I've gotta go, but it's, um…
it's great to see you.
So convincing. [sighs]
[knocks on door]
Hello. I'm Briar.
I'm in the room next door.
Oh, hey.
Which statistically means we're
pretty much doomed to be best friends,
whether we like it or not. [exclaims]
So I was wondering if you
wanted to just sort of jump the gun
and start by getting pissed together?
- [dance music playing]
- [cheering]
[all cheer]
[speaks indistinctly]
[Briar] Which one do you want?
- [Noah] Hmm?
- Mister Stripes or Mister Tie?
- [chuckles]
- Or Mister Ankle Socks?
- No.
- I think stripy boy has
a little crush on me,
but if you have a pref, I don't mind.
- I'm good, I'm good.
- What do you mean you're good?
- I kind of have a boyfriend.
- Noah! Absolutely not.
- [chuckles]
- That is so boring for me.
Uni is literally for exploring
your options. You're young.
- You sound like my mother.
- She sounds fucking cool then.
- [chuckles]
- Seriously.
- I mean, is he hotter than those guys?
- Yeah. He is.
- Is he? Actually?
- Yeah. You'll see.
- You're gonna meet him.
- Really?
- Yeah, he dropped me off this morning.
- Okay.
- Oh, did he?
- Mm-hmm.
Okay, well, tell me everything.
It's kind of a secret.
Perfect, I love secrets.
[bell tolling]
[hopeful music playing]
Ooh. Sorry, sorry.
[professor] Good morning, and welcome
to aerothermal engineering.
Uh, shall we get started then?
Who can tell me what we're looking at?
How about you?
[music stops]
Um…
Uh, that's the Brawn GP F1 car from 2009.
They found a loophole
in the air regulations
and, uh, created the double
diffuser which increases downforce.
You're both absolutely correct.
The Brawn diffuser was carefully shaped
with winglets along the edge.
Who can tell me what they do?
They manage the transition
of air between high and low spaces.
Yeah. And they're made to help
with uplift on aeroplanes.
The guy who invented them
was actually inspired by birds
who curl their wing feathers up.
- You're correct.
- [professor clears throat]
- [both] Yes?
- Sorry to interrupt this mating ritual…
[students laugh]
…but may I continue my class, please?
Thank you.
Today we're covering
the purpose of winglets,
first applications…
[students chattering]
Well, that was fun, wasn't it?
Shouldn't have finished my sentences
if you didn't want me finishing yours.
Good. Finally met my match.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Michael.
I'm Noah.
Okay, Noah.
So which part of America are you from?
Which posh British boarding school
spat you out?
Very good, but wrong.
See, at my school, if you spoke in class,
you were more likely to get a black eye
than a girl ask for your number.
I didn't ask you for your number.
Not yet.
Also, some second-year advice.
There's a tradition around campus that
if you drop a book in front of someone,
- they have to write their number in it.
- Is there?
Yeah, it's actually, uh,
in the Oxford handbook right there,
- on page…
- [thuds]
- Oops.
- [scoffs]
- Let me get that for you.
- [chuckles]
Oh, my God. [scoffs]
Wow.
It's a little much, but lesson learned.
There.
Just in case you need me.
Maybe if I need to fact check you.
See you around, Noah.
[Nick chuckles] So, you're telling me
you got called out in your first lecture?
[Noah] I knew the answer.
[scoffs] God, you're such a teacher's pet.
I don't know about that.
It is stiff competition in intro
to aerothermal engineering.
- What, is everyone a nerd?
- [chuckles]
Uh, yeah. One in particular.
One in particular?
Well, does this nerd have a name?
[chuckles] Uh, Michael.
He's a second year.
Yeah, well, you know I'll kill
any guy who comes near you.
[chuckles] Stop.
[grunts] I'm tired.
My dad's putting a lot of pressure
on me with this merger.
I'm just nervous about Friday.
Hey, it'll be great.
I'll be there watching.
Oh, God, now I'm more nervous.
[chuckles] Why? If you blow it, I'll just
pull the fire alarm or something.
[both chuckle]
I love you.
I love you more. Will you stay
on the phone while I go to sleep?
Yeah, of course.
It's like you're here in my flat,
right next to me.
[chuckles]
[chattering]
[announcer] The press event
will be starting in 15 minutes.
Please make your way
to the conference room.
- Hiya. How you doing?
- All right.
[speaks indistinctly]
[water running]
[water stops]
- [object clatters]
- Ooh, shoot.
Oh, um…
Use mine.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
- Gosh, thank you so much.
- [chuckles]
You're a life saver. [chuckles]
[breathes deeply]
You look great.
Thank you.
I'm not usually this nervous.
Maybe it's because
I'm sat next to the golden boy of tech…
who's also annoyingly attractive. [laughs]
What a combo, right?
Anyway, thank you. Wish me luck.
Good luck.
[door opens, closes]
[announcer] Please make your way
to the conference room.
Hi, sweetheart.
They're about to start, shall we sit?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Yeah?
[audience applauding]
Now, before we wrap up today, a question
that's on everyone's minds…
- [camera shutter clicking]
- …a-a heavy question.
Was this new direction
for Leister Enterprises
influenced by your stepdaughter's
kidnapping last June?
[Will] Actually, it was Nick's idea
to acquire a security start-up.
Um… [clicks tongue]
Look, this isn't exactly easy
to talk about
because, like you're touching on, Sandra,
it hits close to home. Literally.
Um, after what happened last year,
I just… [stammers]
I felt like I had to do something.
Because when it's your family and…
and the people you love, you protect them.
And, uh, that's why we're doing this.
It's as simple as that.
Uh, a question. Yes, David?
[David] Question for Sophia Aitken.
Uh, the tech that you pioneered has had no
shortage of offers from Silicon Valley.
So why choose
Nick and Leister Enterprises,
who have considerably
less experience in the industry?
Well, I've always had
big ambitions for my tech
and a strong desire
to see it do well in the market,
so, yes,
I was very particular in my search.
But Nick is the first person I've met
whose passion and drive
genuinely matches my own.
Oh, well, I feel the exact same.
[Sophia] So, very excited
to work with him on this.
[Sandra] Well, hard to argue
with a connection like that.
[audience applauds]
[Sandra] That's all we have
time for today, folks. Thank you.
She's so impressive, isn't she?
Mm-hmm.
- [lift dings]
- [Noah's mum] Shall we go back home?
Um… Oh, I think I'm…
I'm going to see Jenna.
Oh, really? Where are you meeting her?
I can't remember the name.
Why are you here?
What?
Why did you drive all the way from Oxford
for a boring corporate press event?
I just wanted to support the family.
Please don't lie to me.
You looked at Sophia the way
that Nick looked at those rugby players.
There's something going on
between you two.
Come on. No, I didn't, Mom.
I'm your mother. I can feel it.
Okay. I promise I was going…
- I was gonna tell you.
- You're step siblings, for God's sake.
[lift doors open]
[Will] It went really well.
Nick did great.
- [Noah's mum] No, I agree.
- [Will] I knew he wouldn't let me down.
Made a great team, eh?
[Noah's mum] You're gonna be
really happy with the press coverage.
Right, ladies,
you're gonna have to excuse us,
'cause Nick and I
are gonna take Sophia to lunch.
And then throw her straight into
a big meeting this afternoon.
Uh, I haven't got it on my calendar.
I booked the afternoon off.
That's nonsense,
this is much more important.
You gotta strike
while the iron's hot. [chuckles]
- [kisses]
- [whispers] She knows.
- Have a lovely afternoon.
- Bye, darling.
[whispers] She knows.
[Will] Nick. The work starts now.
Noah, you and Nick need to end
whatever this is right now,
because if you think this is a reaction,
just wait and see what William
would do if it gets back to him.
- Hi, Ella!
- Isabelle.
[sighs]
[Briar] Well, it sounds like London
was an absolute nightmare.
- Yeah, Nick's freaking out.
- [Noah] Duh.
But you know what?
Maybe it's not the worst thing,
- if it's out in the open.
- Mmm. Okay. [scoffs]
Noah, wake up, he's never telling his dad.
- Okay. Come on.
- He has commitment issues.
Babe, you can't let guys play you.
They'll take advantage every time.
- Nick's not like that. You'll see.
- Will I?
I mean, we're at a buffet
of Britain's finest male specimens,
- and you're not even gonna have a taste?
- [chuckles]
No? Not even a little…
Oh, look who it is.
Sweet, sweet lover boy.
I'll eat him if you won't.
Look, Briar, don't say anything weird.
Never.
Oh, shit. [clears throat]
Behave. [clears throat]
Here.
While you were off gallivanting yesterday,
I was busy making notes on traction.
- Enjoy.
- Oh.
Uh, thank you. That is very kind of you.
Briar. So, Michael, Noah tells me
that you are a second year.
- [Noah chuckles]
- Older, wiser.
Bet you've got so much to teach us.
- She's been talking about me?
- Yeah, these notes, thank you again.
Uh, I owe you one.
[Michael] You do. What about tonight?
Yes, perfect. Oh, my God,
we're going to the pub tonight.
You can be my date.
We're meeting Noah's boyfriend.
- Boyfriend?
- Yeah, boyfriend.
Boyfriend.
- I don't have a boyfriend.
- [Noah, Michael chuckles]
[Michael]
Cannot believe you got that one wrong.
[Noah] I didn't.
You just answered first. [scoffs]
- Yeah, it was obviously upward thrust.
- [scoffs] Right.
- It's not about power, it's about control.
- [doors open]
[Noah] Right, obviously. Only an idiot
wouldn't have gotten it, thank you.
[Briar] Fascinating.
How's your upward thrust, Michael?
- [chuckles] Briar.
- [Briar] Genuine question.
- It's pretty good, I think.
- Do you focus on power or control?
Guys, Nick's here.
[Michael] Bit of both, I think.
Hey.
Look, they know about us. It's fine.
Guys, this is Nick.
Nick, this is Briar.
She's, um, in my halls.
[Briar] Nice to meet you.
Nick, is it? I've heard a lot about you.
- [Noah] And this is Michael, the guy that…
- Hi.
…jumped in on my answer
in the first class.
- Bailed you out.
- Mmm, I don't know about that.
Someone's a bit competitive. [chuckles]
I take notes for Noah when she's
skipping classes for her boyfriend.
- Right.
- So, do you take notes
for all the freshers?
No, I think it's just Noah. Yeah.
- Yeah, only the smart ones. [chuckles]
- Thank you.
Finally. [chuckles]
- And how did you guys…
- We're next-door neighbours.
- Doomed to be best friends, I was told.
- Yeah. No, absolutely.
Can I get you a drink?
No, no. Drinks are on me.
- Are you getting the same again?
- [Noah] Yeah.
I might get something different.
I'll go help him.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, yeah.
Okay.
He seems really nice.
- You'll get to know him better.
- Yeah. He seems fun.
Gin and lemonade, please.
Uh, double, and you can put it on his tab.
[inhales sharply]
Briar, what the hell are you doing?
I don't know what you mean.
Okay, look,
I feel bad about what happened,
but it has nothing to do with Noah,
so leave her out of it.
God, you make everything
about yourself, Nick.
I like Noah. Is that so hard to believe?
Thank you.
Would you like me to take that for you?
Otherwise you'll have
your hands a bit full.
Go on, then.
- That is…
- [Briar] Aw.
Better luck next… Oh, darling.
- Don't cry. Don't cry, baby.
- I'm not. [chuckles] Shut up.
Right, watch and learn.
- Unlucky.
- Mmm.
[kisses]
- [Michael] You can't just do that.
- Yes, I can.
- [chuckles]
- [Michael] Play.
- Don't you just love Briar?
- [balls knocking]
She's so funny. [chuckles]
[whispers] I kind of thought
we were gonna be alone.
You want me alone?
["Los Ageless" by St. Vincent playing]
♪ The Los Ageless hang out by the bar ♪
♪ Burn the pages of unwritten memoirs ♪
♪ But I can keep running
No, I can keep running ♪
♪ How can anybody have you? ♪
♪ How can anybody have you and lose you? ♪
♪ How can anybody have you and lose you
and not lose their minds…
[music stops]
[door opens]
[lights flickering]
[whistles]
You let yourself in, yeah?
Hey, I've always thought
this gym was nice, man.
Could do with a few touch-ups,
but, you know, it's got character.
[scoffs] I hear it's been
in your family for time, yeah?
Yeah, my dad left it to me when he passed.
You got balls for… [scoffs]
…putting it all on the line.
That's quite the risk.
Yeah.
- [scoffs]
- Shall we?
It's all there.
[inhales deeply]
You're barely scraping by, man.
What you gonna do when your boy loses?
He's not gonna lose.
- [chuckles]
- [taps bank notes on table]
I'm excited.
You know, Ronnie's excited too.
I don't know whether he cares
more about taking over this shithole,
or making Nick pay for putting him away.
Pick that shit up, man.
- [door opens]
- [sighs]
[door closes]
[phone buzzes]
[scoffs]
I can't believe you bought a motorcycle.
I thought you were done
with the bad boy clichés.
I know you like it. Just admit it.
[closes zip]
I thought you were gonna take me
for a ride this weekend.
- I'll take you for a ride right now.
- No. Duty calls.
I'm sorry, I'd love to stay,
but I've got so much work.
- Yeah, how's that going?
- Uh, good, actually.
I'm learning a lot.
Sophia has a lot to teach.
- Who's the teacher's pet now?
- Ha, ha. Very funny.
I think you'd like her, you know.
She's coming on Saturday to the tennis.
- Why?
- I don't know, my dad invited her.
Great, family lunch, and Sophia. [scoffs]
We're just playing pretend.
I don't wanna keep hiding us
now that my mom knows, okay?
I don't know how much longer
I can keep on doing this.
Hey. Let's not be dramatic.
You look beautiful.
[engine starts, revs]
[Sophia grunts]
[Sophia] Wonderful shot!
William, I didn't take you
for a professional.
- [grunts]
- [Will chuckles] Ooh.
- I like that.
- [Sophia laughs]
One second, Noah, me and Sophia just
need to finish thrashing the opposition.
[Will chuckles]
[Sophia laughs]
- [grunts]
- [Will] That was fantastic.
Great shot.
- [Sophia laughing]
- Come on!
Beautiful.
[teasing music playing]
[chuckles]
Lovely stroke, Nick.
Good game. Yes.
That's 40-love.
- [ball thuds]
- [grunts]
- [Nick] Lovely.
Strong backhand.
- [grunts]
- [Nick] Come on, Sophia.
- Oh, yes!
- [Sophia] Yes!
- Yes!
- [Nick chuckles] Yes!
- Give me some.
- [laughs]
- We are the best. Well done, everybody.
- [music stops]
- Well done.
- Good game.
- Fantastic. Well done.
- Well done.
[Will, Ella chuckle]
[Ella] Hi, sweetheart.
[Will] Noah, have you met Sophia?
- Leister Enterprises' hottest recruit.
- [Sophia] Oh.
Yeah. Yeah, we met at the launch.
Yeah. Sorry, I feel like I took your spot.
Did you want to play?
- [Ella chuckles]
- Noah hates tennis.
- Why? It's so much fun.
- [Will] Of course it is…
- [Sophia chuckles]
- …with a game as strong as yours.
You were rather carrying
your team, I thought.
Well, I guess we're taking it
in turns then.
You should've seen Nick
at the investment meeting, Will.
- He was brilliant.
- [Will] Now,
will you join us for lunch at the club?
- Oh, no. Too much to prepare for Monday.
- [Ella] Oh, do.
Oh, come on, Monday's ages away.
I think she said she couldn't.
Okay, well, I have a couple of calls
to catch up on,
- but then I'll come join you.
- Awesome.
[Will] Working on a Saturday? Wow.
You should take note, Nick.
Gosh, she's got great tennis game.
You'd think she was a semi-pro.
[Nick] She's, like, real head-girl energy.
[Will] Now that is
an impressive young woman.
You two really complement each other,
on the court, in the office.
Have you considered
teaming up socially, perhaps?
- Dad.
- Come on! You'd make a great couple.
Wouldn't they, ladies?
- She is lovely.
- Mom.
[Ella] What?
She's a very eligible bachelorette.
[Will] If you're not seeing anyone,
why not throw your hat in the ring?
Yeah. Why not, Nick?
Throw your hat in the ring?
She really is the full package.
[Will] Am I missing something? [chuckles]
Well, are you seeing someone?
[Nick] Noah, don't.
Oh, that's right. He is.
Me.
[scoffs]
[ice rattles]
[sighs]
Have you thought about this at all?
What happens when you fall out?
[sighs]
Dad.
Say something.
What do you expect me to say?
I don't know how you can be so reckless.
Can you imagine if this got out?
One seedy tabloid headline
and the investors would run for the hills!
[cutlery clatters]
This isn't about ethics.
This is about optics.
And I will not let you
destroy the family business.
I don't see what we're doing wrong.
Okay, if this is so serious,
then I'm sure you'd be willing
to make the necessary sacrifices.
If you choose to pursue this relationship,
then Nick,
you can cease working
for Leister Enterprises for good.
- Dad…
- And, Noah,
you can either find another way to pay
your tuition fees for Oxford or drop out.
- [gasps]
- [Ella] William…
So sorry to make you all wait.
[Will]
Oh, don't be so silly. Perfectly timed.
- [chair scrapes]
- How was the call?
[Sophia] Great, yeah.
- I'll drop you an email on Monday.
- [Will] Ah, excellent.
That went a lot worse
than I thought it would.
Really? 'Cause that seemed
to go pretty well to me.
Oh, God.
This is exactly what I was avoiding!
The exact thing!
[sighs] Sorry. Okay, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I just think
that we could've handled that way better.
I know.
- What are we gonna do?
- I don't know.
[sighs]
Okay, we-we have to lay low.
Make them… Make them think it's over,
and then we-we have to be
on our best behaviour.
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
Back to sneaking around.
[sighs]
Why don't we stay at yours tonight?
Spend the day together tomorrow.
- I don't wanna have to go back with them…
- I can't tonight. I've got work tomorrow.
It's a Sunday.
It's like a… It's like a Zoom…
It's like a Zoom thing.
Zoom with a colleague.
Okay. Of course you do.
[both sigh]
[Noah] It just couldn't have gone
any worse.
Shit, I didn't realise William
had it in him.
And my mom was just sat there,
saying nothing.
I just wish I could talk to Nick,
but he's working, so I can't.
Uh, yeah, so about…
So we're back
to sneaking around and lying.
So are we just gonna, what, pretend
to break up? Fake break up?
I don't know. It just feels like
we're taking steps back,
- not steps forward.
- On the subject of lying, um,
I don't think Nick's at work today.
- What?
- I got a text from Zach.
"Yo, Jen, you coming?" and his location.
They're at an abandoned airbase
at the moment.
What does that mean?
If I know our boys, they're not exactly
there to soak up the history of the place.
You've gotta be kidding me.
["STARTAFIGHT"
by Joey Valence & Brae playing]
[engines roaring]
[Nick] Oh, my God. This race really
couldn't have come at a worse time.
And why is there always so much drama?
All she had to do
was wait two weeks at most.
What does she go do?
Tells my dad at tennis.
- Do you get what I mean?
- Yes. Yeah, yeah.
Look, let's save it for Monday, all right?
All this stuff with your dad, okay?
But right now, I need you to lock in.
[music continues]
♪ Let's start a fight, let's start a fight
let's start a fight…
[engine revving]
[music stops]
- Ooh.
- You're joking.
- [car door opens]
- Oh, my God.
Wow. Who you meant to be?
Ronnie's back up dancer?
I see the big man with the shit hair
and the knitted vest.
What you doing, man? Where you been?
I thought your girl had you on a leash.
Isn't that right, Lion?
[scoffs] This guy.
Is something funny to you?
- Everything you say is funny.
- [chuckles]
You know what is funny?
- What?
- If you don't win,
your boy's gym is mine.
Save your boy, man.
Cruz? I'm racing Cruz?
Yeah, I mentioned. I mentioned.
- You didn't mention that.
- A race is a race, come on. Lock in.
- Is he wearing a crop top?
- Here we go.
- My boy.
- [Nick] Great, just what I needed.
Seems the girlfriends
are letting 'em out to play.
Nah, we've just got better places
to be than you, JP.
[JP] I'm glad it's you behind the wheel.
Lion would've got battered.
Okay, okay. That's why he's my best man.
[kisses] Let's go. Let's do it. Love.
- He good?
- Yeah. Yeah, he's sweet, man.
He's good, he's good.
Today just might not be the day for all
the girlfriend chit-chat, you feel me?
Speaking of girlfriends, Jenna's coming.
What do you mean, Jenna's coming?
Jenna. I texted her.
- Why? Is that a problem?
- [engine roars]
- [car horn honks]
- [tyres screech]
[engine stops]
["CPR" by Wet Leg playing]
♪ Put your mouth to mine and give me CPR ♪
[engines revving]
♪ Call the triple nine and give me CPR…
No, no, no. God.
- [music stops]
- [car door opens]
- Noah. What are you doing here?
- I could ask you the same thing.
- Is this your Zoom with a colleague?
- Get out the car.
- The race is about to start. Get out.
- [buzzer sounds]
- [engines rev]
- [crowd cheering, applauding]
Get out the car! It's about to start!
- [buzzer sounds]
- [engines revving]
Let's fucking go.
If you race, I race.
[Nick] Shit!
- ["GREEN LIGHT" by NOISY playing]
- [cheering]
- [engines roaring]
- [tyres squealing]
Yeah, boy, I'm coming for you.
- I know you're mad.
- What the fuck are you doing here?
- I thought we were done with this shit.
- I'm sorry, I'm here for Lion.
- That's not helping, you both promised!
- Yes, and we meant it.
It was… It was a last-minute thing.
- Last minute thing?
- They called me. I showed up, okay?
Have you bet our money on this race? Lion?
Just one last race, okay?
And then we're done.
But I have to win, otherwise this
will have all been for nothing.
I can't drive and debate
with you at the same fucking time!
Fine!
- [tyres squealing]
- [music continues]
- Get in the slipstream.
- What?
Do you wanna win?
Oh, you think you can get ahead, yeah?
I'm right behind you.
[engines roaring]
You can out-brake him,
just pull the inside line.
- Holding.
- [tyres squeal]
[Noah] Watch out, watch out, watch out!
Told you.
[groans] Why's he so fast, man?
Why you driving a Ford Focus, man?
Get out the way!
What?
I make the rules, yeah?
[laughs]
Where's he gone?
- Shit.
- No way is that part of the track!
[music muffled]
[music continues]
Shit, shit, shit, shit.
Go, go, go, go!
[laughs] Your gym's mine, man!
- Shit.
- Go, go, go, go.
- [groans] Come on!
- What the hell?
- No!
- Yes!
Come on!
[tyres squealing]
[crowd cheering]
Bap, bap, bap. Come on, bro.
[sighs]
- I'm sorry.
- [cheering continues]
[engine revs]
What's the point of being the best
if no one knows it?
Come on! [laughs]
- Nick, he cheated.
- Don't.
- How fucking dare he?
- [Nick] Noah, don't.
- [person] That's how you do it, bro.
- Hey!
[grunts]
You cheated.
That wasn't part of the track.
Prove it.
- I want a rematch.
- [scoffs] I don't do rematches.
- [Nick] Noah, come on. Let's go.
- Ooh, Noah?
I know you.
Nick, this is your girl, yeah?
You know what?
Normally, I don't do rematches,
but for a legend like you,
I can make an exception.
No, Noah.
- Let's do it.
- Get in your car.
Come on, Noah.
You're just making it worse.
Lion, let's see if this girl
can save your gym.
- We're going again!
- [cheering]
Yo, boss man. I won.
And you'll never guess who just asked me
for a rematch. [chuckles]
The one person you hate more
than Nick Leister.
No way.
Come on, Noah.
Why can't you stay out of shit
that has nothing to do with you?
Okay? We were handling it.
- You bet the gym on a race?
- I didn't have a choice.
- Classic.
- [sirens wailing]
- Shit.
- [Lion] Where's Jenna?
[Nick] We need to go.
[wailing continues]
- Jenna!
- Lion, come on. We gotta go.
Get in the car. We gotta go.
Hey. I'll let you know
when and where, yeah?
- [engine roars]
- Go, go, go, go.
- You're not racing that guy.
- But I'll win, easily.
- I don't care if you win. It's not safe.
- So it's fine for you to do it,
- but not for me?
- No, it's not fine.
It was stupid, I shouldn't have done it.
But you have to admit,
it was a little fun.
[scoffs]
Jen? Jen?
I'm taking responsibility, all right?
Look, please. Please.
- Lion, not now. No.
- Please.
[groans]
Babe, can I come with you
to Oxford for a couple of days?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- [Nick] You good?
- Yeah.
- Got left with a warning, so I'm great.
- She's good, she's good. Jen?
But now I'm warning you to leave me alone.
Just talk to me, please.
Lion, I love you,
but I need a minute, okay?
Okay?
[Lion] Yeah.
Sort your shit out, man.
- I love you.
- [engine starts]
[upbeat music plays on radio]
[engine roars in distance]
I'm sorry, man.
All right? I lied to you, and…
- Noah's not racing Cruz.
- No way.
- I know.
- If she knew he worked for Ronnie…
Of course. Of course, I get it.
I just…
I don't know what I'm gonna do, bro.
I'm… [stammers]
I'm gonna lose the gym,
I'm gonna lose Jenna.
Right, look,
I'm gonna say this for the last time.
Let me help you.
How?
I've seen Jenna's business plans.
They're good.
Let me take them to the company, show them
to the board, let us invest in you.
I'm not gonna let you say no, so… [sighs]
[both chuckle]
- You're crazy.
- Yeah?
[chuckles]
I love you, man.
[students chattering]
[door opens]
- [items thud]
- [keys jingle]
[chuckles]
- [Michael chuckles] Nice.
- [Noah] Why are you so bad?
- [phone buzzing]
- [Michael chuckling] Come on, come on.
Oh, gosh.
- Hey.
- [Nick] Hi.
Glad you liked your flowers.
[chuckles] Yeah.
I'm impressed you remembered.
Are you still with Jenna? [sighs]
How's she doing?
Um…
[video game music playing]
Yeah, she's okay.
We're dressing up for the British Icons
party tonight. Spice Girls.
- Fancy dress? Is there…
- Pause! [chuckles] Sorry, um,
I'm currently thrashing Michael
at this vid… video game!
- Yes! [laughs]
- [Michael grunts, sighs]
You too hang out a lot.
Yeah, he's… he's just a friend.
Yeah, as long as he knows that.
Listen, don't freak out.
Why would I freak out?
I have to go on a little work trip,
um, to meet some investors.
It's only one night. We have to play golf.
Which is annoying, because
I'm even worse at that than tennis.
We?
[stammers] Me and Sophia.
[scoffs] Right.
Well, you too hang out a lot.
Yes, for work, Noah.
She's just a colleague.
- As long as she knows that.
- She knows.
Listen,
we can still do our goodnight call.
I have a dinner first,
but I'll call you after, okay?
I promise.
Yeah. Okay, fine.
- [door opens]
- What time do you…
[Nick] Yes. I'll get the files
to you by end of play.
- Nick?
- Yeah. Take care.
Nicholas. [sighs]
Have you taken care
of what we spoke about?
You okay, babe?
- Uh, yeah.
- Yeah?
Yeah. Yeah, it's, uh, sorted.
Good.
Listen, I plan to oversee this deal.
But you've proven to me
that you're more than up to the task.
You're starting to remind me
of myself when I was your age.
I want you to lead on this.
Really?
This was always part of the plan,
you know.
Look… [sighs]
I know I wasn't around
a lot when you were younger.
I was busy building all of this for you.
[helicopter blades whirring]
[indistinct chatter on radio]
[Sophia] Are you scared
of heights or something?
No, I'm scared of golf.
You're all over the pitch,
that's what matters.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
You have a very clear, very compelling
vision for the business, Nick.
You're gonna smash it.
Okay.
Let's do this.
[inspirational music playing]
- [music stops]
- [grunts]
- [birds squawk]
- [caddy] Four!
[Nick] I need to get a grip,
I need to get a grip.
- [chuckles]
- This is humiliating.
Don't worry,
it's better for business if you lose.
- [sighing]
- You're doing great.
I think I'm just terrified
of disappointing my dad.
- It's pathetic, isn't it?
- No, I get it.
My house was a bit of a pressure cooker
growing up.
My mum had an affair.
And I saw how ruthless my dad is with
people who disappoint him, so I didn't.
I made sure I was perfect.
At everything.
Well, we have a lot in common,
except I did the complete opposite.
Went completely off the rails.
Drink, drugs, illegal racing, fighting.
As you do.
- So, I've got a lot to prove.
- Hmm.
Well, well, well. Aren't you a dark horse?
That's the wrong one.
["1999" by Charli XCX
and Troye Sivan playing]
♪ Back to 1999…
- [Briar] No, get closer.
- [Noah] Come on, take a picture.
- [camera shutter clicks]
- [Briar] Yes, smile. Whoo!
- Yes, Jenna.
- [shrieking]
- Oh, wait, be careful.
- [Michael] Oh, my God, yes.
- [laughing]
- [Noah] You look great.
Cheers!
[Briar] Michael!
- [all laughing, cheering]
- [camera shutter clicking]
♪ I just wanna go back, back to 1999 ♪
♪ Take a ride to my old neighborhood…
[laughs]
- [music fades]
- [classical music playing]
We've had a great day of playing golf.
- Well, some of us.
- [all laugh]
We're building so much more
than just a company.
We're building something that will
hopefully shift the entire landscape
of security technology,
which is why Nick and I feel so confident
in this partnership.
We're ready to move forward when you are.
- [all] Cheers.
- [glasses clinking]
[Nick] Cheers.
["19-2000 (Soulchild Remix)" by Gorillaz
playing on speakers]
[guests cheering, laughing]
- [laughs]
- Okay. Okay, okay, okay.
Truth or dare?
- Truth.
- Ooh.
Um, okay.
Tell… Tell us something
that you've never told Nick.
- [chuckles] You cheeky girl.
- I'm not sure if he knows everything…
- [giggles]
- Okay.
- [Jenna] Go on.
- Don't tell him.
I'm kind of excited to race Cruz.
- [laughs]
- Wait, his name is Cruz,
and he races cars?
You should've seen this guy.
What kind of prick gets the word
"savage" tattooed on his own face?
He was wearing my outfit.
[both laugh]
- Wait, why do you wanna race this guy?
- [Noah] I don't know.
I kind of… I guess I ran away from racing
after everything that happened
with my dad. [inhales deeply]
So, this feels like a sign.
- To face my fear.
- [Michael] Mm-hmm.
[chuckles] You remind me of my mum.
- I'm sorry, what?
- Excellent.
- It's a compliment.
- [scoffs] Is it?
[stammers] She's a boss.
No, she's a boss. [chuckles]
Yeah, she flew jets
for the Royal Air Force.
- Mad. Really?
- No way.
Yeah, big adrenaline junkie, like you.
And she saw some dark shit.
And she always said that the only way
to deal with her trauma
was to get back in the cockpit.
- She sounds awesome.
- [Michael] She is.
I-I'd love to see you race.
Well, you should come.
- It's kind of like hush-hush though.
- [Briar] 'Scuse, 'scuse. Coming through.
Noah, slightly awkward question for you.
- Mm-hmm?
- [clears throat] Um,
a girl at the bar was asking about Nick.
She said that she saw you guys together,
and she was just, like,
wondering if you're an item,
and if not, uh,
whether you could hook her up.
- Oh. Right. [chuckles]
- Yeah, I know, big stalker vibes.
Thing is, I wasn't really sure,
like, what… like, what to say.
[Michael] What were you so unsure about?
He is your boyfriend, isn't he?
Y-Yeah, yeah.
- Yeah, but it's a secret.
- It's just, we're kind of keeping it quiet
at the moment, um,
just 'cause of his work situation.
Right.
- It's not a big deal.
- Mmm.
Can we not talk about
our dickhead boyfriends for one night…
- [slurping]
- …and just get really wasted
and have a little boogie?
[all chattering, cheering]
["Memories (2021 Remix)" by David Guetta
ft. Kid Cudi playing on speakers]
- Let's dance!
- [cheering]
[music continues faintly]
Did we actually just do that?
- Yeah. [laughs]
- You were incredible.
- Thank you.
- Let's party.
Okay.
- [glasses clatter]
- [Nick] That's everything from my room.
Tequila.
- Congratulations, good sir.
- Congratulations.
- We did the deal. We did the deal.
- We did the deal.
- [cheering]
- [music continues]
[speaking indistinctly]
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Hey, hey ♪
♪ All the crazy shit I did tonight ♪
♪ Those will be the best memories ♪
♪ I just wanna let it go for the night…
- [Briar] Hey, get off your phone!
- Are you okay?
- Come on then.
- [chuckles]
♪ All the crazy shit I did tonight ♪
♪ Those will be the best memories…
[music continues, muffled]
- [phone buzzing]
- [music continues]
[Noah] Hey, it's me.
Uh, guess you're still at your dinner?
Call me after? Uh, love you.
♪ Hey, hey ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ It's gettin' late but I don't mind ♪
♪ It's gettin' late but I don't mind…
[stammers] It's hot in here.
- [both chuckle]
- Let's get some air.
Okay.
♪ All the crazy shit I did tonight ♪
♪ Those will be the best memories ♪
♪ I just wanna let it go for the night…
[music fades]
- This is cool. [chuckles]
- [chuckles]
Okay, your second-year knowledge
finally coming in handy.
Hey, can I ask you a question?
Sure.
Shoot.
Do you really just not mind…
keeping your relationship
with Nick a secret?
Of course I mind.
It's humiliating.
You don't have to say anything.
- I know you think I'm pathetic.
- [scoffs]
- I can feel you pitying me from here.
- Noah, I-I…
I don't think that.
If I was pitying anyone, it was Nick.
Nick?
Well, you're clearly crazy about him,
and he's too insecure to enjoy it.
Nick's a lot of things,
but he's not insecure.
We're all insecure.
Some of us just hide it
better than others.
If that's the truth,
why didn't he just talk to me about it?
But it can be tough. Especially for guys.
We are conditioned to put up a front.
You're a guy.
How come you're so…
- open?
- [chuckles]
Being emotionally available
helps me pick up girls.
[both chuckle]
I'm serious.
- [both laugh]
- I'm serious.
My therapy bills are high,
but it's worth every penny.
[chuckles] Does that line actually work?
I don't know yet.
[tender music playing]
[guests cheering in distance]
How the fuck do we get down?
The stairs.
Right. [chuckles]
[rhythmic music playing]
- [knocks on door]
- [shushes] Get down. Get down.
[shushes]
[knocks]
- [chuckles]
- [music stops]
[footsteps departing]
[whispers] I think they've gone.
- Wait, why are we hiding?
- [laughs]
I don't know.
[chuckles]
- I feel terrible.
- Why?
- Because.
- Because what?
I hate noisy hotel guests. They are
selfish pricks who deserve to die.
And now I am one.
Deserve to die? That's a little bit harsh,
don't you think?
- Mmm.
- Am I in danger?
[gasps] Maybe.
A cold-blooded killer.
[whispers] I knew it.
Well, maybe you're
getting to know me better.
- What else don't I know?
- Hmm.
I can't show you yet.
But I am full of surprises.
Oh, okay.
[chuckles, scoffs]
Who am I kidding?
I'm usually very buttoned up.
That's not how I see you.
How do you see me, Nick?
[softly] It's late.
I should probably go.
Do you have to?
Yeah.
Goodnight.
[door opens, closes]
- [birds chirping]
- [alarm chiming]
[grunts]
[alarm continues]
Shit.
[grunts]
[alarm stops]
[sighs] Shit.
[line ringing]
Hey, you've reached Noah. Leave a message.
- [line beeps]
- [sighs]
Hey, Noah. It's me.
I'm so sorry I missed our call.
I fell asleep early, I was so tired.
But, you know, I'm gonna come to Oxford
today. I'm gonna come make it up to you.
All right? I'm sorry. Love you.
[grunts]
[sighs]
So, I'd call that a successful trip.
Yep. [sighs]
- Even if the celebrations got a bit…
- Yeah.
It's probably safe to say
we both had a bit too much to drink.
- [sighs]
- Right. [chuckles] Shall we?
Yeah.
[phone buzzes]
[helicopter blades whirring]
[dramatic music playing]
[car engine roaring]
[line ringing]
Hey, you've reached Noah, leave a message.
[Nick] Noah, can you call me back?
I'm started to get really worried.
Okay? I need to know
you got home last night.
I'm on my way to Oxford, call me back.
[knocking on door]
[Noah laughs] Wait, come here.
[chuckling]
Oh, hey. Do you wanna come in?
[Noah] Who is it?
What the fuck are you doing
- in my girlfriend's--
- Nick, stop!
Oh, brilliant. Morning, Leister.
Got some energy today?
No, he went to sleep early, remember?
Oh. So you did get my messages?
So you're ignoring my calls?
- Is that what's happening?
- Well, why didn't you call me last night?
[Jenna] Maybe we should give
these guys some privacy.
Yes. Good luck, babe.
- Get out of my face.
- Nice to see you too, mate. [chuckles]
Go and see Lion, he's miserable.
Oh, okay, moody boy.
- Do you want me to stay?
- No, it's fine. Thank you.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah. Thanks.
- Shall I… Do you want me to…
- Yes.
- Well, that was embarrassing, wasn't it?
- Why is he in your room?
Why are you here? Nick, you ignore me
all night, and then you just barge in.
Can we have this conversation
somewhere else,
- without your friends listening in?
- Fine.
Let's go to yours.
- [door closes]
- [keys clatter]
[Nick sighs]
So, are you gonna keep giving me
the silent treatment,
or do you wanna talk like adults?
Fine, let's talk like adults.
Are you gonna go first, or shall I?
What happened last night?
I told you, I fell asleep.
No, you told me you were gonna call me.
That's what you told me.
I was waiting up for you.
I know, and… [stammers]
…I apologised, okay?
- But I literally just missed your call.
- Okay, well, the last guy that said that
was literally fucking my best friend
behind my back, so…
- I'm not Dan. Don't compare me to Dan.
- I know you're not.
But when you specifically tell me
you're gonna call me and you don't,
and I know that you're staying in a hotel
- with a girl who clearly likes you…
- Oh, my God. For work!
- …my mind goes there.
- Nothing happened, Noah.
It takes two seconds to call me, Nick,
and one second to pick up the phone.
Yeah, well, it takes no seconds
to not be all over Michael.
- What does that even mean?
- I saw the photos from last night.
- That guy is all over you.
- Oh, my God, Nick,
- his arm was around me in a group photo.
- So you know what I'm talking about?
Are you threatened by Michael?
- No, I'm not threatened by Michael.
- Just say it. You're threatened.
- Don't do that. Stop! That pisses me off!
- What?
I'll stop when you stop acting like a baby
and own up to how you feel.
You can talk! [chuckles]
You're literally jealous of Sophia!
Yes. [chuckles] Yes, I am.
I'm jealous of Sophia, okay?
But at least
I can fucking say it. [scoffs]
Okay, fine, I'm jealous of Michael.
Are you happy now?
I don't like that he spends
more time with you than I do,
I don't like that it feels like
he's replacing me,
I know that he's waiting for his moment,
but he's not gonna get his moment
because you're mine.
You don't own me.
I know I don't own you.
But you're still mine.
Say it again.
You're mine.
["Fame is a Gun" by Addison Rae playing]
[breathing heavily]
♪ Tell me who I am ♪
♪ Do I provoke you
with my tone of innocence? ♪
♪ Don't ask too many questions
that is my one suggestion ♪
♪ You know I keep it real
I live for the appeal ♪
♪ Knew it from the start ♪
♪ It was the only way
to mend my broken heart ♪
♪ Don't ask too many questions
This is my one confession ♪
♪ It never was enough
I always wanted more ♪
♪ I always wanted more ♪
♪ Fame is a gun
and I point it blind ♪
♪ Crash and burn, girl
Baby, swallow it dry ♪
♪ You've got a front row seat
and I… ♪
♪ I got a taste of the glamorous life ♪
♪ Nothing makes me feel as good ♪
♪ as being loved by you ♪
♪ Fame is a gun
and I point it blind ♪
♪ Crash and burn, girl
Baby, swallow it dry ♪
♪ You've got a front row seat
and I… ♪
♪ I got a taste of the glamorous life ♪
♪ I got a taste of the glamorous life…
[music fades]
Cheers, cheers, cheers.
Don't get mad at me,
but I might've got a bit carried away.
Nick!
- It's not that bad.
- A hickey?
- It is quite bad.
- Is this high school?
I've marked you,
now everyone's gonna know you're mine.
Okay. Well, how would you like it
if I marked you?
I'd bloody love it.
- Mark me.
- Well, then.
Where are you going?
All right. [clears throat] Stay still.
- No, not pen. No, not pen.
- [laughs] I'm not giving you a hickey.
- I'm not 12.
- Okay, do it there then.
Okay. Ready?
[Nick] I'm sorry we argued.
I'm sorry too.
You know you have nothing
to worry about with Michael.
And I promise you, you have absolutely
nothing to worry about with Sophia.
I like this.
When you're honest with me.
I just need to know
what's going on up there.
It's hard when we're apart.
I love it.
Hey, do you think Jenna
and Lion will be okay?
I do.
Lion's coming in to the office next week.
Leister Enterprises
is investing in his gym.
Yeah, we're coming on as a partner.
Lion's gonna be at the helm.
We're gonna settle his debts.
That's amazing.
And now, you don't have
to race that guy anymore.
Because we've paid him back.
That's a good thing.
I know, I know. I know. I know.
I don't know, part of me was kind of…
looking forward to getting
behind the wheel, feeling…
in control again.
Noah, please promise me you won't do that.
Forget it. Jenna is gonna be so happy
about the gym. [chuckles]
[Nick] She is.
Everything feels like it's gonna be okay.
["Love Me Not" by Ravyn Lenae playing]
Hi.
I'm sorry.
♪ See, right now, I need you ♪
♪ I'll meet you somewhere now ♪
♪ You up now, I see you ♪
♪ I get you, take care now ♪
♪ Slow down, be cool ♪
♪ I miss you, come here now…
- Who does he look like?
- [all chattering indistinctly]
♪ I need you right now ♪
♪ Once I leave you I'm strung out ♪
♪ If I get you…
- Morning.
♪ …I'm slowly breaking down…
- You're early. [laughs]
- I knew you were gonna say that.
I knew you'd just… [sighs]
Well, it's not my fault
you're so predictable.
Oh. [chuckles]
♪ You gotta say that you're sorry…
[speaks indistinctly]
♪ …at the end of the night ♪
♪ Wake up in the morning
Everything's alright ♪
♪ At the end of the story
you're holdin' me tight ♪
♪ I don't need to worry ♪
♪ Am I out of my mind…
- [engine roaring]
- [Noah cheers]
♪ But I wish you were right here…
Oh, come on, go faster.
[Nick] Hold on tight!
♪ All this time I'm thinking
I'm strong enough to sink it ♪
♪ Oh, no, I don't need you
but I miss you, come here…
[music fades]
[chuckles]
What?
Nothing.
I'm just imagining you and Nick
in Ancient Greece.
What do you mean by that, Briar?
No, it's just your situation,
it would just be funny.
Like, if you were a goddess,
and he was a god. You know?
'Cause their punishments were brutal.
And you forgave him, like, super quickly.
I know you think Nick is possessive,
but I get jealous too.
- It's just 'cause we care.
- Mmm.
It's a bit toxic though, no?
Speaking of getting jealous, have you,
uh, stalked Sophia lately?
No, Briar, I don't do that stuff.
What do you mean?
Well, she's not my friend.
No, she's your arch enemy. Look.
Yeah.
They were playing golf with an investor.
It's a work thing.
A work thing?
[shushes]
Shush yourself.
Jesus Christ.
Well, you know what they say,
work hard, play hard?
[sighs]
Wait.
What?
Didn't Nick say he missed your call
because he fell asleep early?
Yes.
Hiya, fancy seeing you two here.
- [student shushes]
- What you two working on?
What's up her arse?
[chuckles]
- You all right?
- [Briar] What?
Noah? Noah?
[door opens]
[Michael] What's going on?
[inhales deeply] What do you think?
[line ringing]
- [phone buzzing]
- [rock music playing on speakers]
Hey, you.
- Thank you.
- Why didn't you answer my call?
At the hotel?
Tell me the truth.
I told you. I fell asleep.
- Don't lie to me.
- What?
Sophia posted pictures of you
in her hotel room at 2.00 a.m.
Okay, look, I know this is gonna look bad.
Nick, what were you doing in her room?
Nothing happened that night, okay?
[stammers] I promise you.
You have to believe me.
I lost track of time.
Why should I believe you?
Okay, I'm sorry. It was just a white lie.
I didn't want you
to get jealous over nothing.
We literally just went to her hotel room.
We had some ch… some champagne,
and we, like… We were
just celebrating closing the deal.
It was nothing. I promise you.
Does she know about me?
About us?
Sophia? No. What?
No, she works for my dad.
That would be too risky.
- Of course not.
- Then it wasn't nothing, Nick.
Even if you are telling the truth.
When a girl likes you
and she thinks you're single,
and you're in her fucking room
at 2.00 a.m., that is not nothing.
- But I didn't--
- When you lied to me about it,
that is a huge betrayal.
- [line beeps]
- Noah?
[phone buzzing]
[buzzing stops]
[Briar sighs] I've been trying
to tell her, but she's not listening.
- I mean, she's right to be jealous.
- Wait. [shushes]
[footsteps approaching]
[desk thuds]
- [Noah breathes shakily]
- Are you okay?
No, I'm not okay.
What happened?
You were right.
He's a piece of shit!
He's a total piece of shit, Noah.
Fuck, I'm so fucking angry, I just wanna…
What?
What do you wanna do?
- We'll do it.
- Yeah.
Do you have plans tonight?
No.
I wanna drive.
Really fucking fast.
- And you're gonna go with her?
- Yeah. [chuckles]
Have fun!
Do you mind?
Can you not see that we're in crisis?
- ["PAYRI$E" by Greta Isaac playing]
- [tyres screeching]
♪ I don't think I like you anymore ♪
♪ I don't know how we got here…
Wow.
- [music continues in background]
- [people chattering]
Smooth.
[both chuckle]
- Wait, do you know all these people?
- Oh!
If it isn't my favourite little toy,
and, uh…
Who's this weirdo? You're not Nick.
- Fuck off, Tom.
- [Tom chuckles]
- Oi, she's a feisty one, isn't she?
- Yeah. She is.
By the way, babes, if you ever need
a drink, you know where to find me.
[grunts]
Oh, my… [stammers]
You smashed my nose again!
Ah, that felt good.
- [groans] Why is it always the nose, bro?
- [chuckles]
Who are you?
- [engine revs]
- [laughing]
Ah, look at you,
look at you, look at you, huh?
I was surprised to hear the race
was back on. [smacks lips]
Aw. Did you get dressed up
just for me, yeah?
You did, innit?
Let's see if you're still laughing
after the race.
Yeah, we will.
What you looking at?
[scoffs]
[engines revving]
[line rings]
- [Ronnie] She there yet?
- [Cruz] She's right on time.
Good. Call me before you start.
I'll stay on the phone with you.
When she's ahead of you, just let us know,
and we'll take care of the rest.
But what if I'm winning?
She's gonna be behind me.
Cruz, my son, she's gonna wipe
the fucking floor with you…
- [scoffs]
- …so you don't need to know the plan.
Okay? Is Nick there?
- I want him to see this.
- Nah, she's with some random.
[sighs] That won't do.
- Right, so I'm just, like…
- [phone beeps]
- …fine--
- [line disconnects]
Did not just hang up on me.
[door closes]
Noah, I'm sorry, I fucked up,
I was just trying to protect you, okay?
I'm coming to talk.
- [phone buzzes]
- Hey, Noah?
Hello, mate. How you doing?
It's good to hear your voice.
Ronnie.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I just wanted
to give you a quick bell, mate.
I'm still here. I'm still here.
I hear that your girlfriend's racing
my boy tonight, and, uh,
well, I just wanted to say
that I'm gutted I can't be there.
You better hurry up, mate,
it's gonna be one to remember.
Shit. Shit.
[tense music playing]
[engine starts, roars]
[music stops]
[Michael] Are you okay?
Yeah.
Are you sure you wanna do this?
'Cause you don't have to.
I know. I want to.
Hey, I'll see you at the finish line.
You got this.
I know.
[chattering indistinctly]
- [seat belt clicks]
- [thuds on door]
I thought I'd let you know, that's
the steering wheel, that's the shift,
- and just put the car in cruise control.
- [engine starts, revs]
[chuckles]
[groans]
[engine starts]
[crowd cheering]
[engines revving]
[Cruz] Oi!
Ronnie sends his love, yeah?
[high-pitched ringing]
[engine roars]
Shit!
[cheering]
- [engines roaring]
- [intense music playing]
[laughs]
[exhales] Fuck. Come on.
[Ronnie]
What's going on? Talk to me, mate.
Boss man, I… [chuckles]
She's way behind.
I thought you said this girl could drive.
Don't worry, she'll catch you.
[music stops]
[music continues]
Here we go.
Come on, yeah. [laughs]
[Noah grunts]
[chuckles]
Come on, catch up. [chuckles]
Oh, I'm coming for you, girl.
Don't you fucking dare.
- [music stops]
- [tyres squeal]
[groans]
[Ronnie] I told you, she's the best.
[exhilarating music playing]
[breathing deeply]
Come on, come on, come on.
There it is.
[tyres screech]
[Nick] Where is she?
You're too late, bro.
[laughs]
[music continues]
Since when is there a bike?
You've gotta tell me the plan, man.
Good, Nick's here. Always the hero.
- [engine roaring]
- Come on, Noah!
[tyres screeching]
Wait, where's he gone?
[Ronnie] Cruz, come on, mate.
Keep speaking to me, son. Where is he?
I can't see anything, man. I'm trying…
I'm doing ten things at once, bro.
[Ronnie] All right, everything's in place.
Tell me when.
All right. But wait, for what?
He's right in front of me. [laughs]
[music stops]
- What the fuck?
- Noah, pull over.
- Pull the car over.
- What?
- Whoa!
- [tyres squeal]
- I told you to stop.
- [engine humming]
It's not safe.
- What the fuck are you doing, Nick?
- [Nick] It's a trap!
[intense music playing]
[laughs] All right, I guess I'm gonna win.
I'm gonna do you proud, Ron-Ron!
[Ronnie] Wait. What did you say?
[person] Coming now, get ready.
- [Ronnie] Cruz, can you hear me?
- They're behind me.
- Cruz.
- I did it, Ronnie!
[person] Go, go, go! Deploy!
- [engine roars]
- I did it!
- Cruz.
- [laughs]
- [music stops]
- [grunts]
[car alarm blaring]
[alarm continues through phone]
[clatters]
- Fuck!
- [engine roars]
- [tyres screech]
- [engine stops]
[tyres screeching]
- [people clamouring]
- [friend] Cruz, bro. You all right?
[clamouring continues in distance]
- You okay?
- Yeah.
[Michael] What happened?
- Get your fucking hands off her!
- Mate, I'm just checking if she's okay.
When are you gonna get it
in your thick little head?
- Stop! Stop it!
- [grunts]
What are you doing?
- Did he bring you here?
- No! I brought myself here!
Noah, why?
You promised me you wouldn't race!
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Nick, does it hurt
that I broke a promise I made?
Is this a joke to you?
Cruz is working with Ronnie!
This is a set-up!
[breathes heavily]
[melancholic music playing]
- Don't fucking come near her.
- [Noah] You knew that?
You knew that?
[sniffles]
- [Michael] Come on.
- Can you just give me a second, Michael?
- Noah, I was trying to protect you.
- [Noah sighs]
I didn't wanna scare you, okay?
[pants] This is exactly
what I was trying to prevent.
Are you serious?
Nick, how do you not understand
that if you'd have just told me the truth,
none of this would have happened?
You always do this, Nick.
You withhold these little pieces
of the truth to protect me,
and it just hurts more!
I don't know…
I don't know if I can do this anymore.
- Go on then, go back to Michael.
- Oh, my God, Nick,
- do you even care about me?
- Yes, I care.
I care whether my girlfriend wants
to fuck another guy.
I don't wanna fuck Michael!
But I'm not really
your girlfriend either, am I?
Not in public, not in front of
our parents, not in front of Sophia.
[pants]
Okay then, Noah,
what do you expect me to do?
- [stammers] I don't…
- Go on. No, you…
- Tell me what you expect me to do.
- [stammers] I don't know, Nick,
but we can't keep doing this.
I'm exhausted.
What's that supposed to mean?
This is it.
I think we need to take a break.
You want a break?
- I need some space and some time.
- Do you want to take a break?
And then you need to figure out
what your priorities are.
You want a break?
Fine, I'll give you a break.
[engine starts, revving]
[breathes heavily]
["In The Name Of Healing"
by Griff playing]
♪ Losin' track of time
and my head went quiet ♪
♪ It only ever happened with you ♪
♪ Losin' all the weight
of the world on fire ♪
♪ It only ever happened with you ♪
- ♪ Now, baby, when I try to walk…
- [no audible dialogue]
♪ …my gaze is out of focus ♪
♪ I know it's in the name of healin'
you and I don't talk ♪
♪ I'm tryin' to remember
all the reasons that we parted ♪
♪ But my brain keeps clouding up ♪
♪ 'Cause all I know is when we loved ♪
♪ it didn't seem so loud for once ♪
[music ends]
[Lion] Four.
Easy, breathe.
One, two, step, left upper hand.
Relax, all right? Eight.
[grunts]
- You wanna talk about it?
- No, I'm good.
Let's talk about it. What's up?
Is she coming?
To the gym reopening?
Yeah, but not for you, for Jenna.
[sighs] All right. Okay. Let's go.
Listen, listen, there's a lot of emotions
hanging over from the race.
You were trying to protect her, clearly,
but maybe it landed like control.
You've just gotta let
things air out, all right?
I can't lose her.
It's gonna work out, man.
You're gonna be good.
I promise, all right?
Jab.
Hi, babe.
Just wellness check. Anything I can do?
If you promise
to hold my hand at the party.
I'm not really looking forward
to seeing Nick or talking to my mom.
Or William or Sophia.
- What?
- I know, I know.
But it's-it's a Leister Enterprises thing.
She has to be there.
But I'll be there too.
I'll hold your hand.
Promise.
Okay.
- Death grip, yeah?
- Duh.
You are still gonna come, right?
Yeah, of course. I wouldn't miss it.
I'm glad. Appreciate ya.
Bye. Love you.
[Michael] Noah!
Oh, would you look at that.
- It's Noah Morgan, back from the dead.
- [chuckles]
- You all right?
- Yeah.
- Are you headed back to campus?
- Uh, I am now.
- I finally get my chance.
- What?
To beat you in a race.
I've got a head start.
Oh, have you? Okay.
- Whoo!
- [chuckles]
You don't know who you're racing, dude.
Come on.
- [imitates car] Come on then.
- [chuckles]
- Watch out, watch out, watch out!
- [Noah exclaims, laughs]
[Michael] Come on, then.
[chuckles, exclaims]
[both laugh]
[Michael groans]
- Go, go, go.
- No, no, no, no.
It's a dream come true, really.
I just believe that boxing provides
a lifeline for these kids, you know.
One, two.
- Good. One, two, slip, slip, roll.
- [mellow music playing on speakers]
Good, I like that.
Don't forget to exhale when you punch,
inhale between punches.
Okay, one, two.
[Lion] Jenna here has put so much work…
[speaks indistinctly]
…making it a welcome space.
- [laughs]
- [Jenna squeals]
Oh, babe. Ah, I'm so glad you're here.
I am so proud of you.
Aw, thank you.
Everyone did such a good job, and…
Mmm. He's in the back corner.
He got here super early
to help set everything up.
He's really took this
whole business partnership thing to heart.
- And he's more nervous than you.
- [scoffs]
I promise. If that helps in any way.
- [speaks indistinctly]
- Yeah, it helps.
You had a drink?
- [laughs] Not yet.
- No?
- Uh, Mum's incoming.
- [Lion] Jen?
- Behind me.
- Good luck.
- Okay.
- Yeah, coming.
- I'm gonna do this. You'll be fine.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- [Lion] Jen?
- [Jenna] Coming, coming, coming.
Hello, Noah.
How are you?
Been better.
I've really missed you.
Dying to hear how college is.
I feel so out of the loop.
Whose fault is that?
You'll come to this, won't you?
Wouldn't be the same without you.
[scoffs] Right.
Optics. Wouldn't want the PR to suffer.
[bell rings]
- [music fades]
- [audience cheering, applauding]
Hello everyone. Uh, yeah,
I appreciate you for coming.
We're so grateful to finally
be sharing this with you all, you know?
- Um, I have to start by thanking Nick…
- [camera shutter clicks]
…and everyone at Leister Enterprises.
Nick, truly, I don't know
what I'd do without you, man,
so… so thank you. Thank you.
[audience cheering, applauding]
[Lion] And, of course, there is…
there is another person
that none of this is possible without.
- Uh, Jenna.
- [audience applauding]
- [Noah] Yeah!
- [chuckles]
Now… [stammers] …I know
you don't like the attention,
so I'm gonna be quick, all right?
None of this exists without you.
- [sentimental music playing]
- All right, you've…
you got this rare ability
to leave things better
than how you found them,
including me,
and I just…
I can't get over how lucky I am.
When we met, I didn't think
you'd give me the time of day,
so the fact
that you're still here right now…
baffles me, truly.
Jenna, I love you.
What's this? [chuckles]
- Just a little something.
- [Jenna laughs]
What you doing? [laughs]
Will you marry me?
- No.
- [audience gasping]
[whispering, murmuring]
- Not no. Just get up, get up.
- Hmm?
You don't have to kneel. [laughs]
But you do wanna marry me, yeah?
- [laughs] Yeah. Yeah, I do.
- [chuckles]
[audience applauding, cheering]
It's Grandma's, innit?
Yes! Wassup, wassup?
[cheers]
Babe, look.
Oh, my God, Jen.
- [speaks indistinctly]
- [Zach] Hey, everyone, good work.
- [squeals]
- I'm so happy for you.
Proper stressful for a minute,
I didn't know what you were gonna say.
- [Zach] That's mean.
- [chuckles]
- [Zach] Men, we're best men.
- [JP] Yeah.
[Jenna squeals] I'm engaged.
[giggles]
We're getting married!
- [Lion] She said yes.
- [Jenna] Can you believe it? Look.
- [Lion] Beyoncé. I like the sound of that.
- [Jenna] Whoo!
[cheering]
[sentimental music continues]
[chuckles] I'm not gonna stop,
that's the plan.
[laughs]
[Briar] No, I know, but it's actually
a thing. It's getting actually…
[Michael] I'll try and explain, again.
You coming or not?
- Come on, darling.
- Put a smile on that dial.
- [Briar laughs]
- Come on. Oh.
[music continues]
[line ringing]
[buzzing]
[Michael] I-I thought this
was a group project.
[Noah] I get it.
You're good at everything.
Come on, Noah… [chuckles]
- …put a little bit of effort in.
- [buzzing continues]
[Noah] Right.
[clears throat]
Hey, Noah. Um…
[Briar] No.
One of the many other women
who hates your guts. Try again.
Briar, put Noah on.
[sighs] She doesn't wanna talk to you.
Briar, please.
- Just…
- No, you really hurt her, Nick.
- But she's…
- [Noah, Michael laughing]
…she's actually finally moved on.
- [Noah] You win. Oh, my God.
- [Michael cheers]
What do you mean, "moved on"?
Read between the lines, Nick.
There's a reason why
she's not answering your call.
So if you really care about her,
you'll just leave her alone.
[Noah chuckles] Michael.
She's happy.
Don't ruin it.
She's happy?
Michael, stop. [chuckles]
Yeah.
[melancholic music playing]
Now, can we be done? I'm just…
I'm not in the mood today.
It's all good. I understand.
- [no audible dialogue]
- [music continues]
[muffled dialogue]
[colleague, distorted] Uh, Nick?
[music fades]
[normal] Nick?
Thank you, everyone.
Um, let's pick this up tomorrow.
- [Briar] Noah, darling?
- [knocks]
- [Noah] Go away.
- Right, that's it. [grunts]
["Spell" by Witch Post
playing on speakers]
Tragic. [sighs]
- [door closes]
- [Briar] Enough!
[claps]
You are torturing yourself, darling.
- It is 2.00 p.m. The sun is shining.
- [groans]
And there is no reason to still be in bed,
unless you're as hungover as I am,
which you are not, because you don't…
- [music stops]
- …go out anymore.
[Noah] I can't believe
he still hasn't even called.
I just…
Why does it hurt so bad?
I know.
I've been there. It sucks.
- What happened?
- [groans]
[sucks teeth]
A few years ago,
I was really in love with this guy.
You know, super handsome, charming.
Uh, I was obsessed with him.
Sounds doomed.
I was young.
But it felt real,
until I walked in on him
fucking my best friend.
My ex did the same thing.
What? Shut up.
- [chuckles] Yeah, seriously.
- Men are absolute shits.
Trust me, the best thing you can do
is let him see you thriving without him.
- [laughs]
- It is!
- Thriving? [chuckles]
- Well… [stammers] …yeah.
We've got some work to do,
but you've got me, so it's okay.
Now, if only there was an amazing excuse
to get dressed up and show
off a little bit of arm candy.
- Arm candy? [chuckles]
- Michael.
- Right.
- Oh, what? Is he too hot?
Too clever? Too into you?
It's too soon.
Fine. We'll go as a throuple.
[both chuckle]
Love a bit of roleplay.
Now, I took it upon myself
to do a little bit of closet shopping,
and I have made my selection,
but I am open to feedback.
You're a good friend.
What do you think?
Very strappy. Sexy. [meows]
[ambient music playing]
[Sophia] Hey.
You following me?
Just following the scent of despair.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- [chuckles]
You've been miserable.
My girlfriend said she needed some space,
and then she swiftly filled
that space with another guy.
- Your girlfriend?
- Yeah.
We were keeping it quiet.
'Cause your dad didn't approve?
Was it that obvious?
I put some pieces together.
So, not only can I not escape her,
but she's bringing this arsehole
to the company party. Mm-hmm.
Poor Nick Leister.
So, you'll be the heartbroken loser
alone in the corner?
- Yes, I will.
- Mmm.
- Well, you are a loser.
- Mmm. Thank you.
I appreciate that.
But you won't be alone.
["Good Ones" by Charli XCX playing]
- Gala!
- [Michael] Gala time!
- [pops]
- [all laughing]
[Briar] Oh, my god, Michael, fuck!
- Okay.
- [Michael cheers] Yes.
Gala. [chuckles]
Oh, my God. That is so funny.
♪ Let you down easy, I'm trying ♪
♪ 'Cause you're everything
I've spent my whole life fighting ♪
♪ So when I walk away
it's not your fault ♪
♪ I always let the good ones go ♪
♪ And baby, you couldn't have
loved me any better…
You look great.
I fucking better.
- [music continues]
- [chattering]
Right, cheer up, buttercup.
- Go on… [mutters]
- You can't be frowning
with that sexy little number…
[camera shutters clicking]
Right, avert your eyes. Let's get a drink.
- [music fades]
- Let's.
[gentle instrumental music playing]
- Kind of nervous.
- Nervous?
Why are you nervous?
My date's kind of cute.
- [glass clinking]
- [Will] Welcome, everyone.
Thank you for joining us this evening
to celebrate the past 25 years
of Leister Enterprises
and all its achievements.
[guests cheer, applauding]
Hey, don't worry about them.
This is the fun table.
- Right, Briar? Yeah.
- Hell yeah. Always.
I've always hoped
for this to be a family business,
so Nicholas, I'm so proud
of the man you've become.
[guests] Aw.
[Will chuckles] And to Sophia,
our newest member
of the Leister Enterprises family.
I can see how you've brought out
the very best in my son.
You're welcome.
[all chuckle]
It's not easy, I know.
[all laughing]
I see a bright and successful future
with the two of you at the helm.
To the dream team.
[guests cheering, applauding]
[lively instrumental music playing]
[Michael] Come on, let's go dance.
Come on, darling, little bit of that,
little bit of that, little bit of that.
[speaking indistinctly]
Michael!
- [speaks indistinctly]
- [laughs]
[music ends]
[gentle instrumental music playing]
May I have this dance?
You can indeed.
[Briar] Boo, this shit is boring.
Come on, let's go.
All right. Let's… [sighs]
…get out of here.
[Briar] Excuse me, excuse me,
coming through, thank you.
You're good.
Who knew you were such a good dancer.
Well, guess where I learnt.
[both] Finishing school.
[chuckling]
Classic.
This is nice.
Nick.
[music distorting]
[emotional music playing]
- [gasps] Oh…
- [glasses shatter]
You all right? Noah, you all right?
Noah. Noah.
- Noah. You have to let me explain.
- Leave me alone.
- Nick, leave me alone.
- Nick, back off!
- Briar, this has nothing to do with you.
- Oh, but it really does.
Briar, fuck off.
- Noah.
- What does that mean?
Don't you think you've done enough damage?
- Briar, don't.
- Or…
does it make you feel good?
Toying with girls' hearts
until they're a broken mess.
- What is she talking about?
- I have no idea.
Would you like to tell her, or shall I?
- Tell me what?
- [Nick] Nothing, Noah.
You're not the first girl to have
their heart broken by Nick Leister.
- [Nick] Noah…
- You two?
Noah, I can explain.
It was years ago, it meant nothing.
Is this a joke?
I thought you were my friend.
And you…
[Nick] Noah.
…I don't know who the fuck you are.
I hope you're happy with Sophia,
with Briar, with whoever.
- Noah, it was ages ago, I was ashamed.
- Don't.
I didn't know how to tell you.
Come on, Noah.
[guests whispering indistinctly]
[Nick] Noah!
Do you even realise
how much she fucking loves you?
If she loves me so much,
then why the hell are you here?
I'm here 'cause I'm a good friend.
Friend?
You're not together?
Holy shit.
Nick. Please, you're making a scene.
It's too late.
[footsteps departing]
["Crystalised" by The xx playing]
♪ You've applied the pressure…
Time for tea.
♪ …to have me crystalised ♪
[keys jingle]
♪ And you've got the faith…
- [line ringing]
- [sighs]
♪ …that I could bring paradise ♪
[fire crackling]
♪ I'll forgive and forget ♪
♪ before I'm paralysed ♪
Thank you.
♪ Do I have to keep up the pace…
[line ringing]
♪ …to keep you satisfied? ♪
♪ Things have gotten closer to the sun ♪
♪ and I've done things in small doses ♪
♪ So don't think
that I'm pushing you away ♪
♪ when you're the one
that I've kept closest…
What is wrong with me?
[chuckles]
Nothing.
There is literally nothing wrong with you.
- Hey, I'm being serious.
- And so am I.
I can't think of a single thing.
I've tried…
to find something. Anything.
A shit sense of humour, a cruel streak.
Gross habits. [chuckles]
Any reason not to like you.
You're just saying that
to make me feel better.
Is it working?
[chuckles] A bit.
[sighs]
Hey. Hey.
You deserve to be happy.
♪ And you just keep on getting closer ♪
- ♪ Glaciers have melted to the sea ♪
- ♪ Things have gotten closer to the sun…
- ♪ I wish the tide would take me over ♪
- ♪ …and I've done things in small doses ♪
♪ So don't think…
- ♪ I've been down onto my knees…
- ♪ …that I'm pushing you away…
- ♪ …and you just keep on…
- ♪ …when you're the one…
- ♪ …getting closer ♪
- ♪ …that I've kept closest ♪
- ♪ Go slow ♪
- [music ends]
- [phone buzzing]
[sighs]
[melancholic music playing]
[door opens]
Hey.
I came straight here after the party.
Are you okay?
Noah, I… I wanted to explain about Briar.
You and Briar.
Were you ever gonna tell me?
You let me get close to her,
Nick, this whole time.
- You could've told me.
- I know. I know.
And I'm sorry. But she's been playing us.
- She's been trying to push us apart.
- Briar is not why we broke up.
I know she's not,
but she's been manipulating us.
Okay? The only reason that I kissed Sophia
was because Briar told me
you were with Michael.
I don't know, I guess I wanted to hurt you
because I was hurting,
and now I… [stammers]
…I'm just-just in fucking agony.
[breathing heavily]
But do you know what happened
when she kissed me, Noah?
- Nothing. I felt nothing.
- [sniffles]
Because, Noah,
I'm incapable of loving anyone but you.
[tender music playing]
And I wanted to tell you all of that…
[sniffles, breathes shakily]
…but you weren't here.
[sniffles]
Noah, where were you?
Whose jacket is that?
Noah, whose jacket is that?
[phone buzzing]
[Noah breathing shakily]
Oh, Noah.
[sniffles]
[Nick] What have you done?
[whimpers]
Nick.
[door opens, closes]
[tender music continues]
[pounding on door]
[door opens]
[thuds]
I don't want any trouble.
[breathes shakily]
[line ringing]
- Come on.
- [ringing continues]
[Michael] Do you wanna sit down?
No, I think I'm good.
[inhales deeply]
What have you got that I haven't?
Let's not do this.
- [line ringing]
- Come on, Nick.
- [ringing continues]
- [sighs] Come on.
Go on.
Fine.
I'm thoughtful.
I'm emotionally available.
And I make her laugh.
And if she were mine,
I would tell every fucker in the universe
instead of hiding her away
and making her feel unworthy.
It's all irrelevant, right?
Because I couldn't steal her,
Nick, even if I tried.
Because she is obsessed with you.
[laughs]
Don't fucking laugh at me.
Hi, you've reached Nicholas--
Oh, come on. Come on.
No one else could've made her leave you.
You've done this to yourself.
You know that?
You pushed her away.
- Don't touch me.
- [chuckles]
Don't touch me.
[line beeps]
Nick, we can't leave it like that, please.
This is all a huge fucking mess,
and it hurts.
Just don't do anything stupid,
and call me back.
- [music continues]
- [Michael chuckles]
You could've been happy.
Instead, you broke her heart.
Fuck, Nick. Please don't do anything.
Please.
[music intensifies]
Oh, shit.
[gasps] Oh, my God.
Hey, are you okay?
Hey. Hey, I'm sorry.
[tender music continues]
Look, I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
You have to understand.
I didn't know about you and Sophia, okay?
It meant nothing. Look at me. Look at me.
Nick, it didn't mean anything,
I promise you.
I'm sorry.
[sirens wailing]
I have to go now, Noah.
Nick, what did you do?
[car doors closing]
[radio chatter]
[officer] Nick Leister?
You are under arrest on suspicion
of assault causing actual bodily harm.
[handcuffs click]
You do not have to say anything,
but it may harm your defence…
[officer continues indistinctly,
distorted]
- [engine starts]
- [no audible dialogue]
[sirens wailing]
["Breaking Up Slowly"
by Lana Del Rey ft. Nikki Lane playing]
["Come Down" by Asha Banks playing]