[All characters, behaviors, locations,
organizations, professions, and events
shown in this series are entirely fictional,
created solely for entertainment purposes,
with no intention of instructing
or endorsing any kind of behaviors;
viewer discretion is advised]
I always make everything worse.
It's my fault...
What happened last night
shouldn't have happened to anyone,
whether it was me,
the others on the farm,
or you.
This place is like your home now.
Mr. Sila,
can you come to
the meeting room right away?
There's an important guest
who wants to meet you.
Hello.
Is there something important
that requires the head of Khum Rimpha
to come all the way here?
It's nothing serious.
I'm just here to congratulate you.
I've heard that Phusangdao Farm
is about to close the deal with K Group.
Congratulations.
My friend...
These flowers are pretty.
We've known each other for a long time now.
And since you're like family to me,
I'd like to give you some advice.
Business is like a game.
Whoever has the upper hand
gets the benefits.
But don't let your guard down.
Because when you fall,
the one who gets hurt
is you.
Mr. Sila.
What is it?
Our partner just emailed me
that the deal will have to
be postponed indefinitely.
According to them,
further review is required
due to issues with the figures.
I think...
maybe you're not quite ready
to play this game yet.
How did you manage to screw up
a simple deal like this?
I would've been so ashamed.
Some people only know how to play dirty
and are too cowardly to face the truth.
Is this impressive to you?
Because I think it's pathetic.
When you play dirty,
it will come back to bite you.
Remember that.
It seems
you're a bit tied up,
so Muang and I won't keep you any longer.
Oh,
if you need any help from Khum Rimpha,
you can let me know.
♫But no one sees what's behind my smiles♫
♫It's the loneliness I try to hide♫
♫Will there be someone my heart's seeking?♫
♫Then today, I got you near♫
♫You made my heart drift away,♫
♫lost in your gaze♫
♫Like a stream washing over me♫
♫Wanna give this a try,
like it's more than one night?♫
♫Let's change one night♫
♫into something more, alright♫
♫Let's follow our hearts once♫
♫Wanna give this a try,
just let me get inside?♫
♫Deep inside, I'll make you feel whole♫
♫May I ask you to be my last?♫
[Phusangdao]
You're awfully loyal to the family,
aren't you, Chakkrit?
You and your father
are exactly alike.
Except your father
is a little smarter than you.
If I were you,
I'd pick the obviously better choice.
But I don't think
you'd want to be
an underling your whole life,
would you?
Haven't you considered
that maybe
you deserve more than this?
My duty
is to protect this farm.
Call it what you like,
but I know
what I'm doing.
But are you sure
the person you're protecting
still deserves your loyalty?
Chiang Rai isn't that big.
There's nowhere
my influence doesn’t reach.
Perhaps it might be
even bigger than you think.
I won't let whoever tries to destroy
this work get away with it.
Oh.
Give my regards to your Boss.
Tell him I have a surprise for him.
I'll see him at the Summit.
Don't cry, alright?
I'm here now.
Are you awake?
How are you?
Are you feeling any better?
I feel better now.
But...
You don't have to push yourself.
It's okay
if you still need time.
Thank you, Sila.
I can't believe
I truly deserve your love like this.
I think...
everyone deserves to be loved, Saitharn.
It's easy for you to say that.
But I'm scared.
I've been hurt before
because I believed in it.
Then let me prove it.
Not with words
but with time.
Don't you hate me?
I'm not that good a person, you know?
Saitharn,
you may say bad things about yourself.
You can blame yourself
as much as you want.
But I want you to know
I would never judge you by your past
or what you've been through.
The Saitharn I'm with right now
has shown me
he isn't a bad person.
And everything that happened
isn't your fault.
But I already said
- that I...
- Saitharn.
You can believe that if you want,
but I'll be here
to remind you it's not your fault.
I'll keep reminding you
until you believe me.
I don't know if you'll
believe what I'm saying,
but I promise
I won't let anyone make
you feel worthless again.
I promise.
♫I wanna thank you for making me feel♫
♫Just how beautiful love can be♫
♫Every chamber of my heart♫
♫Will be yours from now on♫
♫You're a godsent present from above♫
♫I'll always belong to you evermore♫
♫My heart will always be yours forever♫
Mok, let me come with you.
What?
Don't follow me!
Let me join you.
I don't want to stay at my place alone.
I'm getting you your meal.
I have to hurry.
Let me come with you, please.
Please.
Hey.
Are you good?
Come on. Let's head back.
You're not heading out there?
It's okay. I'll come for it another time.
Let's get you back first.
I don't want to be there alone.
[Phusangdao Group]
Phae, look at this.
Hm?
Let me have a look.
Whoa.
It's gorgeous.
Gorgeous.
Thank you, Gale,
for letting me be part of this project.
It's me who needs to thank you, Phae.
You've helped me so much that
you haven't caught a break.
On top of that,
without you,
it wouldn't turn out this perfect.
You're really amazing, you know?
Really?
I don't know.
I...
I've never been confident in myself.
I don't know
if I can truly be good at anything.
That's why I want to find out
whether your compliment
was just out of politeness
or genuinely because of my talent.
I don't know
how much
your achievements have been ignored,
but right here
and right now,
I do feel that you are talented.
For every compliment you didn't receive,
you shall receive all of it from me.
I'll reassure you
how valuable
you truly are,
in my eyes
at least.
If that's the case...
can you promise me
that you'll...
always be right by my side
to compliment me?
Hm?
I promise.
Thank you.
Have you ever thought about how Sila and I
gave you the chance to work here again?
This project decides
the future of Phusangdao Group.
If we fail again, the deal will not be
the only thing we will lose.
Ms. Wipa, we have already rechecked.
You are making up an excuse
after we lost the deal?
We are not, but it's not our fault.
The statistics team...
It's not our fault.
It's the marketing team's fault
for failing to carefully check the details.
So what?
You guys are in the same boat!
What are you guys doing?
Do you think shifting blame will help?
But Ms. Wipa,
if we don't have the data
from the management,
we won't have anything to compare.
That is an excuse.
Why didn't you recheck the details
before the submission?
You always throw things at us.
You dare say that to me?!
If I weren't the project coordinator,
you wouldn't know
anything about the partner.
But we've been overworked for
the entire month now, Ms. Wipa.
It was just a minor mistake.
Why are you putting all the blame on us?
"A minor mistake"?
Losing a multi-million-baht deal
is a minor mistake?
Who was the one submitting
the files to the partner?
Silence!
I require every team
to recheck every page and every number.
There must be zero margin for error.
Yes, Mr. Sila.
If we fail a simple task such as this,
how, then, would we fare
against Khum Rimpha?
You may all return to your work now.
Ms. Wipa.
Do you know
who is behind this mess?
It can only be those from Khum Rimpha.
I will gather evidence for us.
They won't wiggle their way out.
Mr. Sila.
I would like you to think about this.
Aside from me,
who else is always right by your side?
Is there a problem, Boss?
You know
the culprit behind this, don't you?
I do.
And I have already coordinated
with the local police.
They won't get away with this.
That is not what I meant.
If such is the case...
what is it you are referring to?
Can you help me with something?
Of course.
It is my duty to serve you.
So you are going to do
whatever I say, correct?
Certainly.
Good.
Then I have something for you to do.
It is something that only you can do.
I knew it.
It has to be you.
Nonsense.
How can anyone tell
who it is just from a knock on the door?
Not just a knock on the door, though.
I even recognize the sound of you breathing.
Righto.
Sila, a man with a sixth sense.
Right. Here.
I'm bringing you some tea.
I brewed it myself, by the way.
I even sorted each tea leaf myself.
You must've been hard at work on this.
No wonder I could smell
the aroma right from the door.
Here you go.
Oh, it smells delightful.
Try it for yourself.
Hey!
Hm.
Did you dump
a whole sugar factory in the cup?
It's too sweet?
I'll brew you a new cup, then.
No need.
Hey, what are you doing?
Others might see us.
It's still in the middle of the day.
So I can do this to you at night?
Oh, I need to write that down.
Hey!
Whoa.
You turn into a perverted old man again.
Aww...
I really want you to be by my side.
Right now, my head...
It's full of thoughts.
Hey.
Share them with me.
But...
I don't think I can help much.
I simply want to care for you.
I'm currently suspicious of someone.
Mm.
Every clue points to that person,
but I don't want to believe it,
as I once trusted that person.
And...
How much do you trust this individual?
A whole lot,
as if this person is part of my family.
Mm...
I think
it's normal to be suspicious of someone.
But don't forget
how much you've been through with them.
You need to consider
the past for it to be fair.
I didn't know you could come up with
something like this.
I copied it and noted it down here.
Thank you.
Feeling better?
It's better,
but I still can't find a way out of this.
You're thinking too much.
You're not that old to be doing that.
The simplest solution
is to deal with the root of the problem.
How so?
Think back to
what made you suspicious
of the person in the first place.
I think
you can find the answer from there.
"What made me suspicious of that person?"
What do you think?
Have you figured out
how it started?
I've figured it out.
Now, I know
where I should begin.
If you say that the answer
lies within the root of the problem,
I simply have to look for it there.
You haven't lost your touch, Dad.
It's been ages since you last played,
but your shots are still
more accurate than mine.
I first played golf when I was thirteen.
What about you?
When did you start?
Well...
When I was about twenty, I think.
Back when I was still in university,
and you brought me along.
Hmph...
It's only seven years.
But that small gap
can decide who's in the lead
and who falls behind.
Just like Sila,
who learned the ropes from a young age.
That's why he surpasses you in every way.
And you?
You're always his inferior.
But isn't Sila about to fail miserably?
Khum Rimpha is about to
seal the deal in his place.
His investments will go to waste.
That's because of me.
I was the one who sent in the spy.
If it weren't for that,
do you really think
we'd be having the last laugh like this?
Yes...
This will be the last time
I ask for your help.
After this,
I'll fight him on my own.
You can't catch up to him.
He won't let you destroy him that easily.
As long as I can win,
I'll use any method I can.
Just like you've always done.
That's my son.
I'm confident this time.
But I need your trump card.
I know
you have someone working for you.
But I really don't know who it is.
It's all going to be over soon.
Can't you just tell me now?
Once everything is settled,
you'll know.
But for now, just know that
it's someone close to Sila.
Boss.
Mr. Manmuang.
What?
You wanted to see me so badly
you had to send someone to fetch me,
my friend?
Friend?
How many years has it been
since you last called me that?
Ever since you refused to marry Mueanphae
because you were...
Gay?
Mm... gay.
Why hesitate to say that word?
Just say it,
no need to be scared.
You've always been a coward.
You’ve never been better than me at anything,
no matter how badly your father
wants you to be.
This stupid deal is going to end soon.
When that time comes, you'll know
if the victor is going to be me or you.
You're the root of every problem.
I used to see you as my friend.
As my brother.
I f*cking trusted you.
Is this really how you repay me?
You're the f*cking cause
of all these problems!
If you weren't gay,
if you had married Mueanphae,
do you think our families
would've ended up like this?!
And that f*cking deal!
You're a f*cking idiot for
trusting the wrong person!
I won't even be mad about that deal
if you didn't play dirty
and sent those two to hurt my workers.
What?
I just sent someone to see who
your young consort is.
I’ve been wondering
what's so special about him
that you're so hooked on him.
So hooked you sneak off
to see him at night.
So hooked you can’t even focus on work.
Don't you dare lay a finger on Saitharn.
How could you hurt defenseless people?
You're f*cking pathetic.
Your father must be very proud of
a lowly scum like you!
At least I'm not gay,
making my father wish he were dead!
F*cker!
F*ck you!
You b*stard!
Piece of sh*t!
Shoot me!
Shoot.
Ow!
Do it!
If you think punching me...
can help you get that deal,
then do it!
Ptui!
Muang.
Hey...
What happened to you?
Hey!
Let go... Phae.
Oh, your face too.
Let me see...
Why are the wounds like that?
Let go.
What did you do?
I got into a fight with Sila.
What? Why did you do that?
How is Sila?
Your brother is standing here,
bleeding in front of you,
yet you're more concerned
for that f*cking b*stard than me?
We might not be related,
but he took care of me.
He understands me better
than my real brother.
Why?
Why...
Why!
Am I that f*cking terrible!?
Huh?!
Is that why you keep praising that f*cker?!
Answer me!
Just you wait, Phae.
This upcoming Summit,
I'll make Sila lose in front of everyone.
I'll wipe Phusangdao Farm off the map.
I'll make sure everyone knows
that Sila lost to me.
That Khum Rimpha won!
We’re going to be back on top again!
Do you understand me now?!
Your brother is hurt right in front of you,
but you still asked about that f*cker!
Or what?
Or do you want me to get hurt even more?!
Why don't you go be with him, then?!
Pack up your things and just f*cking go!
[Chakkrit]
Here, let me help.
Thank you.
Hey!
Let me help...
What the hell, man?
I can do it myself.
No.
What are you embarrassed about?
It's nothing I've never seen.
Get off, man...
I'd hit you back
if your arm wasn't injured.
Come here.
Can you help me here?
Yeah, gimme a sec.
Taking this off.
Here.
- It's really cold out there.
- It is...
- Sh*t!
- Sh*t!!
- Shit!
What the hell are you two doing?
I just helped him undress
so that he could take a shower.
Grab my towels for me.
Alright.
Wan.
Hm?
Help me bathe too, will you?
You idiot.
Saying things like that.
My back is itchy, you know?
- Go, go. Close it.
- Please, please, please?
- Hell no.
- Aw...
[Mueanphae is calling]
I can't sleep,
so I want to talk to you for a bit.
Are you sure there's nothing behind this?
Or...
Do you miss me?
Are you crazy?
Answer me.
Do you miss me or not?
Who would say such a thing, Gale?!
It would be good if you answered it,
as I'm actually...
more than ready to listen
to you all night, too.
Hearing you say that
makes me want to stay awake even more.
Right, right.
I'll sing you to sleep, then.
♫Rumbling, rumbling,♫
♫Clouds are weeping♫
Oh, that's enough.
The way you sing is so funny.
What?
It's not romantic at all?
No, it's comical, more than anything.
Mm...
Actually,
I can't sleep, not because I'm exhausted.
But why, then?
Is there something on your mind?
Tonight...
I had a very terrible fight with Muang.
He suddenly came to me
covered in wounds.
And...
He said he had a fight with Sila.
Are you okay now?
Mm...
I am.
I was thinking...
Gale.
I have something to tell you.
Oh, hey.
What is it?
What happened to you?
Oh, I'm really sorry.
I totally forgot
I was supposed to take you to dinner.
Let me get changed for a minute.
Stop.
I'm asking you what happened to you.
- It's just...
- Hey, there's this.
And then here.
Here, too.
It's obvious you had a fight with someone.
You're acting like a child.
Hey...
What happened? Tell me.
Don't be like this.
I just had a little bit of an accident.
Huh?!
- Did they break into the farm again?!
- Hey, calm down. Be calm.
See? I'm totally fine.
I'm okay.
Oh, you.
Whatever.
Get changed and rest up already.
Shut off your laptop and call it a night.
I'm out of juice.
Please let me charge myself up.
Get some rest if you're tired.
Hey...
Does it hurt a lot?
Simply having you here,
half of the pain is already gone.
Turn around.
I'll massage you.
Ouch!
You're an adult now,
yet you got into fights
like you're still in school.
Do you know that
I don't like it at all
when I see you get hurt?
But after coming home to see you,
I've already forgotten
where it hurts.
Saitharn...
Don't disappear from me, okay?
This is totally a tease.
More...
I love you, too.
Today, we shall make Phusangdao Group
remember our name, Khum Rimpha.
Thank you for taking the time
to celebrate with us.
You are so confident that
good news
will come your way, are you not?
Ms. Gale.
There is a model we are unable to contact.
I have no idea what happened.
♫I wanna thank you for making me feel♫
♫Just how beautiful love can be♫
♫Every chamber of my heart♫
♫Will be yours from now on♫
♫You're a godsent present from above♫
♫I'll always belong to you evermore♫
♫My heart will always be yours forever♫
♫I wanna thank you for making me feel♫
♫Just how beautiful love can be♫
♫Every chamber of my heart♫
♫Will be yours from now on♫
♫You're a godsent present from above♫
♫I'll always belong to you evermore♫
♫My heart will always be yours forever♫