[All characters, behaviors, locations,
organizations, professions, and events
shown in this series are entirely fictional,
created solely for entertainment purposes,
with no intention of instructing
or endorsing any kind of behaviors;
viewer discretion is advised]
At least I'm not gay,
making my father wish he were dead!
F*cker!
F*ck you!
Do it!
If you think punching me...
can help you get that deal,
then do it!
Give my regards to your Boss.
Tell him I have a surprise for him.
I'll see him at the Summit.
[NORTHERN SUMMIT 2026]
These chairs aren't spaced right.
Can you move them over
about half a meter
to make room for the guests?
One, two, check.
Can you make the stage lights whiter?
I don't want it to look too yellow.
I think it's a little dull.
Can you add three more lilies?
Thank you.
Ms. Wipa,
the Governor's name is
misspelled on the VIP name tag.
Correct it and have them
print a new one within 30 minutes.
Yes.
Thank you.
Everyone,
everything has to be finished by 11 A.M.
There'll be no adjustments after that.
And Mr. Sila will be arriving soon, alright?
Okay.
Your coffee.
Thank you.
You're always supporting me.
It's to give you energy for work.
Sounds good?
Ms. Gale,
we can't contact one of our models.
I have no idea what happened.
Which one?
The fifth model.
The fifth model...
has short hair
and is 170 centimeters tall.
Phae,
I need your help.
♫But no one sees what's behind my smiles♫
♫It's the loneliness I try to hide♫
♫Will there be someone my heart's seeking?♫
♫Then today, I got you near♫
♫You made my heart drift away,♫
♫lost in your gaze♫
♫Like a stream washing over me♫
♫Wanna give this a try,
like it’s more than one night?♫
♫Let's change one night♫
♫into something more, alright♫
♫Let's follow our hearts once♫
♫Wanna give this a try,
just let me get inside?♫
♫Deep inside, I'll make you feel whole♫
♫May I ask you to be my last?♫
[NORTHERN SUMMIT 2026]
Hello, Wipa.
Oh.
Yes.
Everyone?
Okay,
we have less than five hours left.
Make sure the lights and sound
are checked by 1 P.M.
Don't forget to place labels at
the cocktail zone as well.
Who is in charge of this?
Me.
Don't forget to check
all the desserts by 1 P.M.
Right.
The opening lights and screen must
come up at the same time without delays.
Please make sure they're in sync.
Yes, Mr. Sila.
Who is in charge of the main entrance?
You need to welcome the VIP guests.
I'll contact Orn.
Every reception zone needs to
have personnel on standby.
Understood?
Does everyone know their duties now?
I want this summit to be the best,
with no mistakes.
At 2 P.M.,
we'll begin guest registration.
At 3 P.M., we'll start the summit
according to the stage schedule.
Don't leave dead air or pause for too long.
We will have guests from
both here and outside the area,
so we must ensure
there are no security issues
and make sure this summit
is as flawless as possible.
If there are any issues,
report to your leader right away.
Don't let it escalate.
Let's get to work.
- Everything is in order, Wipa?
- Yes.
- May I see the front?
- With pleasure.
Understood.
Oh, come on!
Who swapped these foods?
Why didn't they read
the menu before placing them?
Dumb*ss!
Hey!
Where are you dragging me?!
Are you crazy?
Ugh, just come with me.
- No.
- Come here!
Gale.
Gale...
Hm?
Where is Saitharn?
In the dressing room.
I asked him to be my model.
A model?
One of my models dropped out.
So she thought
Saitharn could come help.
Ugh, it was so hard to bring him here.
Saitharn has a similar build to that model.
If we do his hair and put him in this dress,
I think he'll look really handsome.
Wow,
- look at his eyes.
- Hi.
See that?
He's a bit possessive, isn't he?
Okay. Thank you.
- Looks good?
- Yeah.
Hello.
Alright.
Let's give this a try.
Saitharn,
you got this.
Have I gained weight?
Why can't I zip up?
Thank you, Gale.
I've been trying for a while now.
Maybe...
I've gained some weight
since coming to the farm.
Hey!
You.
Why are you here?
You don't want to be a farmer anymore?
Is this why you chose to be a model?
Is this model
pretty, then?
Stop teasing me already.
You're more beautiful than I expected.
So beautiful.
That's enough.
Someone might hear us.
I'll go stand by the runway
as fast as I can.
I'm just cheering for you, Saitharn.
Everyone, get ready.
Please form a line.
Hey.
Get out already.
Move, I need to get to standby now.
Good luck then.
I know it'll turn out well.
Right.
Good luck.
I'm ready, Gale.
[NORTHERN SUMMIT 2026]
Hello, Boss Montri.
Hello, hello.
Hello.
Make sure you get plenty of rest.
Yes.
You've arrived very early, Boss.
This summit
will certainly be grand.
A grand summit needs a grand supervisor.
Otherwise, it wouldn't be any fun, would it?
If this summit ends well,
I wish to meet with Mr. Montri
and Khum Rimpha once more.
With pleasure.
I'll see you inside.
Alright.
Hmph.
Today,
we will make Phusangdao remember
the name Khum Rimpha.
Rest assured, Dad.
They will never forget us after today.
Hello.
Uncle Montri.
This is a truly grand summit,
befitting Phusangdao.
You're dependable as always,
as expected of Boss Sila.
Good job.
If your father could see this,
he'd certainly be proud.
Thank you
for praising me.
Today is a good day,
shall we go inside to hear the good news?
That's right.
Thank you for taking the time
to celebrate with Phusangdao.
You're so confident
that good news
will come your way, are you not?
Come now,
we've been close.
We should be happy
for whoever gets good news.
Isn't that right, Sila?
Yes.
Let's go, Dad.
[NORTHERN SUMMIT 2026]
[GALMONÉ]
And that brings
our opening fashion showcase
to a beautiful close.
All of the clothing and elements
in this showcase
are designed by Gale,
Gaewkamon Amnuaychainon,
the owner of the brand GALMONÉ.
Please give her a warm round of applause!
I must say, the showcase we just saw
truly amazed our audience,
especially the finale piece.
So I'd like to ask you:
What was the inspiration
and original concept behind this show?
Well,
I must first confess that
my original vision wasn't as perfect
as what you're seeing now.
I'm the kind of person who tends
to make decisions quickly,
which sometimes
causes me to overlook the finer details.
But there was...
someone
who
could always spot the little mistakes,
help me grow,
and turn my ideas
into something more tangible.
She is incredibly talented.
All the time we worked together,
I could see her talent shining through.
Without her,
this showcase wouldn't have
been this perfect,
and I might not love
my pieces as much as I do now.
Thank you so much,
Mueanphae.
♫I wanna thank you for making me feel♫
♫Just how beautiful love can be♫
♫Every chamber of my heart♫
♫Will be yours from now on♫
♫You're a godsent present from above♫
♫I'll always belong to you evermore♫
♫My heart will always be yours forever♫
Next up
is the moment you've all been waiting for.
I have to say,
this is great news
that Northern Thailand and
our country as a whole should be proud of,
as we're about to enter
into a partnership with one of
South Korea's leading companies.
Please give a warm round of applause to
Mr. Hosuk, President of
South Korea's No.1 tea export company.
Hello.
I'm Choi Hosuk.
The CEO of K Group from Korea.
Hello.
My name is Choi Hosuk
from K Group in South Korea.
It is a pleasure to be working with Thailand,
and today's summit is truly
a special occasion for me.
We are delighted to be
collaborating with Khum Rimpha.
This is truly wonderful news.
Congratulations again to Khum Rimpha.
What?
Oh, the light's back.
I would like to thank our Korean partner
for their trust in
Northern Thailand's agriculture.
However, I would like everyone
to take a closer look at this first.
You are spreading misinformation
and defaming Khum Rimpha.
Are you really going to argue
with these statistics?
Please let me finish.
I promise the truth never hurts anyone.
Except those who fear it.
Manmuang, sit down.
What you're seeing right now
is the actual export data from
Phusangdao Farm and Khum Rimpha
over the past five years.
This line graph shows the real trend,
rather than just numbers
on presentation slides.
And right here
is the original partnership
agreement that I signed,
which contains the actual data
we first submitted to K Group.
And this is the latest document
sent to Mr. Hosuk and his team in Korea,
which does not bear my signature.
All the figures also differ from
what we originally proposed.
I understand that someone on our side
altered the data before
sending it to Mr. Hosuk,
without my knowledge.
Isn't that right,
Ms. Wipa,
the illegitimate daughter
of Mr. Montri?
You can go to the crime scene.
Yes.
Then I have something for you to do.
It is something that only you can do.
Boss called us.
Let's go.
Yes.
This is the key evidence
that will leave Mr. Montri and
his illegitimate daughter, Ms. Wipa,
with no way to deny it.
Well done.
What is the meaning of this, Dad?
I'm his child too, just like you!
You're an idiot.
Dad put you in charge of Khum Rimpha,
and this is all you can do?
I'm the one who has to clean up your mess
because of an incompetent son like you...
Enough!
Do you really think
I see you as my daughter?
Because you and your mother
are nothing but worthless trash!
All these years,
you've been forcing your way into my life.
I only have one daughter...
and that's Mueanphae.
You only have one daughter?
Well, if she's gone,
will you accept me as your daughter then?
Hey!
Get her out of here.
Quickly!
- You'll have to leave, Ms. Wipa.
- No, no!
No!!
- Let me go! No!
- Quick, get her out of here.
Ugh, no!!
Quick, get her out.
No!
Let go!
Let go of me!
You got everything because you're his son!
Dad, dad, help me!
Dad.
Dad!
Let go.
Dad.
Dad, I love you. Please, help me!
Go.
Dad!
Let me go!
Dad help...
Help me.
- I love you, dad.
- Are you alright?
Dad!!
Dad!
- Dad, don't leave me!
- Was it forged?
- Was it really forged, Mr. Montri?
- Dad!
Is she really your illegitimate child?
Mr. Sila.
We are truly sorry for what happened.
We will review all the documents
and get back to you with our feedback.
I look forward to working with you.
May the misfortunes be gone.
And may good things come your way.
Our Phusangdao Farm
has been through many bad things.
Yet you have been treating us
with utmost care.
That is why we are here together.
May your life be filled with happiness
and prosperity.
Thank you, Auntie.
You're welcome.
Come, now, Saitharn.
You, too, have been through many bad things.
From now on,
since you were sent from the heavens,
no matter what happens,
whether it's good or bad,
or whatever they are,
you are
part of our family here. You are welcome.
May you find peace and solace here.
Thank you, Auntie.
I promise
to work hard to repay Sila
and...
everyone here.
Righto. No need to be so emotional.
Next time, don't just pull the plants
from their roots like you did.
Remember what you did?
That was ridiculous.
I won't stop bringing it up.
I, too, promise
to take care of everyone well.
And thank you, everyone,
for dedicating yourselves to this work.
I will do my best to improve our farm
and become the boss
that everyone can count on.
Alright, alright.
It's our turn now.
Come on.
Please make way, Boss.
Give us a very great blessing, Auntie.
Don't make it sound too old like you just did.
"Old"? Nonsense.
I have been giving the same blessing
countless times now.
I have already been giving
the same blessing many times.
- May you find peace and solace here.
- Auntie.
- From now on,
- Still the same blessings.
may you find happiness and prosperity
and be free from all hardships.
Thank you.
Come, now.
Auntie.
That still sounded too old.
- Bless me in the Gen Z manner, will you?
- One day, you'll be old, too.
- Right.
- Oh, now, now.
- May you find happiness here.
- It sounds really old.
Can you give them blessings
in the Gen Z manner?
- No?
- May you find peace.
It's the same.
What about me, Auntie?
Give me one in the Gen Z tone.
No, "May you live a long and healthy life," please.
None of that.
May you find happiness and prosperity.
May a wealthy man come your way.
May you have lines of guys
waiting to date you.
"Handsome guys," too.
Yes, absolutely.
So many people have come to the ceremony.
In my whole life,
I've never been to a blessing ceremony.
It's called "Bai Sri Su Kwan," right?
I've never been to one.
And there's so much food there.
I'll make sure to enjoy it as much as I can
so that it's worth the visit.
How's that?
Have you been to one, Phae?
Phae.
Is there something wrong?
Gale.
I...
I don't know
if I should come here.
Why?
You're still thinking about what happened?
Mm.
Dad and Muang
did really terrible things to Sila,
and I think
I should hold myself accountable.
You're this tiny,
yet you're full of thoughts.
There's nothing for you
to hold yourself accountable for.
You have nothing to do with it.
On top of that,
the one at fault
has received the punishment.
Yes, I'm well aware,
but I still feel like...
There's no more to that.
Saitharn invited you here, Phae.
Sila still adores you,
as he always has.
The same goes for others.
Believe me, Phae.
No one hates you.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
I'm right here with you.
Let's go, shall we?
Others are waiting.
Hi.
Come, now.
Let me tie the blessing thread on your wrist.
I've known you since you were born.
Why wouldn't I know
what is clouding your mind?
Don't feel sorry
for anything that happened, Phae.
To me, my little Mueanphae
is still as sweet as always.
Just like the first day we met.
Sila.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry on my dad's behalf
and Muang.
- I'm sorry for everything...
- Phae, Phae.
There's no need to apologize
for something you didn't do.
Remember this:
no matter what happens,
I'm still your brother, as always.
It's okay.
It's okay, alright?
Phae.
Come this way.
Allow me to tie a blessing thread
on your wrist.
Go.
May you find peace and solace,
and may you live a long and healthy life.
May you find happiness.
Here you go.
Khao tom hua ngok.
Please enjoy.
Boss.
Does this mean that
we have closed the deal
about that, have we not?
Precisely.
I just signed the contract yesterday.
But from now on,
you might have to work a bit harder,
as we need a higher yield.
But do not worry.
I'll hire more workers
to balance the workload.
Oh! That is not something
I'm worrying about, Boss.
Hard work doesn't scare me. I'm ready.
That's good.
Please enjoy, Uncle.
Hey, here's your khao tom hua ngok.
I've only learned what it is today.
It's my first time hearing its name.
Auntie Nong taught me how to make it.
That's when I realized how tasty it is!
Let's see if it's as tasty as you said.
I also helped make it.
Aside from adding coconut and sugar,
I also added a dash of love.
I hope you can feel it, Boss.
Deary me, Paula.
Why are you trying to flirt with him?
Just help me collect
the pedestal trays already.
Huh?
Why do you have to bug him?
Oh, gosh!
You already finished it?
It must've tasted good, right?
See? I told you.
It's just my first attempt, too.
Mm. It's tasty.
Just like the one who made it.
Hey, come on.
What are you saying? It's embarrassing.
Eat up already.
Whoa.
Time flies, doesn't it?
- Yeah.
- I'm about to turn 20 soon.
Time really does fly.
Come on. Let's celebrate you hitting 20.
Let me measure your height.
Mm.
Uh...
How tall am I?
You're taller than I was last year.
Whoa.
Hey!
What are you two doing here, huh?
What are you talking about?
I'm measuring his height, alright?
- Yeah.
- Really?
Oh, Saitharn!
Come measure your height with us.
What? No!
Aren't these the kids' height marks?
- It's fine.
- It's okay.
No, I don't want to do it.
Come on. You can do it. It's fine, isn't it?
- Come on, Mok, hold him.
- This way.
Come here.
Get out.
How tall is he?
Paula, it's your turn.
Measure your height after him.
Come on, come on.
It's your turn.
- Let's see how tall she is.
- Why am I only...
Phae,
what's wrong?
I'll miss you so much.
I haven't even gone through the gate,
and you already miss me?
Well...
I don't know when we'll meet again.
Bangkok is not that far.
If you miss me, come visit.
Or...
do you want me to come see you?
You can't do that.
You're there to work,
so just stay there.
It's alright.
But I want to take care of you, Phae.
Would you like to...
come with me?
Go work with me.
Do you want to come?
Of course.
I really want to go with you.
But can you
wait for me, Gale?
I want to stay here
and finish what I need to do.
Then I'll follow you.
So when that time comes,
you can be proud
to have a talented girlfriend like me.
Hm?
Of course I can wait.
I'll always wait for you.
But you don't need to prove anything anymore.
You're already the best,
and I know that.
Understood?
I'm not trying to prove myself to anyone.
I just want to prove it to myself
and make my dreams come true
on my own.
Then...
I'll always be here
to cheer for you.
Thank you, Gale.
Do you have to go now?
Mm.
I have to go now.
I'm off, then.
Good luck.
[3 months later]
You're used to living there now, huh?
Mom.
Come on now,
if you're worried about me, just say it.
Stop pretending to scold me.
I'm not worried about you.
I'm worried about the others on the farm.
If you cause them trouble,
they might blame me
for how I raised you.
Come on, Mom!
I'm not causing any trouble, alright?
See,
I got promoted
to be in charge of accounting.
In place of that traitor?
Huh?
How did you know that?
Who wouldn't?
It's all over the news.
I'm glad you didn't have to give
an interview to that famous news anchor.
I'm tired of answering my friends' questions.
They sent me photos of you
wearing weird clothes from the news.
Am I pretty, then?
Fine, you're pretty.
You probably got that from your mom.
Oh, and what about your debt?
It's been almost four months now.
If you've cleared your debts,
just come back home already.
Come on, Mom!
I'm not even close to paying off all my debt.
I'll probably have to stay here
for a long time.
I have to go now.
Boss called me.
Let's talk again soon.
Bye-bye.
Yes, like that.
If you're so sure, then come after me.
We'll see about that.
Mok, get back to work, you prick.
Auntie!
You're not surprised?
Hey, Mok, wait!
Oh, sorry, Auntie.
- Take this!
- Ow.
Come back and do your work.
You've been here for a few months now.
How's it going?
Mm...
How's it going, huh?
Well,
it's fun
but exhausting.
Very exhausting.
Extremely exhausting.
What?
Why are you laughing?
I'm this tired
because of you.
What?
How is this my fault?
Can't be my fault.
So...
am I close to clearing my debt?
I want to go home.
Oh?
You're sad, huh?
Just kidding.
I've come this far.
You're making me work this hard,
so why don't you clear my debt for me?
Please?
Hey, hey, that's enough!
Stop it.
Hey.
You've been here for a long time,
so when are you going to call me 'Boss'?
Come on.
I'd rather not.
It sounds creepy.
Please.
Try calling me
'Boss,' will you?
Hey, you!
I refuse.
Can I call you something else?
Something else, you say?
Something else?
Uh...
'Daddy'?
'Daddy.'
Ew!
Please.
Call me, Saitharn.
Call me your 'Daddy,' please.
Call me 'Daddy.'
Oh, you.
Okay, fine. You win.
Ugh!
Boss.
Hey.
Get back here.
Watch it.
♫I almost gave up on love♫
♫I thought I would never find the right one♫
♫But destiny led you to me♫
Saitharn.
From now on,
you are no longer my debtor.
You are my lover.
You are part of my family.
Thank you.
You make me realize that...
that...
someone like me
also deserves a love like this,
from you
and everyone here
who has become my friends
and my new family.
Saitharn,
stay with me, will you?
Stay here at Phusangdao Farm with me
forever.
Yes,
Boss.
♫I wanna thank you for making me feel♫
♫Just how beautiful love can be♫
♫Every chamber of my heart♫
♫Will be yours from now on♫
♫You're a godsent present from above♫
♫I'll always belong to you evermore♫
♫My heart will always be yours forever♫
I love you.
Right.
I love you, too.
What a big ring.
Thank you.
Hey.
♫You're a godsent present from above♫
♫I'll always belong to you evermore♫
♫My heart will always be yours forever♫
May I see your ID, please?
Your ID, please.
[Mr. Thiwachai Saelim]
[Date of birth: June 14, 2006]
Yes!