[You Have My Heart]
[Episode 20
A Misplaced Heart, Hard to Restore]
Boss Qian,
please wait a moment.
Thank you.
Magistrate,
why is it you?
You...
Have a seat, Boss Qian.
Whatever it is, let's sit down and talk.
My men are all outside.
If this gets out of hand,
it won't end well
for you.
I know what he wants.
Speaking of which,
this body of mine
was his first choice,
and the best fit.
I came here this time,
hoping that
everything returns to where it began.
Then,
what do you mean by that?
My time is short.
All I want is
peace for Yin-Yang Crossing
and safety for its people.
I will trade this body
he's always dreamed of,
to end the war,
and bring back the people he abducted.
If I fulfill his lifelong wish,
perhaps,
it'llplease him,
and your Jinlang
will come back unharmed.
[Gilded Grotto]
The people are innocent.
How could you kill them all?
A little nourishment,
but better than nothing.
To be devoured by me
is a worthy end for them.
Take a good look
at yourself.
Now that you have lost the tree heart,
to me,
you're nothing but a well-crafted vessel.
No different from those ants.
I don't want it that much anymore.
Guess
why I am still willing to see you
and agree to your ridiculous deal?
Because I mean something
to Liu Fufeng.
Once you possess my body,
the next time you face her,
she will hesitate.
And this moment of hesitation
will be your chance of survival.
You're half right.
Young Magistrate.
The other half is
I want to see for myself
what tricks you can play
with your dying body.
No tricks.
I came this time
for the peace of Yin-Yang Crossing.
She's also willing to make a concession
to grant your wish,
sacrificing me alone for a time of peace.
She has finally
learned to compromise.
Wait for me.
As expected,
this body is the most comfortable.
Qian Wanqian,
you did well this time.
No need.
This body has long been hollowed out
by evil power.
Leave it to me
as nourishment.
Spirit-Trapping Spell.
A gift for you.
Hurry. Purge...
Purge the evil power.
Keep purging it.
Quick!
You... You... You!
What are you doing?
Stop her quickly!
Fengling,
I'll protect you.
Go quickly!
Qian Wanqian,
open your eyes!
See how many lives he has taken.
Now he wants to devour your son.
To him, you and your son
are nothing but disposable vessels.
Do you want to watch
Jinlang's soul be destroyed forever?
Purge!
Let her purge it quickly!
Let her purge it!
Trying to trap me?
Jinlang, hurry,
come with me.
Hurry. Let's go.
Hurry.
Remember,
when the Spirit-Trapping Spell
takes effect,
it will temporarily trap
Bai Han's spiritual consciousness
within your body.
Your only way out
is to rely on your sheer willpower
to walk out of the Gilded Grotto,
and step into the formation I have set.
Only then
can we destroy him
once and for all.
Fufeng,
it's me.
Your imitation
is not convincing.
Are you going to watch us die together?
His mortal body
cannot withstand the life-force backlash
from the spiritual pool.
His main meridians are severed,
and his soul is fading.
The spiritual pool can at best
preserve his flesh
until 9 AM tomorrow.
Then isn't there any other way?
Don't you have
plenty of reishi mushrooms
and celestial herbs at Xiqianhua?
Or ginseng?
Even thousand-year-old ginseng would do.
I'll get it.
I'd brave mountains of blades
and seas of fire to get it.
What's the use of you risking your life?
Xiaohu,
you must understand.
He is not a spirit or monster.
He has no spiritual consciousness
to gather,
nor a demon core to nourish.
His mortal days are over,
and his soul returns to the underworld.
Xiqianhua is not the Hall of Yama.
We cannot rewrite
the Book of Life and Death.
What about Lady Fufeng?
She is a thousand-year demon.
She must have a way, right?
Master has done everything she could.
I don't believe it.
Lord Bai won't...
He won't...
He won't just...
Xiqianhua will follow proper rites
to bathe him, dress him,
and prepare his coffin.
Since you are here,
please relay this
to Deputy Magistrate Shi:
in keeping with the rites
for a fallen imperial official,
detail Lord Bai's achievements
and the circumstances of his death.
As for the funeral,
Xiqianhua will handle it.
This is
how it ends.
You said
people should do what they want to do.
All I want is to be a constable.
Now that you're gone,
where am I supposed to go?
Master, don't go to look.
Your heart will soften again.
And if it does,
will you give him that half-heart again?
Now this half-heart has been nourished
by spiritual power.
It has revived.
If you give it to Lord Bai,
it would be like letting him
share half of your power.
Power corrupts the heart.
Eternal life warps desire.
Bai Han is proof of that.
If you give him this heart
at all costs today,
ten or a hundred years from now,
will he become the next Bai Han?
Will he become the next
source of chaos in Yin-Yang Crossing?
Besides,
the method of reversing life
is extremely perilous.
If you separate the tree heart again
to infuse it into a mortal body,
his mortal body
likely could not bear that power,
and in the end,
he might scatter to nothing.
Master, you may suffer
the backlash of having your heart
torn out once more.
Now that this half-heart
has finally returned to you.
It cannot endure another separation.
Since there is no next life,
may you forget this old friend soon.
May spring fill all your days ahead.
Lady Fufeng.
I will go find Bai Han tomorrow.
I brought wine from Zuiwang Tavern.
Fengling said it's your favorite.
Let's have a drink together,
shall we?
My Lady.
I thought the day I returned the heart
would be my final day.
I didn't expect
to be granted a little more time.
Today, let's set aside official business,
just drink and be merry,
shall we?
Okay.
The willow leaf jade pendant you gave me,
does it have spiritual consciousness?
It's too young.
It has yet to awaken.
Is that so?
Then if there is a next life,
I will become that jade pendant,
just like the Ring Spirit.
Once I gain spiritual consciousness,
I will take human form
and stay by your side
as your most capable helper.
How about that?
The light fades with one's passing.
What talk is there of reincarnation?
Lady Fufeng, you truly are no fun.
I know
our paths crossed too briefly,
but I never got a chance
to look my fill of you.
What a pity.
Here.
Since that's the case,
I wish Lady Fufeng
all the best.
I know
you are different from Bai Han.
Bai Shanjun,
don't let me down.
If you think our time together
was too brief,
then live on.
If you prove yourself useless,
I will do as you said:
forget this old friend soon,
and let all days ahead be spring.